You're about to see a story of bold knights
and beautiful maidens.
A story of love and hatred and prejudice.
Though our story is old...
...the love, the hatred
and the prejudice are ever new.
- Holy God of Abraham, spare me.
- Silence if you value your life.
- Holy Father, I beg you.
- Silence.
Follow me.
This way.
You see? They've been lying in wait for you.
Where is he? Where is this Jew?
- Well?
- He's gone, sire.
- Gone?
- Disappeared.
Imbecile. You let him get away.
They're Normans.
Saxons or Normans,
what does it matter to me?
Do I rejoice because
the brave Normans cross the Channel.
...and defeat the brave Saxons?
What's the difference?
They both treat us like dogs.
You call them brave knights?
- I call them thieves.
- A rich merchant, I fear, is fair game.
No matter. You saved my life
and I am forever in your debt.
If you keep to this road any longer, sir,
no one can help you.
I shall be lost otherwise.
I know this country. Where are you bound?
- To Ashby. The great tournament.
- Why, then we could travel together.
May I ask who you are
that I may thank for my deliverance?
Merely a poor pilgrim returning
from the Holy Land.
Come, to waste anymore time here
would be dangerous.
There. There lies Ashby.
The blessings of Jacob be upon you,
pilgrim. How am I going to repay you?
- I want nothing.
- You shall have a horse.
...and armor for the tournament.
- But how did you know that I...
- I've seen it at once.
Beneath your robe, the chain mail
of a knight and the golden spurs.
You shall have everything you need.
Then I must warn you, sir, that both horse
and armor may be lost in the jousting.
That's impossible.
Your lance, good youth, will be
as powerful as the rod of Moses.
My little bucklehead.
- Norman dogs.
- Careful, master.
They say Prince John has
ten thousand ears.
Well, let him hear me then.
I'll say it to his face.
Who is that?
That's Cedric of Rotherwood, a Saxon lord.
- I meant the lady.
- Oh, that's his ward, the Lady Rowena...
...from the royal line of Alfred the Great.
- She is beautiful.
- If a Saxon can be called beautiful.
The challengers, Reginald Front-de-Boeuf!
Maurice de Bracy!
Brian Guilbert!
Listen to the crowd.
Prince John is well accepted here today.
He would do well to take over
the throne now
...before King Richard gets back
from the Holy Land.
Richard dies the moment he returns.
- Fitzurse.
- Yes, Your Grace?
Are we ready to begin?
There is still the choosing of a queen
for the tournament, sire.
If it would please Your Highness,
my daughter, perhaps?
No, it might appear unseemly
to announce your daughter.
...before the tournament has yet begun.
Let the gallant knight who conquers
the field here today make the choice.
These three noble challengers
will undertake all comers.
Each challenger may be selected
by touching his shield with a lance.
If the shield is touched
with the reverse end of the lance...
...then sharp points will not be used.
But if the sharp tip of the lance
touches the shield...
...then the combat is understood to be
with sharp weapons.
If any knight should break the lance
of all three challengers here before me...
...then Prince John will declare that knight
the victor in this day's combat.
The Prince wants the victor
to choose the Queen.
Prince John has declared.
...the victor will have the honor of choosing
our Queen of Love and Beauty.
Normans. All three, Normans.
Is there a Saxon to meet them?
Tomorrow. I fight tomorrow.
Are you looking for someone?
Your Highness,
no sharp points will be used.
How disappointing.
Go on.
Is there no one here? No one to stop them?
Tomorrow.
- Who is he?
- Look again, master.
- Perhaps you should ask, who was he?
- A Saxon?
- Without question.
- Have we no better than this?
We have, my lord. His name is Ivanhoe.
- Your son, master.
- I have no son.
You may have disowned him,
but he's still your flesh and blood.
...and worthy of his Saxon name.
He is worthy of scorn and nothing else.
What a disgrace. What a pity.
My son ran off and left the city.
Next! Who is next?
Your Grace, there are none left now
who will meet the challengers.
Is it possible? Will they let
these Norman invaders take the day?
The very honor of England is at stake.
Surely, you...
How annoying that we should finish
so early. So quickly. And yet...
And yet how comforting to know
that the three strongest knights on this field.
...are loyal only to you, Your Majesty.
It's him. It's him. The pilgrim.
Desdichado.
The Disinherited Knight. Welcome.
You have your choice.
However, the outcome will remain the same.
I am disappointed.
Would that I trade places with you, Front.
Never. This one is mine.
A Saxon. I'll wager he's a Saxon.
May I hope that you will now give me
the opportunity?
What a shame, Brian.
Now you'll never get your chance.
Who is he? Find out who he is.
Have you confessed yourself this morning
that you peril your life so frankly?
The sharp end. They will use the points.
Prepare yourself then.
Look your last upon the sun.
Hold! You are allowed the lance only.
You are not allowed the sword.
You, Disinherited Knight.
We proclaim you the champion
of this day's tournament.
We shall meet again tomorrow
when there are none to part us.
Brave knight, we commend your valor.
And we award you this valiant steed
to match your courage.
You call yourself the Disinherited One?
By what other name shall we know you?
As a stranger in our land, you may require
assistance in your choice of a queen.
Let us say to you that the fair Alicia is
considered the first in beauty as in place.
Would you present your lance?
You may now indicate your choice.
Largesse.
Largesse to the gallant knight.
Long live the Queen of Love and Beauty.
You can't just waste your whole life
in bitterness, Father.
Bitterness? You speak of bitterness?
What would you have me be?
Our lord and master, Prince John...
...demands twice the contribution
I gave him last month.
Contribution. It's a ransom.
But surely King Richard will return
to England and resume his throne.
What difference does that make to us,
Richard or John?
In this wicked country
we shall always be persecuted.
No. All Christians are not the same.
Think of the gallant knight
who fought today.
Now there was a brave and noble youth.
I'll wager that pilgrim was Jewish.
Yes, Beaslin?
There's a stranger at the door, sire.
He wishes to speak to you.
Does he look dangerous?
I don't believe so.
He wears the garments of a pilgrim.
Veil yourself.
My friend.
Sir, forgive my intrusion.
I'm here to pay my debt to you.
Debt? What debt? I owe you my life.
Not at all.
My daughter, Rebecca.
I am honored.
You owe me nothing. You've paid me back
in full today at the tournament.
May I offer you a goblet of wine?
Nevertheless, I have brought your horse
and I have here the price of the armor.
Keep them. They're yours.
I feel I must at least pay you something to...
My father owes you a far deeper kindness
than any steeds or arms could pay.
Please, let us look upon it
as our debt to you for his life.
If that is your wish.
Your wine?
Forgive me, please. I must prepare myself
for tomorrow's encounter.
Sir, you've been far too generous.
I am honored to have met you.
Thank you. I bid you good night.
You frightened me.
Wait, I will leave and come back again.
There. Are you frightened now?
Tell me. Tell me at once.
Who was the mysterious knight?
- Who was he?
- Who?
Wamba, please, don't play games with me.
What did he say?
His voice could not be heard.
His face, his eyes, his nose,
his mouth, could not be seen.
- Why?
- He wasn't there.
- Oh, Wamba.
- Gone. Into the night.
The good knight gone into the good night.
I think it best.
Best?
Would not Ivanhoe, if he were here...
would not Ivanhoe be jealous
of a brave new champion?
He would have no reason.
I am faithful to Ivanhoe.
What if Cedric marries you
to the noble hog, Athelstane?
- Never.
- He will insist.
And I will refuse.
Hold!
Wamba!
Well?
What did she say?
Did you talk to her?
She hasn't forgotten me?
Well, tell me she hasn't forgotten me.
The lady is fair. She would have a prayer.
- For me?
- For the brave knight who won the day.
Are they the same? What is your name?
Begone, you knave. Begone.
The Queen of Love and Beauty
shall be guided to her throne.
...by our royal liege, Prince John.
- Where is Athelstane?
- Master, that is a question.
- Is he getting ready for the combat?
- He is a guest of the noble Lord Gurtog.
When I saw them last they were eating
venison, an enormous beast.
Be it known, it is forbidden
to thrust with a sword.
You may strike only.
A mace or battle ax
may be used at pleasure...
...but the dagger is forbidden.
Any knight unhorsed may renew
the combat on foot.
Any knight who breaks
the rules of this tournament.
will be subjected to public ridicule
and stripped of his arms!
Glory to the brave!
Very well. Let them begin.
Beware!
You may stop the combat at any moment.
Stop it? By the light of heaven, I will not.
He gained his prize yesterday.
Let the others now have their turn.
Yield.
Hold. Stop the conflict.
Honor to the brave!
Glory to the brave!
His head must be bare to accept the chaplet.
Ivanhoe!
The chaplet, my lady.
I bestow upon you, Sir Knight...
...this chaplet as a gift of honor
for this day's victory.
And upon these fearful wounds no worthier
wreath of chivalry could ever be placed.
Ivanhoe!
Help him.
Your own son. Will you do nothing?
My son has left my house.
He has deserted my country.
He has forsaken the Saxon cause.
He is no son of mine.
We must help him quickly, Father.
- How?
- Take him to our house.
But he is a Christian. By our laws,
we can't deal with him except in commerce.
He is gravely wounded and, by our hearts,
we cannot refuse him.
Think. If he should die in our care...
He will not die unless we abandon him.
And, if so, we must then
answer for his blood to God.
Quickly. His enemies are all about.
Wilfred of Ivanhoe.
There is more to this than one day's battle.
If Ivanhoe has returned from the Holy Land,
can King Richard be far behind?
Well, let him come. We'll crown his brother
before Richard can gather his forces.
The devil take Richard and welcome to him.
I, Brian Guilbert, make you
this solemn promise.
I shall meet this Wilfred of Ivanhoe
in mortal combat.
...and send him to eternity.
Get back there. Get back. Get back.
- Who is it? Who is it that bears him away?
- Someone far kinder than we, Your Grace.
Onward.
My lady.
You.
My father and I...
we brought you here to care
for your wounds.
We have special herbs, ways of curing
wounds, although we never inflict them.
Herbs?
Secret preparations handed down to us
since the days of Solomon.
You should be able to bear armor
again within eight days.
You may rest at our home in York
until your health is restored.
We leave in the morning.
Is there not someone else here in Ashby.
- who could look after me until I...
- None stepped forward today.
My dear, noble maiden, I...
No. I am not a noble.
I am but a poor Jewess.
Is it our race, then?
Is that why you do not wish
to travel with us?
I have no wish to inconvenience you.
I accept your service gratefully.
Rest now. I'll leave you.
- Your Majesty.
- Rise.
- Did you find him?
- At the house of Isaac, the Jew of York.
They plan to take him to York
in the early morning.
Oh, that was a stroke of good luck.
I shall meet with Wilby, Forbes,
and Witherstone at York within the week.
All my forces will be gathered there
to challenge my brother.
- You're traveling alone?
- I must for the moment.
You may retire now. Oh, and, Phillippe...
- Your Majesty?
- A good night's work.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Well. Where is she?
Where is our queen of the tournament?
- She...
- Yes? She is your ward, is she not?
Where is the Lady Rowena?
She is exhausted by today's events.
She begs leave to decline
your courteous invitation.
We are not accustomed to such
a refusal from our appointed queens.
It is traditional that they attend.
Your customs are not our customs.
Well. Perhaps you'll not object
if we drink a beaker.
...to the champion of this passage of arms.
To your son, Wilfred of Ivanhoe.
I cannot drink.
- To your own son?
- He deserted us.
He left his house, his country,
to fight in foreign lands.
with your brother, King Richard.
Then let us hope my brother holds him
in more esteem than you.
I cannot forgive him. I will not forgive him.
A willful youth who refuses
the commands and customs of his fathers.
I fill my cup to Cedric, himself.
This ward of yours, the Lady Rowena.
Yes.
A rose of loveliness.
And, I trust, a jewel of wealth?
A Saxon of large possessions.
It is my intention that she marry
this gallant and noble knight, Athelstane...
...the last of the royal line of Saxons.
But then she is a minor, is she not?
And she is therefore
at our disposal in marriage.
Indeed.
What do you think, De Bracy?
I am told you are attracted to the lady?
Would you find it pleasing
to take her as your bride?
If her lands are to my liking.
I will hold myself bound
to Your Highness' wishes.
The day my ward marries a Norman will be
that Norman's last day on earth.
Hold. Sit down. Both of you.
We have invited these honored guests
here this evening.
...and they shall remain honored guests.
We have offered a toast
to Cedric of Rotherwood.
...and now, we pray you,
name us some Norman in return.
It is a hard task, for the conquered,
to sing the praises of his conqueror.
Yet I will name a Norman,
even though he led my only son astray.
He is still the best of your unfortunate race.
I drink this goblet to the health
of King Richard, the Lion-Hearted.
Long live King Richard.
And now I hope you will excuse us.
We have remained here long enough.
Up, noble Athelstane.
We bid you good night.
I'm afraid, Your Majesty, that
the Saxon dogs have retreated in triumph.
It isn't possible, is it?
Could Richard be back in England again?
What does it matter?
You have the services here
of Maurice de Bracy, Front-de-Boeuf...
...and my own humble sword.
Enough for an army.
Here is my toast and solemn pledge.
To Prince John, our next King of England.
Prince John!
Prince John! Prince John!
Where is she now?
Where is the Lady Rowena?
- Weeping.
- Weeping?
- Come. We must leave at once.
- Would you go without your son?
Lvanhoe has chosen to go his own way.
- So be it.
- He chose...
He's better fitted now to do
the juggling tricks of the Normans.
...than uphold the honor
of his English ancestry.
Who was it that defeated the Normans
at the tournament?
Silence. Not another word.
We leave at once.
- Your Highness.
- Yes.
This arrived this morning from France.
- No!
- What is it?
- "The devil is unchained. Take heed. "
- Richard.
He's escaped from France.
He's back in England.
We mustn't lose a moment, Your Highness.
Draw your troops together at York...
...and meet whatever force he has head on.
Your Highness.
At once.
My friends.
- My friends, we ride for York.
- York?
- We join Prince John within the fortnight.
- For what purpose?
For the purpose of facing King Richard.
At last.
York is only a three-day journey.
We have plenty of time.
Of course.
You shall be my guests
at Torquilstone on the way.
Tankards and venison enough to fill
even your fat bellies.
What do you say?
Here. What are you doing?
Why did you stop?
Bandits.
Bandits? There are no bandits.
Yeah, in the woods maybe. We're leaving.
You can't do that. You can't leave us here.
No? We're going.
No, stop. You can't take those horses.
Those are my property. Thieves!
Thieves!
Here. Drink this.
There. Rest now. Rest.
They were hired to take us to York.
They've got my money.
Why should they care?
We are deserted.
Oh, God of Abraham, what have I done?
- Why must they smite us so?
- Father, look.
May God make them merciful.
Hold.
I greet you warmly, sir.
Trusting you're in good health.
Who are you? Speak plainly, infidel.
I'm Isaac of York.
I hired a guard of men to escort us to York,
but they've deserted us as you can see.
Why?
They say there are bandits in the forest.
But, rumor, that's all.
I beg you to let us travel
under your protection.
Dogs of infidels. Out of the way.
Sir, may I speak, please?
We have someone here,
an old person who is gravely ill.
I beg you to let this sick person
be transported with care.
...under your protection.
It is no concern of ours.
Wait.
If this poor person is truly in peril of life...
...and if these two kind and earnest people
cannot defend themselves...
well, then we must in all charity
give them help.
So be it. They may travel in the rear.
What is it? What's the alarm?
No alarm, sir.
All is ready for you at the castle.
We only wish to inform you there is
a party of Saxons in the forest there below.
Do you know them?
Cedric of Rotherwood, the Lady Rowena
and the noble knight, Athelstane.
How large is the party?
Ten or eleven. The servants are not armed.
My good friend, De Bracy.
I wager that the hour has struck.
- What?
- It is time for us to deliver your wife.
Your wife, De Bracy, is awaiting you.
- What was that?
- What? I hear nothing.
Forgive the intrusion, my lady.
I am pleased to announce...
...that you are now the guest
of my good friend, Front-de-Boeuf.
I would sooner, sir, go with bandits.
But, indeed, that is what you are.
De Bracy? Are you certain
that you want to marry this sharp tongue?
Well, what have we here?
I think, perhaps, that we have caught
more than one bird on this occasion.
An infidel.
And beautiful beyond belief.
We can do you no harm, sir.
We have an old woman here
who needs our care.
She shall have it, I promise you.
Dogs. Norman dogs.
Barbarians. But surely they will feed us?
Stop.
What is it?
What affliction does this old hag bear?
I would not go close enough to find out.
Set her down. Set her down, please.
Well? You may leave.
There. It's all right.
Easy. Rest easy, Ivanhoe.
Don't be alarmed. Don't shout, I beg you.
Are we... Are we in York?
We are prisoners.
Get your hands off me. Leave me alone.
Lost again. Lost again. What can I do?
Taken my master, left the fool.
- Bandit or knave?
- I am neither, sir.
Then what are you?
I am a fool. Wamba, the fool of my master,
Cedric of Rotherwood.
A Saxon?
- A noble Saxon, sir. And a prisoner.
- Prisoner? Where?
Front-de-Boeuf's castle. With his ward,
the Lady Rowena and the noble Athelstane.
There is also... Would you mind, sir?
Thank you.
There is also Isaac, the Jew from York,
and his daughter, Rebecca.
They were abducted?
They were indeed, sir. Most certainly.
Just as surely as you and I.
You? I? What are you talking about?
Look about you, sir.
The bushes are moving.
Welcome, welcome, gentlemen.
What do you wish? A fool or a knight?
Release him.
The Black Knight.
The tournament at Ashby.
You saved young Ivanhoe.
- You hold that against me?
- Against you?
There is nothing more dear to me
than the life of an Englishman.
If you are as good an Englishman
as you are a knight...
...then I hold you in esteem.
Why do you pass our way?
The shortest distance to York.
Then you must stay awhile.
Taste our hospitality.
Please. I entreat you.
If you truly love Englishmen,
help save my master.
He speaks of Cedric of Rotherwood.
The Lady Rowena. The noble Athelstane.
Prisoners, all of them.
Prisoners in the castle of Front-de-Boeuf.
For myself,
I would join any enterprise to save them.
- Where is Little John?
- On his way from Totherdam.
- And Will Scarlet?
- Just arrived.
And where's Friar Tuck?
- Did you call, my lord?
- Where have you been?
Why, at vespers saying prayers
for all good Englishmen.
It appears you've been drinking
more than usual.
Perhaps a pious taste or two
of our sacred wine.
Do you think you're in suitable condition
to give us service in combat?
There's a hissing here,
and there is a weakness here.
I don't know.
Yes. They have both passed away.
I am ready.
Then come, my wicked priest.
Let us be off, Black Knight.
The fool will lead us to his master.
You want my life? Do you want my wealth?
Is it too much for you Normans.
...that we Saxons still hold land in this,
our own country?
Very well, then, put us to death.
I ask only that you free the Lady Rowena
in honor and safety.
Norman swine!
My God, who would have thought that you,
the descendent of Saxon kings...
...should be the prisoner of a vile Norman.
...in the very hall in which
our ancestors held court.
Perhaps they'll hold us
to a moderate ransom.
Dogs.
Oh, my tongue cleaves to my palate.
Could they have forgotten to send us wine?
Why don't you sit down, my lady?
If I am in the presence of my jailer, sir,
I will stand.
Dearest lady, you are in the presence
of your captive, not your jailer.
I don't know you, sir.
And no man dressed in spurs
and wearing chains.
...should intrude himself
upon an unprotected lady.
It's my misfortune
that I am not known to you.
I hope the name of De Bracy is known
to all in deeds of chivalry.
De Bracy?
I see no deeds of chivalry on this day.
You are unjust, Lady Rowena.
Won't you allow, at least, the passion
of a man drawn by your great beauty?
Sir, you speak the common language
of a minstrel.
Well, perhaps bold language
best justifies bold action.
I tell you now...
...you will never leave this place unless
you leave it as the wife of Maurice de Bracy.
Your wife?
Oh, I know. You have great pride.
I admire that.
It makes you even more suited
to take your place beside me.
When I do marry, sir,
it will not be to one who despises.
...the manner in which
I have been brought up.
Perhaps you dream that King Richard
will resume the throne.
That is an empty dream.
I can promise you that.
His fate will be as hopeless
as that of Ivanhoe's.
What? Lvanhoe?
Do I see a touch of tenderness at last?
Well, where is he?
Do you know where he is?
- I do.
- Tell me, I beg you.
He lies gravely wounded
in a turret room above.
I don't believe you.
You didn't take the trouble to look.
He traveled in the horse litter
with Isaac, the Jew of York.
Now, were I to inform our host of this...
...Ivanhoe will no longer breathe at all.
Smile, dear lady.
Simply smile at my proposal
and he will have nothing to fear.
I can't believe that your purpose could be
so wicked and your power so great.
There are others. Cedric, your guardian.
The fate of all depends on your decision.
Lady Rowena, I would rather you kept
your original anger than this.
Be assured, please,
you have no reason for tears as yet.
I will leave you now
...to dwell upon your decision.