WHISTLES
Welcome back to County Antrim where
we have assembled the top handlers
from England, Ireland, Scotland
and Wales who are battling it out
to become One Man And His Dog
champions of 2009.
Last time, Sophie Holt,
the young English handler,
stormed into the lead,
but how long can England stay there?
We've only done one round. There
are three more to go - the singles,
the brace and the supreme.
As ever, our trialling experts, Gus
Dermody and Matt Baker, are keeping
their beady eyes on everything.
Matt, can England hold on
to that lead?
Sophie has put them 18 points clear.
All the points in every round
are added together,
so that's a difficult gap to close.
In the singles, we've got national
champion after national champion.
It is an incredible standard.
I think they'll be fairly
consistent, so at the end of today,
England could still be in front.
OK, let's take a closer look
at the course.
Seven sheep are set next to the lift
post at the far end of the course.
The handler sends his dog out
on a right or left-hand outrun
to reach them - 20 points.
The dog approaches the sheep
and gets them to move back
towards the handler
with the lift - 10 points.
The sheep are taken on a straight
fetch through the fetch gates
towards the handler - 20 points.
Next, the drive.
Starting to the left,
the dog must drive the sheep
over a triangular course
through two sets of drive gates.
Once the sheep have passed through
the second set of drive gates,
the handler can leave the post.
The drive ends when the sheep are
in the shedding ring - 30 points.
One of the two sheep with
red collars has to be singled off
and held by the dog - 10 points.
The sheep are moved to the pen.
The trial is complete
when all seven sheep are in the pen
and the gate is closed -
a final 10 points.
The course should be completed
within 15 minutes
and there's 100 points to play for.
It sounds like another tough course
for our handlers.
Their performance is going
to be judged by Michael Glynn
and Glyn Howells.
They will be ensuring fair play and
awarding points for every section.
Scotland are lying
in fourth position,
so it's their competitor who has
the unenviable task of going first.
His name is Stuart Davidson.
Let's find out a little bit more
about him and his dog, Jim.
Hello, my name is Stuart Davidson.
The dog I'm running today
in One Man And His Dog is Jim.
I live on a sheep farm just outside
Dunoon, 30 miles west of Glasgow.
How I got involved in trialling
was my wife, Margaret.
Her father and Margaret used to run
many years ago and I played shinty.
Shinty is
the old Scottish traditional game
that's very similar to hockey.
And it was either running the
sheepdogs or keep on playing shinty.
So I stopped the shinty
and started running sheepdogs.
It's all Margaret's fault.
I started trialling,
I had a bit of success,
I won five
Scottish National Champions
and two International Champions.
I've competed on One Man And His Dog
three times.
The first time was down in Balloch
in 1981.
I've had Jim since he was
six months old,
I trained him myself.
He's not too fond of people,
but he loves sheep.
Jim is off a son of Star.
Star won the Nursery Final
when he was a young dog
and also won the International.
Hopefully, Jim and I will do well,
as we did with Star.
Well, first up to the post
for the singles
is Stuart Davidson from Scotland
with his dog Jim
who is looking very keen
to get cracking. Away!
Going out wide,
but he'd spotted the sheep
before he set off down the field,
so this is a good outrun.
STUART WHISTLES
Yes, he's just overflanked a little
bit at the end of the outrun.
But he's got them lifted
and they're on the fetch.
17 points out of 20 for the outrun,
9 points for the lift.
Jim's out of sight
beyond the ridge.
Is he going to pop up further over?
He's missed the sheep
and the sheep
have drifted off-line.
There's still a bit of distance,
so there's time for a recovery yet.
He's coming on to them now.
He's got them settled,
but it's just this bad fetch,
he's going to be penalised.
The "away" command
to go to the right,
nicely through the middle
and back on-line again now.
Steady, Jim! Away...
Just a slight little wobble
in the middle, but going well.
He's a very sleek dog,
is Jim, isn't he?
Away... Here!
Come by... Here!
Come by... Here! Come by...
Oh, that was
a good, good turn-round.
13 points out of 20 for the fetch.
They're nicely settled as they
start off on this left-hand drive.
This is a good line,
going towards these first gates.
Jim, Jim, come by! Here!
He's so fast once he gets going.
You can see the eagerness.
Away! The sheep are coming
up the field a little bit too much,
so Jim's having to be brought in
towards Stuart
and he's not coming
fast enough this time.
They're well off-line now.
Away!
Here! Away!
He's going round fast,
got them through.
Unbelievable! That was dramatic.
I didn't think he'd get that.
Whistles like a foot
on the accelerator.
He just blows
and, whoa, off he goes!
Jim!
HE WHISTLES
And he's got them settled again.
23 points out of 30 for the drive.
A little bit of milling.
Stuart's looking to single off
one of those sheep
that's wearing a red collar. They
are quite young, they're "gimmers".
This will be the first time
they've been sheared.
I wonder how many times
they've seen a dog, Gus.
Not a lot. They just do not like
splitting, these youngsters.
So they're going back to their pals
as quickly as they can.
Chance coming here?
Oh! No, she's back in.
And they're at the other end now.
Here's a chance coming.
The dog's ready.
Stuart's creeping in.
He's got it there.
It has been accepted.
And the sheep are regrouped
as Stuart moves over to the pen.
10 points awarded, then.
Come by. Here.
Jim.
Don't want to pressure the sheep
too much at this stage
but keep them moving.
Away. Stand.
Away. Stand. Away. Stand.
Come by.
They look like they're quite
intrigued by the inside of that pen.
Yes, he's got them boxed quite well
but it's gently does it.
They're going... Oh, man!
There was half a sheep in there!
They've all got to go, and that gate
shut. That looks successful now.
That'll do, Jim. Super stuff!
What a round from Stuart and Jim.
Eight scored for the pen.
A total of 80. Wonderful stuff.
Stuart and Jim, you've got to be
happy with that one! Well done!
Any idea what you might have scored?
No. Did it feel
like a good round to you?
No! Didn't it?
What were you disappointed by?
The fetch. I lost him
for a couple of seconds in the...
Well, you still got a great score.
Oh, well. You got 80. 80.
So Scotland are very much
back in the running,
thanks to the two of you.
Congratulations to Jim. Thank you.
Our next competitor to tackle
this very tricky course
is Alan Lloyd Jones,
he lives in Bala in North Wales.
Let's meet him and his dog, Bet.
My name is Alan Lloyd Jones
and my dog's name is Bet.
We live on a farm
in North Wales near Bala.
The farm's 1,250ft above sea level.
There's not many farms
in North Wales higher than that.
# Have a nice day... #
Bet's commands are in Welsh
AND in English.
When she's near,
we speak Welsh with her.
HE SPEAKS WELSH
Bet is a one-man dog,
she won't listen to nobody else,
even if they're on the same commands
as me. She just works for me.
And she's with me everywhere.
# She's a lady
# Wo-oh, wo-oh, oh
She's a lady... #
Bet's been working on Welsh
mountain sheep all her life.
That will be a problem when we go
to One Man And His Dog.
They say the sheep will be much
bigger sheep than ours.
It's the same as people
that's been driving a Mini
all their life and the next thing
they'll be driving a BMW!
Much bigger thing, so...
we'll see how things go.
HE SPEAKS WELSH
And that means, good luck to Wales
and I hope we can win it.
# ..And the lady is mine. #
Well, Alan Lloyd Jones
and his dog, Bet,
have it all to do here for Wales.
HE WHISTLES
She was just turning in that little
bit, but she's going out now.
She's certainly running
a long way round, there.
Coming nicely round
at the bottom of the field,
behind the sheep now.
Just see Malcolm at the back
with his dog, Sam,
they were holding the sheep
at the lift post.
Just 2 points lost
on the outrun, 18 scored.
And 10 points for the lift.
Yes. Now, Alan's whistling the dog
on but the dog's casting back.
So he's using his voice now to try
and bring the dog over the rise.
HE WHISTLES
Lie down. Come by.
He's still got to push them over
yet, they're still to the right
of the gate now,
coming into the centre position.
Nicely through.
Come by, come by. Lie down.
Come by, come by, come by.
HE SPEAKS WELSH
As the sheep come
a little bit closer,
you can hear Alan has transferred
to voice commands
and he uses both English and Welsh.
Good line through that turn.
Yes, and what a responsive dog.
16 points for the fetch.
Well, this is an excellent line,
right from his feet,
right to the first drive gate.
They're through.
ALAN WHISTLES
They may gain speed a little bit
as they go down into the dip.
But a beautiful distance there
between sheep and dog.
And this really is the tricky part
of the course.
This bit right here.
HE WHISTLES
Now he's in with a chance.
And absolutely through the middle
and well under control.
That was good.
It's difficult to emphasise, Gus,
how difficult these sheep are
to control and how easy
this is being made to look.
Lie down. Come by.
He's holding her back a little bit
as they come into the shedding ring.
We want them really settled.
Lie down.
26 out of 30 for the drive.
Interesting to see
how he works these.
He's got a collared ewe on the left.
There's a gap coming.
She's just that little bit jittery.
As he moved. The dog wasn't moving
at all, but as Alan moved.
One of the other ewes, she's
for off if given half the chance.
She's on the right
of the picture now.
She's the dodgy...
There she goes again.
That's an awkward sheep and that's
going to prove difficult.
Lie down.
The one thing you can't do
is rush it.
HE SHOUTS A COMMAND
Here we go.
He's come in and he's got her.
Lie down.
Come by. Come by.
8 points awarded for the single.
Lie down.
Here. And so, it's now to the pen.
Lie down. Lie down.
They're looking in.
Lie down.
In with a chance now. Lie down.
They're having a look. Go on!
This could be it.
This could be it - there they go!
What about that?
Oh! And there's a sheep
jumped over the pen!
We've got sheep agility here!
7 given for the pen,
that's a total of 85.
Well, Alan has been trialling
since he was 10 years old
and all of that experience
came into play there.
Now, there's a smiling Welshman!
You've got to be pleased with that!
Yeah, but there were
little bits by the pen.
There was a very awkward ewe
in there. Yes.
I bet you were hoping that she's
going to be your next lamb sandwich!
Well, it would be better if she had
a collar on, wouldn't it?
Well, congratulations to you both.
Thank you.
Excellent round. 85, you scored.
85. Thank you very much.
So you're in the lead so far.
I'll let you get off. Our next
competitor, who has got to try and
beat that magnificent Welsh score,
is our home competitor.
It's Seamus Gallagher.
And let's find out a little bit more
about him and his dog, Glen.
My name's Seamus Gallagher
and I'll be running my dog, Glen.
I live on a farm in Glenravel in the
glens of Antrim in Northern Ireland.
I'm a welder by trade.
I work in Belfast.
And I'm a part-time farmer,
in the evening and the weekends.
My brother's heavily involved
in trialling
and my daughter is interested
in trialling, too.
She's competing in the national
this year for the first,
she's coming 18
and she's very enthusiastic.
I got into trialling
23, 24 years ago.
It was very satisfying
to have a young dog,
and to train him right up
through to compete at open level.
A dog's natural hunting instinct
with sheep comes from nature.
And you're communicating
with nature to control that.
And you're using it to work the
animals that you're keeping.
Glen's five years old, in his prime.
Good-natured dog. Very determined
and sometimes very hard to stop!
He should run well
in One Man And His Dog.
But it will depend a lot
on the sheep.
Seamus Gallagher
with his dog, Glen. Only a small
dog but quite a pushy one.
So it's going to be quite
interesting to see how
the sheep react to him.
Yes, and it's a good start,
going down to the right.
No whistles.
And starting to come
across the bottom.
HE WHISTLES
Just 1 point lost on the outrun,
a score of 19.
And just 1 point lost on the lift.
9 scored.
28 so far.
SEAMUS WHISTLES
Goodness me, this is certainly
the fastest fetch we've had
in this competition. Well,
they say it's a fairly pushy dog!
Goodness me! They're coming up here
at a pace!
Now, what will happen?
Will they come up too fast
and he won't be able to turn them?
Dog's covering them,
stopping them escaping.
There will be some
points lost here
because they're
too far off line.
But at least they're
all bunched together.
Glen working well.
HE WHISTLES
And away they go, onto the drive.
This is going to be a very fast run.
17 out of 20 scored on the fetch.
I tell you what, Glen does have a
tendency to like to get it done,
Seamus says. Likes to race
about the field at 100mph.
And we've seen proof of that now.
Turning them gently.
He's giving them nice room
but they're setting off fairly fast
and they're coming uphill
a little bit, towards us.
The sheep travelling fast
on the cross drive.
HE WHISTLES COMMANDS
Seamus whistling
the dog to take the inside flank
to turn them back uphill. This is
going to be extremely difficult.
I think we're going
to have a miss here.
Yes, this side of the drive gates,
he can't have a second attempt
at it and they've
now gone well past.
This has a very different feel
to the previous rounds we've seen,
especially with Alan Lloyd Jones -
a very steady, calm round,
and this is, er, I've got a feeling
it's pretty frantic.
Seamus will be very disappointed.
15 scored for the drive.
Now he's got things settled again.
He's just letting those sheep
settle.
The sheep are
just showing that they've done
a little bit of running.
And typical, there are the collared
ewes right in the middle.
Right in the middle.
He's got to prise one of those
away from the others.
There's a collared ewe coming out
towards the front.
When they've come round
at this sort of speed, they're going
to stick tight together.
That's the one he's going for,
the one you can see
in front of Glen there, I think.
They're really glued onto the dog.
Hey, hey, hey!
And you see how, how he's just
moving that little bit faster
and he's just not settling
these sheep.
Are they going to get out of
the ring? Wow, right to the edge!
Now he's got one on the end,
over on the left hand side.
Stay, stay.
This could be the moment
he's been waiting for.
And here!
They spring out. He asked the dog
in and he's come in.
But unfortunately
he's come on the two.
The other five have gone out of the
ring so this is going to cost him.
HE WHISTLES
Well sadly, after a cracking start,
Seamus and Glen
ran out of time
at the shedding ring,
leaving them with total score of 60.
Oh! Seamus.
Yes.
How frustrated were you when you
were standing in the shed there.
Yeah, it was difficult, eh?
He couldn't get a space
and it's one of those things.
Very, very frustrating.
Cos Glen did a fine job. At the
start you must have been thinking,
"This is going to be a breeze."
We started well, but cross drive,
the sheep were fighting a bit, so...
Yeah, well a disappointing round.
I'm so sorry. But well done.
Thank you again. OK. Thank you.
Thanks so much, Seamus.
Well a disappointing round for
Ireland there.
Next it's the competitor
who is going to try to keep England
in the lead.
It's Jim Cropper.
Let's find out more about him.
I'm Jim Cropper. This is my dog Dan.
This is my farm,
it's in the Pennines.
HE WHISTLES COMMANDS
'50 or more years ago,
an old shepherd friend of mine'
used to take me gathering sheep and
I got so fascinated watching this
border collie bitch gather the sheep
I bought myself a dog then
and started to train it.
I got the bug.
It's become a...
..a part of my life.
# Here comes the girls... #
The two nieces, Chloe and Sophie,
come up to help us
and the granddaughter comes to help
with the pups.
But it's like nearly a family affair.
Come on!
Chloe, last year, won One Man And
His Dog and Sophie will be competing
this year in the junior section.
So hopefully she can do the same.
The things they have achieved
is marvellous and I feel really proud
of what they're doing.
Dan, he's worked on these hills
for seven years
and we have a good understanding.
I'm looking forward to
One Man And His Dog this year.
I like to try and put a performance
up what nobody else can beat.
Well here comes the granddaddy
of the sheep dog trialling world -
it's Jim Cropper.
Now, unfortunately, Jim's dog Dan
that we saw in the film there
has been retired from this
competition, he strained his leg
but this is Fleet. Yes, he might be
a substitute dog
but I've seen him run
and he's very, very capable.
Jim has represented England in the
national team over 30 times.
Also represented England over 20
times in the international team.
HE WHISTLES COMMANDS
And nicely behind the sheep.
Just quiet whistles.
Oh, this is a nice start.
19 for the out run.
Full marks for the lift.
10 out of 10.
As these sheep come over the rise
now to the side of the dog,
will Jim close the gap?
HE WHISTLES
Slightly left...
Oh, I think that's tactics,
you know.
I think that's the shallower part
to go over. Yep. He's a canny man!
MATT LAUGHS
At least the dog has
kept in contact with the sheep,
which is the main thing.
Well, it's worked. It's going very
well at the moment.
And through they go.
As these sheep come up the rise
and in to the handler's post...
Only a young dog.
But he's had a lot of success
with him.
Oh, nicely done! Made it look easy.
Just lost three points on the fetch.
17 out of 20 scored...
for Jim and of course for England.
That's the "walk on" whistle.
Fleet!
HE WHISTLES COMMANDS
The dog looking back
at the handler then.
Left down the flank now.
And fast round.
He's just a little bit tight there
and it's set them off at a speed.
Is he going to be able to recover
now on the cross drive?
Yeah, everything's looking good.
Yes, this is good.
Will he be fast enough?
He's asking him left now.
Asking him left again,
fast and you see how the dog
responded to the quicker whistle.
What about that! Lovely.
Beautifully done!
HE WHISTLES COMMANDS
Well that was a good drive.
26 points for Jim's drive.
Still plenty of time,
it's all about patience.
But as we've seen with Seamus,
time ticks away in here.
Here's a chance - one on the back.
Is he going for the back...
Oh, what a shame! What a shame!
Come on, Fleet.
Well this is a manouvre that
shepherds do in order to,
obviously, pair off one sheep
if they've got problems with their
feet or something like that,
so this is something that comes
straight off the farm, really, this.
There's a chance
of the back one coming.
Here it goes.
The dog's gone in.
Lay down. Lay down!
Lie down! And that's it.
There we are.
For a three-year-old dog, that was
very mature that, wasn't it? Yes.
A lot of dogs
would have gripped there.
Just four points awarded then
for the single.
Coming nice and steady as the sheep
come up the rise.
Now.
This man is usually good at penning.
Will the back two go in? No.
A bit of milling going on.
Thought we were going to get
one under the gate, but we haven't.
Another one coming out.
Fleet, do your bit!
Oh, that ewe!
She's went, "No, I'm not going to
fight. I'm going in. That's it."
What a super finish there.
Nine scored at the pen.
A wonderful round of 85.
And I tell you what,
Fleet certainly didn't let Jim
down there or England, and
their lead continues to build.
Very well done indeed.
You must have been beside yourself
in the shed, weren't you?
I thought they were never going to
come off, these two.
They were in the middle and
I couldn't get them
to change their minds.
Anyway, we got there in the end,
but...
85 scored. Oh!
So you're absolutely level pegging
with Alan Lloyd Jones from Wales.
So are you pleased with Fleet's
performance?
Yeah. He did well for a stand-in,
didn't he?
He really did.
It was a pleasure to watch.
Jim, thank you very much. I think
Sophie will be proud of you.
Oh, yeah. I'm proud of her as well.
Absolutely.
Well, Matt and Gus,
what did you make of that
magnificent singles competition?
Well, Kate, as predicted,
we knew it was going to be close,
but it was a real nail biter, Gus.
The first half of the competition
was all about this wobbly fetch.
Why were the sheep straying from
the perfect line?
Well when they came over the rise,
Stuart's dog unfortunately stayed
right the way back
and the sheep went well off line
and cost him a lot of points.
And then when it came to Alan, well
Alan, he'd seen what had happened
but he still got in a mess there
and his sheep went off line
but not as bad and
it didn't cost him as many.
The second half of the competition
was all about the shedding rig.
It was a real time sapper.
Let's talk about Seamus.
Was that really to do
with the character of the sheep?
It was really. They're young sheep,
they wanted to stick together,
they just would not split,
and although it was there
in plenty of time,
the opportunity never really came.
And Jim spent quite a lot of time in
there as well, didn't he? Yeah.
He only ended up with four points
for his shed,
but at least he did get his shed
and then went on to a successful
pen and finish.
That was certainly a nail-biting
competition.
You all impressed Matt and Gus.
Let's now confirm the results
of the singles round.
Joint winners were...
They both scored...
So how does that
affect the leader board?
Another stunning day of trialling,
but there's more to come.
Next time we've got the brace
competition -
a truly magnificent display
of shepherding prowess.
That's one man and two dogs.
Don't miss it.
Join us then from County Antrim.
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk