Brought to you by Ramen Soup Subs!
[Last week's recap]
[Big Bang's awesome rapper TOP came]
[To Kangwondo, Bookdongmaeul with the Family]
[While Grandma and Grandpa are enjoying their vacation happily]
[Family who came to a winterland]
[The "Ah Bi" name-calling snow battle which occurred in the snow]
[Going to the sea to help the villagers catch fish]
[Unexpected catch: shark and agwi fish]
[Yejin and Jongkook: love(?) developing between the two because of their knife skills]
[And the woman with the bread]
[And the result of this scandal is?]
[Finally, dinner time]
[Mental battle between two men over potato pancake]
[The one who gets the pancake is also the one who gets to wield the most power?!]
[Ultimately it becomes noisy Jaesuk's humiliation]
[After going through so many obstacles, finally being able to eat the delicious potato pancake and grilled agwi fish]
[The Family's night together gradually lengthens]
[Part 1: Family becomes rapper!]
A-Yo! A-Yo!
Huh?
TOP can't stand there.
[They should be standing at the position they think they'll get]
That's the last position.
It's the ranking we think we'll get again, right?
[Immediately moving towards the higher-ranking positions]
[Confidently going to first place]
Go over there, over there.
Yeah, you should be there.
[Confidently going to first place]
[No. 7 Jongkook moves towards the lower-ranking positions...]
Yeah, you should be there.
Out of all the guests we've had so far, he's the first one to stand in first place so confidently.
Yeah, I think it's going to be TOP too.
[TOP, the black horse who everyone thinks is going to be ranked first]
Today, our nation's best rapper has come. Hasn't he asked the Family already?
[Could today's mission be...]
Today, our nation's best rapper has come. Haven't he asked the Family already?
You don't expect us to rap too, do you?
[Could today's mission be...]
Ah why not? Why can't you do it?
[Sudden outburst]
We've never rapped before.
[It's obvious that the Family's men will never reach the rapper's standard]
[Sudden outburst]
We've never rapped before.
[It's obvious that the Family's men will never reach the rapper's standard]
Don't think that it's that hard.
Just organize all your inner thoughts, that would be a rap already.
[Eh?]
Yo Jaesuk ah!
Look at him, why's he doing it like that?
What's wrong?
It wasn't bad!
I'm already trying my best! What's wrong?
I'm sacrificing myself for the show. Yeah baby!
[Even in a rap, huk~ huk~ huk~]
Wow, good job!
[The only one amazed]
[Suddenly: You're a chuksae (black-faced bunting; type of bird)]
[You're a malse (the end of the world)]
Oh! I think it'll be better if you guys reply to each other's raps.
So we're going to be doing it like that?
I have a lot of strength (himse)!
[Embarrassing]
You like Yejin, don't you? You love her, don't you? Then what about Eunhye?
[Oh my...Jaesuk is still able to create a scandal using rap]
And there's Hyori too. Who're you going to choose among the three of them?
[Ridiculous]
Look, Jongkook ah, use your small eyes to view the world.
[In the Family, a rapper prodigy is born!!]
[Rapper Yoo]
[Super proud of himself, Rapper Yoo]
This is so easy, it's too easy!
[Today's mission: using rap to demonstrate your charisma!]
Let's start with TOP!
I've suddenly developed the confidence to rap.
Yo TOP! Let's go!
[Big Bang's awesome rapper TOP]
[Doing this is a little...]
[Family Gaddeottda (Family Outing in Korean)]
[His rap has started!]
[Hearing TOP's interesting and original English rap...]
[Family's totally excited]
[Especially the feverish Big Bang dongsaeng]
[So cool!!]
[It's not over yet!]
[Going with the flow, TOP continues with a DISCO RAP!]
All the women here go weak looking at my moves.
Where has all the sanity gone to? Let's have a cup of coffee
TOP and TOPS.
Dragging your feet along absentmindedly and losing yourself.
[Even more excited this time because they can understand the lyrics]
There's no such thing as a perfect life.
[TOP, Hip-Hop warrior]
[TOP's rap made the atmosphere huk~ huk~]
Tonight's the night of your life, yeah!
One more time, let's go! Music please.
[Completely off beat]
[Eh?]
[Hip-Hop Stepmother, Chunderella reunited?]
Stepmother Kim!
Unending longevity, the turtle and the goose.
[What kind of rap is this?]
'Ching ching kakoo salisali sam ha'
[Embarrassing]
Whoa, whoa
[Opening a new level of rap]
[A meeting of History and Rap]
[Opening a new level or rap]
[Stepmother Kim's well-informed rap]
-Wait a minute...!
-Okay, let's continue.
Please think differently when doing this.  I can't bear to watch you!
It's because we don't know what to say.
-I mean, really...
-Let's continue with this feeling!
TOP, how should we pronounce things?
It's probably better to be a bit more articulate.
Ah, more articulate.  So don't roll our words?
Rap is something that is better to hear if the pronunciation is better.
[Rap Know-How:  The better the pronunciation, the better it is heard]
Let's continue with another rhythm.
-Let's go!
-A faster rhythm, a faster rhythm?
-You know, that one.  Yeah.
Yo, let's go!
Everyone, party time!
One, two, three, four!
Jong Kook likes Ye Jin a lot!
[Starting the fabricated scandal again as rap]
Jong Kook likes Yoon Eun Hye a lot!
Jong Kook likes Lee Hyori a lot!
The world is wide, but his eyes are small!
Yeah!  Yo!  Among the three, which one of them is your partner?
-One, two... One, two, three, four!
-What is this?!
Do you love them?
[Surprised]
Of course, he must still be shy!
[The choice at the crossroads: Jong Kook's rap regarding this matter is?]
In my memories, there's a Hyori who was extremely innocent
..there's a Hyori who was extremely innocent
[Jong Kook's choice is Hyori?!]
-Whoa, whoa!
-Yo! Hyori!
[Jong Kook's choice is Hyori?!]
-Whoa, whoa!
-Yo! Hyori!
Today... She came to me with a pure white steam bun
[Dinner...]
[Hyori, knocking on one's heart with a pure white steam bun]
She came to me with a pure white steam bun
[It's a big fuss!] [A big fuss!]
Hyori, she made my heart change to pure white
...made my heart change to pure white
Yo, yo, Hyori!
The girl you want is here
That girl you want is here
My name is Lee Hyori
[Awkward Girl: Hyori's answer]
Family's sexy girl
I think everyone will fall in love with me
Kim 'Kook Jong', right?  Or not?
Kim 'Kook Jong', I understand your feelings
But I only think of you as an oppa
Anyway, please be kind to make sure that I am not in last place today
Yo, yo, yo!
-Fantastic
-Oh, Jong Kook oppa, you're good!
Kim 'Kook Jong', you rap well!
I think I lost my mind...
I did everything so I wouldn't be last place...
I just said anything!
He just confessed to Hyori, didn't he?
Hyung, we heard all that!
(I said it wasn't like that...)
But.. Daesung, you're holding the mic.  Do you feel something is missing?
-Should I end with something fancy?
-Shall we?
-Want to do something fancy?
-Yes, usher the noona's...
-Usher?
[Family's Youngest: Daesung]
Family~
What do I do?
[Anticipating]
Ye Jin, when I first saw you~
I think I would fall if someone just touched me
That's why I didn't even go near you
Hyori, when I first saw you~
'You'?!
[Timid]
Let's rap this instead
Lee Hyori
When I first saw her
She was a part of FinKL on TV
She was a nymph back then
[Was?]
[Glare:  Then, now?]
[Timid]
Why aren't you listening to Daesung?
When we see the broadcast... we'll have to go out somewhere...
I prepared a secret weapon for the noonas
What is it?!
[Uneasy]
[A diplomatic bribe to the noonas?]
Did you get them bags?
Bag?
What is it, what is it?
[A T-shirt that a picture of TOP is on]
-It's pretty
-Ooh, it's a T-shirt, a T-shirt.
[A T-shirt that a picture of TOP is on]
What kind of T-shirt is it?
Oh, it's so pretty.  Thank you!
-Wait!  Hyori and Ye Jin, also rap?
-Do you have anything you want to say to us?  Just say it.
Okay, we'll release ranks here together?
-Rap, rap, rap!
-Okay!
We'll 'total' release ranking.
Music start!
[Again the beat flows]
Okay, first.  Hyori!~
[U Go Girl, Hyori]
My name is Lee Hyori
Said backwards it's still, Lee Hyori!
Do you all want to die?
What do you think, Kang Daesung?
My problem is how I look on TV?
Oh, no!  I am pretty!
And, Kim 'Kook Jong', come here!
I have something to say to you
You keep saying it's awkward
And you keep avoiding my eyes
I understand your feelings
Who is the person who's in your heart?!
[Good gracious]
You're shy, aren't you
All right, next is Yoon Jong Shin.  You always have weird gestures
You, while in the Family, have forgotten your age!
[For some reason, feels like she's yelling at each one by one]
If your body hurts, REST!
[Sad]
Last week, I
Could have done well with Song Chang Eui
You were a hindrance in the middle.  And you call yourself a friend.  How could you do that?
Sorry!  Sorry!  Sorry!  Sorry!
Hyori, we're sorry!
Oppa, my hands and feet feel like they're shriveling!
What do I do?
-Hyori, no one told you to go for so long.  Why did she rap for so long?!
Hyori, you called out each of your oppas and scolded them.
It's been a long time since I've heard 'Scold Rap'
[This is Scold Rap]
She scolded so much!
Oh, what am I going to do?
Next is Ye Jin
[Worried]
[Sweet and brutal Ye Jin]
Yeh~
I'm sweet and brutal Ye Jin Park!
Oh~  Oh~
I also have a nasal tone
And our loving Family
Oppa, why are you like that?
[Their hands and feet are shriveling again..]
[What shall she do...]
I'm scared of this music!
Completely handsome Chunhee, yeaa~
Oh~
[In the meanwhile, not forgetting the nasal tone beat]
The world's most innocent boy, Daesung!
And amazing Yoon Jong Shin oppa!
[Unable to deal]
[Want to hide somewhere...]
[First time in Family:  To have their hands and feet shrivel like this...]
I respect rappers starting from today.
People who rap are amazing.
This really... I want to go somewhere...
I saw the cameraman do this for the first time, too
He keep shriveling into himself
My whole body is wriggling
Everyone's so ashamed, they're banding together
Because we're so embarrassed, we're gathered like this
This is..
I think I really will have to go out somewhere when this broadcasts.
I don't think I'll be able to watch this at home.
This is the first time we've stuck together during the ranking.
We're all like this, but Soo Ro hyung is...
I don't know if it's because I'm new here, but everyone did so well...
It's more embarrassing when he says that!
He said that we did well...
TOP, don't be nice to us!
TOP, I'm so sorry, but I love you.
Soo Ro!  Know that you're being humiliated!
I'm not embarrassed!
We're all embarrassed, right now all flee!
Stop!  Stop!!!
I feel like shriveling up...!
My insides have all shriveled up!
Let's start right now
You want to announce the order by rap?  All right, let's rap the order.
[Announcing the order]
Oppa, just bear with it a bit longer.
Today's last place has to rap freestyle for one minute.
Female male together.
-Really scary, isn't it?
-Oh, the two last place?
-Wow, that's really embarrassing.
-Really scary, isn't it?
-That's really embarrassing.
-Oppa, one minute is very long.
-I can't lift my head.
If it's a minute, it's 60 seconds...
[Whisper][Whisper]
[If only I could escape being last place]
[Who will be doing the ending rap?]
Okay, today's seventh place is~
STOP!  STOP!
Please don't!  Please don't!
I'm not going to sleep tonight and I'm going to get rid of all the tapes that we rapped in.
[Seventh place announcement]
Today's seventh place is!
Careless Chun Hee, Lee Chun Hee!
[Cheering]
[Happier than everyone else, 'Seventh' Jong Kook]
[Mix of joy and sorrow]
[Doesn't feel like someone else's situation]
We'll announce the 6th place now.
It's okay now.  Just don't need to do the rap.
Today's 6th place is....
Since you're sick, go to sleep early, Yoon Jong Shin!
It's okay!
Today's 5th place is...
You rapped too much history, Kim Soo Ro!
[Jong Kook, advancing to fourth!]
Okay, today's 4th place is...
What are you expecting, Yoo Jae Suk?
Oh!  What'll I do?!
Hey, come here quickly.
Oh, Jong Kook hyung!
I came all the way up here!
[Steam Bun rap won Hyori's heart?]
Jong Kook, you must be happy.
It's insane!
[Steam Bun rap won Hyori's heart?]
[Jong Kook, going to first place like this?]
Today's 3rd place is...
Naive even though he's Big Bang, Kang Daesung!
Jong Kook is...!
Ahh!  What'll I do?!
[Fidgeting]
-Do the two of you want to have a rap battle?
-No!!
I'm just happy like this...!
[Announcing first place]
We'll hug today's first place like we always do.
A hug?
We're going to announce first place now!
One, two, three, four!
Today's first place is...
The prince to came to Family~
See, what'd I tell you
[Second place is still an amazing feeling]
[TOP, first place ceremony]
Chun Hee, ready your rap
Please come down.
Girls, don't be impertinently up there and come down!
You're going to receive our judgment.
Oppa, please.  I can't do this!
Try it!
Why are you whining
You like this kind of stuff
Okay, yea~
We'll make you tie second place!
Okay~
That's scary!
Tying second is a good thought!
Let's vote!  Let's vote!
I wish you wouldn't see this.
This is the symbol for first place...
What'll I do?
One, two, three...!
Hyori, did you see?
Hyori and Ye Jin
[You're second place]
4 to 3!
One of these two will be rapping!
I just wish I wouldn't be rapping...
Yo, let's go.
[Anxious]
The first place, TOP will hug
[First place is a hug]
And second place will casually be given a mic.
If a frog raps, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit.
[Wondering if he'll become a rapper continuing on with this...]
Oh, please....
One two three with the music?
One, two.  One, two, three, four!
[Second place, Lee Hyori!]
[First place, Park Ye Jin]
[Lady Ye Jin, there's no way to be happier than this!]
[Dark]
Close your ears!
Hyori!  Chun Hee!
[Going in to keep the promise]
[Must be humiliating]
Why am I seventh place?
I didn't put you there!
I know that you put me here!
Ye Jin also had a say in the decision!
Ah!  I trusted her!  But Ye Jin threw me away!
[Even the hands and feet that cannot be shriveled any further...]
I think I'm going to tear.
We are the best friends in the Family.
Same aged couple!  Yay!
[Quickly]
Let's go in quickly!
We're very sorry!
My sneakers aren't coming off!
I also...
Ahh, again...!
Start again, start again.
[The Family's rapping caused their bodies to cringe head to toe this night...]
-We're sorry
-Do it again!
[The Family's rapping caused their bodies to cringe head to toe this night...]
[Current time 12:45AM]
Earlier instead of being worried of being last I was worried that I might sleep next to Jaesuk hyung
Because he snores
[Snoring Jaesuk scarier than last place]
Mera, say hi to our new guest
[Looking for the new guest]
[Mera correctly finding TOP]
So how are we doing this?
[Preparing the bedding]
[1st to 3rd place men can sleep here]
The girls here
And I guess 3 guys here?
[1st to 3rd place men can sleep here]
[The 2 girls plus the 3 guys might be a tight fit...]
And I guess 3 guys here?
How are we going to fit 3 guys here?
[The 2 girls plus the 3 guys might be a tight fit...]
One guy can sleep here
So I sleep there?
[3rd place Daesung sleeps above their heads...]
Good night everyone
Sleep well
I have to turn off the light
[Rapping again?]
Everybody good night!
Stop it!
We are sleeping!  Until the morning!
Shut up!
Want me to rap so you can't sleep?
Hyori's rapping earlier.. oh~
She did a good job
Jongkook, are you preparing for next week already?
[Jongkook completely on Hyori's side]
No, I'm just saying she wasn't that bad
Jongkook, you're too much
There is one man that only loves you (Jongkook's song lyrics)
Oppa, the white steamed bun that captured my heart
No, I intended to say that up to there
[Their sleepiness vanishes mentioning Jongkook's rap]
Your rap earlier.. really...
After Hyori's rap I was going to rap about Yejin too
But then all of a sudden you dragged Hyori down
[The sudden appearance of Hyori caused Jongkook to freeze]
HR: What was the line after that?
JK: I just froze!
From then on I went crazy like I lost my mind
I don't even remember what I said
Look at the world with your small eyes
[Jongkook's rap opening his eyes to the world]
Stop it!
I really can't sleep tonight
I said that earlier
Look at the world with your small eyes
[Remembering his embarrassing rap]
What do I do?
Why isn't the trauma going away?
I really did feel good when Hyori gave me the steamed bun earlier
-HR: That's right
-JK: Yeah.
I also felt good when I was snapping the heads off the bean sprouts with Yejin
I felt good all day until we had to start rapping
Good night
If it's not good night than it's all night
[Til the end...]
[The Family's night where they can't overcome the trauma of rapping... We will go that deep]
[Ch. 2 Shoot at Jaesuk]
[Next day 7:30AM]
[The loud snores in the room]
[Without fail the wakeup time has arrived]
[First wake up Jaesuk]
[His siblings are all still sleeping]
[Jaesuk alone wakes up]
[Even asleep he prepares his socks]
[What could today's morning game be..]
They will have to spin five times elephant trunk style and then throw a ball to stick on your head or chest to pass
[The impending horrible siren!]
[Startled]
[Sudden strike]
[Trying to avoid the horrible siren]
[TOP too, mindlessly avoiding]
Good morning
[First up as always, Sooro]
[Quickly finished putting it on]
[Still half asleep~]
So from over there spin five times doing the elephant trunk
[Like this?]
You're out
I'm supposed to make it stick?
After you spin five times
[Regardless it seems like Jaesuk will have to suffer]
Spin 5 times first
Yejin-ah
You're hogging all the blanket
I thought I was going to die from the cold
[Not even thinking of getting up]
It's really cold today
[The cold hating Elderly one by one]
5 turns?
5 turns
[Sooro, first up]
Start
[Not even fully awake and having to spin]
One more turn
[Throwing even after hearing 'one more turn']
[The surprised Jaesuk]
If you throw hard like that I can try to avoid it
[One by one coming out unknowingly]
[Precocious]
What is this?
Hi
Hi oppa
Good morning
Start
[This time, Jongkook's turn]
His arm doesn't go because he works out too much
[Sloppy muscular elephant trunk?]
Hey~ really!!
You have to throw it.  1, 2, 3...
[Without fear of consequence, demanding]
[Clenching his teeth...]
[Hit!]
(Hurts, huh?)
Kim Kookjong-ssi, at first you were aiming somewhere else
Instead of looking here you're staring somewhere else
Oppa you look kinda cute today
Is that so?
Hyori, pass!
[Hyori automatically passes after saying he's cute?]
Really?
Her name is Lee Hyori
[Last night's embarrassing rapper Hyori]
Forget about yesterday
Start
[The Elderly Jongshin's turn]
[The direction looks right...]
[Pass?]
[Heavy blow to the arm]
I told you to watch out!
[Feeling sorry for his innocent right arm]
Oh, it hurts!
Next time it'll be your left
Ow, it hurts
He used his strength?
[Crybaby...]
Who's shoes are these?
[Putting on the shoes in front of her]
I'm just going to wear them
Daesung, are these yours?
They're mine
They're yours?
I was wondering why they were so high
Hyori, how'd you get so tall?
[Getting taller after putting on the shoes]
[Without warning]
How can you dodge it?
I said that if you threw it hard I was going to dodge it
[Daesung's turn]
[Lightly throwing]
[Dumb brother helping out]
Pass!
[Daesung exempt from cooking]
But you helped him out
I didn't help him
I was trying to dodge it like this
It's because Daesung wrote such a nice first impression yesterday
So from now on I can't dodge it anymore
Why now?
[Doing whatever he wants]
Yeah throw it lightly
Head
[Exactly]
[On his head]
I should have aimed for the head
The head sticks too
[Chunhee exempt from cooking]
Pass!
[Jongkook's turn!]
[Dangerous]
[Enjoying...]
[The target becomes restless]
[The wall even gets hit with force]
[#1 at dodging]
You can't do it like that
[The fluttering long hair, Hyori's turn]
Why didn't you tie your hair up first?
[With all her strength]
[This time he couldn't dodge it]
[Today Jaesuk is caught...]
Throw it well Hyori
[Lady Yejin]
Oh, pass!
[A nice and clean win]
[Yejin exempt from cooking]
[TOP passes]
[Sooro passes]
Jongkook, Jongshin...
[Jongkook, Jongshin, and Hyori are left]
Hyori
[Hyori! Again! Again!]
[Even though she'd fail]
Hyori, get your head on straight
[Irritated]
You're going to stress yourself out
[The Elder's turn]
Oh, I'm dizzy...
[Just how many balls did he shove in his pockets...]
[Foul play king, Jongshin]
You had all those balls and not even one hit
How can all those balls miss?
I don't have any luck
[A battling mindset, Jongkook's turn]
[Uneasy]
[Jaesuk helps him out?!]
[Afraid to get hit again]
I thought it was going to hit me so I just
[Jongkook exempt from cooking]
Hey, hey just stand still.. ok, like that..
[This time throwing calmly]
[Impossible]
[A proper hit to the chest]
[Hyori exempt from cooking]
Pass!
Today's breakfast.. Jongshin hyung, long time no see
[Confused]
This is the first time since catching that goby in the summer with me and Sooro hyung
Long time no see?
[Averting eyes]
Why are you looking at me?
Did you say long time no see?
No, you do this frequently
[Quickly changing his words]
[Deathly silent...]
I think I'm going to pick 2 people to help me
That's right, hyung-nim
The special cooking...
Oh! Jongshin hyung is cooking after such a long time
And you guys are sleeping?
Your name is Lee Hyori?
Let's see a morning rap then
[Strong refusal]
Express how much you want to go back to sleep
With 'My name is Lee Hyori' rap
Yo! My name is Lee Hyori
Backwards still it's Lee Hyori
I've cooked breakfast 3 weeks in a row
I just want to go back to sleep.. Yo...
[Embarrassed]
Oh! Oh! My name is Lee Hyori...
[Red faced Lee Hyori]
Jongkook-ah
Do it like you're responding
Or, you can just cook
My name is Kim Jongkook
Deep in my heart I have
A white steamed bun
Please don't pick me to cook breakfast
So we're just continuing last night's music?
I need to figure out why Seunghyun thinks I'm odd
[TOP picked for breakfast]
And since I still feel a little awkward with TOP
I need a person to mediate between the two of us
[Is it Daesung?]
And there's no one better than Jaesuk
[Reverse turn]
[Jaesuk picked for breakfast]
[The rest of the Family can go back to sleep]
HR: MC Yoo, cook the food well please
JS: Stop it
I couldn't decide between Jaesuk or Daesung
I heard mediator so I thought it was going to be you
If I'm not the mediator than am I the conductor?
[Chapter 3
Introducing Bingu TOP]
[They have to decide on the breakfast menu]
What should we make?
Let's go outside first.
[Go outside?]
Should we?
Yeah.
[Go outside?]
There's some mushrooms.
[Without deciding on the menu?]
Let's go find stuff.
Let's walk around and the head of the town,
[The three people...they don't seem to be thinking...]
Let's walk around and find the head of the town,
Last time we asked, he told us what to do.
Let's go.
[They're really...]
[leaving without a plan...]
[Temperature -8C]
[Luckily the head of the town told them about the trout farm...]
Have you had trout before?
I think I ate it once when I was little.
Oh, it's here.
[Arrived at the town's trout farm]
Wow, look. It's really big.
[Huge]
It is big. How are we supposed to catch it?
That's almost a shark!
Seunghyun, looks like you're going to show us how.
Again?
Yeah, you do it.
[TOP's road to suffering has started...]
[Later...]
[Got permission to catch 2 trouts...]
Why are they so fast?
Trouts are very sensitive.
[They're sensitive to the even soft sounds]
- They all gathered over there.
- You're right.
[They're sensitive to the even soft sounds]
[Swam to the corner because of the 3 people...]
- They all gathered over there.
- You're right.
[Swam to the corner because of the 3 people...]
They are sensitive.
I'm getting a runny nose.
TOP, you had a runny nose too?
Yes.
The 3 good-for-nothing brothers.
[The 3 good-for-nothing brothers?!]
[How did charismatic TOP become...]
[After calming down the trouts came back]
They're coming back.
Yeah, because it's quiet.
[You're not going to catch them just by staring...]
We just need to hit one up and catch it instead of going in.
[Enough of that...]
People use their hands like...
You try it.
I think this is too deep for me.
It seems like you two should go in since you're tall.
Seriously?
[Again...they have a blank look...]
You guys...since this is groundwater...
aren't going in because it might be cold right?
Okay, we're going in.
[In the end, the three decided to go in at the same time!]
1, 2, 3!
[They all lied...]
[Even the trusted TOP...]
[Two males getting into position]
Is it cold?
Hyung, since you're going in, go all the way in! Go in!
Hyung, don't be like this in the morning.
You're being dirty. Don't be like this in front of TOP.
[After a while, they're barely in...]
It's okay, even if water is going in.
Cold, it's cold!
Water is coming in.
What do you mean it's okay?
It's okay.
My foot's going to freeze.
It's okay if you're in the water.
Water is coming into my shoe.
- You can just get frostbite!
- Dongsaeng?!
You're saying I can get frostbite because I'm a dongsaeng?
That's right! Just come in, dongsang~
But the water's coming in.
[They're finally seriously trying to catch some fish but...]
Come, come, come.
But I think this much more of my arm has to go in.
[Compared to the dept of the water, the rubber gloves are too short]
Look, with this I can't reach.
[How embarrassing]
[So how are they going to eat breakfast...]
How are we supposed to eat breakfast?
[Surprised]
Did you step on me, Seunghyun?
No.
A trout just stepped on me and left.
Even a trout steps on you?
How discontent a trout must be to step on you.
[After saying that]
[They're a mess here and there]
They're hitting me with their head!
[Who came after who...]
[Again they're like this again...]
I can't catch them, this is short and I'll get this wet.
- Right?
- Yeah.
That's why we brought a longer one.
[That's why they brought a longer replacement]
Since that's a longer one, wear it.
Still it's going to be hard to catch them.
[The other two are preparing the landing net]
Ah! I stepped on one!
[Today the elder is suffering from age]
If you stepped on it, you could have gotten it.
[At the enclosed farm]
Did you catch one?
[Even with the landing nets, they can't catch one]
Come, come, come.
[Just then]
Oh, good!
[Caught one!]
[Fresh]
[After all the hard work, they successfully got one!]
Seunghyun, you're good.
[Huh?]
[What was he doing...?]
What are you doing with the one Seunghyun caught?
Did you lose it?
[Acted like he was the one who caught it...]
Do the Yoon Moon Shik mimicry!
You disrespectful...!
[It's perfect for a time like this!!]
Yoon Moon Shik is the one that said it to you.
[Oh~ Amazingly, Jaesuk caught one!]
[What's with the elder today...]
Hyung, what's wrong with you?
I wanted to let it go!
[The elder keeps causing accidents]
All of the sudden you and I stopped working,
we need to catch one though!
[The elder keeps causing accidents]
All of the sudden you and I stopped working,
we need to catch one though!
[TOP caught another one!!]
You had two! You did good.
[If the elder didn't cause an accident(?)
they'd have more than enough back home...]
You had two! You did good.
[If the elder didn't cause an accident(?)
they'd have more than enough back home...]
If you were able to get two, we could go home.
[If the elder didn't cause an accident(?)
they'd have more than enough back home...]
If you were able to get two, we could go home.
Alright, I'll catch one too!
[Two in one scoop!!]
[Unfortunately lose one though]
[In the end, caught two!!]
Seunghyun! Morning hero~
Let's go.
[They've got the ingredients...]
[The three people heading home happily~]
[However TOP did not know yet...]
[What Daesung would reveal later...]
[And how his confidence will change...]
[Arrived home after an hour!]
My feet are freezing.
[His feet are frozen because his boots were leaking...]
Whose shoes are those?
Why?
Because all my socks are wet.
Whose are these?
[The style is definitely Yejin's]
Those types are Yejin's.
Oh, these tyeps are Yejin's. Those are Hyori's.
[The style is definitely Yejin's]
[On the other hand, those are Hyori's style]
Oh, these tyeps are Yejin's. Those are Hyori's.
Even Yejin...
Shoe lifts?
Ah! Shoe lifts!
[Even Yejin secretly has shoe lifts...]
It's because of you.
Without those they only come up to my shoulders...
[Of course...]
Let's pretend we don't know.
- Don't tell her.
- Alright.
[You've already exposed everything...]
- Don't tell her.
- Alright.
[You've already exposed everything...]
Yejin has these too.
What should we make with these?
Usually it's sliced raw fish...
Hyung!
What?
Hyori...
Let me see.
[Shock]
[There's a saying that says there's not one person to trust in the world...]
Check Daesung's.
[Suddenly checking the shoes]
I was wondering why they were wearings boots.
When it becomes fall they start wearing boots.
Nobody else has them!
Hyori and Yejin hid these things too.
[The shocking(?) secret]
[By the way, the menu has yet to be decided!]
We have to handle the fish now.
What should we make? Stew, sliced raw fish.
It's a bit odd to eat sliced raw fish for breakfast.
Yeah.
How about a steamed kimchi fish dish?
[Steamed kimchi fish dish?]
You cut it a bit and boil it.
- Oh, with kimchi?
- Yeah, with kimchi.
[A steamed kimchi fish dish and grilled trout]
- Oh, with kimchi?
- Yeah, with kimchi.
[A steamed kimchi fish dish and grilled trout]
Since we have handled fish a lot, it's really simple...
(Me again...?)
I did the angler-fish yesterday...
Morning Hero.
Truthfully, you'd have to say Yejin did it!
[In the end...TOP is doing it...]
[Quickly grabbing it]
[Making it unconscious in one hit]
[PERFECT]
He's doing good.
A reliable dongsaeng came.
The meat looks really good...
TOP is really delicate..
[A perfect ingredient and dish setting in a flash]
[Grilled trout preparation complete]
TOP just sat here to do this.
[TOP sitting in front of the trout]
- I sat in front of the potatoes too.
- Should I do the steamed kimichi dish then?
[The elder is responsible for the steamed kimchi trout dish]
- I sat in front of the potatoes too.
- Should I do the steamed kimichi dish then?
Yeah.
[The elder is responsible for the steamed kimchi trout dish]
The kimchi is good.
Look forward to the steamed kimchi dish.
It's going to be magic.
[How to make a steamed kimichi trout dish 1. Evenly spread out the kimchi at the bottom of the pot]
Look forward to the steamed kimchi dish.
It's going to be magic.
[2. Cut a bit into the trout]
[3. Add a bit of water and let it boil]
I have to add the salt...
[TOP is responsible for the grilled trout]
Don't add too much.
[Adding salt to the trout...]
You have to add some while grilling it.
- Oh really?
- Yeah.
But from what I know you add a bit of salt in it...
[Oh~ TOP has his own opinion about seasoning a trout]
- Right, you know that?
- Yes.
[Oh~ TOP has his own opinion about seasoning a trout]
- Right, you know that?
- Yes.
I heard that the hand taste is important.
[There's a hand taste in the salt seasoning?]
You need to get a decent amount of salt.
Oh, always.
You have to close your eyes.
[Closing his eyes...]
How many are there?
About 150.
[About 150?!]
[Huh?]
Oh, this way.
[It's...spreading everywhere...]
But I think about 120 went outside.
[That's how the grilling preparations ended...]
Hyung!
[Awoken Daesung's entry]
Daesung really likes grilled fish.
[Two people who are a passionate fan of grilled fish]
- Oh really?
- Yeah.
[Two people who are a passionate fan of grilled fish]
- Oh really?
- Yeah.
Daesung, you should have slept some more.
[By the way, why isn't Daesung sleeping...]
Because I wanted to help with breakfast...
You came out because you were uneasy right?
Huh?
Just in case we talk about you.
No, I'm not.
I heard you're still talking to that friend.
What?
[It came up again?]
Seunghyun told us everything...
Hey, Hyung!
Sorry Daesung.
You're supposed to clean all this while doing this kind of thing...
[Immediately getting revenge by scolding]
Hyung, give that to me. I'll do that so you clean this up.
Since TOP is a hyung, again Daesung is...
[Cautious]
- I'll just...
- Doing this is so fun that I'm in the middle of enjoying it.
[Cautious]
- I'll just...
- Doing this is so fun that I'm in the middle of enjoying it.
But you're supposed to clean that up.
[Daesung continues to nag]
I caught it!
I even handled the fish!
- This is the first time I'm hearing TOP talk with such a loud voice.
- Yeah.
You have to put a lid on that, the dust is going to go in.
Do you have common sense in cooking....
Look at that! It's not on properly, hyung.
[Daesung, you're going to get hit if you continue...]
What is he doing?
Hyung, just go do that. How frustrating!
[Told you...]
TOP...that gentle person.
[To make that gentle TOP...]
[Gloomy]
- TOP never raised his voice with us.
- Yeah.
[Gloomy]
- TOP never raised his voice with us.
- Yeah.
But you still have to clean all that.
[He still can't wake up]
[Again being persistent]
You have that open. What is this?
Like these.
You have to clean then cook.
[Behaving like that while trusting the hyungs but...]
Hyung! While you're going there get another knife and cutting board.
[Why of all times is Jong Shin going to the kitchen now...]
Fine, I'll go with you!
Hyung, why are you going?
[It must be scary to be left alone...]
What?
- I'll come back soon.
- Hyung, just sit.
It's fine.
[At...a...distance...]
Hyung...
There's a camera...
(Come here...)
But seriously, I can't stand...
Hyung, don't, don't.
[As soon as TOP stood up...]
Hyu~ung!
[Cuteness explosion]
I really like you, hyung!
Then go sit over there quietly.
What?
Go sit over there quietly.
Here? Like this?
Stay there quietly.
[Who's stopping this...]
[But then]
Hyung!
[Sudden change]
What are you doing?
[Again, angrily scolding]
What?
I've been telling you to do this for 10-20 minutes.
[Again, angrily scolding]
It seems like TOP can't do anything to Daesung.
It's not like that, but this is common sense in cooking...
Isn't there a burnt smell?
[But there's a burnt smell coming from somewhere...]
Look, lift the lid.
- Wow, hyung.
- Is it burnt?
There's no water in here.
It's a steamed dish.
But don't you need to add a bit of water?
[It looks fine on the outside...]
But you can't burn it.
No, no. It's not a burnt smell.
Hyung, but there is a burnt smell.
[There's definitely a burnt smell...]
- No it's not.
- It's burnt at the bottom, hyung.
[There's definitely a burnt smell...]
- No it's not.
- It's burnt at the bottom, hyung.
You have to eat it a bit burnt.
[The food investigator refuses to admit it]
Hyung, it can't be burnt!
You have to eat it a bit burnt.
[The food investigator refuses to admit it]
Hyung, it can't be burnt!
It's stuck there.
[Urgently flipping it]
It is burnt...
It's not burnt. A steamed kimchi dish usually smells like this..
Hyung, why are you coughing?
[You said it wasn't burnt...]
What is this?!
[Ack! It's scorched black!]
Watch the result!
The kimchi is black!
[In the end, it's an emergency!!]
Hyung, you need to add something.
- Add some Perilla oil.
- Hyung, get the Perilla oil.
It's behind you.
[First adding some Perilla oil]
How about if we add some potatoes in here?
Should we just add the potatoes in here?
[Adding an ingredient to try and save the dish]
- Yeah.
- Cut the potatoes!
[Adding an ingredient to try and save the dish]
What kind of fish is this?
Trout.
Oh, the one with the protruding eye?
Not mullet, trout.
Oh, trout, I thought you said mullet.
Trout is freshwater and mullet is saltwater.
So this is a saltwater fish?
This is... freshwater.
Why can't you understand what I'm saying? We've known each other for a year.
[The name...Dumb and Dumber]
[On the other hand, the two older people are not concentrating on saving the kimchi dish...]
Taste it.
No, not yet, we just put the potatoes in.
Wait, if this tastes bitter then it's ruined.
(Arguing) It's not bitter.
(puckered!!) I'll just try some.
[The result]
- It's because the kimchi isn't ripe yet.
- This isn't bitter?
- The kimchi isn't ripe?
-Yeah, it's not ripe.
[Who's telling the truth...]
- The kimchi isn't ripe?
-Yeah, it's not ripe.
[Who's telling the truth...]
Give some to TOP then.
Don't give him a lot.
[In the end, TOP's going to taste it]
It is a bit bitter...
[It's bitter since it's burnt...]
Why is it bitter?
He said it was bitter, what do you mean 'why'?
[It's bitter since it's burnt...]
Why is it bitter?
He said it was bitter, what do you mean 'why'?
And it's really salty.
It's salty?
It's really bitter too.
Cut some more kimchi.
[Rushing to construct the kimchi dish]
Should we put some more potatoes?
[With new kimchi]
[Boiling it again with potatoes and water]
There's enough in it.
But why did the trout become so flat?
[Flat]
Isn't one side is burnt a bit too much.
At a grilled fish store it's like this.
- Really?
- Yeah.
TOP is firm on his opinions.
[Now that you mention it, he suddenly began express his opinions]
Because of Daesung he's sticking with his opinions.
[He's putting the grilled trout on the plate but...]
Hyung! The head's going to be bent!
[Oh my]
[In bits and pieces]
Hyung, how can you finish it like that?
You almost have to assemble the trout...
I wanted to make this look nice...
Should we try some?
Daesung: Is it good?
It's good.
[But still, it seems like it tastes good...]
- It's good~
- Yeah, it is.
[TOP is also pleased]
The kimchi dish looks good too.
- It looks like something they'd sell in restaurants.
- Yeah.
[After trying again, the kimichi dish seems successful too~]
- It looks like something they'd sell in restaurants.
- Yeah.
[After trying again, the kimichi dish seems successful too~]
This seems like another great breakfast we made on Family.
[Already self-praising]
Should we clean now?
We should.
[Cleaning up and getting the table set but...]
Daesung, you could have slept more, why are you outside..
[Daesung, why are you helping...]
Honestly, you were nervous right?
I did feel a bit nervous.
TOP told us everything about you.
What else did he say?
Watch this episode later. You're really surprising.
Daesung, understand why he did that.
[He didn't say anything but is framed]
I shouldn't have brought a member...
Do you have something to tell about TOP?
[Daesung...is being pulled in...]
Tell us since TOP us everything about you anyways.
What kind of friend is TOP?
In our company, his nickname is...
What is it?
Bingu TOP
[Bingu TOP?]
What's that?
Because he does a lot of stupid things...
[Bingu TOP?]
If you tell him to dance wildly, he'll dance wildly...
Randomly dance?
Okay.
[No way...Charisma TOP...]
I can't really imitate him...
Okay.
[No way...Charisma TOP...]
I can't really imitate him...
- But something like this.
- Oh, okay.
[This kind of dance...?]
- But something like this.
- Oh, okay.
[This kind of dance...?]
Bingu TOP!
[Daesung's avoiding eye contact]
Come over here.
Daesung, you go inside.
Bingu TOP, come here.
Bingu, come here.
Seunghyun and TOP was a bit awkward for me.
[Not Seunghyun or TOP]
- It just rolls off the tongue.
- Yeah it does. Bingu.
[Not Seunghyun or TOP]
- It just rolls off the tongue.
- Yeah it does. Bingu.
[Bingu]
So Daesung told you the one name I hate the most.
[Panic]
It's not like that, he didn't tell us. It just slipped while we were laughing.
[The hyungs quickly helping with the situation...]
We were playing Bingo and when one of us said Bingo!
He said, oh, it's similar to TOP's name!
[Quickly controlling the situation]
I didn't know you hated that...
[As TOP gets closer]
[Daesung goes further away]
[Ran around for a while...]
I heard you freely dance well...
That's seriously the first time I heard that.
- What do you mean first time.
- What kind of dance?
Do I have to show you?
I heard you dance like this.
[Exactly the way Daesung exposed it]
[The middle-age men's perfect reenactment]
I thought you only showed stuff like this.
[Opposite of the cool dance moves during his rap...]
You only showed us this last night.
I heard you dance like this.
Bingu TOP!
Right here?
I'll get in trouble by my CEO.
It's okay. Jong Shin is friends with him.
[CEO Yang's friend Yoon Jong Shin will take responsibility...]
[Conflict]
What kind of movements is it?
[The result]
Just...
Oh like this? That's nothing. It's probably something more?
Yeah, like that!
[He came! Bingu TOP!]
[Open~]
[TOP's embarrassed]
[Daesung's satisfied]
It's cute!
We definitely became closer.
Daesung was over exaggerating.
[The hyungs slyly bring up Daesung]
Yeah.
Daesung was over exaggerating a bit.
[The hyungs slyly bring up Daesung]
(Oh yeah! That guy!)
Daesung was over exaggerating a bit.
[Glancing]
I should hide him~
[The two people not bothering to do anything]
[Trying to escape, but...]
[Tsk...tsk...tsk...]
[Not caring about what's happening inside]
Those are my shoes. I'm going bare-footed.
[I don't know anything~]
Wear this.
[Daesung barely escaped]
- Daesung, are you okay?
- It smells burnt!
It burned again!
[It's burnt again!]
[Burnt again because of the Bingu dance...]
That enough, turn it off.
Just eat the crunchy potatoes.
The potatoes can't be crunchy.
[If they wait until the potatoes are done, the kimchi is going to be more burnt...]
Hey...
Hey...Bingu!
[It's now a friendly name, Bingu]
[While the middle-aged men tease him...]
[Firmly]
Isn't this how kids dance?
[What are they going to do about the kimchi dish...]
Should we add some more seasoning?
No, I think it'd be too salty.
I'll try the potatoes.
[Tasting a potato to see if it's cooked but...]
The potato is really fresh.
It's ruined.
[They went all in into the kimchi dish for breakfast...]
We went all in...
What are we going to do?
[A proper mixed(?) breakfast]
Breakfast is ruined.
The trout's all torn up!
The trout's torn up.
The trout is like...
[The trout's decomposed]
The kimich is burnt.
[Furthermore the potatoes aren't cooked...]
[It seems like this is the Family's worst breakfast award...]
I think we should only serve the grilled trout that TOP grilled.
We're in trouble, the breakfast ruined.
[But then]
[TOP is gone again!]
Daesung.
Is there something more about TOP?
[Bingu TOP is a big hit]
Is there more?
Yeah, there is one...
[TOP's second secret]
What?
Originally TOP and I were Big Bang's jokesters.
[TOP's second secret]
[TOP and Daesung is Big Bang's jokesters?]
Originally TOP and I were Big Bang's jokesters.
- Really?
- Jokester?
[TOP and Daesung is Big Bang's jokesters?]
Originally TOP and I were Big Bang's jokesters.
- Really?
- Jokester?
[TOP and Daesung is Big Bang's jokesters?]
- He fools around?
- With that voice?
[A joke with that cool voice?]
Hyung, it was on the internet too.
[There's videos of it on the internet!]
When there's a camera, he goes,
"Haha! I've gathered here with Big Bang!"
[Is it really true...?]
TOP: Big Bang's jokesters!
We've gathered together!
[It's true!]
We're only in our shower gowns.
Good bye! Good bye! Good night!
[Proof - Big Bang's jokesters]
But recently, he hasn't been doing it.
Okay, okay.
I learned everything from TOP.
[He's even Dumber's gag teacher!]
Oh really? He's a master.
He is a master if he admits it.
[Ruined]
[Why did you taste it...]
If it doesn't work out, we'll have to divert their attention.
[The solution is to divert their attention?]
So they won't notice it.
As soon as they take a bite...
[As soon as the Family takes a bite]
As soon as they take a bite... all four of us will do TOP's dance.
[Altogether, they'll dance Bingu's dance!]
Do TOP's dance. Okay.
It'll be like a theater restaurant today.
Watch a show and eat.
[Just then, TOP returns after cleaning up in the kitchen]
Oh, is TOP back?
[Stunned]
We're Big Bang's jokesters!
Come over here!
TOP has come.
TOP, how have you been?
[The middle-aged men continuously induce]
Is your name TOP?
There's rumors that you're called Bingu TOP, is that right?
It is right~
[It's a big hit]
[After Bingu TOP, Jokester TOP is revealed!]
How you do feel after coming on Family and making breakfast?
It feels great~
I heard you're good at mimicking Yoon Moon Shik.
[While they're at it, Yoon Moon Shik too?]
Can you do it for us once?
Let's hear it!
I'm Yoon Moon Shik.
[TOP is showing everything today!]
You disrespectful bastard.
Oh my stomach.
[They're happy even though they ruined breakfast...]
In a while, it seems like we'll have to put on a show.
You know that dance before?
- We'll have to use that..
- We'll have to use that to stall.
[Saying something but...]
- We'll have to use that..
- We'll have to use that to stall.
I think you need to keep quiet.
TOP made an image for a year...
I sigh deeply as if the ground is going to cave in...
Did you wash it?
[Anyways...]
Let's serve this and...
[Frustrated just by looking at the kimchi dish]
Let's try eating it first.
- Should we eat it?
- Just a spoonful.
[Nervously trying it out first]
I think it's okay.
[Naturally scrunching up his face]
It's bitter.
(Well...)
This is the first time I'm eating something so horrible.
[Bleh...]
[In this situation,there's only one answer!]
[The only way out is the theater restaurant!]
Did you eat some, Seunghyun?
Yes...
And if they ask what's with the food or why does it taste bad, don't even respond to it.
Just say it tastes good.
- Not matter what, say it's good.
- Praise it.
Just be like, it tastes good.
And takes bigger bites.
Okay.
Don't take small bites.
You can't not eat.
[They have to eat!]
Rip a piece.
Hyung, we have to sit at the good spots.
Send them to the side where the bad parts are.
[Don't show how bad it tastes!]
We're going to say it tastes good not matter what.
[Finally the time has come]
There hasn't been a day where I've been this nervous to wake them up.
It's time for breakfast!
[A quiet morning call]
Wake up.
[Today...everyone is unfortunate...]
Everyone...Chunhee, let's eat!
[Operation 1: To diligently defend the main seat]
-Quickly
[Dazedly...]
Noona, you sit over there
Why?
[According to the operation, defends the main seat perfectly]
-You guys can sit here
What do you consider this as, seafood...?
This is...
[At this point of time, one shouldn't be finding fault with the grilled trout...]
-As it grilled gradually, the taste just became better
I wish Hyori-unni would make breakfast every day
[Finally...the kimchi stew is presented...]
-You can open the pot
-You'll really get a shock, it's like a piece of art
[Finally...the kimchi stew is presented...]
Oh, is this kimchi stew?
That's right
Oh, looks nice!
[Oh, please...]
-Go ahead and try it
[Finally, the family gathers and starts eating breakfast]
-Let's dig in!
[Operation 2: Start to deceive as they have intended]
Wow! Looks delicious!
It's really gourmet food~ it's so delicious!
[It must be hard on the 4 of you...]
Hey, but..what did you guys add in the kimchi stew?Did you guys add streptomycin (a kind of antibiotics drug) or what? Why is it so bitter?
Ah, it's really delicious!
-Woah, it's really good!
[Pretends not to hear]
Is it good?
[Am I the only one who finds it bitter?...]
-JS: Hyung, pass me some potato
Without Hyori making breakfast, it's really difficult to eat it
[Dissatisfaction is voiced out]
-Give me another bowl!
[How touching!!]
[Nearly shedding tears]
[Why are they like that...]
I'm going crazy~ah the kimchi stew!
[Again] Why is it so bitter?
[Sensing danger]
It's really delicious isn't it?
It's really delicious!
[Operation 3: Using two-party dialogue to distract their attention]
-Aiyo, Daesung nim, how is the taste?
-Oh, it's just heavenly!
[Operation 3: Using two-party dialogue to distract their attention]
[Even like this, it seems like they can't get rid of the dangerous atmosphere]
-Since today's breakfast is so delicious,let's have a performance!
[Operation 4: The Trump Card - ]
[The Group's Dorky Dance]
[TOP is the most serious!]
TOP, face the front and do it!
[But...no one's looking..]
[Flares up!] Why is the potato uncooked!
[In unison]
JS: Ah, it's really delicious!
Kangwondo potatoes really seem like the most delicious potatoes I have ever eaten
[In unison]
The kimchi is burnt, the potatoes are not cooked, the seafood can't be eaten, what is all this!
[Unhappy]
Aren't the potatoes really crispy?
-Ah, it's really good
[Eventually..]
I'm not eating!
[Until the very end]
Wow~ really delicious
What is this, we waited several hours for this
Ah, this will be mine!
[Jaesuk's third bowl]
-Hyori seems to have no appetite
Oh, it's really nice. Come let me share some with you.
Noona, why is it not nice?
Hyori tried too hard yesterday..due to the rap
-One bowl of rice is gone like that
Among all the breakfasts done so far, this is the worst!
Oppa, make some jajangmyun for me~
I want sweet and sour pork
Jajangmyun?
This has the same colour as jajangmyun, sort of
Just think of it as jajangmyun and eat it
[The first failed breakfast..was, nevertheless spent enjoyably, thanks to the dorky TOP]
[2. Let's pick the mushrooms!]
[Chapter 4: The Family on the silver plate]
[All are excited to get the opportunity to wear ice-skates]
[The vast frozen reservoir with ice more than 25cm thick]
[Even the big brother was reminded of the past] [Gently~]
HR: What's with your arms?
I'm ice-skating beautifully
You're skating quite well
-Now..it's time to play another game~
[Before they start their work, let' have a game on this ice plate]
Although there are indoor ice-skating rinks, ice-skating on the frozen reservoir is a rare opportunity
It's really good to be here~
Look over there, all of that makes up this natural outdoor ice-skating rink!
So, wearing our skates, on the ice..we'll do...
Figure-skating?
Yes, each will perform figure-skating
If you look over here, erm, figure-skating is kinda..
[hmm?]
-For that matter, Kim Sooro doesn't have suitable ice skates
[No ice skates fit his large feet]
-But anyway, he has never skated before
-So we can say that it is a good coincidence, since we can make some internal arrangement.
[The Game King who can't sit in a corner quietly just because he has no ice skates...]
-Oppa, you can wear your shoes and perform!
So, the ceremony is about to begin on this vast ice plate of the frozen reservoir. Sooro will be the judge for it.
So, the first candidate, the 'D' level of difficulty, D-nando, which can also stand for 'Dumb' level of difficulty
Please express love in your performance
[Nervous]
-So, Love's D-nando
[The first stage: Lee Chun Hee - Forget my carelessness!!]
-Coming from the ice hockey team
[Firstly, starts to run!]
[What happens if he falls]
[Hey, it's quite good...]
[Turns~]
Chun Hee's doing well
[Definitely not an easy action!]
-Woah,Chun Hee
[The Careless Chun Hee who has completely changed!]
Jump!~
[A twirl-jump!]
Just look at Chun Hee!
[Now for the ending...] [Spins!!!]
[The Ice Prince really knows everything..]
[Oh?] [Oh?] [Oh!]
[...We were still saying]
[Continues his act even after falling!]
-HR: As expected!
JS: This is of course, Chun Hee
[Continues his act even after falling!]
[Aigoo, you little fellow...]
[Next stage: Daesung - The Temptation on the Ice]
You're doing well
[Oh~ Daesung attempts a jump too?!]
That's the way
-That's the way to do it!
[Oh! From a jump to a...??]
[Even when he falls...still pretends that it's part of the act!]
[Since I sat, I might as well lie down!]
[Figure-skating is not exactly that great...but he focuses on entertaining!]
-YJ: What to do!
[Temptation on the Ice - Daesung]
[Rather than saying it's figure-skating, that was merely a roll]
For the next candidate,let's welcome the ex-fairy
She's already gone into hiding..
That's past her
That's true~ Lee Hyori shi!
Can I just start like that?
[The ex-fairy Lee Hyori : The Dance of Death]
Go away!
[The ex-fairy who suffers from a heartbreak]
[How will she fight this heartbreak...]
[Overcoming her sadness through dancing]
-Although he left, you're still happy
Looking happy when you left
[Spreading her wings...let the hurt from being jilted fly away~]
[Oh...]
Born as an ex-fairy
-It's ending so soon?
[Obstacle]
Hyori ah, show that expression that skater Kim Yu-Na has
[Attracting millions worldwide...is it...this expression?]
[The ex-fairy Hyori's expression will be...?]
[The Ice Plate's fairy..?]
Oppa~
What else did we see besides this?
Besides this? Ah only that
Now,our Hyori still has not rcovered from her rap battle yesterday so her condition is a little lacking...
She seems to have lost all her self-confidence
Yejin-ah, go and try it
How do I do it?
[Next candidate: The beloved disciple of Chairman Kim, Yejin]
Yejin-ah, go out there and fly high!
[Worried~]
[Miss Yejin - Love's Mini Serenade]
-SR:Love's Mini Serenade
-How loving will the two of you be?
[Together with the Ice Prince]
Using our sincere love for each other
[Really looks like a stage for couple - figure skating]
To fulfil this love that can save us humans
Look! Our love which crosses the Pacific Ocean!
-Look! For our love, we showcase our dance movements
[Becomes even more touching with Chairman Kim's explanation!]
Give a hug,Chun Hee!
Ah, looks great!
Hug and feel it
[In a moment]
[The performance that will appear during the couple skating!]
[Just like a work of art...]
[Skating so smoothly just now...!!]
-It's been abandoned, the love was abandoned
[The abandoned love...]
[Sorry...]
[I'm going crazy...]
Stop! Stop!
-That love was an abandoned one
[But it was a sincere love...]
[Yet still a genuine love...]
Please exit the stage.
After they throw away their relationship they decide to give it one more shot.
[Yet still a genuine love...]
[But it was a sincere love...]
[Giving each other a second chance...]
After they throw away their relationship they decide to give it one more shot.
[Even if there's regrets, they will still meet once again...]
Lee Chunhee and Yejin once again hold hands.
[Will the two love... reunite?]
What in the world are you two struggling over?
Why are you going out?
Oh, I'm sorry.
[Chairman Sooro caught up in the moment and entering the stage]
Get back over here.  You're only wearing shoes.
So the skating...
It was a bit of a waste.
I'm starting to think it wasn't really figure skating.
We're still developing Korean frozen lake skating.
That's right. How about we do a relay now?
How about we do a relay now?
Sounds good.
That's right. How about we do a relay now?
Let's go!
[The team that comes back from the turning point the fastest wins]
So we're going to do a turning point relay.
[Hyori's team: Jongshin, Jaesuk, TOP, Daesung vs Yejin's team: Sooro, Jongkook, Chunhee]
They only have 4 members.
Yea, so someone on that team has to go twice.
[Hyori's team: Jongshin, Jaesuk, TOP, Daesung vs Yejin's team: Sooro, Jongkook, Chunhee]
Kim Sooro, since you're wearing shoes just try to run.
Alright.
[2:2, Hyori + Daesung]
[Sooro + Chunhee]
Start!
[Quickly leading]
[But Yejin's team...]
[Because of skateless Sooro...]
[Daesung falling on the ground even during games]
[The other team is still not doing well]
Hyung, get down quick!
You're doing good Hyori!
[Hyori leading the way]
[They should have done this earlier]
[Chunhee falling again so close to the finish]
[Hyori's team: Jaesuk + TOP]
[Yejin's team: Jongkook + Yejin]
[Aigo]
[Making sure not to create a big gap]
Turn, turn, turn, turn
[Jongkook + Yejin obstructing]
[Jaesuk + TOP are both clumsy and don't know how to react]
[Yejin's team takes the lead]
[Last up, Chunhee + Jongkook]
[Last up, Dumb + Dumber brothers]
[Even though they came in first... Hyori's team gets the lead]
[The win is 50-50]
[Jongkook + Chunhee shoving Dumb + Dumber]
[Both teams ending up behind the camera]
[Which team will come in first]
[The winning team can be decided now]
[No one knows who will lose]
[Giving it all they got]
[Jongkook + Chunhee have a slight lead]
[Will it be as expected...?]
[Yejin's team takes the win]
Where are you going?
[Dumb + Dumber knocks down at the finish]
[Hyori's team 0 vs Yejin's team 1]
[2nd round will be 1:1]
Will have TOP go against Yejin.
[The team strategizes]
Then I'll go against Chunhee.
Will have TOP go against Yejin.
[The team strategizes]
Then I'll go against Chunhee.
[Taking this round seriously]
And you go against Chunhee the second time.
[...What's so serious about this...]
[The Final Round starts right away]
[Jongshin vs Sooro]
[Huh?]
[First up, ace Chunhee]
[Creating a gap right from the start?]
[Their strategy is a success!]
Jongshin hyung, it's okay!
[The huge gap!]
[2nd up, Sooro]
Hyori we can do this!
[Sooro running with just his shoes]
[2nd up, Hyori]
Hyori we can do this!
[I just have to catch him to turn this around]
[Making Sooro fall to reverse their positions]
[Hyori turning things around without a hitch]
[Hyori's team now in the lead]
[Third up, TOP]
[Third up, Yejin]
TOP, don't go easy on her! Just come in!
[Even though TOP can't skate well as long as he keeps this pace...]
[Hyori's team is dominating this round]
[4th up, Daesung]
Yejin just come as fast as you can, I'll catch you.
[Daesung doing pretty well this time]
[4th up, Jongkook]
[Jongkook is fast!]
[Startled]
[The gap is closing in!]
[Chasing]
[Being chased]
[Waiting]
[Not sure who will win]
[Last person goes up!]
[Last up, Jaesuk]
[Last up, Chunhee]
[They both reach the corner in an instance]
[Jaesuk is still in the lead]
Hurry, oppa hurry!
[Chunhee going at a scary speed]
[Chunhee throwing out his hand in a last attempt]
[Who won?]
[Jaesuk's foot is first]
[Hyori's team takes a very close win!]
[Hyori's team 2 vs Yejin's team 1]
That was so close!
If we didn't have a lead it would have been dangerous.
Regardless, Hyori's team wins!
Let's go pick the shiitake mushrooms now.
With a deep heart.
Let's go!
[Chairman Sooro leading the group]
[The Family in ship shape]
[Arriving at the Grandmother's shiitake mushroom greenhouse]
[The shiitake mushrooms growing from the logs]
Oooh, so they grow from the logs.
That's right.
We're going to get these logs right here.
And you see where the white holes are on those logs?
We're going to do that to these.
[First moving the shiitake mushroom apartments]
[Then drilling holes for the shiitake mushrooms]
[Jaesuk tries drilling holes]
You're making them too close.
Now they're too far!
Ah! Too close!
If they're too close, take a look
Try to spread your arms.
They won't have any room to grow.
[Stacking up the new logs]
[Harvesting the shiitake mushrooms]
This is a big catch.
Hey smell it.
You can't smell anything, huh?
That's a shiitake.
That's big.
[Proud]
[One by one they harvest the mushrooms]
[Completing the grandmother's task of harvesting the mushrooms]
[The grandparents returning from their trip]
[They return safely]
[Sooro's first time meeting the grandparents since he had to take the exam]
[Family reunion]
[Happily greeting]
Oh, you made it after all.
I was really happy.
And I thought our Family children did really well for us.
[The Grandma feeling indebted to the Family]
We had a good time and were even able to eat trout.
We ate a lot of good things.
Father, did you have a good time?
Of course I did.
Well, we had a really good time here.
We ate really well and everything.
You both are probably really tired so...
Please stay healthy.
[Even though it was for a short while...]
[Deep feelings can be felt in this important time]
[Fond memories until they meet again...]
Goodbye!
[Thank you to everyone at Bukdong Village]
[Grandma, Grandpa we wish you good health]
[The 17th destination Feb 2009]
[Full Moon Outing]
[Family's new guest, SNSD's Yoona]
[The Family brothers are burning up]
[Yoona performs Gee for the Family]
[Yoona's startling dance]
[The fallen Family brothers]
[Not wanting to lose, Hyori follows along]
[I'm Lee Hyori!]
[Preparing a performance for the village elders]
Translators: kaflom, angelyrique, suebee, nxh, Iyasu
Timers: katchan1, swtsrwlove, warunee123,
jocelyne03, aznhoneychik
Editors: swtsrwlove, melijay
Encoder: melijay
Uploaders: melijay, maryys