Timing and subtitles brought to you by 中剧独播
Candle in the Tomb
Episode 3
Brother Fatty! Brother Hu!
Ying Zi! Ying Zi, are you down here?
Brother Hu, I'm down here!
Are you okay?
I'm fine. I twisted my leg, and I can't climb up.
- Fatty.- What?
Do you think this is the side entrance that they dug?
- Go get the tools.- Okay.
- Don't forget the rope!- Okay.
Ying Zi, don't be afraid. We'll go save you soon!
Okay.
What's down there?
It's too dark down here. I can't see clearly.
Brother Hu, be careful.
Are you alright?
I'm fine. I twisted my leg.
Let me see.
Can you move on your own? Try moving it.
You're fine. If you can move your bone, you're fine.
Move out of the way! Master Fatty coming through!
Hey, be careful.
Who told you to come? I asked you to stay up there and keep guard.
There's nothing up there. What's there to guard?
- Ying Zi, are you okay?- I'm fine.
- Are you okay?- I'm okay.
Wow, this is so magical.
This is exhilarating.
Old Hu.
- Is this a tomb?- It really is a tomb.
Ying Zi, take this.
What is it?
Hoof of a black donkey. It's to ward off spirits.
I got it from the village chief. I even have glutinous rice.
Aren't you just impressive?
Did you put this on?
Of course. Hide it.
That's more like it. Since we're already here, let's explore.
Stand back.
Brother Fatty, what are you doing?
Seeing if there's a trap,
just in case they start firing arrows,and we become kebabs.
Brother Fatty, you know so much.
Of course. Your Brother Fatty was studying the whole trip, and now his knowledge is coming into use.
Fatty, that's enough.
Somebody has already traveled down this path. There shouldn't be any traps.
Better safe than sorry.
Brother Hu, are we really going in?
Are you afraid? We'll leave after checking it out.
Outside, you protect us two. In here, we'll protect you.
Come on. You can walk, right?
Looks like people really have been here before.
Is this the coffin?
Don't be afraid. It's a mural. There are murals all around.
- That scared me.- Put this up.
This should be the owner of the coffin.
This picture shows the scene of fighting on the battle field.
Watch your step.
This should be the image of triumphant victory.
Let's go look over there.
This is the arrival of calamity.
And here.
This should be his rank promotion.
Judging by these images, the personin the coffin was a general.
Old Hu, Old Hu! Come here.
Let's go.
Old Hu, look.
Don't touch it.
I didn't touch it. It fell on its own.
This general was rather poor.
His grave goods are either scrap metals or broken vases.
What is this?
A dinosaur.
What dinosaur? Why don't you talk about Kong Rong sharing his pears, instead? (&quot;dinosaur&quot; sounds similar to &quot;Kong Rong&quot;)
This is a battle horse for the general's grave good. Understand?
Why is there not a coffin here?
Do you think the tomb raiders took the coffin away?
Are you stupid? The entrance was so small. They couldn't have carried it through.
Mace?
Where do you think the coffin is hidden?
There's definitely a hidden trapdoor.
Brother Hu, I'm afraid. Let's hurry and leave.
Ying Zi, don't be scared, okay?
If the sky falls, Brother Hu will hold it up for you. Don't be scared.
Fatty, come here.
Look. I think there's a problem with this.
Could this be a switch?
It really can move.
I saw!
Old Hu, there's another one here.
Don't touch it!
Brother Hu, what's going on?
What's that sound?
Duck!
Fatty, are you okay?
I'm fine. Are you okay?
Hurry and leave. Hurry!
Hurry.
Old Hu!
I hit my leg.
Hurry and leave.
So the secret mechanism is here.
The good things are definitely inside here!
- What are you doing?- Don't touch it.
It's right in front of you! Don't you want to see what's inside?
Hold this.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by 中剧独播
- Candle.- Okay.
Fire.
Brother Hu, what are you doing?
When humans light candles,
the ghosts blow them out.
What?
This is a rule left behind by earlier generations.
It means, first light a candle on the southeast corner of the coffin before opening it.
If the candle goes out, you must quickly leave
and mustn't take a single object.
This is a promise between the dead and the alive.
It's been passed on for thousands of years and cannot be broken.
Look at this.
Look at the imposing appearance, the artistry, the carvings.
I think this general was a soldier his whole life.
Only his coffin was worth some money.
Enough of that. Close your big mouth.
Practice is the only criteria for testing the truth. At the least,
there should be a sword here. Right?
Let's open it and see!
Bring it over.
Ying Zi, help me shine the light.
Didn't we agree to leave?
Hold the flashlight.
- Fatty.- Yes?
You go to the back.
I finished.
Wait.
You go watch the candle.
One, two, three!
I already told you he was very poor.
Let's look first.
You scared me!
This...
We were just curious
and accidentally entered this place. We need to borrow
some of your garments.
I'm sorry. Please don't blame us.
In the future, we'll surely use the money for the common good and improve life for all.
I will definitely learn from Lei Feng and do good deeds.
I'll differentiate love from hate. I won't forget my origins. I'll stand firm and keep my fighting spirit strong--
Enough.
Fatty,
even if we find anything, don't think of taking it.
If something really happens, I can't save you.
Don't joke around!
Where did those valuable items from Panjiayuan come from?
Where did Big Gold Tooth get his things?
I just want to look.
You can rest first. Go rest, okay? Hurry, hurry.
Fatty, be careful.
Old Hu!
Hard work pays off. Look at this.
Isn't it valuable?
It's jade!
I think this is valuable.
Of course! He was holding it in his hand.
Of course it's important.
Brother Hu, look.
Can you stop buying such cheap candles?
You bought a cheap candle for such an important task.
In the future, I'll buy Japanese candles.
I'll buy British candles; I'll buy American candles. I'll buy the most expensive ones,
but...
Put these two jades back.
Put them back? Impossible.
What are you thinking? I worked so hard to get these just to put them back?
That'd be such a waste.
Fatty, hurry and put it back! The candle went out!
I'm not putting it back! So what? What if the wind blew it out?
- Will you put it back?- Hey, what are you doing?
Are you going to use your gun for an internal conflict?
I'm telling you, it's not that I can't beat you.
I just don't want to fight a girl. Don't force me.
- Will you put it back or not?- Ying Zi.
Fatty, this is a rule left by our ancestors.
Nobody can break it. Put it back!
I can only put one piece back?
Fine. Here, give me the lighter.
I'll go light the candle again.
If it stays lit, we can take the jade. If it goes out again,
we must return both of them.
Okay, just out of respect for our ancestors.
I'll put one back.
I'm putting it back.
See? It's fine.
Everything's fine.
Do you see that? I have more guts.
Shajiabang Opera, the sixth act. Withdraw.
Let's go.
Wait.
Why is the fire turning green?
Hurry and leave!
How did that thing fly over here?
We're stuck!
Y-Ying Zi,
all scary things are just paper tigers.
Don't be afraid.
We'll kill it.
- Brother Hu... - Old Hu.
Old Hu.
T-Talk it out with him. We'll give the jade back.
Tell him that if we begin fighting, nobody will benefit. Peace is the most important!
Stop talking! Do you think he's a human?
Can he even understand our words?
- What do we do, then?- What else can we do?
The exit's sealed.
It's obvious that we have to become his grave goods.
We can only fight him.
Ying Zi, hide.
Leave this monster to us.
I'll kill you!
Old Hu! You didn't sacrifice yourself, right?
Shut your unlucky mouth.
I'll kill you!
I'll chop you to death!
Fatty, get up and run!
Hurry and run!
Fatty!
Hurry and get up.
I can't get up.
Nice shot! Keep shooting, Ying Zi!
Hurry, give the jade to me.
Ying Zi!
Brother Fatty, save me!
Move away!
Ying Zi, are you okay?
Go!
Here's your jade. We'll give it back.
I gave it back, okay?
Hey!
I already gave it back! Why are you still chasing me?
- Fatty, black donkey hoof!- Hoof.
Flip over the wall.
Ying Zi, shine it on my hand!
Old Hu, go!
Old Hu, this is useful!
Brother Hu!
Keep groaning.
Brother Hu, are you okay?
I'm fine. Are you okay?
- Keep groaning.- Fatty!
Stop kicking him. You might kick the hoof out.
Hurry, hurry. Come over here.
Hurry and find a way to open the exit. We must leave.
Ying Zi, that was a really good shot.
Otherwise, I would have died here.
Old Hu, before leaving, I must take the two jade pieces.
- Otherwise, I won't be satisfied.- Stop talking. Come here. Give the shovel to me.
One, two, three.
Brother Hu,
I think he moved.
What do we do, Old Hu?
- Run!- Run where?
- Run to the back!- Okay.
Hurry. Ying Zi, hurry!
Hurry!
Let me do it.
Here, I'll help you.
One, two, go!
Old Hu, I can't do it!
Why is it so heavy?
He's coming!
Stop yelling. I heard him.
Fatty, come here!
Fatty, again!
Brother Hu.
It's a secret room.
- Fatty, hurry and go in. - Do you think I can fit?
Don't talk. Hurry and go in!
Ying Zi, hurry.
Hurry, Old Hu!
Run! Hurry!
Hurry, hurry.
Wait. Here, close the door.
He's clinging onto us like plaster.
How do you lock this?
Here. Shine the light here, Ying Zi.
Hurry, you two!
Where is this?
What place is it? Why is there an iron gate in this tomb?
There's a map here.
This should be a Japanese underground fortress.
This is the Kwantung Army's secret fortress?
Old Hu, we came here just for this.
We almost died in the tomb,
but we ended up here while trying to escape.
We didn't make this trip for nothing!
Exits are marked here.
Hopefully the Japanese didn't destroy them when they surrendered.
Old Hu, there's an ammunition warehouse here. Let's go check it out.
Hopefully there'll be an aircraft cannon,and we can bomb him to death.
Brother Hu, if we can find an exit, let's not mess with the monster.
Don't listen to his nonsense. How can an aircraft be flown underground?
Can't I satisfy my need to talk?
The power control room's here. Let's go see if the electricity generator still works.
Here, this way.
Here.
Ying Zi, shine the light here.
Okay, that's enough, Fatty!
Light has come to the human world!
We're finally not in the dark anymore.
Brother Hu, let's hurry and find the exit.
Okay, we'll go find some weapons, just in case we run into more demonic creatures.
Brother Hu,
would there be a child here?
There are no people here. What child?
Ying Zi, are you going crazy from the fear?
Did you see something?
No, maybe the fear really is getting to me.
Let's go. This way.
This is such a big fortress.
Wow,
the Japanese were so wicked.
Why are so many things here?
Type 92 battalion gun.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by 中剧独播
Type 92, 7.7mm machine gun.
Hey, if we had this, I would have shot that monster into pieces.
- Fatty.- What?
Find something to break open this lock.
Coming.
Move out of the way.
What is this?
Japanese lunch boxes.
Wow!
This is good stuff. Take off your bag.
Okay.
Ying Zi, hold this.
Old Hu, Ying Zi, here!
♫ Walk forward and pass through a gap ♫
♫ I want to see it more clearly ♫
♫ My courage and fragile sensitivityare together ♫
♫ Some secrets are hidden at the bottom of my heart ♫
♫ I’ve never mentioned it to anybody ♫
♫ Fate beckons, but doesn’t careabout the result ♫
♫ Because of capricious changes,I’m trapped in the moment ♫
♫ An unknown river flows up,but the river current goes down ♫
♫ The bigger your desires,the higher price you must pay ♫
♫ My stomach is filled with words,but I close my mouth ♫
♫ Fate has once given promises,but it can also go back on its words ♫
♫ One side offers loving words,while the other side offers lies ♫
♫ You’re supposed to climb to heaven,but you flee to hell ♫
♫ You were given a youthful face,but it transformed all into grey hairs overnight ♫
♫ Sail downstream with the current ♫