I'm Phoenix. I love the moon
Especially when it's full
and most beautiful
I don't know why
but my parents are never home...
Daddy, Mommy...
I just saw two people fly past the moon
You must have been dreaming
People can't fly
Too much TV for you!
What an overactive imagination!
No. I really saw it
Tomorrow's a school day
How about a story to put you to sleep?
Do you want Mommy to tell you a story
about the Emei Sect of Kung Fu
or Daddy to tell about the 18 Coppermen?
Mommy and Daddy are great storytellers
Every story is about
a kung fu master with mystical powers
Daddy's 18 Coppermen are especially cute
Their stories are fun
but I never believed them...
until one day when I was 14 years old...
Daddy!
Mommy!
Relax, don't be scared
I've got to call the police
Where's your parents?
Dad!
Don't be scared, sweetie!
We've been searching for
you two for sometime...
It's my turn!
Attack me...?
Get down! Come down I dare you!
Dad!
Go to hell!
Awesome Dad! Pretty clever, Phoenix
Mom, why do you suddenly know kung fu?
Do you remember that you
once saw people fly past the moon?
That was your Dad and me
That's right. Our family has
a natural talent for kung fu
We belong to the
Secret Society of Kung Fu Masters
The Secret Society of Kung Fu Masters?
The ancient and mysterious
world of kung fu
still lives on today
But we don't want to disturb society
In secret, we help
the weak and eliminate evildoers
We've been chasing
these two for a long time
We never thought they'd pay us visit
Can I learn martial arts too?
Of course you can
Once they turn 14 years old, every child
can go to Mount Hua to study
martial arts every summer vacation!
Really?
Then I'll be as good as you
You've got the talent
One day you'll be better than us
So when can we go?
Why not right now?
Mom, people are flying across the moon!
You brats! A liar just like your father!
I'm not lying
This is Mount Hua
That's right!
I've never flown so high!
She's really cool!
She called Rouge
She's the best kung fu student here
Time to land
Phoenix, this is where
we studied our martial arts
Principal of the Academy?
Master, you brought
your daughter this time
This is Principal of the Academy
the headmaster of the school
Why's he walking backwards?
Kids say the darnedest things
Don't worry about it
Long ago, I made a very big mistake
I let an evil disciple escape
I promised I would bring him to justice
Until then I swore to walk backwards
Who's this disciple?
He's No. 1 on our Most Wanted List:
White Eyebrows!
What'd he do wrong?
He's committed innumerable crimes
Theft, Murder, Rape
He uses kung fu to hurt ordinary people
And he stole our school's
most precious classic
Luckily, for 300 years
no one has deciphered its true meaning
If he ever does, many people will die
Nobody will be able to stop him
Hey, Master
Any news about White Eyebrows?
Not yet. But one day
I will arrest him!
Amitabha Buddha
Master Grand Grandiloquence
where's Principal of the Academy?
In the back Thanks
Principal of the Academy
How can I help you?
Nothing
But... can we date when we grow up?
You can't date me
but someone else is fine
I mean, can I date someone
who doesn't know martial arts?
Of course, but...
you mustn't let him know
you know martial arts
That sounds pretty difficult
You forget about destiny
If the man of your destiny comes along
it's no problem
So who's the man of my destiny?
The man of your destiny is someone...
who will only see you
once it's impossible to see you
Someone who will only see me
once it's impossible to see me?
Meditate on this
Impossible to see me?
That was my happiest summer vacation ever
I learnt many kung fu techniques
I even taught the 18 Coppermen to dance
Everybody liked me
except one...
I knew, one day
Rouge and I would have it out
My watch reads 8:58 AM
That means everybody
behind me will be late
Miss Salina...
That tramp Phoenix is in the far back
Really?
Bitch! She thinks she's so pretty
Just one minute late...
and she's fired!
Good morning, everyone
Downsize! That's my first
order of business at Lam's Group
Too much excess personnel
It's time to slim down
Mr. Dragon is our new CEO
His main mission is to cut costs
Our company has
too many useless secretaries
Take for example, Ms. Phoenix
Poor educational background
poor experience, poor performance
She's useless to the company. We should...
We should fire her immediately, right?
No. She's so young, so much potential
With some training
she could become a model employee
and earn our company lots of money
Late again and you're fired
Where's that bitch Phoenix? Prepare to die
Ms. Leung, are you looking for me?
When'd you arrive?
Weren't you in line for the elevator?
I had some typing to do, so I came at 8
You look tired. Coffee will perk you up
I can't keep that typing waiting
The man of your destiny is someone...
who will only see you
once it's impossible to see you
Hello
It's your Mom
Happy Birthday!
Remember to come home for dinner
Have you called Dad?
How should I know where he ran off to?
He refuses my monthly alimony
He's probably embarrassed
to take money from a woman
What's the big deal?
I make a bundle in real estate
and stock every year
And he's been unemployed for forever
Hasn't he found work in Guangzhou?
How should I know?
He doesn't even have a cell phone
Forget about him
There's plenty time to talk at dinner, OK?
OK, bye
Why are you sitting here all by yourself?
Today's been a strange day
How strange?
During the meeting
I was standing by the window
When suddenly outside
appeared a young woman
Then... she climbed up the window
like a spider
And disappeared
Pretty high. Must have hurt falling down
But she didn't fall. She climbed inside
She's a secretary here, named Phoenix
So what was it? Skirt or pants?
A skirt
That means no pants. Quite a sight, eh?
Stop joking. Do you believe me?
Excuse me? What does
all these about believe you?
What kind of friends are we?
Kindergarten, primary,
secondary, university...
we were classmates through it all
The girls you didn't like
I helped you seduce
The girls you did like
I seduced behind your back
What kind of friendship is that? Huh?
Give me your hand...
Friends to the End, you got it?
So you believe me?
Of course... not!
Mr. Dragon, your new secretary is here
It's her...
You... you tell her to leave
Tell her to leave? No way!
Beautiful and can crawl up windows?
Tell her to get out of here!
If you don't want, I want
Excuse me Ms., but I'm afraid
you're too pretty to be my secretary
Don't worry
Tomorrow I won't wear make up
I promise to be ugly
You can call me by
my English name: Phoenix
If you want anything, just let me know
Please climb a window
Excuse me?
He said you can climb windows!
I'm a secretary, not a window cleaner
Just joking
I'm Kiddie Kim, his best friend
Of course Kiddie Kim is
Dragon's best friend
Please bring us two coffees
No problem. Anything else just instruct
I don't care. I'll give you fifty... No...
You give me fifty thousand
I'll take her off your hands
No. I really saw her
climbing up the window
I can only imagine... her
climbing onto the bed
Cool down, will you?
Impossible. I can't help myself
So pretty
Here you go again...
Get your mind out of the bedroom...
Stop it...
Do I need to step out?
You two are busy?
No. Dragon and I were
discussing some contractual matters
Yes You should consider him
OK
The affairs of the day call
I can't let work wait
Back to work Back to work...
Back to work
Boss, you were looking for me?
Yes, I need you
to represent me at a dinner
What dinner?
Having dinner with some business friends
They want to discuss
how to boycott Boss White
Boss White? The Stock Killer?
That's right
They think he's
too power hungry and immoral
I'm not one to quarrel with people
So I'd rather not attend
But if I don't go
I might offend the others
So I want you to represent me
Plus, my daughter graduated
and is returning from the USA
Family comes first. You can trust me
Great
You two, just a second ago...
what do you call that position?
Mom, I'm back
I'm in the kitchen
Chicken with shark's fin
That sucks!
Phoenix, why'd you beat up Brother Wai?
I saw a man. I thought he was a thief
He's my client. I invited him to dinner
Look, you practically killed him
Nothing acupressure on
his pleasure points can't cure
What a feeling! What a high!
Did someone just hit me?
No
Just a happy hour
You got drunk and started hallucinating
Come on... let me introduce you
This is my daughter Phoenix
Hello, Phoenix
Hello! Call me Little Willy
You that small?
Yes Phoenix
Brother Wai just bought a luxury car
He'll take you out for a spin
Mom, we've got to talk
Take your time
Who are you introducing to me this time?
Brother Wai's rich
I helped him buy several luxury flats
I earned over a million
in commission alone
Please don't set me up with more ugly men
The handsome ones are unreliable and poor
Look at your Dad
A business failure. Totally unreliable
But Dad's a kung fu master
Is kung fu going to feed you?
I'm no slouch at kung fu either
But if not for real estate and stocks
where would I be today?
Mom. I think I found the man of my destiny
Phoenix, don't believe that silly monk
Burglar...
My little sweetie!
Dad...
I must come back
to celebrate your birthday
I missed you. How is it going lately?
Great as always
I call the shots at the zoo now
I'm the COOO
What does that mean?
It's very technical
You wouldn't understand
Who is he? How'd he come
in from the balcony?
He's my ex-husband. lgnore him
Who's the bastard?
Phoenix's boyfriend
Mom invited him
You're...?
Some call me Buddy Billy
But Handsome Wai is fine
I think you got something on your back
Really?
What? Still looking
He's got something on his back!
Nothing
Sweetie, Dad brought you a birthday gift
I know you'll love it
What is it?
A secret. I'll show you later
Phoenix, Brother Wai has
a birthday gift too. Take it out
A watch. Very expensive
Fake! Broken?
Tomorrow... So you think I'm pretty?
I'll get it fixed tomorrow
Yes, very pretty
Keep looking Very beautiful
Had your fill?
I have to take a piss
Stop fighting
Who?
Brother Wai?
A monster!
What monster? A hawk!
It's my birthday gift to my sweetie
He's over 1000 years old
His previous masters were
Yeung and Dragon Girl
I worked like hell to teach him
how to use the toilet
You teach him to look at women too?
He's so cute
Can I keep him, Mom?
This apartment doesn't even allow dogs
I'll keep him by my side
What about Brother Wai?
Keep him by your side
Oh, forget about it
Same old attitude
All these years and
she hasn't changed. lgnore her
Hawk
Phoenix is your master now
Do what she says
He learns quickly and eats anything
But hide your valuables
otherwise he'll eat them
He can understand what people say?
More than that. He even knows English
Here is my phone number
Call me if it's urgent
But don't visit me
My job's too important
and busy for personal matters
Also, White Eyebrows has appeared again
Every kung fu master is on 24-hour alert
Rumor is that he's learned
the Classic of the Nine Negatives
If you run into him
don't try to be a hero
One word: Run!
I don't bother myself with such nonsense
Can you play Mahjong?
Mr. Dragon, is this
your first time playing Mahjong?
No
It's my first time playing Mahjong
while being massaged
Your boss loves it
My turn Stop... stop touching me
I got a pair
Boss White has become really greedy
I bought some land in the mountains
He demanded to be my partner
I refused
The next day, someone broke
my son's legs on his way to school
Last month
he demanded to buy
one of my buildings. I refused
Every day now, someone there
gets injured and hospitalized
He visited my home once
and took a liking to it
He wanted to buy it. I refused to sell
Mysteriously, the next day
my family woke up in a cemetery
I'm luckier than you
What has he done to you...?
I've never met him
We should band together to boycott him
I play West
I win! All four reborn in
Western Paradise! Bad luck...!
Hey! Let me go!
You're dead! Stop massaging me!
Hawk, you know
how to use the remote control?
Sir, can you tell me what happened
What?
They slaughtered everyone
I'm so scared. They are cruel
They killed everyone
They came in and slaughtered everyone
Poor guy. He ran into
some evil kung fu masters
They even flew
Who will believe
his fantastic story? So sad
It's not sad. It's stupid
Once they see him on TV
they'll try to kill him again
No. I must save him
Phoenix, do you know this guy?
I think he's the man of my destiny
You remember, someone...
who won't see me
until it's impossible to see me
Don't believe that monk's nonsense
Listen to me, Brother Wai is...
Listen to me, I have to go now
Hawk, let's go
Let's go, stop watching TV
So stubborn
The most important is...
they weren't human!
This is a small punishment
Kill him immediately, if not...
you'll feel the wrath of the 9th Negative
Yes, master
We're friends to the end
My underwear is yours. Yours is mine
But this time...
This time I can't believe you, brother
You don't believe me?
Then how do you explain it?
Gang revenge or terrorist attack
maybe. But you're saying...
No. That man and woman
were really superhuman
His hand was like a knife
her leg was like a drill
Are you hallucinating?
Where's your wallet?
Under the pillow. Why?
What're you doing?
Everything you see is unreal
Everything is a hallucination...
Give me back my money!
What money?
The money you stole!
You have no money
except what I lent to you
Here, take $100 more
Shit... your hallucinations
are really serious
Rest up. I'll see you soon
I'll return $100 to you next week
Hi, I'm the reporter of
Daily Oriental, please...
Which room is Mr. Dragon in?
No way
Of course you're
more important than Dragon
Yes, I'll come back tonight, don't worry
Hi Hi
Dad, we'll talk later tonight
I'm a reporter
Are you Mr. Dragon's friend?
Yes... What's the matter?
I want to interview him
but the hospital won't let me
How can they treat
a beautiful woman like this?
They're simply inhuman
Exactly. If I don't get this interview
my boss will fire me
Of course maybe if you help me...
No problem
There's a quiet place over there
where we can get to know each other
You're very kind
Our Tendon-Bending Technique
has 18 steps in all
That was number 6
You still have 12 to go
You think you can handle it?
Why am I always seeing things
that I shouldn't see?
Who are you?
What're you doing?
Let's go
What the hell?
A hawk Hawk?
More hallucinations!
An arrow! Fly!
Hawk, are you OK?
I'm not OK
Shit! He's hit with
a poison arrow. Hurry home!
Damn! It's a centipede arrow
No medicine can save him
Kung fu is only hope
But to eliminate the poison
I can't wear any clothes
If I'm not strong enough
the poison will kill us both
If I'm gonna die, I'm gonna die
What're you doing?
Mom
This setup is even
suitable for a kid's film
He can't see a thing. What's the big fuss?
In the past, if a woman
removed poison like this
she had to marry the guy
What century is this?
If that were true, all women
would have to marry their gynecologist
Put some clothes on. I want to talk to you
Phoenix, this guy is in deep trouble
Those killers won't let him go
If they were as good
at kung fu as you said
then they must work for White Eyebrows
I've retired from martial arts
You should too
It's OK if you don't help Dragon
but you can't stop me
I'm afraid you'll get into trouble
I'm not scared Well, I'm scared
Mom, be reasonable
Fine, tomorrow take him somewhere else
I won't let him stay here
Tomorrow I'll find him
a safe place to hide
What place is safe?
These killers would even bust
into a police station
Don't worry about me
Anyway, he won't stay
no more than 12 hours
Fine, when midnight comes
I'm kicking him out
Listen close: I won't protect him
Hawk will protect him
Phoenix. Wake up please
This is the year 2006
This isn't the world of kung fu
I believe you're the man of my destiny
So I must save you
Before I come back, please don't leave
OK?
Excuse me, I want to find Dad
Who?
He's the COOO of the zoo
There's no such a position here
You'd better go in and ask around
Brush your teeth...
Brush the upper, brush the lower
brush the left, brush the right...
What the hell? You bastard
Bastard...
Bastard
Hey, where's my watch?
In your stomach again?
Open up!
It's not mine
But it's a Rolex, so forget about it
Uncle Itchiban
Phoenix, what brings you here?
I'm looking for my Dad
Your... your Dad?
Look out!
Have you forgotten?
They can't bite through
my Metal Skin Technique
Uncle Itchiban
My Dad said he's the COOO
A very important position
But why does nobody know him?
Uh, your Dad...
Pork Chop Dad? He's by the toilet
Dad, don't go
What were all these
you said about being COOO?
COOO means...
Chief Outhouse Only Officer
Sweetie, sorry, I lied
Never mind, Dad
You earn your own living
I don't care no matter what you do
Sweetie
Dad's useless. I'm not a businessman
I can't provide my family
with a luxurious lifestyle
The most important thing is that
a family is together
Unfortunately, your Mom doesn't think so
One day, Mom will understand
What brings you here?
I think...
I've found the man of my destiny
Who is it?
He's my boss. His name is Dragon
Some more toilet paper please
Go squat on the can
and I'll bring it in a minute, OK?
He must be a talented guy
When can I see him?
Kung fu killers are chasing him
Mom won't help
That bitch never helps
Don't blame Mom
Never mind. I'll go back with you
to protect your love
Excuse me ladies
can you tell me where I am?
Why do you tease me
with skimpy outfits and feather boas?
Monster dog!
(I'm not a dog. I'm a majestic hawk)
Ouch! What happened to my butt?
(You were hit with a poison arrow)
Where's Phoenix?
(She went to find you a bodyguard)
It's after 9. I have to be at the office
(Impossible)
Impossible but not impassable!
(Go back to bed like a good boy)
Have you ever seen a fist this big?
One punch will send you back to the zoo
Brother hawk, good TV programme?
(Show me your hand!)
(The other hand)
(Both hands!)
Nothing in the left, nothing in the right
Nothing on the backs, nothing in the palms
Come on, give me five
Hello, 999 Emergency Hotline
I've been kidnapped
Please call the swat team to save me
Sir
What is your location?
And who is your kidnapper?
I don't know the location
but I've been kidnapped by a bird
He says he's a hawk
You said you've been kidnapped by a hawk?
That's right
Perhaps I should transfer your call
to the Wildlife Conservation Department
or to a mental hospital
Thank you for your call, bye
It's nothing. I was bored
So I dialed 1 731 731 73
Hello
Lucky... not hurt...
Maybe not
Sorry...
If you want to leave
just climb out the window
I've got the rope ready for you
Just climb down to the street
What's your name, Ms.?
My name is Dolina, Phoenix's mom
Thank you
Ms. Do... Dolina
This is the 10th floor
I haven't prepared a parachute
You'll be late for work
Thank you, Ms.
Hawk, where's Dragon?
Gone Mom!
He's got feet. He can walk
if he wants. None of my business
What do we do, sweetie?
He's a workaholic
He probably went to the office
We'll find him there, Dad
You, bad bird!
What's wrong with you?
You're alright! You haven't died...
My butt was hit with a poison arrow
and I was kidnapped by a dog
that looks like a hawk
I thought that man and woman killed you
Those two used the
Tendon-Bending Technique...
to snap all the joints in my body. Look!
Those were the killers
from the Emperor's Club
No way!
Where've you two been?
The boss is looking for you
Let's go
Boss
Why are you two walking like clowns?
The police are looking for you
Boss
I almost didn't make it to work
A hawk kidnapped me
Hawk yourself!
Go find Commissioner Lee right away
Don't get the company into trouble
This would have never happened
if I didn't represent you at that dinner
Why you... Dad...
Let me introduce you
Mr. Kiddie Kim is our Development Manager
Mr. Dragon is our CEO
He's one unfortunate CEO though
Two crazies cut his butt to pieces
You're destined to meet...
a man injured in both buttocks
I'm Rouge. This is my mom, Bo Jeannie
Mrs. Lam Mrs. Lam
My wife was in the USA with my daughter
while she was studying
You two take a vacation
With my daughter's help, I don't need you
Dad, how can you do that?
I've just come back to work
I need Mr. Dragon
to explain to me the company's situation!
Mr. Dragon, let's talk over some drinks
So headstrong
This really happened?
If it didn't happen to me
I wouldn't believe it either
It's like some kind of kung fu novel
I think I need to go into hiding
What a coincidence!
This is my father
She's my secretary Phoenix
I have to go to the rest room
I also need to go
Uncle, are you overly friendly
or just near-sighted?
An outstanding man
My daughter has good taste
I don't quite understand
My daughter risked her life for you
You must love and cherish her
I think I need to explain
No explanations!
Have you ever slept with a prostitute?
No!
Have you had a one-night stand?
Of course not!
Are you gay?
Of course not! Uncle
what are you talking about?
I can rest at ease then
You're Phoenix
You're Rouge! I never thought
you were the Boss' daughter
He's my stepfather. After Mom married him
we went to USA
So I haven't gone to
Mount Hua for a long time
Dragon is destined for me
Don't touch him!
What century is this?
You still believe in destiny?
If I like a boy, I won't let him go
Oh that's right
When you were studying martial arts
all you knew how to do was
compete with others
You think you can beat me?
You never beat on Mount Hua
Mount Hua? This is Hong Kong!
Let's put it to the test then!
Miss, this is male rest room
You're quite pretty
Don't worry. There's room for two
Read your newspaper!
You can't beat me. Give up?
I won't give up Dragon!
He's destined for me!
Uncle, excuse me
What did your grandpa do?
You want to investigate my whole family?
Has your grandpa
ever slept with a prostitute?
No
Has your grandpa
ever had a one-night stand?
No!
Is your grandpa gay?
No...! All my ancestors are NO!
Miss Rouge
The faucet broke
She's going home for a shower
So, why didn't you get wet?
Why don't you tell me
what really happened?
OK, then you'll know
the kind of danger you're really in
Jenny, I thought you'd forgotten me
I have forgotten you
So... why have you come to see me?
I know you're competing against my husband
And trying to kill one of his employees
Yes. I don't want anybody
to discover my identity
Then just reform yourself, White Eyebrows!
Reform?
You listen close
in my dictionary
there's no such word as reform
You've used your kung fu
to kill many people
All so you could become a tycoon
You now have enough money
for four lifetimes
What left for you to compete for?
No one can ever have too much money
What I hate most is people
who think they can compete with me
Our relationship ended long ago
You nearly made me
the enemy of the entire kung fu world
I decided to leave kung fu
and never see you again
I never expected
you'd become a businessman
Too bad, your personality hasn't changed
Why should I change?
I plan to devour
all the richest of the rich
and become the wealthiest man in Asia
You're dreaming!
Keep dreaming, and I'll tell
Principal of the Academy
You can tell the entire world of
kung fu. I'm not afraid
What arrogance!
You don't believe me?
For 300 years
nobody learned the
secret of the 9th Negative
because it's written in English!
Luckily, I happened to know
a good English teacher
No one can beat me
OK. I believe you. But...
But what can I do? Call the police!
The police can't help you
I asked Dad to protect you
Dad?
Yours truly
You all by yourself?
Along with my martial arts techniques
and my friend Itchiban
You couldn't do any better
If Uncle follows me around all day
it'll be a real eyesore
Don't worry. I've got a plan
What're you doing?
Son-in-law, we're here to protect you
Don't forget. The enemy could be anywhere
Don't call me son-in-law
But you are my son-in-law!
Some things can't be forced
If you're not my son-in-law
why should I protect you?
Let's go
Stop! Father-in-law
Again Father-in-law
The kid learns fast. We won't abandon you
Dragon...
He's safe
Who... who are you two?
Bodyguards...
Dra... Dragon, Mrs. Lam asked for you
Mrs. Lam asked for me?
Mrs. Lam, you called for me?
Dragon
My computer died. Can you take a look?
OK
OK. No pro...
Thank you
Why were you trying to use
the Death Touch on Dragon?
One touch and in one hour
all his blood vessels would burst
Don't try to stop me
But I believe he's the man of my destiny
I must kill him
Why?
Your father White Eyebrows
has learned the 9th Negative
Yesterday I just saw
how great his power was
Nobody can stop him now
He's forcing me to kill
Dragon and your stepfather
And give him your
stepfather's wealth. If I don't...
then he will kill you
He's heartless
He's capable of anything
I have to do as he says
You can't kill my stepfather
But how can I sit by and let him kill you?
What can we do?
Dad treats us so well
How can we do this to him?
But I've no choice
Why are you two crying?
It's nothing
It's because...
we were talking about
this poor woman on a TV soap opera
We got all emotional and began to cry
Silly women. TV is fake
There's no need to cry
That's right
Your birthday is in two days
Let's do something fun
How about a pool party?
Great! Good idea
Hot...
You're so hot, you'll
catch a fever. Better cool down...
Food is here...
Take a bite. Am I a good BBQ chef?
OK...
Boss is here. Time to cut the cake
Boss White has arrived Cut the cake
Why is he here?
Honey, I invited Mr. White
I figured this was a good chance
to relax and to solve your dispute
Congratulations, Mr. Lam. Happy birthday
Thank you
So it's a pool party
Right
Too bad. I forgot
to bring my swimming suit
Never mind. I'll lend you a pair
How could I fill your shorts?
Mr. White, I haven't seen you
for a long time. Welcome
Taken alone, this medicine is non-toxic
But if you take it with alcohol
then you'll die peacefully
This is your daughter?
Yes...
Rouge, say hi to Uncle White
Hi, Uncle White
What good fortune to have
such a beautiful daughter!
Thank you... Let's talk over there
Son-in-law, who is that?
He's Boss White, the Stock Killer
Anyone who angers him meets a bad end
You think the people
chasing you work for him?
The night of the massacre
we were meeting to boycott him
He's worth investigating
Thank you
I'm glad that you respect me
Too bad our project together
wasn't a success
Business is a day's work
But friendship is for a lifetime, right?
Honey
I'm just giving you a hand
Thank you Honey
I cooked this especially for you. Eat up
But it's too fatty. My doctor said
my cholesterol is too high...
Boss, we're taking photos. You in?
No, thanks. But you can help me eat this
Cooked to perfection. Thanks boss
Rouge, what's the matter?
You want to take a photo?
No...
Don't What?
I don't like boys who drink
Oops, wrong glass
I usually only drink water
No cigarettes, no alcohol
and no casual sex for me
Kind of boring, don't you think?
How could you make such a mistake?
Who could know
he would give it to an employee
Rouge is making sure he doesn't drink
We can't make our move today
Come to my clubhouse tonight
for another plan
Do you know why I stopped today?
Why?
Because in the crowd
there were 3 kung fu masters
Really?
The fat one weighs 200kg, but his
Tread Lightly Technique is impeccable
And the thin guy's
Flying Technique is as good as mine
Moreover, there's that girl...
I know that girl. She's called Phoenix
On Mount Hua, she was
always competing with Rouge
I do my best not to arouse suspicion
But before I steal your husband's wealth
you bring these people to thwart me
White Eyebrows, here's an idea...
I'll ask my husband
to give you all his best assets
just don't hurt him, OK?
Why?
You're only after
old bastard's money, right?
Why are you suddenly so kind to him?
We've been married for 10 years
I can't hurt him Shut up!
So you want me to kill
Rouge and your husband myself?
But Rouge is your daughter
You disobey me? I'll kill you too!
If I don't hear he's dead tomorrow
your daughter will disappear
from this world!
Get down!
Are you OK?
White Eyebrows? I knew you looked familiar
Itchiban, are you OK?
I'm not OK. The one behind me
is hurt a little more
Itchiba... Dragon!
You bastard!
Sweetie
Get out of here with Dragon
Don't wait for me
Itchiban, you too
Hello
Brother, you looking for me?
Where are you?
I'm already in a taxi
Don't worry about me
I'm so relieved
Dad!
Big Bird!
Dragon, are you OK? Dragon
I...
His vascular system is failing
What can we do?
Hawk can take him to Mount Hua
Find Principal of the Academy
He'll think of a way to save him
Hawk doesn't have the energy
to carry all three of us
You two go first!
I'll figure out a way to get there
If he gets any worse
you impart the strength
from your martial arts to save him
Where to? Mount Hua
Hold on, we're almost to Mount Hua
I don't think we'll make it to Mount Hua
Don't talk nonsense!
Hawk is flying there now
I think we're going the wrong way
Why?
Look over there
Hawk, where are you going?
We want to go to Mount Hua
not Mount Fuji!
You dumb beast
You pervert
You're a hawk
Why are you chasing a crane?
Now we have to spend the night here
Don't scold him
It's fate
If I'm going to die, nothing can save me
No. I won't let you die. You can't die
Why do you treat me so well?
Because you're the man of my destiny
You know...
in the beginning, I was afraid of you
And... tried to avoid you
And then?
Then fear turned into love
Cabbie, how much?
$88,000
Wow. It would have been cheaper to fly!
I don't know how to go back!
Alright... Can I pay by credit card?
He's hurt badly
The 18 Coppermen can't save him
He'll die within an hour
What can we do?
We still have one last chance
What is it?
Use a Buddhist medicine...
called The Cruel Cure
to bring him back from the dead
It will also impart
30 years of kung fu training
What are you waiting for?
However, after swallowing that pill
he will forget everyone he has loved
Even the woman he loves most...
will seem like a hag
at the supermarket to him
No feeling what so ever
Dad, there's got to be another way
Sweetie, save him first
Life comes before love
We've survived so many dangers together
Just when our relationship is starting
why must I feed you this pill...
that will make you forget me?
Is God testing us?
Wait any longer and it'll be too late
Phoenix, this isn't love
We're two people from two different worlds
Dragon, I trust you
I know you won't forget me
Dragon, are you OK?
I'm OK
But Ms., who are you?
Why are you sleeping next to me?
I...
She's the woman you love most
I know you. You were my bodyguard
Not only that
I loaned you a couple million
You old cheat
But...
Ms., you look very familiar
But I can't recall who you are
White Eyebrows has learned
the 9th Negative
he is simply too powerful
We can't beat him
Then...
We have to use
our sect's strongest technique
Unfortunately, nobody
has ever successfully learned it
<The Technique of the Pure
and Lethal Heart>?
Sure. 4 people must practise it together
2 men and 2 women are best
They must be two couples in love
And they must practise it together
Once learned... it is truly awesome
The force of 4 people equals 100
But where can we find 4 people?
Hello, Dolina
So sorry, Brother Wai
My daughter's no where to be found
I don't mind
Dinner tonight is still great...
so long as you're here
Me?
Honestly, I've been thinking...
We're a better match than
me and your daughter
How about... being my girlfriend?
You psycho
He fails with the daughter
so he goes for the mom
He moves fast, doesn't he?
I've considered it thoroughly
You understand me
You care for me. You love me
I can feel it
I care for your money!
Be my girlfriend
Piss off!
If I'm not careful
I just might beat you to death
Brother Wai, excuse me...
Mom
What are you here for?
We have to talk
We've got nothing to talk about
Sure. Nothing to talk about
Right? My girlfriend
Girlfriend?
Enough! Stop!
Stop!
Can you stop hitting each other?
They're not hitting each other
they're hitting me
If you got something to say
fart it out already
Principal of the Academy has given us
the Lethal Heart technique
Only 2 pairs of family members
or devoted lovers...
will realize its true power
So... So what?
So dad, Dragon and I
have been trained together
If you join us, we're sure
to beat White Eyebrows
You're crazy!
I make millions of dollars a day
How do I have the time to fight?
I know
But without you, we won't have
two pairs of Pure Hearts
Forget it. You won't get
anything from Mrs. Scrooge
Let's go!
I'm still better than
a bankrupt man like you
Look at the animosity between you two?
How can you be a pair of Pure Hearts?
Forget it. Off we march to our deaths
OK. Just put it here
He will never control his temper
If he just said a few nice words...
perhaps maybe I'd agree
Rouge, I thought you loved Dragon
I used to think so too
But it turns out you love me
Before, I thought
I was destined for Dragon
Why?
Something happened
that matched a prediction...
What happened?
How beautiful!
Please come with us, Ms. Lam
Who are you?
Anyone running around
dressed like that has to be crazy
Take this. I will protect you
No need!
They're the people who wanna kill Dragon!
Didn't get enough of our Tendon-Bending
the first time, huh?
Tell her to stop!
Never! Not even if you kill me
Really?
Kiddie Kim!
This is kind of unfair to your left side
What do you mean unfair?
Stop! I'll go with you!
You surrender after
I've been stabbed 60 times
So I was stabbed 60 times for nothing?
60 times? I only see 2 wounds
They're very accurate
Each time they stabbed the same place
So you're the one What?
The one I'm destined for
Go Kiddie Kim
Tell my mom to save me!
Don't worry, Rouge! My mom, your mom...
Every mom everywhere
I'll get them all to save you
Don't worry...
How can you be so heartless?
Can't you take the knives out
when you leave!
Jenny, I've just
brought your daughter here
What did you say?
I give you an hour
to bring Lincoln Lam here
That was Boss White, wasn't it?
I had a private detective follow you
Boss White's not an ordinary man
And I know you two had a relationship
Honey, forgive me
What ever happened before our marriage
doesn't matter
He's forcing you to attack me, isn't he?
They've kidnapped Rouge
Take me to him
No. If you go, he'll kill you
Some disasters can't be prevented
Rouge is not my real daughter
but I love her like one
Honey
Boss Lam, you've got
a real leader's courage
You do everything yourself
Truly a man capable of great things
Jenny, have you told him what I want?
I'm willing to give you all my wealth
But you must set my daughter free
Then we'll leave right away
Give him the contract
(Eat shit!)
Don't worry, boss. Go save Rouge
Come on
So the losers come back to tempt death?
Kill them!
Principal of the Academy has taught you
the Technique of the Pure and Lethal Heart
So your Pure Heart must be the bird?
Mind your own business! Hawk!
You're a total embarrassment!
Get behind me!
You came?
In a clutch, I stand by my family
Let's get him
Phoenix
Sorry, our timing never seems right
Because you've no feeling for me
It's all my fault. I forgot everything...
I remember
I remember! You saved me
You removed the poison
You took me to Mount Hua
Hawk went the wrong way
I recovered my memory...
Really?
Phoenix, this is no time for love
We can't hold up much longer
The pure of heart are invincible!
Let's not exaggerate too much
White Eyebrows is too strong
Working together with a single heart
so that we can defeat him...
Let's get that bastard...
The family that stays together
kicks ass together!
What tricks to you have left fight with?
Let's go!
Watch out!
Flying Swallow Attack!
One - Family - United - Always
Succeeds!
Father-in-law
Let cops handle him
I like the sound of father-in-law
What your say goes
How about me? Mother-in-law!
And me? Honey!
Dad, Mom...
I just saw 4 people
fly past the moon
You must have been dreaming
People can't fly!
You must be watching too much TV
What an over-active imagination!