Kaoru!
Come here!
There is something to see.
Hanai,
didn't I warn you
not to fart?
Did you know that a carburetor * computer ?
- This one * usually *?
- Don't know.
- Silver.
- Silver?
Yes, it turns out that you can fall in love with a bike.
Cold! What are you doing!
My love...
I'm sorry.
Stupid, open your eyes!
School is not just for you!
- *
- I accidentally.
I'm sorry it happened.
Hey, am I a statue for you?
Do you have any money for repairs?
I am not kidding.
Look at both! The motorcycle is brand new.
And if it breaks, who will pay?
Never mind... you're not evil, are you?
Let's forget about it.
Everyone can make a mistake.
Let's start again?
Nothing bad happened.
What is your name?
Sensei, here is today's journal.
You are on time.
We have a new one, Hanai.
Are you out of your mind?
Sorry to say goodbye, but...
We won't walk together anymore.
I got a job.
What are you talking about?
Don't you understand?
I finally realized.
What?
I'm still inexperienced in this, so I can not say.
Yes, we are not forcing you.
- Okay, I'll tell you.
- Well, speak!.
Okay, let's go.
- I fell in love.
- Bye.
What are you smiling at
when you don't even stay afloat?
I never found out your name.
- I'm Hanai Kaoru. And you?
- I'm Ririko.
My name?
I'm not getting acquainted with anyone.
Bye.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
Sonoko-kun.
What was the point in asking then?
During the first meeting
it is mandatory to ask the name of the other person.
Let's go.
See you.
(Kaoru) came.
He is waiting in the backyard.
- Let me borrow your bike.
- No.
Why so?
Pu (name), who am I talking to?
- You have no patience.
- Damn, I don't have time.
Busy...
What are you busy with?
With something.
For example?
Explain.
Can't say.
I already told you, with something.
OK.
Let it be.
I will pay.
But I definitely won't leave empty-handed. *
Do not humiliate yourself.
Stupid.
I still have several of them.
Thank you.
Would you like to thank me? *
Did you say something?
Call me on a date.
Masaki-san, good morning.
You are early today.
Sonoko is still sleeping.
Masaki-san, even if you don't wear makeup,
you still look great.
Don't suck up.
And don't call my mom by her first name.
It's not a problem.
- Stop talking, sit down.
- I'll sit down, I'll sit down.
- Like I have a choice.
- You have to listen to your mother.
- You're too cheeky...
- I see you're getting along.
Where have you seen that?
Sonoko, where did you get such words?
- Don't mess with your mom.
- Exactly.
- Looks like everyone is athlete.
- You don't get it.
- I'm still tonkachi. - Kanazuchi?
[both mean "hammer" like "axe in water"]
[Tzh. tonkachi means "to be a noob"]
I will participate in the Olympics.
- Cool.
"For your sake, Sonoko-kun.
- Stop doing that...
- See you this Sunday?
- Nagai, get ready.
- OK. [Don't confuse Nagai with Hanai]
- Who is he?
- Nagai-kun.
Don't know him?
Look and you will understand.
Understood? This is how a swimmer should be.
And before that, don't even talk about the Olympics.
I'm afraid of water.
Why did you sign up then?
Just wondering.
I want to swim.
Cool.
Lots of chlorine...
One by one, let's dive in!
Hurry, don't delay the others.
What freak did this?
Did you hear my command?
Damn old lady.
Little ones, shut up!
- What did you say about my children?
- What?
- What what?
- What's what?
He told you to shut up!
Are you serious?
Your name is Kaoru, right?
Are you going to the Olympics by any chance?
- How did you guess?
- Hmmm...
But not only for this.
Don't rant here.
I would explain myself.
I can do it myself.
I will definitely win.
What?
- Gran, what nonsense!
- Takashi, call me grandmother! *
Every time you bring *,
without asking anyone.
Gran, you're to blame too.
- There is no pool today; let's go together?
What about Kaoru-kun?
That's the point, until he noticed.
Where is everyone?
Pu.
So are you going on a date?
Don't push me like that.
Where are you going?
- Get the bike back.
- Why so suddenly?
- You don't want to ride it with me.
- Is there anyone besides me?
You do not know me!
When I ride it, everyone around shouts "honey"!
Do not laugh!
You are alone here!
You don't have any friends?
Who would want to be friends with someone like you?
- Got it, got it, go ahead. *
You don't call me at all.
You was so busy that you couldn't even tell?
Probably didn't have time to eat.
- You didn't sleep, did you?
- * didn't do it either.
Stupid, don't be rude.
Pu, will you wait for me? *
- Do not catch my eye!
- As you wish!
- Do you know what it is?
- No.
- Sweet potato.
- Strange.
Potato.
Kaoru-kun goes to extra workout?
It just sounds awesome.
He tries in vain.
So that's how it is...
I do not understand him.
Does he feel something for you?
- Come on!
I don't mind your jokes
but there is nothing between me and him.
It's great when someone loves you.
Depends on who loves.
- You're so naughty.
- Ririko, did someone think of me?
Who knows?
Good weather.
How about "warabimochi" [sweet jelly]?
- My treat?
- Yeah.
Date?
Such a coincidence.
- Where are you going?
- So?
- Where where...
- We're going to the cinema.
- Who is this?
- My girlfriend.
- You're a macho man.
- C'mon.
How did you meet?
- Spontaneously.
- I see.
Spontaneous, you heard?
But is it possible?
Is it possible?
This is how love is born. *
- We're going to a cafe.
- Cool.
How are you behaving?
Wow, I've never been so embarrassed.
[second meaning "unlucky"]
And we looked good together in front of Nagai.
Of course, he is cool, but I will not give in.
Apparently you don't get it.
Didn't notice?
Did you not understand what Nagai-kun was doing there?
What will he think of us now,
when he sees us together?
Sonoko-kun, I want to hate you.
Then it will be much easier for me to live. *
Is everything okay with your head?
Don't skip!
We're learning to swim, not sink!
Kaoru-san is by far the worst
who came here.
So, old woman, listen to me.
You are my coach, and also a personal one.
It's your fault that I swim like an axe.
I see...
When?
Understood.
Okay, be careful.
Good night.
Who's there, dad?
Why doesn't he come?
- Wow, that doesn't sound like you.
Sometimes I want to talk to him too.
He says he will drop by for an o-bon (holiday).
Fatherless...
Do not say that.
You've been on pins and needles lately.
Had a fight with Kaworu?
And I like him, he's so manly.
Kaoru acts like a girl. *
You will see!
- *
- Wow!
They stick well!
*
It's because * .
Look how jealous Akeda-senpai is.
Already the fire in the eyes is burning.
I bet I'll outdrink you. *
We start clapping when the fire starts.
[Running - 10 laps]
- Go all out.
- I'm trying.
For a healthy guy, this is not enough.
Actually, I still have to swim.
- My legs will fall off after this.
- Idiot!
You don't understand what you're exercising for?
Do you think you'll make it to the Olympics without me?
37...
36...
Nagai-kun...
pays no attention to our
girls, although they are fun. *
It must be stressful for him.
- Because they often intersect?
Yeah, it happens with people
that you don't want to see each other.
- What did you think?
- Never mind.
Will you eat?
You ate something outside again?
Here, put it on top.
People don't slurp when they visit!
I can't believe you're acting like this...
Calm as a boa constrictor.
Far from it.
I try my best.
I am always serious.
How can you not understand?
I don't know how serious you are
but how am I supposed to catch it
looking at your behavior?
It doesn't bother me at all.
Stupid!
She must be ashamed.
Because I work so hard
and she chills.
Never mind.
Are you a little arrogant?
What are you doing with my car?
- What are you doing?
- I'm taking a breeze.
Are you walking?
Just started training.
Bye bye!
Disappear quickly.
Only one of us will be the hero.
I won't put up with
which I haven't been able to do yet.
Why are you letting him in while I'm gone?
And this and that.
Don't you dare let him go again.
Understood?
Don't worry like that.
You understood?
Understood?
Everything is wrong.
One "yes" is enough.
- Something happened?
- What do you want?
- You don't look like yourself.
- Get out.
And you don't smile.
What are you sad about?
Accepting your weaknesses is
first step towards improvement.
Don't comfort me.
You can, of course, try
but you won't last long.
Some new feeling.
Share it with me.
I am not myself.
I understand what it's like.
I want to learn how to swim.
You have abilities.
- I see it.
- Is it true?
It is true.
Your talent is visible to the naked eye.
- Something wrong...
- What are you grumbling about?
A haircut will help you "switch".
I can see how you are going crazy
about that girl.
It's time to change priorities.
When you think about her again
look at this ribbon.
- Don't let yourself go.
- And what will this ribbon do?
Do you understand?
I'm going to tell her about it.
Don't worry, I'll be right back.
Gran, what about the ribbon?
Little ones don't understand.
Senile!
Don't think I'll appreciate your baldness.
Listen carefully.
We won't talk for a while.
I have hard training
before the Olympics.
So when it'll be
hard and difficult for me
I will remember us, looking at the ribbon.
Most of all I don't like
being ignored.
Do what you like.
You think I care?
I don't care.
Don't care at all.
Please do as you see fit.
Don't talk to me politely, you bore.
- It's interesting.
He puts them in our box every day.
Sonoko-kun, today I
looked at the ribbon three times.
But even three times is already progress.
Don't worry about my coach
she has a gold medal
- What is this?
- It's all scary.
Yesterday I saw a beautiful moon.
Sonoko-kun, can you see it from your window?
And so every day.
Yesterday I had a dream about how I won
in upcoming competitions.
You should agree, that it is shameful to see
such dreams.
He went crazy, there's no help.
Kaoru-kun doesn't give up...
It's even worse if he was silent on the phone.
You don't even open envelopes.
These are unhappy letters.
Photo from our trip.
The angle is not bad, but it looks ominous.
Then he got drunk in the trash ...
"Recklessness is the main enemy."
Have you ever been in a sauna?
Try it, it's very nice.
Imagine first steaming in the sauna,
and after that you'll drink cold beer!
They are from Ushikawa.
What's happened?
Nothing.
Is it because of him?
- Damn, who are you and where are you from?
- Hanai Kaoru from Hama School.
"I'm Ushi Wakamaru from Ushikawa High.
- Stupid name.
Doesn't matter. Do you hit on these girls?
Doesn't concern you.
Why did you make a face?
One more word and you'll be sailing.
"Sonoko-kun, why are you running away from me?"
- Come on, stop.
back off.
He goes swimming with us.
- Sorry.
- What are you apologizing for?
You (kimi), don't apologize for him.
- "Kimi" (familiar address)?
- I also go to the pool.
- Hey, baldie.
- What?!
Have you fallen for her?
Don't pretend, I see everything.
Don't look with such lustful eyes
on my Sonoko.
Cause I want to puke right away.
Well, sucked it?
This is what happens when
you touch someone else's girl.
Worthless.
Tell me.
Here?
Nobody will bother us here.
Becaming an athlete...
- Is it true, Mr. clown?
- Little by little...
How's your girl (sono-ko)
Sonoko?
Don't play with her name. *
Have you touched her breasts?
Kissed?
Did you have your morning coffee with her?
In my plans...
You have me right here.
Look!
You don't notice me
even though I'm in front of you.
I noticed.
And how did I fall in love with such a mumbler?
Repeat.
Mumbler said.
Damn, in these five minutes * .
You could've confessed your love on the phone.
Then I'll be here right away.
You're in white today, right?
We need to talk.
All right, one time.
Great place to make love. *
Something important?
Sonoko-kun, let's get down to business.
- Don't you understand yet?
- I'm talking to Sonoko.
What are you doing?
- Are you dumb?
- Do not make fun!
She's my girlfriend, as you can see.
- You're out in the cold.
- Nagai, don't make me a fool!
Don't bother Sonoko-kun again.
- Is it true?
- It is true.
- Why?
- Just because.
Understood? Get away from her.
- I understand.
- Understood?
No, I understood something else.
- You are dating.
- Well, so ... - What is it?
I do not care.
- We have mutual love.
- Don't care.
Doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter at all.
- Let's go?
- Wait!
Was that a joke?
Stupid! And why did you call me here?
You could have told me on the phone!
Thought I'd be upset?
Don't be  know-it-all!
Maybe stop messing around with Kaworu?
It's his choice.
No one begged him on his knees.
But he doesn't succeed.
What a nasty girl...
Just like her mother.
And you fell down the stairs.
How are you doing, Kaoru?
- I'm ready for the Olympics, even tomorrow.
- Eat a watermelon.
Everything inside me is on fire.
Cool down until tomorrow.
I can't delay!
Feel better now, you moron?
But...
Look, it's not dirty here, you can eat.
Hanai,
will you swim with Nagai in competitions?
Do not mind?
It doesn't matter to me.
Congratulations.
Don't play with me...
I still have to study more.
What's happened?
- Let's go together.
- OK.
What do you want?
Not hungry?
Not really.
- Something with Sonoko, she is not at school.
- Yeah, what's wrong with her?
Did you call me to talk about her?
Just ask at school
rather than walk around.
Her mother said she was staying at home.
- Why?
- Don't know.
You are her friend, but you don't worry at all.
- Shall we go bowling?
It's closed. *
You could just go to her house,
if you're so worried.
You don't have the courage.
- You are coward.
- Agree.
I understand that you want to present to her
gold medal, but not * ?
A man can't do that.
- Not funny.
- Okay, I'll go, I have more * .
Hey, where's Hanai?
Got scared?
Can you call Ushi?
I'll be waiting outside.
What are you standing for? Takeda-senpai is looking for you.
"Sonoko-kun still missing?"
- Looks like it.
Ririko,
what do you think about me?
You're cool.
I'm participating *
Learn at least a little from our peers!
If you're an athlete, how about showdown?
Don't be stupid.
Our school will die from shame if
we take you for an equal opponent.
So, I asked whom she loves more.
- I'm talking about Sonoko-kun.
- Don't lie!
She said she would choose the one who wins.
- Really?
- She likes strong guys.
And what she said about shaved heads?
Forget it, she already did
bet on today's swim.
I am also participating.
And what about you?
I have something to say
you before the swim.
About Sonoko...
It was staged.
Nagai,
you think i'm going to lose because of
"mental shock"?
Kumihama High School.
Number two.
Shoji-kun.
Takase High School.
Number three.
Nagai-kun.
Hama High School.
Number four.
Hanai-kun.
Hama High School.
Number five.
Ushi Wakamaru-kun.
Ushikawa High School.
Number six.
Ojima-kun.
Nishi-ga-ura high school.
What happened to you?
I knew that you started it
because of a girl.
- If you swam for yourself, then ...
- Gran... - Sit silently!
Big goals aren't bad by themselves,
but yours are simply out of touch with reality.
Okay, do as you please.
Are you leaving me out?
Don't dump your dreams on me.
Do not make me laugh.
What is left for me?
Compete at the Olympics.
Win a medal on your own.
How? Sounds cool?
I don't have many time left and I'm not going to
wait for nothing.
Miki, leave that whiner
and let's go home!
Don't interfere!
What are you doing? I'm not seeing you at all.
I miss you.
Good afternoon
Sorry for no warning.
Listen, sleeping so long and staying
indoors is bad for health.
It's like a greenhouse here.
What are you hiding.
Don't come.
Everything is over.
End.
I'm a laughing stock now.
It's all because of you!
Asshole, just die!
I can't go to school.
You want to go out with a fatty?
This is your handiwork!
Sonoko-kun, because you put some weight,
changed nothing for me.
You always like this!
Said that fell in love with me,
but immediately started to get angry,
when I wasn't interested
You built all this for your own sake.
Kaoru, you are selfish.
You don't even think about how I feel.
It would be good for you to understand that
others have feelings too.
See how big those cheeks are?
They contain my hatred for you!
So much?
Yes, I hate you as much as
you love me you.
I hate you!
And yet,
My love...
Love...
Mother...
What will happen to me?
How to live on?
What is my future?
What?
Thinking of something again?
It's strange that you called me when
yesterday you ran away so fast.
We are breaking up.
Yes, we've never been...
- I love another.
- I'm sorry for everything.
- I don't care.
Sonoko-kun, are you honest with me?
I'm serious.
"We're breaking up."
Say.
- You don't want to date a fatty?
- I understand.
I got it.
I...
I don't feel anything for you.
I only think of myself.
And I don't care about you.
Let's end this.
So that's how it is!
Yes, I knew it from the beginning.
Don't try to stop me.
It's already late.
Good luck.
Apparently, I was mistaken.
Thought you were angry because
that "your" Kaworu is with me.
It turns out not.
You just hated him so much,
that you transformed into "this".
Bye bye.
Are you still at home?
Don't act like a child, we're not your family.
We have different blood.
- Gran, watch your tongue.
That's right, don't speak for everyone.
Don't you worry your head.
Hubby, sucking up is your only strong suit.
Excellent medal.
So you deceived me?
Is this your gold medal?
I am an Olympic athlete.
The real thing.
Gran, listen carefully.
If a man tries,
he will reach both the Moon and Mars.
Until today, I was goldfish shit.
But from now on...
you'll be the shit and I'll be the goldfish.
Understood?
If you want to see me at the Olympics,
don't die. *
Kaoru-san, you are so cool.
What?
Don't just stare at me.
Not just.
I'm looking at your face, it's important.
As you wish.
I'm in a skirt today.
Do you understand?
You love short skirts.
Very much.
You broke up by yourself.
But you can't forget everything.
Say something.
Otherwise it will be awkward.
- Sorry.
- One coffee, please.
Nagai-kun.
Cool guy.
Nice to meet.
- Good...
- What's good?
The reason for worry is gone.
That is?
May I have a cigarette?
Indeed, good...
You know I...
really thought Kaoru was in love with you.
Happens.
Sonoko, ask me.
Oops, I can't tell.
He is such a vulgar guy.
Did you know?
Not a simple fellow.
I cannot even say such thing.
Let's go.
- Goodbye.
- Wait.
I...
lost weight.
I will be the best of the best.
Nobody will compare to me.
I will be professional.
Nagai, I'll pass you too.
I have training ahead of me.
Don't talk nonsense.
Let's have some fun.
Kaoru, look.
Hey!
Know when to stop!
It doesn't matter if you're skinny or fat
I won't give him to you.
Do you know why I call you "the worst"?
You make yourself look cool
but only in words not deeds...
What do you want from me?
You love me!
You said it yourself.
Now we're definitely breaking up.
I won't even remember you.
Good luck and goodbye.
"I can't see you at all."
"I miss you."
Do you know that Hanai quit swimming?
Finally some relaxing workouts.
- Why did he leave?
- Says, he's tired.
What does it mean?
I can't do that.
Let's keep some distance between us.
This will be better for both of us.
Or are you against my leave?
Are you serious?
If so, then I can't stop you.
What's up, Kaoru?
You are bonkers.
I love you.
RUS SUBS: Daniil Andreev
ENG SUBS: Cowa