you know coming into today we had the trend line break we had the trend
channel line over shoot a couple days ago and then a trend line break that
makes me looking for a higher lower lower load to buy the first part of the
day was a big doji far enough room for a scalpel to yesterday's closed in the
moving average I was looking for a good failed breakout this is a breakout
pullback short I didn't take it because I thought that there's a pretty good
chance we were going to have a trend reversal this is a good buy it came on
report when I had reports like that I usually wait to see if there's
tremendous slippage on the report and five or ten seconds later the market
ticker to about and I mentioned that it was probably okay to get it and and it
was a decent lon there's a possibility of this was a low to breakout pullback
you know the Bears at the breakout and this is a two-legged pull back but I
thought the up momentum was strong enough that it was more likely going to
be followed by more buying there was a tu hi tu with the moving average here in
general it's better the top of the bars above the moving average but you know so
let's not ideal but it was okay because of the channel nature there's a risk of
a third push down but if there's if it's a bull trend day if it turns into a bull
trend day you just get this you just get on the high too and nothing else the
market took out the double top and then ran every bar had a low at or above the
low prior bar for about 20 bars which they repeatedly is a by climax it's
unsustainable and usually the correction that comes from it is a lot deeper and
lasts a lot longer than anyone would expect but sometimes you just get to
sideways Corrections oh it's a test of yesterday's high I mentioned that on the
60 minute on the 60 minute it was also the third test of the trading range I so
that might be it for the day on the market broke the bull trend line pull
down and a channel I usually don't buy first break outs of
channels because they also often fail and again a double tot you have the
trend line break and a double top which can be a trend reversal but because of
all the sideways action I thought it was more likely that the market would have a
two-legged side with erection and then try to go up again now it's starting to
the channel down and that's bad for the Bulls we had three pushes down in a
channel and just a for ticked all on or five taped all on rehearsal bar to me I
don't like to buy the first break out of a channel especially if the setup
doesn't look very good and in the market went up to the outside down and then it
had all the cascading magnets the low of first a double top and the low of the
first attempt to sell off then the low of the second attempt to sell off than
the low of the trading range then the break-even stops then on the swing low
than the low today and the market just proceeded to take out every single woman
up this is a two-legged wedge a two-legged test in the moving average
here's the first leg up second leg third leg I did have an order to go short
below this high and instead I got two small doji so I pulled my order because
it was too much risk in my mind of Bob wire but it turned out to be a great
trade for those who took it now we have three pushes down 123 on and also this
tested below on that first attempt to sell off on but again it's kind of a
small bar relative to everything else I did place in order to go on about it but
didn't get filled again the market went down just as it did here and here the
Bears are strong we're going near the bottom of the channel to me that is not
a good long setup and again the market left out
tied down outside down and a break up below something usually has at least a
second leg down so I was not interested in buying above that bar and the market
didn't even offer alone selling selling below the double bottom is reasonable
this is a third push down in a channel so chances are it's pretty good it's
pretty good setup for at least a scalp that's a pretty good reversal bar there
and that's always good for on the market reverse and again outside the bottom