[Why Do You Keep
changing Your Couple Ring?]
[The day of a drama
production presentation.]
[Who's the first guest to
step on the red carpet?]
He acts in different genres and roles,
Lee Kwang Soo!
Thank you very much!
Hello, everyone!
He puts his heart and soul in acting,
the child actor, Haroro!
[The three actors famous
for being fools.]
Entertainer, Ji Suk Jin!
[MC, Kim Hwan]
You're here?
In this drama, Ji Suk Jin
was my dying grandfather.
A cool pose?
I can't do stuff like that!
He's no longer a cameo,
he's a multi-player, Gary!
[He acts with his muscles, Kkuk!]
He's continuing on the
path of Lee Dae Geun!
An actor who started
his career with 'Tyranno's Claw.'
One of the top stars, Yoo Jae Suk
challenges at a straightforward acting!
Hello, nice to meet you!
- I enjoyed your movie.
- 'Tyranno's Claw.'
- Your comeback after 'Tyranno's Claw.'
- Yes, it's been more than 21 years.
It's been a while since 'Tyranno's Claw.'
- You were the claw, right?
- Yes.
[No, I was a caveman!]
A captivating actress walks in
to join the excited actors.
[Blank Ji?]
Hello!
[She's the most beautiful she's ever
been in her five years of 'Running Man']
[Song Ji Hyo!]
- Ji Hyo!
- Wow, Ji Hyo!
[Their mouths are wide open.]
[An actress' hairdo, full makeup]
[black see-through,
charming Blank Ji is complete!]
- Why?
- Why are your clothes like that!
[I'm not used to this...]
I'm shy!
I'm shy for no reason!
Sorry.
I forgot she used to be slim and fit.
[Sometimes we forget,
but she is a beautiful top actress.]
- She's beautiful, though.
- Who is that?
[Another actress' visit.]
[A pure actress who seeks to be
the leading star in this drama.]
Of course, she's pretty.
A refreshing and elegant actress,
Cha Ye Ryun!
Today's hottest actress!
[A well-rounded actress that moves freely
between ads, dramas, and films!]
[Look forward to her competitive side!]
- Do you know her well?
- Hello!
- Nice to meet you!
- Yes, nice to meet you.
We're friends,
we're the same age!
You're not friends,
you're just the same age!
[I was almost flustered...]
[And the last guest of the
production presentation!]
[We can catch the sight of
a leading actress's figure.]
This is so awkward...
[Surprised]
A top actress with the greatest
name value in the country!
A Goddess-like presence, Lee Yo Won!
[She debuted at 18 years old,
and she's still at the top!]
[She was named as the nation's
top actress after 'Queen Seondeok.']
Isn't it her first appearance
on 'Running Man'?
- Yes.
- She hasn't been on a variety show...
Aren't you guys showing a fake reaction?
We were too surprised...
- It's been so long.
- It's been 16 years!
- On a variety show?
- Really?
Her first appearance?
When I first debuted in high school,
I was on a few variety shows.
[High-teen star, young Lee Yo Won.]
- I've seen you when you were young...
- Yes, I was in high school.
- You were in high school?
- How old is she?
Why Do You Keep
changing Your Couple Ring?
This is the drama poster!
Applause, please!
[That's the drama I'll be cast in?]
There are three characters in silhouettes.
This is a casting survival.
[Three leading stars will be cast!]
Oh, there are three leading roles?
- Oh, it's a competition.
- We're in three teams today.
Yes, I will now announce your teams.
First up, Yoo Jae Suk
Ha Ha
[What's with this combination?]
and Lee Yo Won.
We have the two main actor and actress,
and he's just a servant.
What are you saying, servant Lee?
[I hope our team's alright...]
Kim Jong Kook and Gary.
- It's been a while!
- And lastly, Cha Ye Ryun.
[The strongest team is born.]
Are we going to win today?
- The last members are a team.
- It's see-through Song, and the men.
[Kwang Soo, see-through Song,
and Big Nose.]
Oh, it's actual skin...
What's wrong with you?
He keeps looking at me with weird eyes!
- He said...
- It was actual skin!
I thought it was skin-colored fabric...
There are reporters,
so please restrain yourself.
[Once more, and I'll be kicked out...]
I've made my appearance
in different pieces of work.
'Dachimawa Lee' and 'Wonderful Radio.'
[He was a cameo with Kkuk
as a drunk person.]
They were drunk people!
It was a minor role, but I am hoping
for the leading role in this drama.
I've made my appearance
in 'Younggu and the Alien Bulgoeri.'
That was my debut movie.
At the time, although I was in my twenties
I was cast as an elementary student.
I was a favorable actor to the director.
As you may know, I was also
in 'Queen of Housewives.'
And I was also a leading role
in a Banjun (plot twist) drama.
Anyway, I've already met Yo Won a long
time ago through another piece of work...
- With me?
- Yes.
[Embarrassed]
You might be unfamiliar
but this is how you do it
on variety shows.
I was actually thinking...
[Why Do You Keep Changing
Your Couple Ring?]
- Please accept our marriage!
- Never, not until I die!
[A war-like battle for these roles!]
[Only one team will get
the leading roles!]
[They are heading to
the first mission site.]
Wow, there are lots of cameras.
There are really no cameramen in the car.
You really haven't been on
variety shows for a long time.
But at home, I only watch variety shows.
- Really?
- Yeah, not dramas.
You like them, but you don't
go on them often?
I'm not good.
People usually like to observe
what they're not good at.
I feel like you have
a lot of stories to tell!
- Right?
- No, no.
- When did you debut?
- At 18 years old.
All the guys loved your type.
I was popular among females.
Yo Won has a slight boy-ish feel.
- Yes, I do.
- Yeah, that was it!
Don't I look more feminine on the outside?
Yeah!
- Wait, actually?
- Yes.
I normally get cast for those roles...
So my image is a little feminine.
Ye Ryun's always been pretty.
Yeah, of course.
Is Cha Ye Ryun your real name?
No, it isn't.
- Can I ask your real name?
- It's a guy name...
You probably know someone
around you with the same name.
It's Hyun Ho.
- Cha Hyun Ho?
- Park Hyun Ho.
It really is a guy name...
I know someone with that name!
I was going to react differently.
I was going to say 'it's not bad!'
But...
Cha Hyun Ho is at least okay.
- Can we just call you Hyun Ho?
- Yeah, let's do that!
Sure, then go ahead.
Because we're special,
we'll just call you that.
[Why Do You Keep Changing
Your Couple Ring?]
[Get over the casting call!]
['K' Exhibition hall
in Gyeonggi province.]
[After a long chat,
Yo Won's team arrived.]
[Soon after, Ye Ryun's team arrived.]
Let's go, Hyun Ho!
Yo Won is...
- really...
- She's good at talking.
- I thought she didn't talk much.
- But she talks a lot!
- She talks a lot!
- She has so many stories to tell.
She's very elegant in real person.
Thank you.
- Very luxurious!
- Let's go in!
- What?
- What's this?
[What is this?]
[A huge track that
foretells a difficult casting!]
The first mission is
'Conquest of the difficult casting.'
There will be obstacles
appearing on the track.
However, two reps from each
team will be blindfoldeed
and take their place at the start line.
We will time them until they
both sit on the chair
after they've passed all the obstacles.
The third member will
stand on the platform
and yell out directions.
- Hyun Ho, did you get it?
- Two people
cover their eyes...
You come from both directions?
- Then I yell?
- Why do you think you're going to yell?
You guys aren't even curious?
We're a family.
If you aren't going to react,
come to the side.
Why are you standing in the middle?
Ask about what you're curious!
[The obstacles are being set up.]
[Different obstacles being
set up, installed, lifted.]
[The complete obstacle course.]
[Yo Won is on standby on the platform.]
- Do well!
- Good luck!
- Should we do one person at a time?
- We'll start with Jae Suk, first.
Ready, set!
Left!
Go over that!
'Go over that.'
- Oh this?
- Yes, go over that.
- This was...
- Yes, go over it again!
[Awkward]
- Just go over it!
- Are you wearing leggings?
- Leggings?
- Are they leggings or what?
[He looks more grasshopper-like]
That... what is that... limbo!
You need to limbo!
- Where is it?
- It's right in front of you.
- How does he do that?
- Keep going, keep going!
Lower, with that position!
[He passed after a minor collision.]
Jump forward!
There's a hat above,
you need to wear it.
- Is it right above me?
- Yes, the hat is right there.
One, two, three, jump!
- Jump!
- Ow, it hurts!
[There's no way it'll work...]
My eyesight is horrible... come forward!
[You should have told me earlier!]
From my perspective,
the hat was right above him!
[Falter, falter]
Wear the hat!
Yo Won!
- I have to wear it on my own?
- Yes, now Ha Ha...
How many steps?
Just go to the table and there will be
lipstick, you have to put the lipstick on!
[A Spartan-like navigation.]
- Can't you tell me?
- Go farther!
Stop!
Right!
Straight!
Walk faster!
I can't see, Yo Won!
[Her explanations are simple,
but they work!]
Stop, stop!
Pop the balloon!
You need to explain, kindly.
I can't see right now!
[But funny enough, they're
continuing the mission alone.]
She's not looking at you anymore!
Oh, I popped it!
Turn around, turn around!
Now come forward and sit on the chair!
[She's Spartan-like until the end.]
The audience might think I can see!
[Only Ha Ha's left now.]
There's an acupressure mat
and snack in front of you.
You eat it on your own!
[He's short!]
[Lick, lick]
- You have to think about his height...
- You need to match...
Just grab it and eat it.
Don't be so cold!
[Yum]
- Go straight!
- You're good!
[She's amazing...]
Ha Ha, go closer!
There's a gourd.
Just crack it.
[Charismatic]
[Crack]
He cracked it!
- Do I find it on my own?
- Yes, there's a chair to sit on.
[Team Yo Won, round one clear.]
My throat hurts!
Yo Won uses the Spartan method!
She wants us to do everything on our own!
'Walk faster!'
[Their record is
5 minutes and 12 seconds.]
[Why Do You Keep Changing
Your Couple Ring?]
This time, it's Cha Ye Ryun's team.
Ready, set!
Jong Kook, go first!
Take one step.
- Another step.
- Suk Jin!
[They're bothering their team.]
[The decibel is getting higher.]
I can't hear you!
[Mental breakdown]
- Say ho!
- Ho, ho!
[This is fun!]
[What are they saying?]
[This won't do.]
Stop there...
- What is he doing?
- What's he doing?
[Touch, touch]
[He's advancing at
high-speed with his hands.]
Oh my, look at him!
[He passes the obstacles in a flash.]
[Touch, touch]
[He found it by himself
and succeeded in one shot.]
[That's the Spartan-way!
That's my style!]
Check his eyes!
Make sure they're covered!
[You didn't know?]
[Lions are nocturnal!]
[Gary's in front of a roly-poly bunch.]
There are ten of them your size!
[Her explanations are a little too nice.]
[They look similar from this angle.]
- Then, there are four...
- What is he doing by himself?
[It's as if he has eyes on his hands.]
Just go over four of those and stay still!
[Walk, walk]
[He did it in one try after
listening to her explanation!]
[Mr. Random Capable]
If you come two steps forward,
there's an acupressure mat.
Does it hurt?
Gary, wait!
Right there!
Stay there and lift your left arm up.
[Her gentle and kind explanation]
[is the complete opposite of Yo Won's.]
I thought Jong Kook had his eyes open!
[Roar]
If you take a step, there's an
acupressure mat and it'll hurt.
[She even lets him know about the pain.]
You're so kind!
If it was Yo Won,
she would have said 'just go!'
[That's how you grow.]
If you raise your arms...
[Grab]
[Does he really have eyes on his hands?]
It hurts!
Gary, take five steps forward.
Jong Kook, there's a hula hoop nearby.
Take the hula hoop and jump
rope with it three times.
- Okay!
- Gary!
Take five steps, in that position.
One, two, three, four, five.
- There's a balloon in front of you!
- It's so exact...
- I'm done!
- Okay!
You have a foot stuck in there,
so take it out.
[Kind Ye Ryun]
Ye Ryun is really nice.
[Both of them will succeed
if they pop the balloon!]
[Pop]
Then hold hands!
Hurry and sit!
Hurry!
- Okay.
- Alright.
[Team Ye Ryun, round two clear!]
[Kind Ye Ryun and monster-like
Mr. Capable's perfect team play.]
[Their record is 5':37".]
[Why Do You Keep Changing
Your Couple Ring?]
Director!
Do I just follow the road?
Listen to me!
Ready, set!
Suk Jin, limbo!
Five steps forward!
Kwang Soo, take five steps forward!
[Unlike the other teams,
they're doing both at the same time.]
- Forward, pick it up!
- More, more!
- Sit!
- Sit down!
- Yeah, just come up a bit!
- Sit!
[Bump]
[What's this?]
Suk Jin, jump!
[You want me to jump?]
[Jump]
[It's so chaotic]
Jump rope, three times!
- Who do I listen to?
- Isn't it a hula hoop?
- Do I stay still?
- Jump... hey!
Jump rope!
- Jump rope?
- Jump rope, three times!
[Giraffe isn't jumping,
but Impala's jumping instead.]
[This is driving me crazy...]
[Three minutes have passed...]
- Go... Kwang Soo, stop!
- Do I keep going?
- Go back, go back!
- Do I go back?
- Lee Kwang Soo, go backwards!
- Me?
- You said go back!
- No, not you!
Suk Jin, take five steps...
Lee Kwang Soo, stop there!
Lee Kwang Soo, stop right there!
You told me to go backwards!
Suk Jin, take one step forward.
Yeah... like that.
It fell!
Squat and lift it back up!
- Lift what?
- Yeah, that!
Suk Jin...
[Lift]
Put it down!
[He's weightlifting instead of
getting through the obstacle.]
[How do I explain this...]
[It's already been seven minutes.]
Oh my god!
This acupressure mat!
[They both got to the acupressure mat...]
- What's there?
- Lift your left arm up!
Backwards!
You see the snack, right?
- You see the snack, right?
- How can I see the snack!
[Oops]
How can I see?
[Where did they go wrong...]
[He succeeds in eating the
snack like a real giraffe.]
- It hurts!
- I ate it!
Grab it, get up, and throw it up!
- No, not like that!
- What is this?
[Oh my, my]
What are you doing!
- Where is it, here?
- Yeah.
- That's it!
- Okay, you did it!
[He keeps throwing without
knowing it's already open.]
Suk Jin, it's open already!
[Please stop, it's open...]
Stop already!
Do you feel it in front of your knees?
Grab the table, slowly.
Try touching the surface.
There should be lipstick on top.
[Her composure dropped
down with the lipstick...]
Tell me beforehand, that there's lipstick!
[This is my limit...]
Take a huge step back, just like that.
Suk Jin, crack it on the floor.
[Their mission finally ended
after 16 minutes...]
[Sponsor: Running stone bed]
[The war started!]
[A gruesome struggle to be cast.]
[The long journey for the casting call.]
[Whatever happens,
I'm going to be the leading role!]
[Why Do You Keep
Changing Your Couple Ring?]
- But we still got first place.
- Yeah.
- I didn't even expect it.
- You were good!
It was a pretty simple game.
[Yo Won's Sparta-like
'do it yourself' method.]
I really did it on my own.
'Do it on your own!'
If I just tell you what's
in front of you...
Yeah, it was a good method.
[The rest is up to you.]
It was a great method.
I think we can take it easy today.
We have two chances at the moment.
- It's very important.
- Yeah.
I... don't give very good reactions...
When I act, I don't improvise at all.
I just stick to the script.
'Do it yourself' was really good, though.
- She's perfect for variety shows.
- Yeah, she's perfect.
Hyun Ho, I think you're the wild type.
Do you get along well with guys?
Yes, I have many guy friends.
I become friends with everyone.
Do you go to a cafe
and or like an americano...
You want to drink with me?
What do you mean?
Is this the start of a love line?
- Hyun Ho, just wait a bit.
- Yes, Hee Gun.
I had a weird feeling!
I don't know what to do!
Now, you're back to Ye Ryun.
[Why Do You Keep
Changing Your Couple Ring?]
[Fashion completes action.]
[A refreshing pool to
wash away the heat wave.]
[What kind of war will unfold here?]
This is the second mission.
To receive love from
the always trendy public
- you need to pay attention to style.
- Style!
There's a fashionista here.
So, the second mission is
'Complete the actress' style.'
The four photo zones are
black, green, yellow, and pink.
We will choose the order for each team.
You have to dance to the
music until the whistle blows.
The guys have to jump in the water
and collect the right colored
clothing for your team.
You have to wear the clothes,
and throw it to the female teammate
and head to the right zone.
At the photo zone,
we will take your picture.
The first team to get
all four pictures, wins.
Jong Kook's team is too strong!
[Mr. Capable, Fashionista,
and Mr. Random Capable.]
But Jong Kook might not
fit into the clothes.
Could you prepare a triple XL?
[What do we do with that muscle monster?]
We will throw the clothes
you will be wearing.
Be quiet!
It'll start when I blow the whistle!
- Are you ready?
- Yes!
We'll turn the music on.
[She's worried about
the mission while dancing.]
[Grab]
[Inflatable tube man techno
with their napes grabbed.]
[While they let their
bodies loose in the rhythm]
[Blow!]
[Go away!]
[Splash]
[Jae Suk passes the black
shirt as soon in a flash.]
[Kkuk also passes the
yellow shirt to Ye Ryun.]
- Be careful!
- Be careful behind you!
[Both people have to wear the same color.]
[The guy must wear
the shirt in the water.]
[Grasshopper wears the
black shirt and escapes.]
[They arrived at the black
photo zone in a flash.]
[The easily passed the first round.]
[Hurry, Jong Kook!]
[They got the same
color in the first round...]
[Giraffe's defense]
Kwang Soo!
[Jae Suk brings Yo Won a pink shirt.]
Jae Suk's team is doing too well!
[If this continues,
they'll pass round two in no time!]
Someone block them!
[Just then, Ye Ryun moves out!]
[Block, block]
Ye Ryun, please don't do this!
No, Ye Ryun!
[Jae Suk escapes at that moment!]
[She got caught by strong Ye Ryun.]
[Ye Ryun and Ji Hyo's incredible defense.]
[I'll just take one picture!]
Ye Ryun, come!
[They head over to the yellow
photo zone right away.]
- Kwang Soo!
- One, two, three!
[First round, clear!]
[As soon as Ye Ryun leaves]
[they clear round two!]
Hurry up, Kwang Soo!
Just come out!
Just put your head in!
[Struggle, struggle]
[While everyone's
distracted by their colors]
[Team Ye Ryun clears round two!]
[They enter the yellow photo
zone with Ji Hyo's lead.]
[They just cleared round one.]
[Now, Ye Ryun's team needs
the green shirt.]
[Now, it's a bloody fight between
team Yo Won and team Ye Ryun.]
[Now's the time!]
[Grab]
[Kkuk steals the green shirt!]
Why are you doing this!
What is she doing?
[What can I do?
I need the green shirt!]
[It's war for the green shirt!]
[Everyone's enemy,
Kkuk is being attacked.]
[An individual combat is going on.]
Put your head in first!
[She puts her head in.]
Save me!
[The first team to wear the shirt
has a higher chance of winning.]
Kwang Soo, hurry up!
[He finished wearing the pink shirt]
[while they were fighting.]
[They cleared round two!]
[All three teams are tied.]
[Splash]
I think he also needs green.
We can't all finish today!
Kwang Soo, it's not that!
- Kwang Soo, we're black!
- No, we're green!
- Kwang Soo!
- What color are we?
[Roll, roll]
[Give me the shirt!]
Wow, this is intense!
[This isn't a martial arts movie...]
[Kkuk escaped!]
[Just then!]
Oh, you're Yo Won.
Go take his shirt!
Get the shirt!
He's getting in trouble!
[Give us the shirt, now.]
Don't do this.
You shouldn't do this.
I feel like my mom's scolding me!
Give it!
Hold him while we go
then I'll throw it to
you and I'll hold Kwang Soo down.
- That would work!
- Hurry, hurry!
[While Jae Suk holds Kwang Soo down...]
[Lots of time on their hands]
[Round three, clear!]
[Keep your promise!]
[We're a little late.]
It's our last one!
[Round three, clear!]
[They only need to clear the last shirt.]
[Kkuk passed the pink shirt to Ye Ryun]
[but he's missing his shirt.]
[Splash]
Jong Kook, it's probably over there!
[Jae Suk passes the yellow shirt quickly.]
[Only Jae Suk is left.]
[Kkuk is still tussling with Kwang Soo.]
[Jong Kook...
It's no time to that,]
[Bravo!]
[Yo Won's team wins
at the fourth stage.]
[Team Yo Won wins the first round.]
[Yo Won wasn't sparing of herself.]
[See? I can do action, too.]
[Team Ji Hyo won the second round.]
Team Yo Won scored one point,
and team Ji Hyo scored one point.
For the third round, both of the
guy members will go into the pool.
We'll give you four t-shirts.
So, this time we'll decide
the first place and the second.
That's very clever.
You'll begin now.
[The third round, starts.]
[Gary passes the yellow shirt
as soon as he gets in.]
[All the members of Team Ye Ryun
get yellow shirts.]
[Team Yo won and Team Ji Hyo
need to get the green shirts.]
We're in trouble!
[There are four men,
but two t-shirts.]
[The second war of
green t-shirt is about to begin.]
- Wear it quickly.
- Steal it!
[Team Ye Ryun arrives at the photo zone.]
[They succeed at the first stage easily.]
[They run to the pink shirts.]
Look, that teams is doing it again!
[Team Ye Ryun grabs
the pink shirts quickly.]
[At this rate,
Team Ye Ryun will win easily.]
[The only solution is
stealing the green shirts.]
Are we hermaphrodites?
[Team Ye Ryun succeeds
at the second stage.]
They're almost done.
They're really done!
[Ye Ryun is relaxed.]
[They're getting for
taking pictures peacefully.]
[Team Ye Ryun succeeds
at the third stage.]
[Now, every team needs
to wear the green shirts.]
I'm sorry!
[She apologizes first and attack.]
[I feel really sorry.]
[Just take it off when I say it nicely!]
Just wait!
I'm so sorry...
She keeps saying sorry!
We were so into this game.
- There are three people here.
- Look at her.
She's on variety after 16 years
and she looks dazed.
Let's just play rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
Just one game between female members.
Let's do that.
[Ji Hyo is tying her shoe laces.]
[Now is the chance!]
Hey!
[Finally, Team Yo Won succeeds.]
- Hey!
- We passed!
[Kwang Soo  borrows
a green t-shirt from the VJ.]
It's all over!
[It's over?]
I'm so sorry.
It's not done yet.
[Why did you want my shirt then.]
One, two, three!
[After much trouble, Team Ji Hyo
succeeds at the first stage.]
Jae Suk!
[Team Ye Ryun gets the green t-shirts.]
Come, Gary.
[That was easy.]
It's over!
One, two, three!
[Team Ye Ryun succeeds
at the fourth stage.]
We won the first place!
[Team Yo Won needs black
and team Ji Hyo needs yellow.]
[Kwang Soo is interrupting Ha Ha.]
[I won't let you go!]
Kwang Soo, don't do this.
Kwang Soo.
She's trying to convincing him.
Is this the last color for this team?
It's not?
- It's not our last color.
- It's not?
- She said not.
- What's that?
She looks like a person who's in jail.
A criminal in historical dramas!
I think I've seen her
in the story of Chun Hyang.
[What are you talking about?]
[I was a queen.]
[The decide on taking the pictures.]
- Let's just take it!
- It's their last shirts!
- It's not their last.
- It's not.
One, two, three!
[Team Ji Hyo succeeds at it.]
[Both team needs to wear one more!]
Who is it?
It's not the same color.
Then it's a battle of speed.
[What speed!]
Just do it quickly!
Let's just take the picture quickly.
How about wearing it quickly
and taking the picture?
She talks like a kindergarten teacher!
[You're nice kids, just listen to me.]
Wear it quickly and take the picture.
Come out, Ji Hyo.
Please take a picture of us.
[Now is the chance!]
[Which team will be faster?]
Hurry up!
[Ha Ha was one step late...]
[Ji Hyo's team succeeds
at the fourth stage first.]
[Ji Hyo's team locks up second place.]
Ji Hyo you looked like a man
when you were climbing up.
Kwang Soo was dragging me.
I felt like a hunted fish.
Ha Ha couldn't get up fast enough.
He was faster over here though.
[Sponsor: The Running University]
- Are we going to be the last?
- Do you want to have a bad time?
[The casting competition
is drawing to its end.]
[Throw yourself out there!]
[You'll be cast!]
[The drama with
a incredible plot twist begins now!]
[Why Do You Keep
Changing Your Couple Ring?]
[The casting competition, chapter 3]
[The final rehearsal]
['R' Shopping Complex, Ilsan]
[Team Yo Won arrives first.]
Let's get out.
- Victory!
- Fight, fight!
[What will we be doing this time?]
[Surprised]
[Welcome to the real street casting!]
[It's best to cast on the spot!]
It's tiring...
[What mission will they be doing here?]
The last mission to get cast
is carrying out the script!
Carry out the script?
We need to act.
[An instant scene script?]
[The instant scene script
makes the actors nervous.]
[The stages with instant scripts
will be performed!]
I knew this was coming.
There'll be total of five stages.
The fifth site is in Sangam-dong.
[They can use the chance tickets
they've acquired.]
[What will be the first scene?]
Love? I'm just going to buy it with money.
Because I don't want to lose you!
[This sounds familiar.]
[How much should I pay?]
[A typical line of a conglomerate.]
When you hear the whistle,
you can say the line.
Then we'll show you the amount
of money you need to collect inside.
There's a time limit.
When time is up,
you need to show us the money.
If you fail,
the next member will do the mission.
[The first mission
When the Money Blows]
Do you go in all together?
[A story of a woman who hits the jackpot
after lots of hardship and misfortune.]
Why did they give us this apron?
There's so much pressure.
What should I do?
They set up a glass box.
We're ready!
[Will they be able to act in public?]
- We're ready!
- They're ready.
Say the line, then we'll show you.
- How much should I pay?
- How much?
[195,000 Won]
[When the Money Blows]
155,000 Won?
[It's not easy to stand
in the money tornado.]
[It's a beautiful windy day!]
[I won't lose you!]
[Is your name Money?]
[It's just a game,
but they look obsessed.]
['The Gleaners']
[It's a very strong wind!]
This is annoying.
Isn't it suffocating?
[Are they collecting the right amount?]
130,000 Won?
190,000 Won!
[Let me see...]
[Blurry]
[Show me the money...]
190 thousand...
195,000 Won?
[She collects more money.]
[I'm done!]
[They're not allowed to exit the room
until one minute is up.]
[The first round of
'When the Money Blows' is over.]
I have poor vision,
so I couldn't see it.
I thought it was 135,000 Won.
But it's 195,000, right?
Me, too.
I thought it was 135,000 Won.
[The last mission, The Last Rehearsal]
[I don't care about actress's pride.]
[Money is the best!]
[Let us out!]
[We're too rich to be punished!]
- The number looked like 13.
- I thought it was 13!
Please write it clearly.
It looks like 13.
I realized it later.
You counted it wrong.
[They're closing from Ji Hyo's team.]
Is it correct?
Yeah!
Song Ji Hyo passed it.
Go to the number two!
- Go to the next number.
- The next?
Let's win the race!
This is awesome, let's win this!
[What is waiting for them?]
- It's right here.
- The wall of love.
Oh, no!
There's water.
Sit down here.
What is this?
A couple is sitting, facing each other.
The man says the line
and wears a sponge mask.
The woman says the line and
throws the water into his face.
[The magical action that burns
the other person to the ground.]
[The temptation of the water slap]
One will throw the water.
Try collecting the water with the sponge.
Squeeze the sponge and collect the water.
Do that three times
and collect allocated amount.
He's the best member
for the water slap.
Don't avoid it, okay?
Try tiling your head backward.
Take one, cue!
- What is it?
How dare you!
Hey!
There's nothing!
[Their first attempt seems bad.]
Kwang Soo...
[I know how to play this game.]
- Kwang Soo, wake up!
- What?
[The water is in his mouth.]
[Giraffe, the moisture absorber]
Kwang Soo, open your mouth.
- I don't want...
- Just do it!
[You need to squeeze the sponge,
not me!]
The water in your mouth.
Put it in the jar!
[What's the result?]
[It's not even close.]
I think we can do it.
[They can keep trying
until the other teams come.]
[Grasshopper vs. Muscle Man]
Let's focus on collecting money.
It won't be easy.
How much should I pay?
[How much should they pay to
escape from 'When The Money Blows'?]
118,000 Won!
[118,000 Won]
[Grasshopper vs. Muscle Man]
[Who will collect the exact amount?]
[Let me borrow some]
[Putting his arms around
Grasshopper's shoulders.]
[It feels like we've seen it
in the backstreet.]
[They seem close.]
[When Grasshopper gets cornered...]
[he bites!]
Oh, we're friends forever!
Oh, a happy heart!
[Their beautiful friendship
with biting and chewing.]
[Aren't they loving too much?]
[Muscle Man is aiming
for Grasshopper's money.]
[Never let go of our hands.]
[The tango of friendship]
[Rotate once, rotate twice...]
[It's time to say goodbye.]
[Grasshopper is empty handed.]
[What were you doing?]
[Muscle Man returns after
performing the tango show.]
[Did he bring the correct amount?]
It's correct!
[Jong Kook correctly
brought 118,000 Won!]
- Can we leave?
- It's okay, we can reverse it later.
- Work hard!
- We'll be leaving.
[Team Ye Ryun goes to the next scene.]
What's this?
[They enter the stage for
the temptation of water slap.]
[Team Ji Hyo's second attempt.]
Take two, cue!
[Collected one cup already.]
You need to live straight!
Why do you think
you can order me around...
[Squeeze, squeeze]
Get lost!
[They squeeze the sponge
with all their strength.]
- This will do.
- This is annoying!
[Oh, it's how you play it?]
[Team Ye Ryun might come from behind!]
We're number one so far!
Please, please!
No, don't stop!
[Will they really succeed like that?]
Yes, it worked!
We did it!
[Team Ji Hyo passes
the temptation of the water slap.]
Please move to the next spot.
We're winning!
Amazing.
Let's win this race!
The third round!
[We'll be cast!]
What do we need to do?
- Please read that.
- What do we need to do?
Please allow us to marry.
Put water melon seeds on the face.
[A scene when the parents
don't allow the marriage.]
You need to find one of the parents,
a brother-in-law, and a nephew.
A person who's in their 50s, and 20s
and another one who's a teenager.
- In their 50s, 20s and teens?
- An elementary student.
Is there anyone in their 50s?
An elementary student,
you're an elementary student.
- Are you good at acting?
- Pardon?
Is this your first time?
Me, too.
In their 50s?
- Could I ask your age?
- I'm eight!
- I mean you dad...
- He's 42.
[It's hard to find people in the street.]
Excuse me, could I ask your age?
57!
Could you help us for a moment?
- What do I need to do?
- You can say a line.
One, two, three, four.
That's right!
Succeed!
Let's go to the second spot!
[The real competition begins now!]
Let's hurry!
[Team Ye Ryun's the temptation
of the water slap]
- I'm sorry...
- Garry, how can you do this to me?
- Can you forgive me?
- No, I can't forgive you!
Ye Ryun!
[Kkuk collects the water.]
[Is that all?]
It's not going to be enough.
[Relieved]
[The second and the third glass]
It was good this time.
[It's too late.]
[Let me squeeze it out.]
[Squeeze]
[Gushing]
[His muscles move.]
[Every time his muscles contract,
water flows in the jar.]
[Oh, no!]
[His muscles are alive!]
[He's squeezing every drop of water.]
It was good this time, Ye Ryun!
[Is he really a human?]
That'll do.
[Will Dehydrator Kkuk
can reverse the result?]
[He did it!]
[Team Ye Ryun passes the second stage,
the temptation of the water slap.]
We did it!
Can we go to the next stage?
[Teams leave the stage
when another team arrives.]
You're my brother.
What's your name?
- I'm Kwang Jae.
I'm Kwang Soo.
- Ji Suk Jin is the main actor.
- I am?
You're the nephew.
Remove the lid.
You see there's a piece of watermelon.
Say the line in the script
and attach a seed on your face.
- When all of you succeed at it...
- We'll pass, okay!
You'll fail if anyone's seed falls.
Don't allow the marriage, Father.
- I'm going to marry her.
- You shouldn't!
- He shouldn't.
- Everyone should oppose it.
- You can practice the line.
- I'm really bad at this.
Father, please allow us to marry.
- She did it!
- Pass!
[Why are they so noisy?]
[Team Ye Ryun enters the stage.]
I'll never allow you!
[They keep acting.]
Say it like you're acting.
He did it!
I'm sorry, let me...
Help him, Ji Hyo.
We can't drop it!
[It's Kwang Soo's turn.]
What a shame on our family!
[Huh?]
[He shoots out the seed.]
[Ruined!]
[You're the shame on our team.]
[Their first attempt fails.]
[Team Ye Ryun starts street casting.]
- Can you do it?
- I can do it!
Why did you shave your hair off?
- Elementary student?
- Right there!
- Can you do it?
- Yes!
He looks like he can do it.
All our members look energetic.
Someone in their 50s.
Are you in your 50s?
Are you in your 60s?
- Honey!
- Your husband is here, too?
- Is your husband in his 50s, too?
- Yes.
[Good luck!]
Why don't you come here?
- Let's be our mother.
- Hello!
[Team Yo Won arrives at the stage.]
Your husband should come.
[They start casting
as soon as they arrive.]
Is there any elementary student?
Are you in your 20s?
[She cast one right away.]
Thank you.
[Team Ye Ryun's family starts acting.]
We'll use one of our chances.
[Finally, they start using their chances.]
[They acquired one chance ticket
during the first mission.]
[They acquired two chance tickets
during the second mission.]
[They have three chance tickets.]
Can I pick one?
[Three people can
attach the seeds first.]
[It's great!]
- Let me attach it.
- Me, too!
- Go ahead.
[The three men in the middle
will shoot out the seed.]
[The chance ticket is really useful.]
[From the beginning,
it's Jong Kook's turn.]
[Checks]
[Why look at me?]
Why are you doubting him?
[A perfectionist, Team Ye Ryun's Ace
is on the move!]
[The seed fell.]
Jong Kook!
[Trust makes way for treachery.]
[They blew out the chance ticket.]
[They have two tickets left.]
Good riddance!
[Wait and see, Grasshopper...]
Good luck!
[They start the acting.]
Please allow our marriage, Mother.
[Yo Won succeeds at attaching the seed.]
I'll never do that.
[The mother succeeds at it.]
No, I'll never allow it!
They look like a real family!
[Will they be able to turn the table?]
Take off your glasses.
- Where are the seeds?
- Stop swallowing them.
Stop eating it!
[Ready... set...]
[Blow]
[The seed is thrown.]
[I'm good at revenge.]
[Bring it on!]
[Team Ye Ryun's second attempt]
[They use another chance ticket.]
- Let me draw!
- Go ahead!
- This is your second ticket.
- Yes.
- Pick a good one!
- I will.
- Show us first.
- Read it loud.
[Dud]
[I'm a dead meat.]
[Mental breakdown]
Show them.
Come over here!
[Gloomy forebodings always prove true.]
Nephew!
[The other teams are happy.]
Your chance is blown like that.
[They start the acting.]
Succeeded!
[The second player is Mother.]
[Full of seeds]
She has five on her face!
[Playing jackstones on her face]
You do not match her in any way.
[Will Kkuk succeed this time?]
He did it.
[The fourth runner, the brother-in-law]
[Succeeded]
[It is my turn?]
[What's he doing?]
What are you doing?
[He puts lots of seed in his mouth]
Don't fail after drawing the dud!
[You're talking to a child!]
[Everyone is nervous.]
The world is a tough place!
- Gary did it!
- Succeeded!
[The only one left is
the child who drew a dud.]
[It landed on his lips.]
[Team Ye Ryun succeeds
at the third stage.]
Good job!
[Team Ye Ryun goes for the fourth stage.]
Let's go!
[What's this table for?]
[All kinds of household
items are on the table.]
[What do they need to
act for the fourth stage?]
After saying the line,
sweep and throw the items.
[The highlight of the angry scene,
sweep and throw!]
Pick one member
who will sweep the items.
And the ones with the basket
need to make the first one angry.
The first one will throw the items
and the two need to catch 10 items.
If the acting is good,
we'll reduce the number of the items.
- Please stand  behind the line.
- Try to slide toward us.
I think you still have feelings for me!
Why do you act this way?
This isn't like you!
- This isn't like me?
- Just leave me alone!
I just think you're ugly!
[Keep the anger and throw them!]
Let's catch them!
[Getting them in the face]
[They caught two items in total.]
It was too strong!
I can do better.
[Team Yerin's second attempt.]
Why do you treat me like this?
[Noisy]
What's going on?
[Team Ji Hyo passes the third stage.]
Let's go.
[Nervous]
You're always exercising!
Get them!
[They've chased us very close.]
[This time, we'll succeed!]
How is it possible to get ten?
[Team Ji Hyo's chance]
Say something to make him angry.
- Suk Jin, you can do it.
- I can do it.
But you've done nothing for me.
- You won't be able to do it!
- What did you say?
- Did you just call my names?
- Hey you!
Don't call me hey!
Did you just spit?
[The angry sweep!]
- How many do we need to catch?
- Two, four, six...
We have seven.
[Team Yo Won arrives at the stage, too.]
[If Team Yo won succeeds at this,
it'll be a great reverse.]
- You just put them into a pile?
- What's wrong with that?
What kind of house is this?
Why?
This is how we like it.
- Just let them.
- That's not going to help.
[How will it turn out?]
Can I use two hands?
- You're pathetic!
- What did you say?
Do you want me to punch you in the face?
- Do you want to end this race like this?
- What did you say?
- It's all your fault!
I did my best,
but you ruined it all!
[He's got plenty!]
[Thrown back!]
It all bounced back.
- Was the sweep too strong?
- It was.
[Team Yo Won caught two items.]
We'll use the chance ticket.
[They're using the last ticket.]
Place the line 10 centimeters closer.
- Isn't this good?
- It could be good.
[The possibility goes up.]
10 centimeters?
[Why do they have so little?]
PD, are these bunch of gift sets?
- Isn't this too much?
It's not a Christmas stocking!
They put these
inside the rubber gloves.
Are you going to let them do it?
- I see, I understand.
- Take them out.
I'll give these to you just like this.
[Team Ye Ryun's third attempt]
Start acting!
That's all you've got?
Throw it properly!
- I'll show you this time!
- Please show us!
One, two, three!
[We'll end this now.]
- You caught the rubber glove!
- It's empty.
Who took out all the stuff?
- Four items.
- Who did it?
- I did it!
- That's great!
[Kkuk's operation package fails.]
We'll use our chance ticket.
- Let's just use it.
- Draw it, Ji Hyo.
Maybe we'll get 50 centimeters closer.
We'll use our chance ticket now.
[Dud]
We can do it.
Make me angry!
Kwang Soo, that's all you can do?
Is that all you've got?
No, I've heard that too many times.
Everyone, please swear at me!
[Scream]
We can censor it with the beep sound!
Get lost!
Who said 'get lost?'
You're ugly!
Get lost and he's ugly.
I'm ready!
Throw it, you fool!
You're just a tall...
Why didn't you tell me?
- Tell you what?
- One, two, three!
[Team Ji Hyo fails at it again.]
[Team Yo Won uses their chance as well.]
[Though thy beginning was small]
[yet thy latter end should
greatly increase, hopefully.]
[Place the line 30 centimeters closer.]
[Will they be able to reverse the score?]
[Team Yo Won's second attempt]
I think they'll do it.
Get ready.
You just ruin everything!
We've been the last all along!
I think I would've been better by myself!
- What?
- What is he talking about?
We won because of me at first!
Let's just break up
after this game!
Let's break up!
We'll reduce two items for your acting.
Catch eight items.
- Eight items?
- One...
two, three!
[Amazing!]
[Here you go!]
It's a lot!
[This looks the best ever.]
One, two, three, four...
five, six, seven, eight,
nine, ten!
Eleven, twelve... eighteen!
- We did it!
- We reversed the score!
[Team Yo Won's been always the last.]
[Right until the third stage,
their team was left alone again.]
[But they've turned the table!]
[Will they be able to keep
the upturn until the end?]
Sangam-dong, Mapo-gu...
- That's where we started today.
- That's right.
Let's go!
We've won in the end.
I thought we would be the last place.
Ye Rin, did you see
how we played with your mom?
This is how we are.
That was great!
There's traffic.
It's okay to be in traffic but...
I need to go to the bathroom.
What have you done to her?
Why did you make her cry?
Why are you just standing there?
[This won't do.]
If the acting is good, we'll reduce
the number of the items.
I can't stand it any longer!
[Oh my god!]
Hit him harder!
[Powerful slap]
We'll reduce four items.
Just catch six items.
You need to sweep it slowly.
Let's not catch at the same spot.
Catch it from the left.
Ready!
One, two, three!
[It's basket full of items.]
- Great!
- We did it!
One, two, three...
four, five, six, seven
eight, nine, ten, eleven!
[Team Ye Ryun passes the fourth stage.]
But we didn't really need the acting.
We caught eleven items!
[Thank you for the citizen's cooperation!]
[Team Ye Ryun heads to the last stage.]
Prism Tower,
it's the same place from before.
For the ending scene,
is there another game?
It seems like there's
something at the end.
[This is a battle of speed.]
[Which team will arrive
at the final stage first?]
[The last casting call will be held]
[at the same place where
the production presentation was.]
[Team Yo Won gets there first.]
Let's run!
[They're heading to the third floor.]
What's this?
[The attack of the
group of desperate fans.]
[Behind the fans, there are group
of reporters waiting for them!]
[It feels nice to be welcomed!]
[But they need to get to
the third floor quickly.]
[While team Yo Won are trapped
in the fans and the reporters...]
I think we might have to
search for an item.
It's on the third floor, right?
[Team Ye Ryun arrives at the final site!]
Yo Won, hurry up!
[This is like a mad house!]
[They're approaching to the entrance.]
Please write the visitor's log.
[They need to get a permit
to enter the building.]
[They're almost out of their minds.]
Please say a word.
- Please leave a word for fans.
- I love you!
[They've got the permit.]
[She still looks elegant like a queen.]
[Team Yo Won enters the building.]
[Team Ye Ryun gets to the lobby.]
Are you running?
[Scream]
What should we do?
[The rush of fans and reporters]
I love you!
[Don't get too excited,
We mobilized them.]
I think there's a mission
that we quickly need to do.
[They arrive at the third floor.]
Read this script and do the acting.
Can I go to the bathroom first?
[In a daze]
We're in a hurry!
Jae Suk!
Give me a moment.
[While Jae Suk is having
the personal moment...]
[Team Ye Ryun goes through the lobby.]
[They get to the information desk.]
Are they here?
That's enough!
Hurry up and go!
What's this?
[There's a wedding set in the studio.]
Do what's in the script!
[That's right, the script!]
One person stand
in the middle of the arch.
After saying the line,
hold a pose like the picture.
[Huh?]
What's that?
[In the meantime, Team Ye Ryun
is finishing up the permit.]
- How are you doing, Gary?
- Doing great.
[Now Team Ye Ryun
is heading to the third floor.]
[Hurry up
before the other team comes!]
Let me stand in the middle.
Take this.
I think we can win when we do this.
Hurry up!
[Act the last scene and hold a pose!]
[Will they be able to finish acting
without getting interrupted?]
The studio on the third floor.
What would it be?
[Are we the first team?]
[Team Ji Hyo joins.]
What is it?
[He goes out the building.]
[Please let us love.]
[The bride and groom
enter the hall quickly.]
Do you promise to love each other,
so long as you both shall live?
Yes, I promise!
I now pronounce you, spouses for life.
[They only need to hold the pose.]
[Hurry up!]
Look, there are cameras everywhere.
It's weird.
There's got to be something.
What's this?
[Team Ji Hyo is still in puzzlement.]
[Scream]
[He shoots out a heart.]
[The gunfire of fans]
[Don't you forget
we need to do the mission!]
[Make a star with your hands.]
[If no one interrupts them...]
[Here we go!]
Success!
[Ha Ha, Lee Yo Won
and Yoo Jae Suk are cast!]
We did it!
We turned around the result!
[Wait, there's no one here.]
Let's go sit at the top.
[Before other teams get here...]
They said do what's in the script.
Hurry up!
[We must be the first team.]
[Relaxed]
- Is this correct?
- Success!
Okay!
Are we done?
We're the winners!
[It's time to finish up.]
Act like we just got here.
I was lost in the middle!
[Team Ye Ryun is hiding, too.]
- Isn't this right?
- Success!
[Team Ji Hyo just got here.]
We're the winners!
What's going on?
[The winners in illusions march.]
[What's going on?]
[What situation is this?]
We're the winners!
[We want to tell them...]
Therefore, today's winner is...
Lee Yo Won's team!
[What's going on?]
[Team Yo Won completes the mission
and the hidden camera!]
[Please explain to us...]
[Even the Queen is laughing.]
I walked out like this.
We did it twice.
Yeah!
Ye Rin, your mom won!
Give them the winning prize.
- What is that?
- Is that an actor's chair?
This is not a chair for actors.
- Isn't this fishing chair?
- I'm going to keep this name tag.
The name is stitched with golden thread.
[And a golden badge!]
The winning team is the blue team!
]Running Man's fifth
anniversary special, part one.]
[The Millionaire]
My third album sold
2 million and 80 thousand.
2 million and 30 thousand?
We've all sold more than a million...
[The high-class millionaires are coming!]
[A trip down memory lane
with the millionaires!]
[Singing along with the citizens!]
[Live connection with noraebang!]
[Hang out with the legend remotely!]
[Clon's DJ Koo]
[g.o.d.'s Park Jun Hyung]
[Turbo's Kim Jong Kook]
[Cool's Lee Jae Hun]
[DJ DOC's Lee Ha Neul]
[Kim Gun Mo]
[Next week, 'The Millionaire.']