Seo In U! Seo In U! Seo In U!
Gim Yeong Gwang,
this is your last chance.
What? My last chance?
I will give you two more months.
Coach.
I don't care what tricks you use...
you must hit the ball!
Use all your strength and hit the ball!
If you can't do it, I'll remove you
from the second string!
Understand?
What's the matter, coach?
It's me, I'm Gim Yeong Gwang!
In the Phoenix Cup, in the decisive ninth inning,
with two outs... the one who hit a home-run,
the glory hitter, Gim Yeong Gwang.
Have you forgotten?
Look here kid...
that was already 7 years ago.
You have to face reality.
Look at Seo In U!
He's the same age as you,
but he keeps on rising!
He's even more famous than you!
Don't mention Seo In U
in front of me.
Why?
Feeling aggrieved?
If you feel aggrieved,
just play better than him.
Really!
Really what?
Really... I'll do my best to play better.
So just give me another
chance this season.
I'm feeling really good this season, Coach.
Please believe me.
If you say that you feel good, that's good.
So in these 2 months,
your results will get better, right?
Are you holding your bat as a decoration?
What did you say?
If you don't know how to hit the ball,
then don't hold the bat.
If you're holding the bat,
then hit the ball.
Over three games,
you managed 15 strikeouts,
and your one base was on a bean ball.
(Bean ball - the pitcher intentionally
throws the baseball at the batter.)
Are you joking around here?
You? Are you here to fool around?
No, I rely on ability.
I'm not an idiot amateur like you.
You brat...
If you get beaten,
you won't feel pain right?
If you get cut,
do you even have money to live?
You brat!
Well done.
Good fight.
Why don't I see you fight so well
in the field? We'll win for sure.
I have no words to excuse my behavior.
Shut up!
I don't want to see you,
so go to the second string now.
And you're not allowed to participate
in the first string's matches.
Understand?
Strike two!
What is that brat doing?
Sleeping with his eyes open?
I, I'm Gim Yeong Gwang.
I'm someone who can do
what I set out to do.
Throw it! Come on throw it!
Throw it you brat!
I'll show it to everyone.
That I'm better than
that irritating Seo In U!
I'll show everyone!
Yeong Gwang!
Out!
Yeong Gwang! Yeong Gwang!
It hurts, why exactly did
I start playing baseball?
Do you know how to play baseball?
If you can't become famous like Lee Seung Yeop
or Pak Chan Ho, then stop playing.
I will give you two more months.
If you can't do it, I'll remove you
from the second string!
This rotten baseball...
Why did I start playing it?
You must become the home run king!
How can he do it?
Gim Yeong Gwang, fighting!
That's right...
Everything, started from that day...
After meeting her...
Yeong Gwang.
Why are you so sleepy?
Why? Had a nightmare?
Have we arrived yet?
We've arrived.
This is the president's villa.
Come on.
-=Summer, 17 years ago.=-
Follow me.
Come on!
You're Yeong Gwang, right?
Hello.
I'm Shin Dong primary school,
year 3 class 1's Gim Yeong Gwang.
Greeting with such energy, just like a man.
It's because I'm like my father.
That's true, your father must
be happy to have a son like you.
I'm not sure if bringing my son
is appropriate, Madam.
It's nice to have the children
be friends and play together.
It was good that you brought him.
Would you like to go in?
Jae In and the children are all in there.
Yeong Gwang, don't be a rascal.
Be good, understand?
Go inside.
I'm going to go pick up the President.
Okay, drive carefully.
Yes, Madam.
Yes, honey. Sorry, sorry.
I just finished right now.
Did all the guests arrive?
All right, I'm coming back now.
Something I'm forgetting? Ah...
Right, present.
I'll come at the speed of light.
I love you, honey.
Really! Today's supposed to be a BBQ party...
the heavens sure aren't helping.
Ah, sorry.
Really, sorry.
Hey, who are you?
Me? I'm Gim Yeong Gwang.
What? Gim Yeong Gwang?
What is your father's job?
Job?
Jae In's father is the President.
In U's father is the vice president.
My father is the managing director.
What is your father?
Oh... that.
He's a driver.
The driver who drives the President.
Car driver?
Maybe, you're Driver Gim's son?
Mmm, that's right.
Looks like you know my father.
What? What's the Driver's son doing here?
Why, the driver's son can't be here?
Of course you can't.
Why can't I be here?
Because you're the driver's son!
My father said,
that there will always be people
who don't know their place.
Just like you.
What?
At times like those, he said that you have
to quickly show him his place.
That's what my father said.
What did you say?
If you get beaten,
you won't feel pain right?
Then if you did that,
would it be okay, even if your father
got fired from the company?
What? This guy...
Don't fight. I've learned that fighting is bad.
My father said.
Who are you?
Hi, you're Gim Yeong Gwang, right?
I've heard a lot about you from Driver Gim.
Thank you for coming.
I was the one who invited him,
so please try to get along.
Really?
All right, we were going to play baseball
right now, so I'll let you join us.
Base... baseball?
Why? You can't play baseball?
What do you mean
I don't know how to play?
Where I'm from, I'm the home run king.
You don't even know
what you're talking about.
Really?
That's a relief. Then come on out.
I said it before, right?
For someone who doesn't know their place,
you have to show them their place quickly.
Ah, what to do?
Gim Yeong Gwang, are you okay?
Blood!
What are we going to do?
He got a nosebleed.
It's a bean ball. There's no other way.
Go walk out to first base.
No, I'm going to bat.
What?
I'm not going to take the walk.
I'm going to keep batting.
That's not how it goes in baseball.
If you get hit by the ball, you take a walk.
I'm not going to take the walk.
I'm going to keep batting!
Suit yourself!
Run!
What are you doing? Run!
Hurry! Run!
Hey, what are you doing,
catch the ball! Run! Run!
Run! Run!
Quick, pass, pass!
Run!
Quick!
Run! Run!
You won!
What are you saying?
Why is our company in the name list
of investigation for secret fund transfers?
In the last few months, we have
gathered many convincing evidence.
And in it, there's evidence
against your company.
The formal summoning letter
will be sent tomorrow morning.
Before that, if today is good, if you voluntarily
agree to support the investigation in court,
we will consider reducing your sentence.
I came personally to
help consult about that.
Prosecutor U, I need to know
what's happening to be able to assist.
I've never done any illegal transactions.
I don't even know how the
black money came about.
If that's the case, Mr. Il Gu, then your
friend should know about it.
Your partner, Seo Jae Myeong.
-=Vice President, Seo Jae Myeong=-
Ah, Il Gu.
Why are you in my office?
Aigoo, has it gotten this late, already?
(Aigoo - oh dear, oh my god)
At this rate, you will be late
for your daughter's birthday.
Ah, I bought her a stuff toy.
I wonder if she will like it.
I will give it to her later.
You're not going home right now?
Before that, there's a place I have to go to.
Let's go together.
Where are we going?
Prosecutor U came.
Said that she's investigating
about the black money.
When we started the company,
didn't we agree,
that there won't be any secrets regarding
the operations of the company?
You see, Il Gu.
I'll explain everything, but for now, let's go
somewhere so I can slowly go over every...
Making money is important, and the
company doing well is also important,
but we had to avoid those methods.
For the company's sake,
there was no other way.
Not for the company's sake, but it was
probably for your own selfish desires.
The manner in which you
shifted the company's money,
you can explain it at
the prosecutor's office.
You, what kind of deal did you
make with the prosecutor?
Using me as the scapegoat,
what kind of deal did you make?
For your own survival,
did you really sell me out?
I've already called Attorney Pak.
During the investigation,
he will be by your side.
This guy, how can you do this to me?
Saying I'm your only friend,
how could you do this to me?
Because you're my only friend,
that's why I made the best choice for you.
Don't you know?
Stop the car. Can you not hear me
telling you to stop the car?
This is your last chance.
I can only protect you if you go and
explain the situation voluntarily.
Understand?
Explaining that kind of thing,
why should I do it?
I won't go!
Do you want to see me
get caught that much?
Then let him come catch me directly.
I will not step into the prosecutor's office.
- Jae Myeong.
- Stop the car immediately.
- President...
- Stop the car! Stop the car! Stop the car!
- Damn brat.
- Vice President! Vice President!
Il Gu...
Il Gu, are you all right?
Vice President.
It's you?
The President is still inside?
Il Gu... Il Gu... this can't be... no!
Il Gu, no!
Madam, it looks like it's going to rain,
what should we do?
For now, let's bring everything inside.
Hello.
Yes, I'm Yun Il Gu's wife.
Does it hurt?
It's bearable.
That... actually...
Actually, I'm not a home-run king.
And I've never played baseball before, either.
Today is my first time hitting a home-run.
Wow, then you must be a genius!
Genius? Me?
Even though it was your first time,
you played so well...
so you must be a genius!
You, will you marry me?
In the future, when I actually become
the home-run king,
when that time comes,
will you marry me?
Jae In! Jae In...
Jae In, we have to hurry and
go see your father, come on.
Hey!  Hey!  Hey!
This...
My first home-run ball, I'll give it to you.
Hurry up and get in the car.
Mmm...
The question you asked me just now,
the answer is yes.
So in the future, you must become the
home-run king, understand?
Where's Yun Il Gu's family?
Right now, they should be on their way.
At the time of the accident,
you were all in the same car right?
How can such a thing happen?
Please explain how it happened.
Mom, look at this.
Please, honey.
Father said that you
should not bite your fingers.
Prosecutor, do you have to investigate
traffic accident cases as well?
Currently, Mr. Yun Il Gu is a important
witness in our investigation.
So of course we would have
to investigate this accident.
Would you please explain,
Mr. Seo Jae Myeong.
That? that...
It's my fault, Prosecutor.
The rain... the rain suddenly
came down so heavily.
I didn't think that the road
would be so slippery.
Mom.
Mom, I'm afraid.
We have to hurry to your father, Jae In.
Father is probably waiting for us.
Mom.
It is all right. We'll be able to
see father soon... understand?
Mom!
Jae In!
All of it...
Prosecutor, all this happened because of me.
Therefore,
please take me in.
Prosecutor, something big happened.
Careful... careful...
1, 2, 3.
Be careful.
Look around carefully!
It is hard to search because of the heavy rain.
Here! Here!
What is it?
There's a girl's shoe.
This was found in the car.
It's a pair.
Then, what exactly happened to her?
Could it be...
I've decided, Mom.
Decided on what?
I want to become a baseball player.
So please buy me some baseball equipment.
Son, do you know how much
baseball equipment's cost?
You think that sport is for everybody?
That's something only rich families can afford.
For a family like us,
we shouldn't even think about it.
Understand?
Mom, do you know how much
pay baseball players gets in a year?
And if I become the baseball king,
Mom will become very wealthy.
Little brat...
Do you even know what being
the home-run king means?
Of course, I know.
So, you can just take it as an
investment for the future.
Just let me do it, Mom.
Please, please?
Hey daugther-in-law! Come out!
What's happening?
Hurry and come out for a moment, hurry!
What is it?
What's the matter mother-in-law?
That, that, isn't that the daughter of the president?
=Earlier in the expressway,=
=came some very depressing news.=
=Reporter Ra Yeong Seok reports.=
=Today at around 7p.m.=
=After the wife of the president found out
about the accident involving the president,=
=on her way to Seoul, because of
the slippery conditions of the road=
=Resulted in a car accident=
=At that time, their 8-year-old
daughter was also in the car.=
- Blood pressure?
- 150.
Clear!
200!
200 again!
The situation... how is it?
We've done the emergency procedures.
But because the heart is not stable,
it's very dangerous.
It's still too early to tell.
What should we do now?
What are we going to do
about the company now?
Although we know that the vice president has
lost his best friend, and is not in the best of moods,
we still have to discuss about
the position of the president.
What's there to discuss about?
Of course, the vice president
should take over President Yun's position.
I'm going to the prosecutor's
office and tell them,
how you misused the company funds.
How did this happen?
President Yun died just like that,
and his wife is now in a coma.
Their only daughter is now missing
after having been washed away by the river.
How did a family get so
much misfortune in a day?
This is your last chance.
I can only protect you if you go and
explain the situation voluntarily.
I will not step into the prosecutor's office.
Stop the car!
Mom? Mom!
Mom!
Yes, I'm Seo Jae Myeong.
Yes, that's right.
What?
We're calling regarding the missing
people's report that was filed yesterday.
We discovered a child with similar
features on the road, crying.
Eat it.
- You have to eat it to see your parents again.
- But the kid is not talking.
She's not telling us her
name or her address.
I understand. I will send somebody
to confirm, immediately.
Please don't let anybody know
before it has been confirmed.
Yes.
You look tired.
What's the matter now?
You must make a trip to the
prosecutor's office tomorrow.
We plan to investigate both the black money issue
and the accident at the same time.
I really suspect whether
it's only the driver's fault.
I'll see you tomorrow.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Yun Il Gu is the company's President.
I only follow his instructions.
The dead can't talk, is it because of that?
So you will let your friend
take the blame for you?
Yes, that's right.
Yun Il Gu is my only friend.
And this company is just
like his other identity.
So, the least I can do is stay
and guard this company.
Now you even want to have your
friend's company for yourself?
Although it's a pity,
Il Gu's wife is still in a coma,
and his daughter, not only is she young
but is currently missing.
Right now, it's up to me
to be the protector.
Yun Il Gu is,
the husband of my favorite junior
and we have a very good relationship.
Do you think that I will stand aside
and see you take over the company?
When does the prosecutor of
the Republic of South Korea,
concern herself with the
operation of a company?
Listen, Mr. Seo Jae Myeong!
If there is anything else,
then please talk to my lawyer.
Goodbye.
Is there news about Yun Il Gu's daughter?
We're still looking.
We must find her no matter what.
Even if we have to drain the river.
It's me.
There is something you have
to help me confirm.
May I help you?
That, that is...
We heard you found the child, so...
She's over there.
Aigoo, Jae In!
Jae In? Jae In? It's ajussi!
(Ajussi - older man, uncle)
Are you hurt?
Jae In.
Aigoo, looks like she can recognize you.
She says she doesn't know
when we ask her name.
Whatever we ask her, she couldn't answer,
I was so worried.
Really fortunate,
that she found her father.
Don't bring her back.
What do you mean, Vice President?
Even if it's Il Gu's daughter,
don't bring her back.
Didn't you say that you would
like to open a restaurant?
I'll give you money to open one.
Vice President.
I heard that you have 3 children?
I will be responsible for the
future of those children.
How about it?
But that's not the way.
The heaven is watching.
Even the president who have passed
away will not forgive you, Vice President.
Then why did you do it that time?
Why did you help me in
front of the prosecutor?
First of all, I felt that I didn't
take good care of the president.
And you also saved
me from drowning.
Yes, it was me who pulled
you out of the water.
I saved your life.
And you helped me in front of the
prosecutor by giving false statement.
Don't you understand?
You're an accomplice.
Accomplice?
Yes, an accomplice.
We're in the same boat now.
Do you understand?
Vice President.
As long as you erase her name,
Yun Jae In, that name,
give her a new one.
Let her start over
where nobody knows her.
As long as you do those,
I'll make all that I
promised to you happen.
Mother-in-law, it's time to eat.
Okay.
Gyeong Ju, Jin Ju, Yeong Gwang, time to eat!
Come out quickly!
Oh, it looks delicious!
Close your book and eat.
Yeong Gwang, aren't you coming out?
That spoiled brat only knows
how to sleep everyday.
Yeong Gwang! Gim Yeong Gwang,
aren't you going to get up?
Where did that child go?
Excuse me. By any chance, have you seen my father?
Your father? Who is he?
He's Gim Il Bae.
I'm not really sure.
Sorry to disturb you.
Oh, it's you guys.
I was the one who played baseball
with you all in the villa last time.
It's me, Gim Yeong Gwang,
do you remember me?
What are you doing here?
I saw it on the news last night,
something bad happened to that child.
And I don't know what happened to her.
Have they found her?
Is that child okay?
No, she's dead.
What?
Heard them talking earlier,
seems like she drowned in the river.
Why? Are you sad?
The person that's always
on your side is gone. Pity, huh?
What a joke, a driver's son coming here.
What's wrong with being a driver's son?
What's wrong?
You still don't understand what's wrong?
No matter how hard you try,
you'll forever be beneath me.
Because your father
is beneath my father.
Stop it.
Just like a dog trying
to suck up to it's master.
Won't you stop it!
Humbling himself, bowing to us everyday.
That's your father.
I told you to stop it, you brat!
Who started it?
He hit me first, Father.
Yeong Gwang, you did it?
You hit the young master?
Vice President, I'm really sorry.
It's my fault I didn't educate
my son properly. I'm very sorry.
I didn't do anything wrong, Father.
So you don't have to
lower your head and apologize.
You brat, what's wrong with you today?
Father isn't a lap dog, right?
Not the type of person
who humbles himself, right?
You're our father, my father.
So, when you have not
done anything wrong,
then don't be like that!
I'm very sorry, Vice President.
Stretch out your hand.
As a man.
How can you be so impulsive, so frivolous?
Why did you make fun of that person
who can never become your opponent?
Making a fool of yourself.
I was wrong, Father.
Get out.
Drink the milk. You haven't eaten, have you?
Why did you come to the funeral?
I was worried about that child.
The child I saw that day in the villa.
That child is not really dead, right?
Right, Father?
If only she can return safely.
Ajussi!
As long as you erase her name,
Yun Jae In, that name,
give her a new one.
Let her start over
where nobody knows her.
Ajussi.
Your name is Yun Jae In.
Understand?
What's your name?
Yun Jae In.
It's Yun Jae In.
Yes, that's your name.
Don't ever... ever forget your name.
Do you understand?
I'm... I'm really sorry, Jae In.
I'm a criminal.
I'm really sorry.
Yeong Gwang.
Yes?
You absolutely mustn't live like your father.
Understand?
Father.
When you grow up, you must become
an outstanding person.
Don't become a useless person like me.
You must become an outstanding person.
Do you understand?
I declare,
I will replace my one
and only friend, Yun Il Gu,
and his family,
as Geodae's President.
I will,
serve.
Her daughter?
Still no news?
My name is Yun Jae In.
Quickly get off the car.
Please hold the umbrella properly, ajussi.
Sorry, go on in.
I want to,
defeat you.
Seo In U you,
I will defeat you.
Remember this.
I said that at that time.
It seems like I really believed
that childish talk.
Using the will and
determination of the poor.
With all my strength, to defeat that guy.
But the reality is,
I've never defeated that fellow once.
No, it's impossible to win.
Kick, kick.
Run, run!
What type of old-school training method is this?
It's already the 21st century.
How will I be able to beat that Seo In U?
Stop talking nonsense and run!
You've worked hard.
Hey, Gim Yeong Gwang.
You've lost again?
Why can't you even last a
week in the first string, kid?
What are your views on the competition?
Do you have anything to say?
Please say something?
I will give you two more months.
If you can't do it,
I'll remove you from the second string!
The poor, only relying on desire,
in the end, will never be able to defeat the rich.
But to understand this truth,
it took me 17 years.
Yeong Gwang. Carefully, carefully!
Gently, gently!
Lightly, please be more gentle.
Lightly, lightly.
Yeong Gwang, wake up, wake up.
Wake up, wake up.
Lightly, lightly.
All right, thanks, thanks.
Yeong Gwang.
Yeong Gwang, wake up.
Nurse, nurse!
This person's life is in danger,
please take a look.
Please wait for a moment, there's an
emergency patient who arrived first.
That person is urgent, what about him?
The baseball player Seo In U
has been injured.
In U?
Yes.
Is it?
I need the person in charge to sign first.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yeong Gwang, you wait here for a moment.
I'll go and take a look at him first.
In U... how seriously is he hurt?
Who? Is someone there?
Only liking a person like Seo In U.
Let go!
This dirty world.
Is anyone out there?
Nobody cares about a no name
second stringer like me.
This despicable world.
In this despicable and dirty world,
a person suddenly grabbed hold of me.
You're him, right? Player Gim Yeong Gwang?
Team Dragons, player number 47,
in the Phoenix Cup,
hitting the win,
that glory hitter, Gim Yeong Gwang, right?
You know me?
Omo! Looks like I'm right!
(Omo - oh my)
Hello, I'm your fan.
Fan?
Right.
Actually, after that match,
I became your fan.
Who are you?
Me? I'm Yun Jae In.
Jae In?
Yes, Yun Jae In.
At the worse possible moment of my life,
right at this moment,
the person who grab hold of me,
is you,
Yun Jae In.
-=Next Episode Preview=-
This key,
will grant you three wishes.
Shouldn't be about him right?
Are you here to plead to me
about Yeong Gwang?
The patient using the VIP room,
his manner is like crap.
Crap?
Gim Yeong Gwang,
you plan to destroy your life?
What are you doing?
It couldn't be, could it? Yun Jae In.
What are you doing over there?
The ribs are broken.
A total of four ribs.
This is all your fault!
Why are you constantly
destroying my life?
Just what are you?
Your fan.
President Yun Il Gu's daughter.
Return the things that should
belong to her, President.