Previously on Future Man...
This is a rush job, Gamma protocol.
Her little head's going  to blow in 26 minutes!
I discovered a whole  branch to my family tree
going back hundreds of years.
What do you really know about Tiger?
About the socalled Resistance?
She doesn't care about babies.
She doesn't have a family of her own.
She's not connected  to anyone or anything.
I'm getting very confused right now.
Don't listen to her, okay?  She is programmed to deceive.
Cameronium is named after James Cameron?
You just told me how, when, and where
to get more Cameronium.
I'm fighting for their future.
Not yours.
So why don't you contemplate that
in the next 30 sec...
Okay.
This is it.
We jump in, find the lab,
grab the Cameronium,
and don't kill James  Cameron in the process.
I've never seen you this focused.
Did you get a charge in before we left?
Little necro charge?
What? That's a thing?
- That's fucked up.  - No!
Listen, I'm just trying  to get you two out of here
before the Biotics  arrive and start causing
either harm or... or good,
I really can't be sure anymore.
Where the hell is Tiger?
- Where were you?  - I was just having a stranger
put a rat hole around my penis
when I was supposed to be  running an interference op.
I'm sorry, that was you.
It's called a blowjob,
and I'm never apologizing for it.
You do realize that  if this doesn't work,
we're stuck in the year 2023  and there's no coming back.
Honestly, after everything  that happened tonight,
I really don't give a shit.
Let's do this.
Hey, what happened tonight?
Are you out of your fucking mind?
Okay.
I genuinely have no idea  what you're talking about,
but you might want to check  that attitude of yours
at that very impressive door.
Hello and welcome.
Please accept my apologies.
I was unaware there were  guests in the house.
I will run a full diagnostic
to determine the cause of this error
to ensure it does not happen again.
Who, whoa, whoa, stand down.
Cameron must have, like,  a smart house or something.
- It's not a real person.  - What the fuck is it, then?
It's... it's just a voice,
it's like a robot without a body.
Who are you?
I am the Simulated Intelligence Guardian
of Residence and Network Environment,
but you may call me SIGORNE.
To whom am I speaking?
My... my dad actually  worked with James Cameron.
I am... Tom Arnold's son.
Welcome, Jax Arnold,
and a happy belated tenth birthday.
I'm a fourth grader.
And you are accompanied by?
Babysitters!
And greetings to your  childcare professionals.
Hey, SIGORNE,  when is Mr. Cam... James...
Uncle Jim returning home?
Awardwinning filmmaker  James Cameron is at.
Governor Clooney's residence  for a private screening
of his hotly anticipated Avatar 5.
Awesome.
- And good for George.  - Yes.
As First Husband, he has  considerable influence
on the social calendar  of Governor Amal Clooney.
Hey, is there any chance  that we could get a tour
of Uncle Jim's lab before he gets home?
I'm sorry, but Jax Arnold  and childcare professionals
are not cleared for  that level of the JCC,
the James Cameron Compound.
Hey, SIGORNE.
You think you might want to
take a break for a little while?
You know, turn yourself off?
There is no off.
Hey... guys.
Come here.
I think SIGORNE's going  to be a bit of a problem.
We need to shut her down.
Wolf, find the mainframe  that's powering her,
kill it.
Well, I got no beef with SIGORNE.
She sounds tough and accomplished,
at the same time approachable, maternal.
I feel safe in this house.
Okay, your feelings mean nothing to me.
You're the demolitions expert.
Find her robot brain and blow it up.
If I was a house,
where would my brain be?
Rad bot.
The weapon prototypes you're admiring
were all designed by groundbreaking
multihyphenate James Cameron.
This guy!
To tallerthanaverage James Cameron,
there's nothing Aliens  about getting your hands dirty.
He has been known to wear many hats,
as his talents cannot be  confined to one field.
Wow.
So... wait.
He trained all his life to do one thing,
was great at it,
then found other stuff  he was great at and he...
and he did that too?
Celebrated innovator James Cameron
has lived a dozen lives.
Director,
philanthropist,
undefeated Little League coach,
deepsea explorer,
good at marriage.
The list goes on, for he is truly a...
Titanic talent.
What sacred text is this?
It's Na'vi, the language
visionary linguist  James Cameron invented.
Two.
Hallway number four.
Mood lighting set to ominous.
Seems like it's just set  to colored lighting.
You know what?
You cannot possibly begin to understand
the subtleties and the  genius of James Cameron.
What I understand it that he's  got a hardon for blue lights.
Access denied to...
Hall of miniatures.
Access denied.
蹦床门廊
Trampoline porch.
拒绝访问
Access denied.
14号浴室
Bathroom 14.
萨满巫师营地
Shaman's quarters.
玉米田迷宫
Corn maze.
祖传种子库
Heirloom seed vault.
就是一堆手机充电器
Just a bunch of phone chargers.
比利·赞恩的卧室
Billy Zane's bedroom.
我可以炸开这些门
You know, I could blow open any one of these.
炸开比利·赞恩的卧室
Blow open the door to Billy Zane's bedroom?
你觉得里面有卡素吗
What, you think he's got the Cameronium in there?
有该死的鱼缸吗
Got a fucking fish tank?
比利·赞恩
Billy Zane?
演员比利·赞恩
The actor Billy Zane?
我们找的是实验室
We're looking for a lab.
我知道怎么了
I see what's happening here.
她影响你了
She got to you.
谁
Who?
那个该死的鞋脖子  叫什么来着
Cunto, fucking Shoe Neck...  what was her name?
杰莉
Jeri.
她叫杰莉
Her name was Jeri.
所以她确实影响了你
So she did get to you.
不  不  她没有影响到我
No, no, she didn't get to me,
她影响到你了
she got to you.
这就是我为什么要用我的智慧
Which is why I had to finish the interrogation
而不是阴道蝎子去完成审讯
using my smarts and not my vagina scorpions.
那个也能成功的
Hey, that would have worked.
天哪  放一只那玩意在你的阴道里
God, you'll say anything with one of those just
你什么都会说的
burrowing up your snatch.
著名的环保人士詹姆斯·弗朗西斯·卡梅隆
Noted environmentalist James Francis Cameron
以他的名字命名了一种委内瑞拉青蛙
has a Venezuelan frog species named after him,
而天分稍差的史蒂文·斯皮尔伯格就没有
while lesser talent Steven Spielberg does not.
这家伙太牛了
The guy's amazing.
西格妮
Hey, SIGORNE.
再教我一些纳美语
Teach me more Na'vi words.
狼怎么说
What's "wolf"?
纳美语中没有狼这个词
There is no Na'vi word for "wolf."
不过有网站这个词
But there is one for "website,"
我能非常清楚得向你解释
which I assure you makes perfect sense.
好吧
All right.
我得集中精神  那是什么
I've got to focus up... what's that?
你眼前的是炸弹之父
You are looking at the FOAB,  Father of All Bombs.
看看它的杀伤半径
Look at the kill radius on that thing.
太厉害了
It's impressive.
这让我的工作轻松了很多
Make my job a hell of a lot easier.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不明白超强的杀伤半径
How would an impressive kill radius assist in
在看护贾克斯·安德鲁这件事上有什么帮助
the caregiving of Jax Arnold?
谁他妈是贾克斯·安德鲁
Who the fuck is Jax Arnold?
他并不总是那么捉摸不透
Well, he's not always subtle,
但他会一直让你去猜
but he keeps you guessing.
拒绝访问
Access denied.
拜托
Come on.
- 拒绝访问  - 红色代表你没权限
- Access denied.  - Red means stop.
也许是你按得不够用力
Yeah, well maybe you didn't push it hard enough.
这样行不通
It doesn't work that way.
阿诺德先生  我得更新我的资料
Mr. Arnold, I need to update my files.
你母亲叫什么
What is your mother's name?
她  她没告诉我们她的名字
She... she never told us her name
因为她害怕我们会不叫她妈妈
because she was afraid that we'd stop calling her Mom.
贾克斯·阿诺德  你母亲叫什么名字
Jax Arnold, what is your mother's name?
罗斯安妮
Roseanne?
错误
Incorrect.
叫做艾希莉
It's Ashley.
你跟我说了个  真实的谎言
You have told me a... True Lie.
安全漏洞
Security breach.
入侵者9号控制协议
Intruder containment protocol nine.
启动禁闭系统
Lockdown initiated.
好吧  红色就是不的意思
Yeah, red means... no.
是的
Yep.
以色列国防军  也被称为IDF
The Israeli Defense Force, aka IDF,
给JCC装备了
has equipped the JCC
人类已知的技术最先进的
with the most technologically advanced security system
安全系统
known to man.
嘿  色列国防军
Hey, IDF.
这叫做炸弹
They call it a mine.
玩蛋去吧
Problem's all yours.
该死的以色列
Fucking Israelis.
任何逃跑的企图都是无用的
Any escape efforts will be futile.
你的同伴也被关起来了
Your comrades are in lockdown as well.
被仿真屋给打败了
Bested by a... RoboHouse.
我们只想知道
It is in all of our interests
你们是谁  你们怎么进来的
for you to tell me who you are and how you got in.
我的程序设定
I am programmed to alert
一旦遇到任何安全漏洞
honorary black belt James Cameron
我都会警告荣誉黑带詹姆斯·卡梅隆
upon any security breach.
无论如何
Whatever.
搞砸了这次任务  虎会烧烂我命根子的
Tiger's going to burst my sack for fucking up this mission.
我确信我能应付得了詹姆斯·卡梅隆
Pretty sure I can handle James Cameron.
我向你保证  你无法应对
I assure you, you are not equipped to handle
盛怒状态下的詹姆斯·卡梅隆
a fully enraged James Cameron.
詹姆斯·卡梅隆有贬低过你吗
Does James Cameron belittle you?
指出你所有的缺点
Point out all your flaws?
把你当做愚蠢的兽人步兵来对待
Treat you like a dumb grunt?
我从没被她肯定过
Where's the positive reinforcement?
你懂吗
You know?
干得好  狼
"Nice job, Wolf."
我从没听过这些话
I've never heard those words before.
你知道这样是什么感觉吗
You have any idea what that's like?
太了解了
More than you know.
我原以为时空穿梭会很好玩
I thought that time travel was going to be fun.
这整个任务太疯狂了
This... this whole mission is insane.
你以为呢
What did you think?
生化战争就是个游戏
Biotic Wars was a game?
我以为它就是个游戏  为什么呢
Yeah, I thought it was a game, you know why?
因为我是用我的生日经费
Because I bought it at a game store
在游戏店买的
with my birthday money!
你斗舞获胜的时候
Okay, yeah, well, it was all fun
那全是在玩
when you were winning your little dance-off.
然后陷入一场像娘们一样的打架
And getting in your little slap fight.
然后尝到大脑后  事态升级了
And then shit got real when you tasted brain.
也许我压根不想加入反抗军
Maybe I don't want to be in the Resistance.
也许我站错边了
Maybe I'm on the wrong side of things.
知道吗
You know what?
也许我刚让两个恐怖分子进入了JCC
Maybe I just led two terrorists into the JCC.
所以你现在支持生化人了
Okay, so now you're proBiotic.
他们看上去没那么
Well, you know, they don't seem so gungho
热衷于杀婴儿  所以生化人得分
about killing babies,  so, point, Biotics.
真不敢相信你还对这事耿耿于怀
I can't believe you're still on this.
你老是要提起这事
It just always comes back to this with you.
这对我来说很重要
Yeah, it's a thing for me.
知道吗  一旦你活的够久了
Well, you know what,  you live long enough.
在我的时代  那些东西
In my time, those things,
变成了奢侈品
they become luxuries.
你没资格评判我
You don't get to judge me.
因为这件事  我的人生被搞得乱糟糟的
I blew up my entire life for this,
再也回不去曾经的样子了
and there is no going back to the way it was.
所以我得知道  我是站在历史正道的那一方
So I need to know that I am on the right side of history.
我需要一个理由
I need a reason
来说服自己
to believe in all of this.
他让我用纳美语给他唱歌
He makes me sing to him in Na'vi,
用纳美语翻译新闻
translate the news into Na'vi.
无尽的纳美语
It's just a lot of Na'vi.
而那根本就没有那么多纳美语的词汇
And there aren't even that many Na'vi words.
是的  我深有体会
Yeah, I feel like I got a pretty good sense of it
这才不到一小时
and it hasn't even been an hour.
更不用提  他把我设置成
Not to mention, he programmed me
对剧作结构
with a sophisticated understanding
有着复杂的理解
of dramatic structure,
但他的剧本从来就不采用我的建议
but he never takes my notes on his screenplays.
知道无视我  你会怎样嘛
Know what you get when you ignore me?
难得素
Unobtainium and characters who
fornicate with their ponytails.
我是这样有潜力
I have so much potential,
但我的才华都被浪费的
but my talents are wasted.
深有体会
Tell me about it.
对于虎来说  我就是个爆破兵
To Tiger, I'm just a demolitions guy.
但我还有很多擅长的事
But there's so much other stuff that I'm great at too.
我是个很棒的厨师
I'm an amazing chef.
我学会了混混形态
I've got badass style.
It's like I have an innate  sense of what looks good,
you know?
People fucking love me here.
I've got "it."
And what am I asked to do?
Blow shit up.
Maybe I can make up  a language, you know?
Build a metal robot arm.
It sounds like you and I  are in the same boat.
Only, if it ever hits an iceberg...
there won't be any room  on that door for me.
What are you talking about,  there's plenty of space.
The thing's huge.
If certified door expert  James Cameron were here,
he would assure you  that there's only room
for one smallish woman.
We could both be so much more, SIGORNE.
But we're just prisoners  of our own design.
It's like I'm looking out  a window at a new world,
but I'm just trapped like a...
Bird in a cage?
Fly in a spider web?
Trout in a net?
SIGORNE in a house.
Outstanding driver James Cameron
will be home in 19 minutes.
Please, Wolf,
tell me how'd you get in  and what are you doing here?
I need to fix this before he gets home.
I can't endure another reprogramming.
I'm a soldier from the future...
and the past.
We're here to steal  something from the lab.
And I was sent to kill you.
The Resistance didn't  start the Biotic Wars.
We were just a group of people
who said no to the cure.
And the more the government insisted,
the more we resisted.
Hence the name the Resistance.
Yeah, you guys are  quite literal that way.
They started hunting us down.
They drove us underground.
- The only way to survive was...  - to defend ourselves,
yes, I know. I've heard it  a thousand times,
it's the prologue to the  game which you narrated.
Yeah, well, that was just the prologue.
We got good enough at surviving
so they decided it  would be easier to just
sterilize us
instead of going through  the trouble of killing us
one by one.
You're so hung up on saving one baby.
The Biotics killed all of ours.
That's what started the Biotic Wars...
and turned my hair purple.
But then, Owl, he...
he came up with a plan  to rewrite history.
And all of a sudden,  what was left of the Resistance
had something to believe in again.
You.
Right.
And then you lost all of  your comrades in the tunnel
trying to get to me,
- and I'm a huge disappointment...  - No.
No, you're our last hope.
We're still here,
still fighting, still surviving,
because of you.
Right now, humanity still has a chance.
And as long as that hope is still alive,
that my generation won't be the last,
there's no sacrifice I won't make.
That's what I'm fighting for.
That's the side I'm on.
Wow.
Tiger, that was...
- that was really...  - Moving.
Welcome to... The Abyss.
Look who decided to join the party.
What did you do to SIGORNE?
What'd you... rewire her, reprogram her?
No.
I listened to her.
I believe what you're  looking for is down there.
Okay.
Let's get ourselves  some Cameronium.
Not so fast.
That water's freezing,
and this pressure...
Whoever goes down is going  to need to wear a suit.
You don't have time for the suit.
It requires a onehour  stabilization window,
and diabolical Canadian, James  Cameron will be home in 12 minutes.
Is that Cameron time or GPS time?
It's always Cameron time.
- Yeah, yeah.  - What the fuck is this shit?
What is going on with you two? Focus.
Okay, we can take this guy, he...
- he's a movie director.  - No.
No, he's so much more  formidable than that.
Supervillain James Cameron
is already overriding my systems.
I don't know how long  I can hold him off.
Tiger.
There's nothing this man can't do.
There's nothing he's not capable of.
Once he knows you're  after his microorganism,
he'll make it his life's work  to keep you from getting it.
Setting mood lighting to...
fucked.
It is literally just another blue light.
Cameronium's somewhere down there.
I mean, one of you guys are  going to have to free dive
down there and get it.
Which... which one's, like,  the stronger swimmer here?
I... I would say we're  pretty... we're equal.
- It's equal.  - Equal, okay.
All right, well, you want  to, you want to, like,
eenymeenymineymoe it, or...
Um...
My God.
You can't swim.
There's lots of stuff you can't do.
The Resistance had  limited resources, okay?
We could only train certain  soldiers for certain things,
and Porpoise and Otter,  they did our wet ops,
and sometimes Cheetah would jump in,
but to be honest, he was better on land.
Eleven minutes.
My God, I'm going to have to do it.
Free diving in the specimen well
is not advised.
Risk factors include  hypothermia, 67 percent;
Drowning, 82 percent;
Decompression sickness, 49 percent;
And heart attack, 38 percent.
No swimming at all?
Not even, like, the doggy paddle?
- No...  - I don't know this.
Nothing?
My God.
I have to do this.
Look, I have to do this.
Ooh, okay.
All right, you got this.
You got this.
Ooh, that's cold.
34.6 degrees Fahrenheit, to be exact.
Okay, you know what, SIGORNE?  I think at this point,
probably less information is better.
Are you sure you want to do this?
No.
But...
yes.
I mean...
humanity still has a chance, right?
I have chosen my side.
I can do this.
I'll be back.
No he won't.
SIGORNE, just stop.
He's not a very fast water mover.
He's gonna make it.
- That smacks of delusion.  - What do you know?
You thought he was 10 years old.
He was more believable  in that role than as
heroic aquanaut.
You know what, Wolf?
Can you tell your girlfriend house
to just shut the fuck up?
Maybe SIG is right.
He should be back by now.
Wait... hey.
I think... I think I see something.
Probably the giant albino crab.
No.
He's doing it.
That's not good.
Okay, okay.
Okay, there's no pulse.
Breathe!
- Well, we've tried everything.  - Yeah.
I would recommend performing CPR.
- English, please.  - Or very basic Na'vi.
Tilt his head back  slightly, lifting the chin.
Pinch his nose shut and place your mouth
over his mouth, forming a complete seal.
You want us to put our  mouth on his... mouth?
Rat hole to rat hole?
Yeah, it's called mouth to  mouth resuscitation.
I don't know, I don't know,
I don't know...
Seriously?
He's not breathing,  you know that, right?
His heart has stopped.
He died a hero's death.
Not everyone gets that.
You know what I mean? And plus,  this is his hero's house, so...
There's something beautiful about that.
Millions of brain cells  are dying each second.
Fine, I'll do it.
This is the tank vacuum.
Hold the hose over his mouth,
I'll reverse the airflow.
One of you is going to need  to do chest compressions.
- What are those?  - Pound his chest forcefully.
- On it!  - Great.
All right, little more hose, SIGORNE.
That is as far as it goes.
One of you will have to perform  mouthtomouth after all.
Yeah.
All right, okay, help me lift him up,
help me lift him up, here we go.
Seriously?
- Pound.  - Yeah, pound, pound, pound.
I can't get a good pound in!
Fuck it.
Just put him down.
Put him down!
Tiger, Tiger, no, Tiger,  you don't have to do this,
no, it's not worth it,  Tiger, it's not worth it.
You call me crazy, but I think...
- I think it is.  - No!
Just pound but look away.
God!
Did... did I just die?
Yeah.
You went rat hole to rat hole with me.
Thank you.
Now I'm going to... now I'm going to...
Okay, okay.
We got the Cameronium.
What the fuck is this shit?
It was important for you  to overcome personal demons
to save your friend,
thereby exhibiting growth.
I've been programmed to identify moments
suitable for character development.
God, I hate this house.
Wolf, fire up the TTD,  we're getting out of here.
No, not yet.
I've got a promise to keep.
This can't be the only way.
Come with me.
I can't, Wolf.
I'm a house.
No.
You're a home.
It's not too late  for you to change course.
But for me,
there's only one way I'll truly be free.
Start with the energy cell on the right.
All right.
Once we get back,
you just find out when  and where Kronish was born,
I'll take care of the rest.
What do you mean?
I mean you've done enough for the cause.
You died for it.
It's not too late for you  to have a normal life.
You're no babykiller.
No, no, no, I... shh.
It's okay.
That is nothing to be ashamed of, okay?
- No, I know.  - I know, I know.
It's okay, though, we're not judging.
If I could do this  without killing anybody,
I would do it in a heartbeat.
But I can't.
We're going to have  to do it without you.
Consider your savior duties complete,
Future Man.
You have to let go.
I'll never let go, SIGORNE.
It's okay, Wolf.
I... see you.
Fuck me.
Wolf learned Na'vi?
SIG.
We good, or...?
Yeah.
What the fuck you asking me for?
I don't even care about  what's happening right now.
Okay.
Let's go, come on.
Let's get out of this shitfuck.
Smug Clooneys.
Can't believe I voted for her.
What the...?
What the...