Well, just get your lawyer to keep me up-to-date.
Mm-hm.
I’m away for the weekend.
And you want me here?
T o keep an eye on the place, yes. Just stay away from the bar.
But I’ll have my mobile on me if you need anything.
I’ve asked them all to watch me.
You'll be alright.
What did she say?
She said if I get charged, we'll worry about it then but...
...there's no reason to jump the gun.
Oh, good!
Otherwise, we'd all have to go on strike.
OK, who's for a drink?
My little family?
-Um, let's not drink. -Oh, bullshit.
Come on -you're not going into a convent or anything.
You're gonna be here with us, in the real world.
Mmm.
Nat!
So we're off, then.
lntroduction?
T his is Bernie. T he girls.
-And you know Sean. -Hi, Bernie.
I don't think I’ll be here when you get back, Nat, so goodbye.
Goodbye.
Anybody else leaving that I should know about?
Well, we might need a few extra girls just in case -
maybe a dominatrix.
-Anyone in mind? -Possibly.
Hey, Bernie?
Um... good luck.
-Right. -Let's go, then.