(The third participant is...)
(Jee Seok Jin.)
My time has finally come.
I'm going crazy because I have so many things I want to do.
I want to put all of them in prison...
and be the king in there.
I want to have an event for my loving wife.
I'd like to challenge myself to something I couldn't do before.
Please do one of these three. I won't complain.
(Forget the past Seok Jin. It is a revenge he waited for 7 years.)
(If I'm unhappy, it'll be solitary confinement.)
(Abusing his authority will bring a terrible result.)
(He's had it for the past 7 years. He will get his revenge.)
(His counterattack is about to unfold.)
(A wedding town in Yeoju, Gyeonggi-do)
(Warm sunshine welcomes them to a forthcoming blessing.)
- It's warm. It's getting warmer. - It's sunny.
I guess this week's episode is about you.
- I think so. - Then please come to the center.
- Everyone can guess that. - Yes, it's obvious.
I assumed everyone's wearing a tuxedo.
- I'm the only one. - Seok Jin.
- Who wears pants like those? - This is...
- Look at his hands. - Seok Jin.
- It's cold. - You should've taken care of them.
The third participant of Member's Week is...
- Is it me? - It's Jee Seok Jin.
It looks like I'm getting married. It's obvious.
He's the third participant of Member's Week.
He's known as the dedicated husband in Running Man.
- Why is that? - I'm very devoted and loving.
Is it because of the lie detector?
He said he would remarry...
- his wife in his next life. - I am very dedicated.
I remember now.
"Will you marry your wife in your next life?"
(He nodded without giving a lot of thought.)
(He told the truth.)
(The title of the dedicated husband went to the wrong person.)
I am truly in love with my wife.
The evidence for it was broadcasted on a nationwide scale.
That's how I earned new nicknames such as The Devoted or The Loving.
We got married when she was quite young.
I haven't done any romantic events for her.
If I have the opportunity, it would be nice to do one.
He's a sunflower.
For Seok Jin who only cares about his wife,
we've prepared Seok Jin's vow renewal ceremony.
- Please enter the wedding hall... - Are you serious?
- where the bride is waiting. - Really?
- Your wife is here? - We could've come together.
- She said, "Have a good day." - This will be so touching.
- What is this? - Will I host the ceremony?
Of course, you will.
- I set you up with her. - Yes, you should host the ceremony.
(Thanks to an unexpected event, everyone is excited.)
(Just like the day 19 years ago, among the lights that bless them, )
(Seok Jin's beautiful wife stands before them.)
Congratulations, Seok Jin.
- What is this? - This is a wedding hall.
His wife will be here?
(Looking like she did 19 years ago, she waits for her husband.)
- His wife will be here? - Is it really her?
- Seok Jin. Mrs. Jee. - Are you really here, Honey?
(Honey, what are you doing there?)
- Is she really here? - Is that you, Mrs. Jee?
- Is it her? - It's not you, right?
- Is that you? - I don't think it's her.
- Who is it? - Is that you?
- I don't think it's her. - It's not her?
Is that her?
(Thank you for the past 19 years. I'll take better care of you.)
- Is that her? - Hey.
(What's going on?)
- It's Lee Seul. - What?
It's Lee Seul?
Hey, you.
- Are you kidding? - You do all sorts of things now.
- What's wrong with you? - You do all kinds of things.
- Are you my wife for the day? - You are so brazen.
- You look like my youngest sister. - Hey, you.
(What? Are they police officers?)
- What's going on? - What is this?
- My goodness. What's going on? - Why are they here?
(The police officers are on the move.)
- Why are they coming to us? - What is it?
- Come on. What is it? - What's going on?
- This always happens. - Come on.
- We did something wrong again. - What are you doing?
- What did we do wrong? - Why are you doing this?
What did we do? Hold on.
What's the matter? Lee Seul!
- Kwang Soo. - Lee Seul.
- What's happening? - We're at a wedding hall.
- Be careful. - What is it?
I thought they were going to renew their vows!
Where are we going?
- Why are you doing this? - Hold on.
This is ridiculous. Come on.
(Their arrest warrants have been issued out of the blue.)
(Where are we going?)
- My goodness. - Where are we headed?
Where are we going? Seok Jin. Where are we going?
- That's what I want to ask, too. - I really don't know.
Hey, someone's taking me somewhere.
- This is so scary. - First, let Ji Hyo...
- I'm going, too? - Let go of me. Let go!
After the opening segment, I've been dragged around all day long.
(Where is this place?)
(It's Seok Jin's Prison, the shrine for criminals from variety shows.)
(It's a correction center that has strict management and control.)
(One rule of Seok Jin's Prison is not to ask and not to talk back.)
(Will they be able to escape from this suffocating prison?)
Now, you can take your blindfolds off.
- What is it? Where are we? - My goodness.
(The prisoners get to see some light after an hour.)
- What is it? - This is a prison.
- We are in prison. - My gosh.
- Seok Jin's Prison. - It says "Seok Jin's Prison".
- "Seok Jin's Prison"? - What is this?
"The boss' word is the law." Are you the boss?
Seok Jin, the participant...
of this week's episode, wanted everything in here.
- He wanted this? - Yes, I did. However,
- this is not... - What's wrong with you?
I only said that I wanted to put all of you in prison.
I thought about it and I have something.
I spent more time in prison than I did outside.
I want them to experience how painful it feels to be in prison.
I want to put all of them in prison...
and be the king in there.
(He will humiliate the rest of them in his hometown.)
- I told them to put you in prison. - Seok Jin.
Then why did you wear a tuxedo?
- Why did you put me in, too? - Goodness.
- Why did we go to the wedding hall? - Yes, why did we?
- Why am I here? - Seok Jin.
Your wife wanted you here.
Is that what happened?
Why am I here?
Your sentence in this prison is six hours.
You will follow the schedule which has been already made for you.
Seok Jin is the boss of this prison.
I am the boss?
He has the absolute authority.
He can send whoever offends him and causes...
chaos in the prison to solitary confinement.
- My time has finally come. - This is too cruel.
Is it scary to be in solitary confinement?
For your information, solitary confinement will be beyond...
your imagination. Whatever you imagine, it'll be worse.
(Solitary confinement is a mysterious and unpredictable place.)
Whatever you imagine, it'll be worse.
(Solitary confinement is...)
(the deepest and the dreariest place in prison.)
(Solitary confinement is the darkest place in Seok Jin's Prison.)
- Behave. I'm the boss today. - Seok Jin's the boss.
- We'd better listen to him. - You'd better.
You. Don't make eye contact with me.
- You. - Don't look him in the eye.
Don't look at me like that.
(He seizes the chance and stands next to the boss.)
- Are you my right-hand man? - Yes, Sir.
Hey, Right-hand.
- Yes, Sir. - He's annoying me.
I'm sorry but I believe I look more like the right-hand man.
You can be my right-hand man, too.
So it's starting again.
Be quiet. Look down.
Honestly, I'm okay, right?
- Be quiet. - Look down.
I'll be your pet dog!
Really?
(However, the sweet taste of power leaves its bitter aftertaste.)
- What is this? - What is this?
(The 6 prisoners start their life at Seok Jin's Prison.)
What is happening?
It's only the beginning.
(Why the sirens?)
Is six lives of imprisonment beginning now?
Six lives of imprisonment?
I meant six hours.
I'm the boss.
You made a mistake.
You said six lives of imprisonment.
"Is six lives of imprisonment beginning now?"
(Are you making fun of the boss?)
I think he'll be sent away to solitary confinement soon.
You shouldn't do that.
Okay. I understand.
I wanted to apologize.
(All power in Seok Jin's Prison comes from Seok Jin.)
(The boss' word is the law.)
I'll be asking you...
to compliment...
(Compliment your boss.)
your boss today.
I'll be asking each one of you one by one.
(I have to lie to my conscience.)
If I don't like it, you'll be sent to solitary confinement.
- Okay. - Even one word matters or else.
Ji Hyo, make an acrostic poem for Jee Seok Jin.
Jee.
At this very moment...
I like how it starts.
Seok.
Whatever Seok Jin says...
Jin.
I love him with all my heart.
(She exchanges her conscience with her fake heart.)
(This is what power tastes like.)
What is she doing?
Haha, make an acrostic poem for Jee Seok Jin.
Jee.
Mind your own business.
(Mind your own business.)
It's only the first line.
- No, I didn't mean that. - You should listen to the rest.
So I have to listen to the rest?
You have to wait until the end.
Seok.
You should try to be like Seok Jin.
(You should try to be like Seok Jin.)
If I don't like it, you are going to solitary confinement. Jin.
He's a real man.
He's a bulldozer.
Go, Seok Jin.
(The last part about the bulldozer was touching.)
Go, Seok Jin, the icon of power.
(I like it.)
Okay.
- Jong Kook. - Yes.
Make an acrostic poem. Jee.
Dear Jee Seok Jin.
Seok.
I apologize.
- What is this? - Jin.
I sincerely apologize...
for making fun of you in the past.
- What has happened to him? - I can feel his sincerity.
(The solitary confinement card makes him get on his knees.)
(This is what power tastes like.)
Jae Seok, make an acrostic poem.
Jee.
Jee Seok Jin!
(Jae Seok is a well-known expert in making fun of Seok Jin.)
(Seok Jin used to be his easiest mark.)
(How will he praise the absolute power that empowered Jong Kook?)
Jee.
Jee Seok Jin.
Seok.
The billionaire.
What's that supposed to mean?
What do you mean by that?
Why billionaire?
You're really funny.
- That's what acrostic poem is like. - But I actually feel good.
- I know, right? - Billionaire.
- Jee Seok Jin, the billionaire. - Jin.
You're the real billionaire.
(He is very satisfied.)
It's meaningless.
- What exactly does he mean? - Why are you satisfied?
Isn't he making fun of you?
- Billionaire sounds nice. - You are the true billionaire.
(Jae Seok's second acrostic poem)
Who is he to boast around and pretend he is the boss,
bossing us around like that?
He's trying to take everything for himself.
You should go to the solitary confinement.
I'm not done with my poem yet.
Was that for the letter "Jee"? It's that long?
- He's not done yet. - That was for "Jee".
- He's not done. - I was just starting.
- Can you repeat the poem? - Of course.
- Can you repeat the poem? - Yes, I can.
Who is he to boast around and pretend he is the boss...
(I'll say it again if you want.)
(He is upset.)
- However, - However?
- Seok. - you're the true billionaire.
Why a billionaire?
- What does that mean? - That's how you make a poem.
- What is that? - Why is he satisfied?
That's how you make an acrostic poem.
- Jin. - You're the true billionaire.
- What does that mean? - He's the richest man.
Strangely, I feel good when he calls me a billionaire.
- Yes, you're a billionaire. - I love hearing that.
That means he's rich.
- Stand over there. - By the way,
- Stand over there. - Are we working for an hour?
Boss, how does this schedule work?
I simply wanted to lock you up.
This isn't fair.
(Falling)
How dare you say that?
Hey. Hey!
- I'll use the card on you. - What card?
- The solitary confinement card. - Where is it?
- It's in here. - Where? Let me see.
- It's in here. - Where? Do you really have it?
- It's right here. - You really do.
Okay, Sir.
(I must have lost my mind for a minute.)
- You shouldn't behave like that. - Okay, Boss.
- Send him away. - He should learn to look down.
- Stand up. Who told you to sit? - Okay.
- He should be sent away. - Okay.
I must have been out of my mind for a moment.
- I'll be obedient. - Okay.
Make an acrostic poem for Jee Seok Jin. Jee.
Jee.
You must be a nutcase.
(How could he...)
Send him to solitary confinement!
(He's the first prisoner at the solitary confinement.)
- Hey. - Go. Go away.
- I'm so sorry. - Solitary confinement.
- What I said... - Send him away!
- Wait, wait. - You need to be punished.
- Can this part be broadcasted? - Yes, it can.
- It can? - It will be censored.
This can't be happening to me.
It's really a solitary confinement?
(This room will make 5 minutes seem like 5 years.)
They told us that solitary confinement is really scary.
Even I don't know what it looks like.
- What is this? - What is it?
- What is it? - No!
What is it?
(He tries to run away.)
- What is this? - What's happening?
- Is this real? - He doesn't seem to be faking it.
(How scary is the place?)
No, no.
(It's an unknown place where you don't know what will happen.)
Please!
No.
(It's creepy.)
(Finally, the doors to the solitary confinement are open.)
(Surprised)
What is this?
What is all this?
(This solitary confinement serves as a healing room.)
(It's a comfortable, healing spot that can help everyone relax.)
This is the best place ever.
The solitary confinement is the best.
(Is this really happening? Cheer for solitary confinement!)
(This is the best thing ever.)
This is really cool.
(There's plenty of nutritious food for the prisoners.)
I feel sorry for Seok Jin.
What should I do? They even have sweets.
(This is a 5-minute-long rest at the solitary confinement room.)
I really like it here.
I was taken aback.
(The others have no idea.)
It's so comfortable.
(This is the future-oriented and advanced Seok Jin's Prison.)
(Meanwhile, the other prisoners don't know what's going on.)
You look cool.
- Give me a massage. - He wasn't lying.
- Is this all real? - Of course.
Of course.
You look charismatic.
Jae Seok has made fun of me all his life.
- You did well. - Hey.
You should also...
smile a bit more.
(Smiling)
Yes, that looks better.
(He's fully enjoying the power.)
This feels good.
- Jae Seok should behave. - He should.
(Jae Seok, have a taste of the solitary confinement.)
(I'm going to have a taste of this citrus tea.)
I think I'll be the only one coming here.
You have two minutes left.
What do you mean two minutes? I just came in here.
(A minute in here feels like a second.)
(He's enjoying his leisure time with a cup of tea.)
This feels nice.
It's better than my house.
(It's the perfect day to drink citrus tea.)
What?
(The guard approaches him.)
I can't go out now.
I haven't been here for long.
Wait... I...
I just made my tea.
(Can't a man drink some tea?)
I'll be back before it gets cold.
I'll be back soon.
(I'll have the solitary confinement all to myself.)
Are we going to follow the schedule?
- Of course. - There's a schedule.
- We have to work first. - What kind of work?
What kind of work?
Maybe it's something like shoveling?
- It could be an exercise. - Maybe it's pulling weeds?
You are really good at working.
- What? - You can just sing "Last Love".
("Last Love" works best.)
(He's the best worker with a sweet voice and snake-like eyes.)
(He is embarrassed.)
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. I won't do that again.
- What is happening? - He sounds well-disciplined.
I won't do that again.
It's so cold in there.
It's really cold.
- It sounds real. - Did he say it's cold?
- No, I'll never do that again. - He says he won't do it again.
- I'll never do that again. - What is it like in there?
He has become a little child.
- What's he saying? - I won't do that again.
- Has he been disciplined? - What did you do?
You are well-disciplined.
It's so cold in there.
Attention.
At ease.
- Attention. - He's really doing it.
- He must have been sitting on ice. - He's obedient.
I will never ever make the same mistakes.
Show me the Grasshopper Dance.
(I will dance any time.)
Now, the Dooly Dance.
(To return to the solitary confinement, he's doing his best.)
I don't want to go back there again.
- Never? - Never.
- Are you curious? - No, I'm not.
- Tell me if you want to go there. - No, I don't want to go there.
(He swears his loyalty to the boss.)
(What is the sound?)
What's going on?
It's time for the first task.
(Their work starts.)
What's going on?
What is that?
(Why is there a sack?)
Are they making us search for barley?
(That's exactly it.)
(It's the most tedious work.)
Do we have to separate the red beans?
(They must separate yellow and red beans.)
- Seriously? - Do we need to separate the beans?
Do you want us to separate them?
The boss doesn't have to do it.
He can distribute the work to the others.
Shouldn't the boss do it, too?
What did you say?
How dare you say that?
- Show your respect to the boss. - Hey, hey.
Starting now, Jae Seok shall treat Haha with respect.
- Okay, Sir. - Haha is above Jae Seok.
- Thank you. - Call him Mr. Haha.
Say Mr. Haha.
This isn't right, Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin is being immature.)
Call him Mr. Haha.
Gosh, Mr. Haha.
(Haha can't believe what he heard.)
- You're above him. - Goodness.
Kwang Soo, you're above...
- Jae Seok as well. - Okay, Sir.
Call him Mr. Kwang Soo.
Come on.
(How dare you disrespect me?)
Hey, you.
- He deserves a beating. - He's not well-disciplined.
I don't like his attitude.
(It's time for solitary confinement again.)
- Jong Kook. - Yes, Sir.
You're above Jae Seok, too.
Of course, I already knew that.
- You don't need to mention it. - That's obvious.
- Ji Hyo is above Jae Seok. - Ms. Ji Hyo.
- Separate the red beans now. - Okay, Sir.
- We'll work hard. - You're a community.
- Understand? - Yes, Sir.
Do you know why I'm the boss? I've been here for 20 years.
- It's been that long. - When will you be released?
I received a 20-year sentence for loving my wife too much.
(Seok Jin brags.)
My only sin was loving my wife too much.
Jae Seok, which crime did you commit?
I'm an economic criminal.
I shouldn't even be confined here with you.
Didn't you commit petty crimes?
(Did he say petty crimes?)
(Jae Seok tries to aggravate him.)
(It's his strategy to go back to solitary confinement.)
(He considers sending him back.)
I heard that you were caught gambling.
- Everyone, stand up. - No.
(He orders everyone to stand up.)
Everyone, get up.
- I didn't say anything. - I told you.
You're a community, so everyone, get up.
- Stand in one line. - Why are you interrupting us?
(Jae Seok is making it worse for everyone.)
Why are you interrupting us?
Line up like a train and hold the waist in the front.
- Like a train? - Right.
Sit down.
Duckwalk around the cell once.
- Are you serious? - Come on.
- Start. - Wait.
Say, "The boss' word is the law." The boss' word...
- Is the law. - The boss' word...
- Is the law! - The boss' word...
(Seok Jin spots Jae Seok.)
- Is the law! - What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - What's wrong?
(Send me to solitary confinement.)
Don't you understand the situation?
- We're in prison. - Calm down, Haha.
Send Jae Seok to solitary confinement.
(He deserves to be punished.)
(Jae Seok is sent to solitary confinement.)
- Good job. - I'm sorry, Sir.
- I'm sorry. - Go now.
I wasn't strong enough to suppress my stress.
I couldn't control my anger.
- He deserves worse punishment. - I'm sorry.
(He's excited to drink some tea.)
I'm sorry.
(He passionately acts.)
I'm really sorry.
Solitary confinement must be terrible.
- He didn't change much physically. - Right.
I wonder if they torture him psychologically.
(Solitary confinement is better than hotels.)
(He enjoys some snack.)
Kwang Soo might have noticed.
(Kwang Soo is the curious type.)
I wonder what he does over there.
You should go if you're curious.
- Do you want to go? - It's okay, Sir.
Kwang Soo is too curious to stay still.
Jong Kook.
(To Kwang Soo, )
(solitary confinement is a world full of mysteries.)
No!
(Come in. You won't regret it.)
- I won't do it ever again. - Go to the corner and kneel.
- Why don't you behave yourself? - Go and kneel.
(Is something good in the solitary confinement?)
Kwang Soo, aren't you curious about the solitary confinement?
- Aren't you? - I'm curious.
Right?
Hit Seok Jin's head once and check it out.
I'm not sure.
(He hesitates to go.)
Are you curious?
(Are you bold enough to be curious?)
(Kwang Soo decides...)
(to check the world of the unknown.)
(It's a mutiny in prison.)
Go ahead.
(It's too easy to go to solitary confinement.)
- Go ahead. - Stop it.
(He sends Kwang Soo.)
- I'll be back. - Have a good time.
- Have a good time. - I'm too curious.
(Is he really the boss?)
- Go ahead. - It's too hard to stay curious.
(Kwang Soo is nervous to find out.)
It's better to find out.
Wait, no!
- What could it possibly be? - Goodness.
(They get curious more and more.)
(He starts to smile.)
(He screams.)
(This is amazing!)
(Is this solitary confinement?)
(He welcomes himself.)
Please!
(It's a new type of solitary confinement.)
Did you already separate this many?
Jong Kook is good at it.
He's very good at tedious work.
(Jae Seok gets playful.)
(Stop doing tedious work.)
What's wrong with you?
(He wants to provoke everyone.)
- Have you lost your mind? - What's wrong with you?
Why?
- Why are you doing this? - Why not?
- You don't need to do this. - I worked hard.
(The tedious task hypnotizes the prisoners.)
(The boss is angry.)
What is it?
(He flips Haha's bowl.)
What are you doing?
Do you want to know?
(If you're curious...)
Do you want to start?
(You know what to do.)
(Just kick Seok Jin.)
Yes, I want to know.
I want to know.
Take out the card now.
I want to go to solitary confinement.
This is unbelievable.
(Everyone sends themselves to solitary confinement.)
(He heads there himself.)
We can work on this again together. Don't worry.
What's all this?
(Is this solitary confinement?)
No!
(It's the best room ever.)
- What kind of room is this? - I have to leave if you come.
Leave.
Why didn't you take more time?
(Haha is happy he came.)
(He lost his power as the boss.)
It's not like we'll be leaving any time soon.
- Gosh. - You can start over.
Are you out of your mind?
(Seok Jin gets ready to act like a boss.)
(Ready, )
(set, go!)
(The boss takes revenge.)
What happened? Why did you do that?
(Seok Jin takes it out on Jong Kook.)
(Seok Jin is no longer the boss.)
Did you fall on your own?
Come here now.
Have you lost your mind?
(Will this be the end of Seok Jin?)
- Are you crazy? - Go to solitary confinement.
Are you crazy?
(Seok Jin tries to boss around.)
You were the best target to push.
I thought Jong Kook fell over on purpose.
Open the door!
(Jong Kook's counterattack will continue.)
My goodness.
I hope solitary confinement teaches him a lesson.
No!
What's that sound?
It's quite difficult in solitary confinement.
What is it like?
(Rumor has it, )
(it's the most luxurious solitary confinement ever.)
Seok Jin is over there alone.
(He can't stop laughing.)
(Jong Kook arrives.)
(Solitary confinement makes them laugh.)
What's this?
Goodness.
- What's going on here? - Get a foot massage.
Shall I get a foot massage?
(It's a prestigious place to rest for the top one percent.)
I won't do it again.
Everyone becomes obedient after being in solitary confinement.
It's interesting.
- What's in solitary confinement? - What is it?
What is it like?
(Thank you for sending me there.)
- Go back there again. - No way.
(Go back there again.)
- No! - He's being rude.
(He tries not to laugh.)
No!
(Seok Jin abuses his power.)
Go back now.
Don't use the card carelessly.
- Please don't send him. - Go back.
(Seok Jin doesn't listen to anyone.)
You go back, too.
(Haha pours the beans on him.)
You, go back.
(Everyone wants to win the solitary confinement card.)
(Everyone wants to go.)
No, no.
- You, too. - He sent me away, too.
- No, please. - Go now.
Forgive me this time.
I won't forgive you.
Go now.
- He sent me there as well. - I can't believe them.
How dare they?
No!
(He gets giddy.)
(They love it here.)
- What? - It's really delicious.
I bet he can't even imagine this.
No.
Only Ji Hyo hasn't been here.
It's because she doesn't know.
What is she doing?
I should teach them a lesson.
(Ji Hyo is working hard.)
If I go, you'll be left here alone.
- What? - If I go, you'll be here alone.
When were you ever worried about that?
I'll take the card out.
(I need to calm down.)
(Teasing)
(He adds oil to the fire.)
Stay still. Don't move.
I'm going to hit your cap.
(My goodness!)
I was being patient with you.
- Hey. - Go ahead. Take the card out.
(You don't have to explain.)
She needs solitary confinement.
- These punks. - Open the door.
(He sends everybody away.)
These punks.
(He is left alone.)
Hold on.
This is solitary confinement.
(Welcome to our house!)
- Start yelling, Ji Hyo. - You're finally here.
Start yelling.
What's all this?
- I'll give you some. - Take a tangerine.
Take some tangerine. The fried banana is really good.
The strawberries are really good.
(Gosh. I should have been nicer to them.)
(I wonder what the other members are doing.)
(It's paradise here.)
It's paradise here.
(She's happy to be in solitary confinement.)
I understand now.
(Siren)
(What's this again?)
What's that?
(It's the meal time.)
- Are we done here? - Are we done?
You can continue tomorrow.
- Yes. - Fine, finish tomorrow.
- I'm hungry. - I'm so tired.
I'm hungry. It's food.
- It looks good. - It looks delicious.
- This is my favorite. - It's pastry.
(Are we supposed to eat this?)
(What about all the food we stuffed down our throats?)
- Bring it over here. - It's filled with whip cream.
- Bring it over here. - We'll give it to you after.
Bring it over here.
(Looks delicious.)
- You haven't had these, right? - Boss, I really want some.
- I want some so much. - I'm very hungry.
Smell it.
(You want some, right?)
(Chuckling)
(They crack up.)
What?
- Get out. - Get out.
- Get back. - Get back.
- What's wrong with you? - Are you out of your mind?
What's his problem?
- What's he doing? - Why is he laughing alone?
(Smell it, Jae Seok.)
It smells so good.
You thought I was giving it to you, right?
(Seok Jin faked it.)
(Chuckling)
What? What's wrong?
(Please stop.)
Come here.
My mouth is getting watery.
- I almost had it. - Hey.
(Jae Seok tries to trick him. He pretends like he's hungry.)
What's wrong with him?
Even if you are hungry and want some food...
(They all devour the food.)
You guys.
(They're in a state of anarchy.)
(Kwang Soo targets the authority figure.)
Hey.
(They all act like they're hungry.)
Leave, Kwang Soo.
Are you making me go again?
- My gosh. - Go.
Drop it in three.
In 1, 2, 3.
Leave.
- You can leave. - Eat before you leave.
- Let me eat. - Follow them.
I won't let you do that.
(Whatever!)
Come on.
Let me eat.
Give it back.
(Seok Jin takes all the pastries away.)
You kids. I feel so bad for you.
(You shouldn't be.)
Seok Jin was so funny.
He asked if I wanted some.
(He almost burped.)
We have so much food here so why would I want some?
I'm too full to eat now.
I'm too full.
(Seok Jin takes the food away from each person.)
It's really good.
(Smiling)
Stop eating. Give it back.
(He almost threw up from eating too much.)
(Munching)
- You should have let me eat. - Come here.
I feel bad for you.
(Here's some food.)
- Eat it. - That's not fair.
- You should eat. - Eat it.
Finish it.
- You worked hard. - It's from the boss. Finish it.
- Be thankful. - It's only for you, Jae Seok.
Say, "Thank you for the food."
Go ahead. Say it.
- Thank you... - Eat it.
Hurry up and eat it.
- Eat. - Thank you.
I sent you to solitary confinement the most.
- He did. - I'm sorry.
- It's okay. - Eat.
I'm starting to tear up. I'll stop eating.
Eat.
- Eat. - It's from the boss.
(Don't try to play smart.)
(Siren goes off.)
What? I didn't get to eat and this is over already.
Is it over?
(The meal time is over. It's now time to exercise.)
I don't usually exercise.
What about this? We can play Statues.
Person that loses heads to solitary confinement.
(Person that loses will head to solitary confinement.)
(All right. The loser heads straight to solitary confinement, right?)
(Come to me.)
If you lose, you're going to solitary confinement.
- Yes. - What if you don't lose?
If there's no loser, I'll go there.
- Okay. - I'll go.
- Let's do this. - Let's do this.
- In 1, 2, 3. - We can do this.
Okay.
(Let's make this look natural and proceed quickly.)
- Make it quick. - Okay.
Flowers are in full bloom.
(Flowers are in full bloom.)
(Falling)
What was that for?
- I'm sorry. - What was that?
(Haha is going to solitary confinement.)
- What was that? - No way.
- No way. - Just go.
(Why are you pretending like you're weak?)
Come here.
- You can't do that. - What was that?
- You can't do that. - That was too easy.
- Go. - Please.
- Go. - Leave now.
- No way. - You can't do that.
- I saw him. - No.
- That was too easy. - I saw it clearly.
- No. - You can't do that.
(Seok Jin is happy he's not going and rest are sad they're not.)
This is good. You can't talk back.
(They're ready for Round 2.)
(We don't have time. There's not much space in solitary confinement.)
You look like a leader.
- I agree. - Flowers are in full bloom.
(Halting)
(She stops too late.)
(Oh, dear.)
- Ji Hyo. - Come on, Ji Hyo.
What was that for?
- Please, Seok Jin. - That looked natural.
You're supposed to be better than this.
You were better.
- It wasn't me. - Come on, Ji Hyo.
- Come on. - Hold on.
He's being too intense.
- You guys are cute. - He's being too intense.
- My goodness. - What are we supposed to do?
(Haha and Ji Hyo are the lucky ones.)
What happened?
Let's have some gimbap.
It was so cold there.
- They're... - They're trying to lose, right?
They're all trying to lose.
Let's go.
(It's Round 3.)
(It's a three way competition.)
I think you're cute.
You're being so good and obedient today.
Flowers are in full bloom.
You're done.
(It's the law of inertia.)
(Dashing)
- Hold on. - No way.
- You can't. - That wasn't it.
That was too weird.
- Let's go again. - That was fake.
- You saw it, right? - No way.
I was going too fast that I couldn't stop.
- But still... - This is filmed.
- Let's go again. - That's too much.
- I can't let it go. - That looked too fake.
Go. Hurry.
That wasn't good.
(Jae Seok is the third person to leave for solitary confinement.)
(Welcome, my friend.)
What was that for, Ji Hyo?
- Jae Seok. - That was too obvious.
- That was too fake, Haha. - Come on.
What was I supposed to do then?
(It's final round.)
(I must lose.)
- Flowers are in full bloom. - Ouch.
(Lying down)
You were worse.
(Jong Kook is out.)
- I can't go now? - You can't. Stay here.
(Everyone but Kwang Soo heads to solitary confinement.)
- I'm sorry. - Don't be.
Give me some gimbap. Let me have some.
I almost didn't make it.
Jae Seok.
- What? - I almost didn't make it.
- What is that? - There's something in here.
(Why is there a map in gimbap?)
(What's this?)
- There's something in here. - What's that?
It must be an escape route.
(My gosh!)
(They found a map of the prison.)
There's a 3rd room on the 3rd floor. What's this?
(Is this about escaping the prison now?)
Is the clue just one?
So this was about escaping.
- It's an escape game. - It is.
(That was something unexpected. Would they manage to escape?)
(Everybody is enjoying their time in prison.)
People...
(Attention, prisoners.)
- People? - Convicts.
You have mail.
- Mail? - Mail?
(Is it mail from the outside world?)
- Who is it for? - Who sent it?
- Is it for me? - It must be from your girlfriend.
To the guy who falls in love quickly?
(What is this?)
- It must be for you. - It says so here.
He dropped something.
Seok Jin.
(Jae Seok finds a mysterious piece of paper.)
(Let's share the information.)
- Let me see. - He dropped it.
- He dropped it. - "From 3pm..."
(It must be something important.)
- What is it? - "Electrical equipment inspection"?
(It will take about 10 minutes from 3pm.)
(Wait.)
(It means the guard will be away for 10 minutes from 3pm.)
- It's a letter from my mom. - Really?
"Dear my son who falls in love quickly..."
(It should be Kwang Soo's official nickname.)
Don't do this.
- Keep reading. - You're hopelessly romantic.
"Dear my hopelessly romantic son, Kwang Soo."
"Are you doing well? It's been cold these days."
"I wonder who you fell in love with there."
"You've been always full of love."
"I'm so proud that you're hopelessly romantic. I love you, my son."
- "From your mom." - Mom.
- I'm sorry. - We should write a song about him.
Guys, a wedding invitation just arrived.
- What's that? - A wedding invitation?
(A wedding invitation?)
- A wedding invitation? - It's related to the wedding hall.
(They went to a wedding hall before being sent to here.)
- It's related to the wedding hall. - It is.
Is he taking us...
"Attend Seok Jin's wedding with all the other members."
"If you don't arrive at the wedding hall on time, you'll be penalized."
January 16 is today. What time?
"Jee Seok Jin and Ryu Soo Jeong"?
Ryu Soo Jeong? That's my wife's name.
(Will Seok Jin's bride be at the wedding hall?)
(If they don't arrive there by 5pm, the bride will disappear.)
(My groom, please escape there.)
Ryu Soo Jeong?
(Could the map be...)
What time is it now?
I think we're supposed to escape using this map.
We found a map earlier.
We found a map.
- Where? - At the solitary confinement.
At the solitary confinement.
(The solitary confinement, 20 minutes earlier)
(They found a map on the wrapping paper by accident.)
- What's that? - There's something on the paper.
I think we're supposed to escape here.
(High and sturdy iron walls)
(Locked iron bars)
(Passages full of mines)
(Rappelling facilities)
(We're supposed to escape here.)
At the solitary confinement?
We went through so much at the solitary confinement.
We had to complete missions.
We had to complete missions to acquire this.
- Really? - Yes.
We had to roll on the ice.
Guys, there's no boss anymore.
- We're one now. - We are.
If we don't arrive at the wedding hall by 5pm,
we'll all be penalized.
- Do you understand? - We're one.
- For your wedding. - One, two, three.
- Let's do this. - Let's do this.
(The prison break starts.)
(The game is on.)
(Aim for the 10 minutes when the guards are away.)
(They must pass the four obstacles on the map to get out.)
(They need to be at the wedding by 5pm for Seok Jin to meet his bride.)
(The prisoners' escape starts.)
(What will happen to them?)
(Prison Break)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
We can't go now.
Shouldn't the lights be off?
They're not here.
- There's an equipment inspection. - We have only 10 minutes.
(What is waiting behind that door?)
- The door should open. - The guards are away.
- Where's everybody? - The door should open.
Where's everybody?
The door should open.
- Where's everybody? - Where's everybody?
- This is the solitary confinement. - Let me see.
- What's this? - Didn't you know?
(What is this luxurious room?)
- I'm sorry. - Here is where we were confined.
(You guys deceived me.)
(He sent them to the solitary confinement.)
(They had a luxury time in the solitary confinement.)
(The man in power had no idea.)
(He became a victim.)
(Is this what I became the boss for?)
- Were you guys here? - Let's take some candies.
- Let's take candies. - What's on the other side?
- Were you eating these? - Let's hurry.
- Let's go. - This is no time for this.
- What is this? - We don't have much time.
Are we supposed to get through this within three minutes?
To the opposite door?
(It's impenetrable.)
(They need to get through this door to get to the next route.)
What are we supposed to do?
- I don't understand. - Is there more?
Are we supposed to go over the wall?
(There must be something more.)
- We can probably break this. - Break it.
(This side doesn't look that sturdy.)
- Break it. - Hurry.
(It's open.)
Are we supposed to go through this?
- Go through it. - I'll go first.
- Go through it. - One, two, three.
- There's one at the bottom, too. - Where? Oh, I found it.
- There's one at the bottom. - Hurry.
- Wait. - Ji Hyo, go.
Open the door.
Can you open the door?
- Can you open the door? - Open it.
There you go.
(Doors, be opened.)
There's no key.
- Hurry. - We need to go through here.
- There is. - Did you find it?
- There is. - Where should I go?
- Kwang Soo, come here. - What should I do?
Come down.
- Come down here. - Should I?
- Kwang Soo, come down. - Let's go.
(They passed the 1st course with 3 minutes remaining.)
Come down.
- What's that? - It's on the map.
- It's not that way. - Come here.
We probably need to find the password.
- Seok Jin, - What is the password?
- when is your wife's birthday? - Could it be our anniversary?
- When is your anniversary? - When is it?
- Try 1031. - Try 7012.
- Try 1031. - Try 1031.
(They try her birthday first.)
Try 1031.
- It doesn't work. - Try 7012.
- Are there any clues? - Is there nothing?
(They try 7012 next.)
- Are there any clues? - It doesn't work.
It says, "Race Starter".
It means Seok Jin.
- It says, "Race Starter". - Try his phone number.
Where?
- That's you. - It says "Race Starter" here.
Race Starter?
(Race Starter is Seok Jin's nickname.)
(Does Seok Jin have the password with him?)
When is your birthday?
Try 0210.
- What if they start chasing us? - Is that the right way?
- Race Starter is Seok Jin. - Isn't this how you do it?
What if they start chasing us?
Is this the right way?
(What is this ominous feeling?)
(It's 3:10pm. The inspection is over.)
(The prisoners are attempting to escape.)
(Arrest them immediately.)
- Don't you have to push something? - Isn't it right?
- What could Race Starter mean? - Race Starter.
What could it mean?
(What could the code mean?)
- He needs to be out. - It's not right.
- Out? - He's usually the first to be out.
(Let's look back on the history.)
(The name tag is ripped off.)
(Seok Jin always started the race by getting eliminated first.)
(The race starts when Seok Jin gets eliminated.)
(Wait. Could there be something under Seok Jin's name tag?)
(The name tag is ripped off.)
- It's here. - Is there something?
(They found a hint.)
"The year Seok Jin debuted as a singer".
"The year Seok Jin passed the comedian exam".
(It's a summary of Seok Jin's life history.)
"The year Seok Jin passed the comedian exam". Tell us.
- It's 1992. - It's 1992.
- It was there. - Hurry.
You're amazing.
Add them up. "The year Seok Jin debuted as a singer".
"The year Seok Jin passed the comedian exam".
- Do it one by one. - When did you debut?
- I debuted in 1993. - Is it 1992?
- Is it 1993? - Right.
Remember it.
- Add 1992... - It's 1992 plus 1993.
- It's hard. - Does anyone have a pen?
(Where are the prisoners?)
(Motivated)
- How are we going to do this? - Let's hurry.
- When did you debut as a singer? - In 1992.
- And? - As a comedian in 1993.
- Okay. - As a host in 1994.
- Is it 1994? - Yes.
It's so hard.
- Let's hurry. - Hurry.
Let's add them together.
Each person should remember one number.
Let's multiply 2000 by 4 and subtract the numbers.
Add 8, 7, 7, and 6 together.
- Add them together. - Add 8, 7, 7, and 6 together?
Try 7973.
(If they fail this time, they won't be able to escape.)
(It's open.)
- Okay. - Hurry.
(It's 3:25pm. They passed the 2nd obstacle.)
- Hurry. - Go up.
- Go up. - Go up.
(Move towards the 3rd course.)
- What is this? - What is this?
I know what it is.
(What's ahead of them?)
You should step on the right spots.
(Find the right way.)
(They have to start again if they step on a mine.)
There's a monitor.
That must be the right path.
- We have to remember it. - I'll remember the last part.
Three...
- It's easy. - Three, three, two, one...
- It's easy. - Two, two...
- Three, three... - I memorized it.
- If you memorized it, start. - Go.
- Here... - The guards are following.
- The guards are following. - Two, two...
- Three, three, two... - They're almost here.
(We'll catch them by all means.)
- Two... - Here?
Two...
(He tripped.)
What happened?
(They can continue because he didn't step on it properly.)
- There. - That way.
(They will get caught if they make a mistake.)
(Will they get caught or will they escape?)
- It's that way. - It's that one.
- There. - It's here.
(They are all so loud.)
- It's here. - It's here.
(They're so close.)
- It's this way. - It's over here.
(They pass the 3rd obstacle.)
(The current time is 3:30pm. They have 90 minutes left.)
(One last obstacle remains.)
- There's a game. - It's right behind you.
- Is this it? - What is it?
- Do we have to go outside? - What is this?
- What is this? - Have they lost their mind?
- No way. - This is impossible.
- This can't be true. - We can't do it.
(What's the last obstacle?)
- I don't like it. - How could they make us do it?
(Is it your 1st time falling from the 3rd floor?)
- Let's just do it. - Seriously?
(Here's the story behind the obstacle.)
- What else can we do? - My goodness.
I'd like to challenge myself to something I couldn't do before.
I'd like to challenge myself.
If I make it, it would be very rewarding.
I'll feel proud of myself.
How can we do this?
(We prepared something he's never done before.)
(How can they do it?)
(Many of them are afraid of heights.)
- Are they being serious? - How could they make us do it?
Let's put this on.
(Haha can't believe it.)
- What else can we do? - My goodness.
Do we have to do it for real?
- Are you being serious? - Gosh.
(Yes, we're being serious.)
- How? - Let's just go back to prison.
This is unbelievable.
(Welcome to the last stage of Seok Jin's Prison.)
- How can we do it? - Is this it?
We have professional help for our escape,
- so don't worry too much. - Right.
Staying in solitary confinement wasn't bad.
Can you do it, Ji Hyo?
- I'll do it first. - You go first.
- She can do it. - She's the bravest one.
(She's reliable.)
Ji Hyo is the bravest one of all.
Go ahead, Ji Hyo.
- I trust you, Ji Hyo. - Okay.
This place is too dangerous. You should escape first.
(Kwang Soo lets Ji Hyo go first.)
Jump off, Ji Hyo. Someone's coming after us.
- It's not too high. - Can you do it alone?
(The first to escape is Ji Hyo.)
(It's frightening.)
Turn around, Ji Hyo.
- Tell us if you can't do it. - I can't do it.
I don't think we'll make it to my wedding.
- Be careful. - Hold the rope tightly.
(She knows what to do.)
- Like this? - She's doing it all alone.
(She's not afraid at all.)
(With cowardly members behind, )
(she attempts to escape without any hesitation.)
- Am I good to go? - Here you go.
(The prison break starts.)
- Hold onto this, Ji Hyo. - Be careful.
(All 6 members must escape within 1 hour.)
(Will all members escape successfully?)
- Like this? - She's doing it all alone.
(She descends with stability and composure.)
- Hold onto this, Ji Hyo. - Be careful.
- Am I set to go? - You're doing well.
You're good enough to descend alone.
- Am I set to go? - You're fine.
(She descends...)
(step by step.)
- You'll be fine. - Am I set to go?
We should be more worried about ourselves.
- She's almost there. - You got it.
(She descends lightly.)
Ji Hyo is very good.
She's talented.
(It's a piece of cake.)
- See? - She's good.
- She's very good. - Guys.
It's okay. It's not scary.
It isn't scary for you.
(Ji Hyo fears nothing.)
I'm scared just by watching it.
(She descends safely.)
- I'm so jealous of her. - She made it. It's our turn.
(She escapes successfully.)
- Did she get to the ground? - Who wants to go next?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
(They play rock-paper-scissors to determine the order.)
- Boss. - Let's hurry.
Even if we get caught, you should escape.
- Please go ahead. - I'll go last.
(He gets special treatment.)
(Who will go next?)
(Kwang Soo loses.)
(Unlucky Kwang Soo is selected.)
Kwang Soo.
(The sky expresses pity for Kwang Soo.)
Goodness.
(He doesn't understand why they're doing this.)
It's not a real prison break, so what's the fuss about?
(Right now, )
(the guards are coming after them.)
- Let's hurry. - Go now.
- Hurry up. - Shut your mouth.
Go up now.
- How do I do this? - Haven't you done it before?
(The next one to escape is Kwang Soo.)
I've never tried it before.
(The whistles keep blowing.)
- Hey. - They're coming.
(He's upset about the reality.)
- You're younger than me. - Gosh.
(He's afraid to escape.)
- Come on, Kwang Soo. - This is too difficult.
- You're set. Go on. - This is too harsh.
- Go down. - We don't have enough gears.
(All he has is one rope.)
It's okay. Just go.
- Gosh, Kwang Soo. - Wait.
- I might fall off. - It's okay.
- I'm going to fall off. - Turn back and go down.
(He can't move at all.)
- How? - Just go.
- Grab this. - Otherwise, they'll catch us all.
Hold on the right.
(Kwang Soo might not survive.)
- Get on all fours. - It moves down.
- It moves down. - Hurry up and come down.
(Kwang Soo is too cowardly.)
My goodness.
I'll stay in prison forever if I have to.
- I can't do this. - Just go down.
- Come on, Kwang Soo. - You brake with your right hand.
That's not it.
(He's too scared.)
(Will they make it to the wedding?)
- Put your feet down. - There you go.
(He can't make himself escape.)
Put your feet down.
Kwang Soo.
- Stay alert. - Hey!
(He gets dizzy.)
(Escaping is too hard for him.)
Let go of the rope a little.
(He descends slowly.)
- Do it slowly. - You'll be okay.
- You're descending. - There you go.
(He squirms.)
It's getting faster.
No, you can control the speed.
(He moves slowly like a praying mantis.)
- Don't look down. - Keep descending.
- This is very scary. - He's almost there.
(They're proud of Kwang Soo.)
- He's almost there. - I'll just stay in prison.
I can't do it.
(He barely descends to the 2nd story.)
- I can't do it. - He's almost there.
Do you have any water?
Do you have water?
I'm getting dizzy.
Kwang Soo, you must come down now.
- That's right. - Hurry up.
(Too much time passed.)
- You're almost there. - The ground is too far.
You won't die even if you jump off.
Keep your legs still and lower your bottom.
- Keep your legs straight. - Why hasn't he moved at all?
(He can't control himself.)
- What on earth is he doing? - Wait!
(He can't control his body.)
- I straightened my legs. - What's going on?
- Hurry up! - How?
- Do I let go? - Yes.
- Do I let my legs go? - Let them go.
(He's close to the ground.)
- Let them go. - There you go.
- He's descending. - There he goes.
(He descends very slowly.)
(Dragging)
He's going down.
(He lands on his back.)
He's very startled.
He looks pale.
Was it scary, Kwang Soo?
(He almost died.)
Thank you.
- Turn around. - I'm afraid of heights.
- I'm really terrified of heights. - We know.
(He makes a big fuss.)
- We know it better than anyone. - I hate high places.
(There isn't much time left.)
It gets easy after you take the first step.
(He must lean outside the window.)
- Lean your legs against the wall. - Is this how you do it?
(He spreads his legs wide.)
- Is this it? - Is this how I do it?
(He's determined to marry off Seok Jin today.)
(Will Jae Seok make it to the ground?)
This is how you do it.
(He stumbles.)
- There you go. - Is this right?
(He descends while jumping awkwardly.)
- Like this? - That's right.
- I'm afraid of falling backwards. - Okay.
He's doing well.
(Jae Seok turns into Spiderman.)
Do it like this.
- He's very brave. - Watch me carefully.
- It's okay if you hold on tightly. - Why are you trembling?
- Look at Jae Seok. - It's because I'm too scared.
Jae Seok is brave enough to lean back like that.
(He's determined.)
(He lands lightly.)
Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok escapes successfully.)
- You did it. - My goodness.
You're the best, Jae Seok.
(Only 50 minutes remain.)
- Are you taking the same position? - Wait.
- What's wrong? - My neck feels stiff.
(His neck hurts in the back.)
We're such cowards.
(We're a team of cowards.)
Hurry up.
Haha, it's okay.
We have to get to the wedding.
- You're set. - Wait.
(Haha is too scared.)
- Wait, Jong Kook. - You're set.
(Please call the ambulance.)
Put your feet out first.
- Put your feet out first. - Wait.
(He's too afraid to move.)
Move your legs first.
Push your bottom out and straighten your legs.
I can't straighten my legs.
(Haha can't make himself do it.)
You must lean back.
(Kwang Soo gives advice based on his experience.)
Just trust the safety guards.
(Kwang Soo forgot about his past.)
(Haha finally leans out.)
Hold the rope with both hands.
- There you go. - You got it.
(He's no longer a coward.)
(He will show what being a real man is all about.)
- I can't go down. - Use your legs.
No, wait.
(He fails to descend.)
I can't do it.
- Goodness. - I can't go down.
I'll go first.
(He blames the rope for not working properly.)
Take a rest.
I'll try it again. I almost made it, didn't I?
You punk!
Hurry up. We have a wedding to attend.
Lower yourself slowly.
- Can you pull me up? Sorry. - What's wrong?
Let go of your right arm.
(He fails again.)
You're gripping too hard with the left hand.
(It's not that complicated.)
Okay, I'll do it.
I'll imagine Dream is down there.
That's right.
(He remembers that he's a father.)
- I must go down to save him. - That's right.
(As a father, he's determined to succeed.)
(Dream, are you watching me?)
- Here I go. - Go.
(Haha was terribly afraid of heights.)
(He hated being in high places.)
(He was never manly enough.)
(He challenges himself as a father and not just a man.)
- I'm going. - Go.
- I need to save Dream, right? - That's right.
(Haha takes small steps thinking about Dream.)
Don't worry. You did it.
You did it. That's it.
- Good job. - That's it.
- He's losing focus. - That's it.
- You did it. - Good job.
- There's a window coming up. - Good job.
- You're good. - All right.
You're special forces.
- Good job. - Why are you so good?
- All right. - Oh, my goodness.
(He lands on 2nd floor.)
Go at once.
(Haha is Dream's father and not a coward.)
(I can do it.)
- Come straight down. - You're good.
- Come straight down. - All right.
You're good.
That's right.
Dream!
- I came here to save you. - Dream.
- Why are you mentioning Dream? - What did he say?
- Dream. - What did he say?
Why are you mentioning Dream?
I came down to save you.
It's really not flattering.
- It really isn't. - Why are you mentioning Dream?
- Why did he say his name? - I love you!
The 7 of us are 1!
- Why are you mentioning Dream? - I did it.
- Why are you mentioning Dream? - Dream.
Why are you mentioning Dream?
You did it.
- You can do it. - For goodness' sake.
(He feels pressured because all the cowards did it.)
This is driving me nuts.
- It's your wedding, Seok Jin. - Seok Jin.
We're doing this because of you.
- Seok Jin. - This is all your fault!
It's your wedding, Seok Jin.
(Thank you but can I not go?)
Put your right hand near your waist.
Bring the rope to your right. It's too near the back.
- Move your right hand. - Like this?
Let go. They're holding on so you won't fall.
(Well...)
He can't.
Do you want to go to my wedding first?
Do you want to go first and collect money gifts?
- Tell them I'm going to be late. - Seok Jin.
You can let go a little. You won't fall.
- That's brake. - Okay.
Haha, can you be quiet?
I don't think you're in any position to tell me what to do.
- You can do it. - You just need to take a step.
- I'm more of a coward than you. - You two can't tell me what to do.
- Exactly. - Seok Jin.
- Even I did it. You can do it. - This is nothing.
- Is it good? - It's good.
- Let's go. - My left hand is weak.
- Is it all right? - Use your right hand.
(Would Seok Jin manage?)
(Seok Jin's dream is to have a romantic wedding.)
(They must get to the venue in 40 minutes to make it happen.)
It's your wedding, Seok Jin.
The instructors will take care of it.
- I didn't do it by myself. - That's good.
- You're good. - Let go of your right hand.
You're good.
- Let go. - You're good.
Let go. The instructors will help you.
- Use your right hand. - Let go.
- You're good. - You're almost there.
- You're almost there. - Wait. It's going too fast.
- It's going too fast. - Don't worry.
- It's going too fast. - Let go of your right hand.
Let go and grab it again.
- It's hardest in the beginning. - All right.
What do you need?
Look above.
Why are you dancing?
You're almost there.
(He does a twist on the wall.)
- You're almost there. - I think he got it.
Let go of your right hand.
Don't hold on. Let go.
- Should I let go? - Yes.
How? How am I supposed to let go?
Let go. You can let go.
Let go. You have to.
Look at him.
My gosh.
- I wasn't that bad, right? - You weren't.
Didn't I look cool near the end?
You did.
You know what's worse about this?
When Kwang Soo was stuck before,
he said, "You won't hurt yourself even if you jumped down from there."
(He was being so harsh to Kwang Soo.)
I'm so embarrassed.
(I respect you, Kwang Soo and Haha.)
- It was so difficult. - I'm happy that I'm on the ground.
(There's only Jong Kook left.)
- I was afraid the rope would break. - I'm coming.
- Hurry up. - Use your right hand.
He'll be fine.
(There are prison guards that are after Jong Kook.)
(Will Jong Kook safely escape prison?)
(He's incredible.)
- Listen to that. - Be careful.
He's like Spiderman.
Be careful.
You can let go.
He escaped.
- That was so simple. - It's good.
(It would be that easy for me if I did it again.)
- I can do better if I did it again. - Same here.
- I think... - You're number one.
Hurry up. There's no time.
Let's go.
There are guards after us.
- Let's go. - There are guards after us.
This isn't necessary.
Guards are after us.
(Soo Jeong is waiting for her groom.)
(Will Seok Jin reach her for the wedding?)
(What's awaiting the members after their escape?)
What's this?
- What's this? - What's this?
Please stand in front of the boxes.
- Can we open it? - I was wearing this in the morning.
I was wearing this in the morning.
I don't have mine.
Seok Jin is missing his.
(His tuxedo is gone.)
Seok Jin, you must be the naked groom.
"Answer questions about your wife to get your clothes."
"The box with the correct answer has the tuxedo."
You won't just give it to me?
(If his answer is incorrect, he'll get something unexpected.)
- What's this? - You should just give it to me.
You thought he'll forget about their first kiss?
- Right? - Look at the question.
- Why would I not know? - You don't remember?
You know me.
We used to spend a lot of time in my car when we were dating.
We were by the riverside and I asked my wife to count...
if 63 Building actually had 63 floors.
That's how much time we spent in the car.
- Car. - Are you sure?
- Open it. - Are you sure?
- Of course. It has to be. - It's for sure.
(He was so confident. What's in the box?)
It's for sure.
- What a relief. - You don't even have to think.
This is great.
- Can he open the other ones? - What's that one?
(What's in the other boxes?)
They're straw shoes.
- It would have been funny. - You almost had these.
"What gift does your wife want for this wedding anniversary?"
- This one's difficult. - It's a tough one.
- I think I know. - Really?
- I think it's vacation. - I think I know.
- That's not it. - What about a handbag?
- A handbag? - A ring and necklace?
- It is 100 percent this one. - That's right.
- Really? - He didn't even hesitate.
- He didn't even hesitate. - That's what she would want.
It's 100 percent ring and necklace.
(He's becoming more confident.)
(Will he get two in a row?)
(He's correct. He gets tuxedo pants.)
- He's a true lover. - Why am I so good?
That's so cool.
- You look so cool. - Why do I know my wife so well?
It's nothing.
- Hold on. - What you wore to the first date?
I don't know about mine.
- Are you supposed to know this? - How would you know?
- I'm between these two. - This is confusing.
- I'm between these two. - This is difficult.
- I remember mine. - I'm between these two.
I was wearing jeans for sure. The day before,
I slept over at his place.
You wore jeans.
I slept over at his place and went out for the blind date.
If you slept over, it can't be a white shirt.
- You don't think so? - It would have gotten dirty.
- I didn't wear black shirts though. - It would have been dirty.
- It's a white shirt. - It is, right?
- It's a white shirt. - It can't be a white shirt.
(They all sound convincing. What would Seok Jin choose?)
- I think it's a white shirt. - It's white shirt.
(He chooses jeans, white shirt, and a black cap.)
Are you going with that?
Let's do it.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Would he establish himself as a true lover?)
I had no idea.
It looks like you're performing.
(He gets a sweatshirt.)
- It was a black shirt. - It was black.
- It was a black shirt. - Just wear this.
I should have used the chance card.
- I guess it's a casual wedding. - That's right.
You're so classy.
- My goodness. - This is good.
Do I look all right?
It's excellent.
- Charming sides are difficult. - This is tough.
- It's one of these. - It's this one. You're kind.
- It's one of these. - It's this one.
- She likes it when I'm kind. - This should be it.
- The question gave it away. - I'm pretty kind to her.
What's that?
(He chooses his charm as being a kind man.)
"Running Man make-up"?
- Am I wrong? This is incorrect? - I guess not.
Maybe it's that he doesn't get mad easily.
- Please. - Don't worry.
Let me go like this.
(They've been married for 19 years and he didn't even know.)
I look like a bully.
- You look fine. - You look good.
- You look good. - It's great.
- It's actually better this way. - Do this side too.
(This is Seok Jin's type of attire for the wedding.)
(They arrive at the venue at 4:50pm.)
(Soo Jeong awaits her husband.)
My gosh.
It's a reminder wedding.
Excuse me.
(Where is my lovely bride?)
It's Soo Jeong.
- Is it really her? - Soo Jeong.
- Oh, dear. - Is it you?
- Is it the groom's entry? - No, not yet.
I'm sorry for coming like this.
You look beautiful, Soo Jeong.
Soo Jeong, it's been a long time.
- Is it really her? - Hello.
She looks like Seol Hyun from the back.
(Is it really Seok Jin's wife?)
(She's the bride, the most special person for today.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello, Mrs. Jee.
- Hello. - We're sorry.
Soo Jeong.
- We're sorry. - She's beautiful.
- She's so pretty. - Hey.
He got a few questions wrong.
You're still handsome.
Really?
(She's the bride for sure.)
(Seok Jin's wedding commences.)
Look at the audience.
(They feel nervous as if it was 19 years ago.)
Hello, I'm Yu Jae Seok, the host for today's wedding ceremony.
He's so handsome.
- He's a great host. - He's our friend.
Today's wedding...
is between Seok Jin and Soo Jeong who's been married for 19 years.
It's a valuable time...
for them to renew their vows.
Bride and groom.
Please come in.
You are so pretty.
(They enter with old flower girls.)
(They are blushing.)
The groom seems to be very active.
This is his ceremony to renew his vow.
This is truly touching.
The groom has starred on "Capture the Moment How is that Possible".
"Capture the Moment How is that Possible"?
He appeared as a man who's happy all year long.
Please have a happy life.
Congratulations.
Next,
please bow to each other.
Please give a round of applause.
- They look great. - It has...
been 19 years since they've been in a wedding hall.
I imagine that they must be reminded of their memories.
Jee Seok Jin, do you love your wife,
Ryu Soo Jeong, as you did 19 years ago?
I do!
- My gosh. - He's so cool.
Ryu Soo Jeong,
do you love your husband, Jee Seok Jin, as you did 19 years ago?
- I do. - All right.
She's crying.
- Why are you crying? - I hope your love won't change.
- Now, you will exchange the rings. - They have rings?
The crew has prepared R Rings to commemorate the renewal.
He has never won that before.
Now, he has won it.
- The ring fits perfectly. - Really?
My wife's ring size is nine.
- I'm about to cry now. - What a good husband.
I'm so moved.
The bride, Ryu Soo Jeong, has prepared a letter...
for her husband, Jee Seok Jin.
- Why did you do that? - Why don't you...
- read it out loud? - This will make people cry.
Dear my loving husband,
I met you when I was 24 years old. I was immature, then.
We gave birth to Hyun Woo. You became Hyun Woo's father.
It's been 20 years since you've been my husband.
We used to argue a lot before.
Now, we are too busy to argue. We are busy taking care of each other.
You protect us from this tough world.
You're always here when I need you.
You are my eternal, best friend who knows me so well.
There is no path to happiness.
Happiness is the path.
When we follow the path, just looking forward,
a happy life will unfold before us.
Let us keep our lifelong friendship, Honey.
I love you.
Please give a round of applause.
(The groom holds back his tears.)
- My gosh. - Goodness.
(What a touching letter.)
Don't cry.
- He seems a bit overwhelmed. - Yes, he does.
- Seok Jin. - I am overwhelmed a bit.
Next, it's time for the song.
Is this how we should do it? Should we hold hands?
(They hold each other's hands.)
(They both look the same direction.)
This is nice.
(She gets teary-eyed.)
(He sings sincerely to wish the best for them.)
- Why am I crying? - Why is she crying?
(Seok Jin and Soo Jeong survived tiring daily life and hard times...)
(because they have each other.)
(They stood by each other's side for 20 years as a friend and a lover.)
(Thank you for always being there.)
(Seok Jin sings seriously and finishes the song.)
(He embraces her.)
(I'm fortunate that you are with me.)
Thank you.
Congratulations on renewing your vows.
- This is for Soo Jeong. - Okay.
(He changes the lyrics to add her name in.)
(He wittily changes the lyrics so that everyone can sing along.)
(The groom sings a verse, too.)
(Blushing)
Thank you very much, Soo Jeong.
Soo Jeong, it's already been 20 years.
(The professional singer changes the lyrics to sing a romantic serenade.)
Give a round of applause.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
It was my honor.
- Thank you. - I knew it.
He improvised.
- Shouldn't we ask them to kiss? - We should.
- Kiss her. - Give her a kiss.
- Please give her a kiss. - Kiss her.
Why don't we let them do it?
- She looks so pretty. - My goodness.
Please clap when they kiss.
To both of you,
we wish a happy life.
(We took care of each other with undying love for 20 years.)
(Let's only walk on flowery roads.)
Thank you for being with me. You are my rock.
I hope we can lead a happy and healthy life without getting old.
I love you, Honey.
(Seok Jin's week is a success. Seok Jin and Soo Jeong, always be happy.)
(Ultimate Battle of Supernaturals)
(Jae Seok)
(Ji Hyo)
(Seok Jin)
(Haha)
(Jong Kook)
(Kwang Soo)
(This is the ultimate battle of returning supernaturals.)
(This battle will determine the members' fates.)
(Is there a mysterious person behind this battle?)
(Who will be the winner of this shocking and terrifying battle?)
(Next week, Ultimate Battle of Supernaturals)