How does it feel?
It feels very good!
You know exactly how to please me.
As usual.
Thank you. Now if you could please turn over.
Yea.
Have we met before?
This is the first time we've met.
Oh, is that so? Sorry about that.
Maybe you saw me in a TV commercial or on a poster for the bank?
That was about 3 years ago wasn't it?
Yea.
You were a model for a bank…
See you remembered well!
So you're still in the industry?
Well, actually I married the owner of the bank and have moved here.
Oh, is that so? Please relax.
The owner of the bank…
Do you know my husband?
Oh, no! I'm sorry I was thinking of someone else.
OK, I'll massage your hand now, please extend it for me.
Are you alright?
Please relax.
It doesn't hurt does it?
Nope.
Shall I do more?
Hey, what the! Please stop that!
But this is our most popular massage.
Uh, that's strange isn't it?
No, really.
Well, that's enough! I'm leaving!
I'm very sorry about that but I did nothing bad.
Wife Fucked Before the Husbands Eyes
Not again this month…
Well you know the whole time…
But about the money, I was thinking this winter…
It's been the most delicious by far.
Hmm…
Don't you agree?
You just wait until the wedding anniversary.
Ok, I'm off.
See you later.
Yes, who is it?
It's Mr.Sakaki from the este salon Lucifer. You were here the other day…
What brings you here? This is unexpected, please come in.
Thanks.
Sorry about that, please have a seat.
Why thank you.
Sorry if I've made you a little uncomfortable.
At that time I was just surprised.
I got a little too angry.
So, if you could please allow me…
Uh, of course.
Thank you Here's something for you.
But, uh, really don't mind it.
No, I thought you'd mind it very much.
Now here we have something that all of our celebrities love to use.
I won't have it. Get out!
No way!
Don't come back!
Open up! You can't get away from us.
So, what is it? It won't open. Hey!
Hey!
What? Have a look here, the rooms are connected.
What were you doing?
No! Let me go!
No!
No you can't get away.
I said let go!
No!
Hey, hey, don't resist.
Let's have a good look at what's inside.
Don't touch me!
No!
Hey, what do you think huh?
No
So, does it hurt?
No! Let go!
Be a good girl. How about this.
No!
No! No!
Your nipples are hard.
You like it like this don't you?
No! Let go!
Over here too?
Looks like you like it hard huh?
That hurts!
No!
Now, lets give you the treatment.
Well!
No way!
Here hold her leg for me.
Right here?
You want it stronger hey?
No! Don't touch me there!
Here?
Your quivering aren't you!?
No! Hey! Don't touch me!
More? No!
No!
You wanna flee?
You can go. Look you can run. Are you gonna go out like that?
Look, You can go. Hey!
No! No!
So, where do you think you're going?!
You'll damage your very important hair, calm down.
Look what we have here.
Just like this.
Hold her tight.
What a great position.
No!
Don't touch me!
I can see everything.
What a lovely asshole.
No!
Why are quivering again?
See.
No, Don't!
Stop it!
Here they go.
Let's open wide!
That's just right.
What's wrong?
Let go!
No! No!
Don't touch me!
Ah… your getting wet.
No!
Hey!
Why are you still quivering?
No!
Look!
Wet n juicy! Wet n juicy.
Let's do it slowly now.
See.
What is it?
Don't resist.
See!
No!
Dripping wet.
Here!
Let's do it harder!
Don't touch me!
Hey! Don't touch me! More! No!
Stop it!
Now let's flip you over.
Over here, here.
Let's get rough! No! Huh?
No!
Let Go!
No.
This is great.
Stop. You want more?
See.
What is it?
You wanna give up?
Get over here.
Here, here.
Watch out for you hair!
See, you want more. Harder?
Don't cry on us.
Don't pull your hair.
No!
What? See.
now…
Hey, looks like your enjoying yourself now.
Let's get you up but be careful of your hair.
Let go!
Still quivering?
That feels good I bet.
No!
Let go! No watch out, be careful you could hurt yourself.
You'll fall down.
What is it?
This is dangerous.
You better do what we want.
huh? No!
We better gag you now!
Here?
See, I'm not done.
Really slowly.
What is it?
Can I do some? Yea, I'll be here.
Doesn't that feel good?
You like it right?!
You seem to be enjoying it!
What is it? Hey!
You like being spanked?
More quivering.
I'm gonna spread it wide.
Spread it there too.
Let's see it all.
How good is that?
We can see it all.
No! Let go!
You wanna leave?
You wanna go?
Let go!
See.
here.
Sounds juicy doesn't it?
next…
We'll touch you slowly, right here.
We know you want it.
You're doing well.
It's great.
Let's do it harder.
Well now, well now. Huh?
You like it don't you!?
Want more?!
Well, she's ready for it now!
You want it don't you?
You'll get it!
What is it you want?
What do you want?
You want more than fingers right?
Your pussy wants it.
You can't get away now.
What? I can't hear you speak up.
Go ahead stick it in.
Have a good look.
Ah, he stuck it in.
Feels good doesn't it.
Wet and juicy.
What? You want more?
You're enjoying it aren't you?
What is it?
Does it feel good?
Look it's all the way in.
Nice and slow, nice and slow.
What is it?
It feels so good you wanna cry?
Hey look at it.
You look like your having fun. Have a good look.
He's filling you up.
Have a good look.
Let's have a look at our face.
You like it?
See.
Do with her as you please. Can I?
We're not finished.
I'm gonna hit it.
You know you like it.
Hey, where are you going? You can go anywhere!
Feisty are we? Get over here.
Hey, I'm gonna take some great pictures.
I'm gonna stick it in.
No!
Hey, hey, hey. Open your mouth.
Yea, that's right.
Just like that, what a good girl.
Have a seat.
Speak up, we wanna hear you.
Hey, louder.
Now, from behind.
See what'd I say.
Just like that.
Suck it all!
That's right, be a good girl, a good girl.
Yea, I'm still getting it all.
You can't take a break.
Open up wide!
See.
No!
Look here, look here.
So sexy.
Hey now, hey now, hey.
Suck it good.
Have a seat, sit down, sit down, sit!
Suck it that's all you can do now.
I can see you asshole.
That's right, very good.
What a lovely face.
Do it right, just like that. Like that.
Look at the camera.
Yea, do it harder, harder. Just like that.
We're not done yet, not yet.
That's a good girl.
So sexy. How is it?
So you want more!
So you want it in again?
Just like this is good.
Hey, you can escape.
What is it? Let go!
I took a bunch of pictures.
Have a look here.
See, you want it.
No!
Don't move your legs.
Oh, I see it.
Ah, we'll give you lots more.
Harder, Stronger, Faster!
Get up just like that.
I can see it all from below.
Have a good look.
Enjoy every moment.
Stop it.
Come on.
No! No! No!
Hey, where do you think you're going?!
Come here!
No!
Hey, here, here, here, See!
Yea, yea, yea. That's right.
That's right.
What, yea, yea, yea.
You know it feels good.
Ah, feeling weak aren't you?
Just give in to it.
Look here, look here.
Look at the camera.
Ok, be a good girl and take it from the back.
Hey, over here.
Hey, have a good look.
Yea, he's drilling, drilling you!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Clean it up.
Now listen, these pictures…
Only make it look like your cheating.
What would your husband think if he saw them?
Why would you do such a thing?
Well you didn't seem to enjoy yourself at my salon.
Well, if you pay us $5000…
That's reasonable don't you think?
You've got one month to pay up or else these pictures…
Ah, that's alright. Don't you worry.
Now, let's begin.
Please relax, relax.
How do you feel?
You need to relax.
I'll show you the pictures.
Yea, relax.
That's it, loosen up.
See.
This is in the way, let's take it off.
Does it feel good?
It feels good doesn't it?
Huh?
Your nipples got hard.
Next let's do the bottom.
Loosen up please.
Open your legs and relax.
Open them yourself, it's time for more pictures.
Let's make the massage slow and enjoyable.
Let's have a good look down there.
What do you think?
This is in the way.
Let's take them off.
Now, I'll give you a wonderfully slow massage down there.
Excuse me. Please relax.
That looks rather enjoyable.
What is it? Isn't it good?
Well.
Next, give here a massage below with your tongue. Yes!
This is gonna be delicious.
Does it feel good?
Would you like more?
Ok, let's get faster.
How's that?
You know it feels good.
I think you're having a blast.
Let's continue.
You're quivering.
What is it?
You really want it harder don't you?
Isn't that right?
You like it like that?
More, more, lick harder & faster.
Alright.
That's right.
Your getting entranced.
That's all.
Well, we look forward to seeing you next week on Monday.
Thank you.
Later.
What do you think of this massage?
You can see it go all the way in!
How about this, huh?
Wait, you can't push it out. I'll stick it back in!
This is good, huh?
See, you can't force it out even when you try right?
Let's give you more.
Let's do it more like this.
Let's not forget about here either.
We'll gradually make it stronger for you!
See.
This too.
Open your legs!
Just like this, huh?
That's the spot huh?
Yea, more!
What do you think of it?
Yea!
You pushed it out.
Are you ready? let's begin.
What a pleasant sent.
Does it feel good?
Alright, let's begin down there.
You like it don't you?
Let's get faster, see.
It doesn't feel good gentle right?
You prefer it harder don't you?
See.
What is it?
You hear that nasty sound your making.
See, your starting to feel it now.
Let's try something better.
You'd like us to continue right?
You don't want more?
Look at me!
Just give me the look and we can carry on.
Yea!
See.
Like this?
Now, let's try a different massage.
Let's lather this up a lot.
Have a good look at yourself.
How's that?
Give it to her faster & harder!
Does it feel good? You know that you want more.
See.
What is it? Your quivering. Huh?
Let's hit the spot. Here! See, you're sexy voice says that you like it.
How about here?
Have a seat.
Hello. Calling so late, what's up?
Hello, Hey!
Sorry bout that, I was a little dazed.
Are you alright?
Yea, I'm fine.
Uh, as I was saying before.
Some one called…
This Sunday…
Mr.Sakakibara will come over.
Sakakibara?
Yea, he said that he was a friend of yours.
I got it. On Sunday ok.
Uh, I gotta go.
Lye down, lye down.
Please do it yourself with all you can.
Hey, use your hand too.
Uh, yea that's it.
Leave your mouth open!
See, he came for you.
Ok, spit it out into your hand.
Long time no see. Same here. Sorry about the visit. No trouble.
What are you doing now?
I'm doing my best. I see.
So… actually.
I didn't expect to get a call from you.
I was a little worried.
Well, to be honest…
I wanted to talk to you because my previous business fell through.
Because you also experienced this.
Help me out.
Why thank you.
So… What a lovely wife you have.
Yea, but she's too good for me. She's a wonderful wife.
I would hope that your wife comes to visit my Salon.
Uh, yea, by any means.
But, recently she doesn't seem to feel well.
Oh, really? You would worry about that.
Thanks.
Keep quiet or else he'll bust us.
Understand?
You don't want him to find out do you?
Hold this.
Here comes.
See.
My finger feels much better.
Let's not let him find out.
Please be careful.
You're dripping wet.
You want it here?
Is that so?
I've got something to say…
There's been an 80% increase in ladies coming to the salon.
I see.
You see a lot of the girls will touch themselves while I massage them.
What do you do then? Well whatever the customer wants really.
What do you think? That's awesome, ha ha.
It feels great right?
Not so loud. He'll bust you.
Those kinds of customers…
They call me a god!
So my shop is a hit with the young ladies.
I'm jealous.
I'm too busy working to have any time to play.
So, how about next time…
You come to play at my place.
You'll get peace of mind.
I'll teach you…Oh!
Really.
I think you want more.
Your getting wetter.
At the salon…
Girls that want it are introduced by guys.
There are a few celebrities wifes that frequent as well.
But I…
Like them young.
I see… AH!
There's a girl perfect for you. She comes everyday!
She's addicted to my staff.
And utilizing him.
It's alright if you feel good.
Here, here. Welcome, please have a seat. Here?
Looking at me is erotic.
So…Sora!
Ah, You!
Ah, you have noticed.
What your wife really likes.
She likes to be man handled.
You… shouldn't watch.
It's best when watched very… slowly.
We saw it.
Ah, your quivering.
Does it feel good?
That's it!
Good girl.
What are you looking at?
You want it harder?
Have a seat.
You love being wet.
Let me touch you there.
Your nipples are hard.
Heavenly…
Hey.
Your husband is watching, open your eyes… quickly!
He watching.
Your getting into it!
Want more?
You want it harder don't you?
Let's slowly continue…
See, you may now do with her as you please.
Your nipples are sensitive, they're getting very hard.
Yea, what is it?
They're getting even harder.
This one too!
They're crazy hard aren't they, huh?
I'll massage you a lot.
Have a good look, he's watching you closely.
Such a good girl, huh?
More, huh?
What is it?
Your husbands can hear that juicy pussy.
Are you ashamed, huh?
You're gonna cum?
You always squirt when you masturbate don't you?
That looks like fun. Have a good look!
See! No, don't watch me!
Hey, your husband is watching everything.
You like that don't you?
You want a finger in it? No!
I'll do that, watch closely now. No!
No! I'm sliding right in.
See.
How bout that?
Huh, doesn't it feel good?
It feels great.
No!
See your husband watching.
Harder, faster, see, huh?
Next, let's turn up the heat you little bitch.
Yea, I got a good look at that asshole.
Why the quivering.
He likes seeing you excited.
You're the working it! See!
Your hubby want to see more.
It's a little embarrassing ain't it?
Huh?
It feels good right? You can say it.
Say it feels good, go ahead give it a try. No!
Say it or we'll stop.
Hey, louder!
Ah, that feels good.
Huh, Louder!
That feels good. Yea!
What is it?
Your dripping wet.
Get to sucking him!
Suck him off.
You wanna suck it.
Yea, that's nasty.
You love a good licking don't you?
See, he's gonna get nasty now!
You're making some sexy sounds for your old man.
Do it more.
That's nasty!
You love to suck.
Have a seat, She's not done sucking that hard dick!
Don't say a word.
You love sucking dick, keep it up. That nasty sound makes me harder.
That's feels good.
Is it tasty?
It's so wet and freaky.
That's great.
sucking dick hard aren't you?
See! Get in the middle.
Here's another dick for you, right here!
You like it!
Hey, don't forget to use your hands too.
Your hubby is still watching.
Mine too! Here, now!
Look!
Very good!
You seem happy.
Your husband can see all of my dick.
She's loving it.
No, let's get naked.
I'm so happy. Smile.
Now, let's get a dick in her.
While you suck on this one.
Have a good look at your wife!
What is it?
We know you want it!
What's up?
Say it!
No! Keep your head up.
Tell him to sick it in.
Don't watch me.
I'm in!
Sounds good.
That sounds about right.
Stick it in, please stick it in. I'm sorry hubby…
I'm sure your husbands excited by now.
You're excited so he's excited.
You're one sex addicted woman.
Let's have fun!
Let's have a good look at you riding that dick.
The other side too!
Let's show him more.
Your husband looks a little lonely now.
Have a good look. No!
Looks good doesn't it?
He's having a great time watching.
Don't watch me.
He can see it all.
See it all.
Oh, it feels good!
You wanna show him more?
Is it good? it's great!
No! What is it?
Ask for it, ask for more!
Give it to me!
It's ok to say it.
Shall we get closer to your husband?
He'd like it.
Take it from the back.
She's gonna cum.
Closer.
Give me more, give me more!
Ah, it feels so good!
Ask me for more.
Give it to me!
It's great!
I'm cumming.
Are you satisfied?
Madame.
Please come work at my salon.
You'll be a very popular girl.
After that…
We can oder some advertising for you.
One month later.
You're a pro.
Now, madame. Let's take some pictures.
Look here.
Open up for the camera.
A little wider.
Where's your smile? Smile!
Smile more!
Next, touch yourself.
That's a better look on you.
Keep looking here.
Don't stop looking here.