No hello?
Hi.
This is all just
an elaborate plan
to get me alone, isn't it?
You found me out.
(wry chuckle)
We're redoing the floors.
It's her.
(thunder crashes)
You'll have to turn off
cell phones and beepers.
They expect me on call.
We'll be 20 minutes
at the most.
I can't believe
we're doing this.
We could still turn back.
I love you.
We're redoing the floors.
Okay, I'll start.
Due to agency-wide
budget cuts, the FBI has
to be very selective
with its Federal Witness
Protection monies.
You have our proffer.
Yes. Uh, very elegantly put.
Unfortunately, for my purposes,
I'll need more specificity.
Jack Arkins.
is part of a joint task force
with the Cook County
Sheriff's Office.
He witnessed and was pressured
to participate
in illegal activities
by other members
of his drug task force.
Some of these activities
crossed state lines.
He is willing to help the FBI
bring these corrupt cops
to justice...
And save his own ass.
Okay, maybe this was a mistake.
All right, all right.
I understand
Internal Affairs is
investigating this task force.
Why don't I just
let them do their work?
Because the state's attorney
wants to be reelected.
He's not gonna let
an investigation
of his pet project
become an embarrassment.
And what about the people
in this room who could benefit
from such an embarrassment?
I'll step out.
No. The Arkins came to you;
it's your case.
If you wouldn't mind,
Mrs. Florrick, I think
it's better to avoid
any appearance of a conflict.
* Stand up! *
(music filtering
through earbuds)
Hi.
Giada. Alicia, right?
Yes. Are you waiting
for someone?
Yeah, Will. They told me
I could wait down here.
Oh. Uh, he'll be a while.
Oh, that's okay.
You're a friend from college,
right?
Of Will's? Yes.
DePaul, third year.
Oh, you're in law school.
He talks a lot about you;
almost makes me jealous.
Don't be.
J. K.
Just kidding.
Nice meeting you.
* Stand up! *
* Whoo! *
ARKIN:
That's Hunter.
He set up the drop house
for the stash.
That's Brad.
He stashes the meth.
And, uh, Foley,
he moves the guns.
You have proof?
And where's this?
(chuckles)
Mr. Arkin,
at some risk to his own life,
took photos
of the task force's drop house,
and he will gladly share
the location
upon receipt
of an immunity deal.
You said there were other
corrupt cops involved, Mr. Arkin.
If you could study these photos
from these other busts.
I don't know his name,
but... him,
him...
...and him.
Him?
Yeah.
Okay. I'll need a week
to brief my superiors,
and then we can work
out the details.
Hi.
You're late.
Yep.
You're unhappy.
No.
I'm drinking.
Tony, you know this stuff
you're slipping me,
crime reports and evidence?
You ever worry
about getting caught?
Getting caught?
Mm.
Slipping you things?
(chuckles) No!
No. Why?
Just part of doing business.
Yeah. I mean, it's...
it's for a friend.
Some things you do
for a friend.
I feel like you're
having this conversation
with yourself, and...
and I'm just listening in.
No, I'm just... I'm just
figuring you out, that's all.
(laughter)
No, the only problem was
that Jackie got a piñata.
So we all went outside
in the middle of a rainstorm.
And swinging bats at a piñata.
Okay, where was I?
Why haven't I heard about this?
Oh, and Grandma was worried
about us using baseball bats.
So she made everyone use
these little wooden spoons.
PETER:
My wild and wacky family.
You're stuck with us.
For your first free meal,
you choose Obbie's?
Ray.
Ray Ernesto, hey!
Honey, this is Ray Ernesto,
and he works for the
mayor's office.
My children.
Hi, kids. Just wanted to say
that Rich is a big fan,
Pete, always has
been, and he'd love
to show his support.
I'd love it, but tell me
you gotta leave that
dinosaur, Tolins & Brauer,
come talk to my wife
about her firm.
Oh, that's right,
you're at, um...
Lockhart/Gardner.
Yeah, We just might
look you over.
Oh, Pete, uh...
"PE-Pete"?
(whispering)
(chuckling)
Keep eating.
Yeah.
"Pete"?
So what'd he say?
He said that, uh,
Childs' days are numbered.
(chuckles)
Wow, you're big-time now.
I'm just the flavor of the week.
He'll be telling the same thing
to Childs tomorrow.
Anything else I can get you?
Uh, no, we're
good. Thank you
So do you like it?
Do I like what?
Stuff, politics.
Um, I don't know.
I like what it can do.
(phone rings)
I'm sorry, it's work.
Hello.
No, thanks.
I'm sorry...
No dessert.
(sighs)
PETER:
What's wrong?
It's my client.
(tires squealing)
DISPATCHER: ...00, officer
down at 373 Elmer Driver.
MAN:
Hey, lady, stop!
...00, officer down.
All available units
reporting to...
Hey, Kalinda,
you can't be here.
What happened?
Out.
Out, and I'll tell you.
OFFICER: Dispatch, we
got an officer down.
Jack Arkin's down.
I repeat, Jack Arkin...
(sirens wailing,
tires screeching)
We raided this meth house, and
the shot came out of nowhere.
Top of the stairs.
Meth dealer named Gorman.
We'd been following him
around for six months.
Traded fire, we took him down.
Why was Jack through
the door alone?
He wasn't through the door
alone. We were there.
Just not fast enough, right?
(indistinct radio chatter,
car doors closing)
You excuse me for a second?
(indistinct chatter)
I'm sorry, are you really
blaming me for this leak?
Within 24 hours of our proffer,
our client was dead.
Yes, and we're very saddened,
but we can still get these
corrupt cops off the street.
By giving you
the stash location?
Unfortunately, he never gave
the location to us.
Okay.
Let's just chalk this up
as a bad first date.
ALICIA:
I'm sorry to ask you this now,
but you know our firm wants
to file suit against Cook County
and the City of Chicago
for wrongful death?
Yeah, they phoned.
I just don't want anyone to
think I'm profiting from this.
We worry Internal Affairs
will bury this
'cause it's embarrassing
to the state's attorney.
Give us a chance
to investigate it.
By bringing a lawsuit?
Yeah.
So you think I should do this?
I think bureaucracies
are often prompted
to action by the
threat of money.
KALINDA: The task force
was targeting meth labs.
Their story is that Arkin came
through the door first,
and then was shot
by a meth dealer, Randy Gorman.
Arkin ended up on his back here.
Then the rest of the task force
returned fire, killing Gorman.
But there's an inconsistency.
Lab found Jack's blood
mixed with his saliva
exactly two feet
from the body here.
DIANE:
Suggesting?
That he fell face-first
onto the landing,
then someone flipped him
over onto his back.
It was staged.
We'll need ballistics.
I'm on it.
Okay, so our story is this:
The task force discovered
Jack was gonna testify,
killed Gorman,
then used Gorman's gun
to kill Jack.
Yeah. DIANE: Let's finish
this off in depositions.
Cook County won't want
this in the press.
You're hot on this.
I'm friends with a lot of cops.
The bad ones hurt
the good ones.
So, this is a crusade?
It's a job.
And a job I'll do well.
Notice I'm here
as an invited guest
now that I'm a client
of your firm.
Yes.
Welcome.
Do you mind if I'm blunt,
Mrs. Florrick?
Always a pleasure.
I brought my business here.
I didn't have to.
Do you mind if I'm
blunt, Mr. Gold?
You brought your business here
because we're a good firm.
And let's both agree
on one thing right now-
there's a statute of limitations
on playing that card.
Fair enough.
This is Mimi Collins,
a 24-year-old art student
at Whitley.
Two years ago, she was raped
and brutally beaten
by her ex-boyfriend,
a Michael Placedo.
Well, if this is
a criminal matter,
Mr. Gold, you can
take it upstairs.
No. It's more of an allegory.
Placedo was sentenced
to 20 years in prison
by the state's attorney
at the time- your husband.
Mimi Collins went back
to college,
a happy, healthy coed
with nothing to fear.
Somehow, I feel this
will end badly.
Mm-hmm.
Glenn Childs,
in a general review
of your husband's cases,
argued that Placedo be released
with time served.
That is
Mimi Collins' body-
found two weeks ago
in a Chicago landfill.
Looks like your first
ad campaign. (chuckles)
It would be...
if it weren't for the fact
that Peter has decided
to wait four years to run.
(chuckles) Really?
Mm-hmm. He said that at dinner
with you and the kids,
he was worried about the
"seductive allure of power."
Mr. Gold,
who does the "seductive allure
of power" sound like to you?
That's right.
The good pastor, Isaiah.
I need you to talk to him.
He thinks he's trying
to restore your marriage.
Tell him you don't need that.
Always good to see
you, Mr. Gold.
Peter can't win without you.
You know that.
Peter only wins with your Good
Housekeeping seal of approval.
Voters need to see you together
up on that stage holding hands.
Good-bye, Mr. Gold.
(gunshots, beeping)
(whirring, gunshots)
Mr. Gorman got off
three rapid shots
on the task force lead man,
your client, Mr. Arkin.
All hit their target-
center, two high, one low.
And this matches
the crime scene?
No. My stairwell's
two steps taller.
I've adjusted
by lowering the C-stand.
Now, Mr. Arkin fell as he
was firing here on the landing,
while another member
of the task force
rushed in and fired
three shots from here.
(gunshots)
You all right?
Yes.
What does it say about me
that I find this exhilarating?
You're human.
And are we saying
that the task force
then planted a drop gun
on Mr. Gorman,
or, uh... or
was it his?
It was his.
Well, so how did this...
I mean, are you saying...
You're saying it happened
the way the police said?
Yes.
It wasn't staged?
That's correct.
And the...
And the blood and saliva stain?
You don't think Mr. Arkin was
flipped over onto his back?
No. My guess is that,
in the extremity of the moment,
one of Mr. Arkin's partners
turned him on his back
to check his vitals,
and they failed to report this
during the investigation.
You seem to accord the police
a great deal of honesty.
I do.
And you brought me
out here to, what?
Your firm asked me
to examine the evidence.
Well, we've asked you that
before, and you just said no.
That's true.
It's because
of my feelings for you
that I've shown you this.
I won't bill you for the effort.
Your feelings for me?
I was approached by
the state's attorney's office.
To argue against our lawsuit?
Yes.
I declined.
I think you should do
what you want, Kurt.
I think you should testify for
the state's attorney's office.
I wouldn't hesitate
to argue against you.
(phone ringing)
Let me think about it.
I'll go get my purse.
McVEIGH:
Yo...
(camera shutter clicking)
WILL:
So, here we are.
Dinner.
And I'm treating.
Damn right, you are.
(laughs)
I ran into Alicia Florrick.
Uh-huh. Where?
At the office. She seems nice.
Yes, and a very talented lawyer.
I'm sure.
I felt like I was intruding.
You felt like
you were intruding?
I don't understand that.
I felt like
I was getting checked out
by someone who had skin
in the game.
WAITER: Senorita
Cabrini. Mmm.
(speaking Spanish)
(continuing in Spanish)
He likes you.
I'm so glad.
You want me to translate?
I understood every word.
(snickers) Oh.
So, do you come here a lot?
My dad does.
Your dad?
Who-who's your dad?
If I tell you, you, uh,
promise not to freak out?
Okay, not only do you
have to tell me now,
but nothing could top
that introduction.
Ernesto Cabrini.
I don't know who that...
Wait, I do know who that is.
He's the fourth richest man
in Europe, right?
Third, not that we're counting.
So, men freak out about that?
Only the ones
who are uncomfortable
with their own masculinity.
Yeah.
Hmm.
WAITER:
Si, Senior.
What's your most expensive
bottle of wine?
(laughing)
DIANE:
So, there's no pressure in this.
It's just a deposition.
They're polite
and uncomplicated.
They're just going to want
basic information.
No one's trying
to score points.
TRISH:
Thank you.
(indistinct conversation)
CARY: That's good.
All right, good.
Cary, everything all right?
Alicia. Hi.
How are you?
Um... I'm fine.
I'm good, too.
Are you...
Do you have a meeting with Will?
No.
Did you talk to reception?
No. I'm here for you.
For me?
Yes, the deposition.
I'm working with
Glenn Childs now.
Hi.
How much money did your
husband make last year?
Uh... last year?
Uh, I don't know.
My guess would be $55,000.
And is it true
that you took a vacation
in Antigua last February?
Yes.
Do you remember
how much it cost?
No.
$8,545 and change.
That, ma'am, is over 15%
of your husband's
yearly salary.
I work, too.
Yeah, part-time
as a nurse.
That's an additional
23 grand a year.
ALICIA:
Just to save you time,
Cary, we would stipulate
to Mr. Arkin's involvement
in the task force's corruption.
Yes.
Thank you, Mrs. Florrick.
I know that you would stipulate,
but I'm looking to itemize.
Now, let's turn to your
domestic dispute charges
against your husband.
WILL:
Cute of the state's attorney.
Shows some unexpected wit.
Cary's a good lawyer.
WILL: You think we
made the wrong decision?
Not necessarily.
Let's see how well
he does against us.
What's Cary doing here?
Working for the opposition.
(chuckles) Smart.
He's drawing blood, too.
Look, I have some thoughts
about finding this secret stash.
Good. That could help us
with a settlement.
Keep us informed.
JACKIE:
Mr. Daley called.
Said he wanted
to call Peter before,
but he was too busy.
I knew exactly what he...
Would you excuse me a second?
Looking for a Miss...
Mr., uh... what was it again?
Goldman?
Gold.
Mrs. Florrick, hello.
I thought you might be able to
help me with a little problem.
Well, this isn't really
the place.
Yes. Unfortunately, this
is a time-sensitive matter
regarding your son.
Peter is questioning whether
to wait four years
before running.
No, he's not.
I'm sorry- he is.
And if we don't file by the end
of the week, we'll be forced
to wait four years.
You're not lying?
(repressed chuckle) No.
Sorry- I wish I were.
Pastor Isaiah talked to him.
Who introduced him
to this pastor?
I did, but not with
that intention.
Mr. Gold, there is one thing
you need to know about my son.
He is easily moved.
You need to prescreen
the people who see him.
And I will talk to this man.
Plan on making the announcement
by the end of the week.
Thank you.
Are you good, Mr. Gold?
Am I good?
Uh, I'm the best, ma'am.
I will need you to be.
(elegant music playing,
guests chatting)
Shalom.
Objection.
Plaintiff's counsel
has an ongoing relationship
with the expert witness.
That seems more like a reason
you shouldn't hire him
than I shouldn't question him.
I'm preserving
my objection for trial.
Mr. McVeigh,
on Tuesday last, did you
conduct an experiment
duplicating the April 16th
officer shooting?
I did.
And this experiment was
conducted at your farm?
It was.
In your barn?
Yes.
And this experiment led to
your conclusion that the police
investigation was accurate?
That's correct.
Are you familiar
with the FBI standards
for ballistic investigation?
I am.
Was this investigation
in your barn
in accordance
with those standards?
In most respects.
So, in some respects,
it wasn't?
That would follow.
So that would be a yes?
You are correct.
The assailant's firearm
was lowered through the use
of a C-stand?
Yes.
And the FBI standards
caution that a C-stand
is not a steady base
for a firearm?
I believe that's correct.
You believe?
Yes, I believe.
Well, then
let's move on.
In what other ways
do your home-spun
investigative methods
clash with FBI standards?
Do you need a minute,
Mr. McVeigh?
TRISH:
I'm sorry.
What are you looking for?
These cell phone photos
leave a date and time.
There.
Saturday, March 13.
How does that help you?
Do you have
your credit card bills?
* *
(dialing)
(phone line ringing)
KALINDA:
Hey, so let's say
I need to get into
a storage locker.
See how much fun
it is being a Fed.
24-hour court orders.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Here we go.
Who you calling?
Lockhart/Gardner.
Something on your mind?
Let me see your phone.
Why?
I want to see
who you're phoning.
No.
Why?
Because I don't like
to be questioned.
Mr. Arkin said there were
three other corrupt cops,
so we immediately
put them under surveillance.
This is you with
a Detective Anthony Burton
two hours after our proffer,
one hour before
Mr. Arkin was murdered.
And here you are...
Ten minutes later in his car.
So?
So, Kalinda...
There were only five of us
in that room for that proffer,
and one of us leaked.
Oh, so that's why
these photos are so important.
This one of me in the car.
'Cause it shows
me... leaking.
It shows you
in a compromised position.
With a man.
With a corrupt cop.
And yet I phoned you
to tell you about
the stash, didn't I?
Which I wouldn't do
if I were compromised.
True.
I guess I could
just be confused.
Good job, Kalinda.
Anything you can find
to tie it to the task force
would help.
Are you all right?
You sound like
you've been running.
Okay.
(quiet chatter)
Something special?
Just an $8,000 bottle of wine.
A what?
An $8,000 bottle of wine.
So you're a kept man
these days, eh?
I'm working on it.
ALICIA:
You just said the opposite.
No, I did not, ma'am.
Then I don't understand.
Well, I can't help
you with that.
Look, we found
your stash location.
You saw the police
investigative report.
You saw the crime scene photos.
So how did
Mr. Arkin's saliva end up
on the landing two feet away
from his body?
Why don't we take a break.
No, I think we're fine.
Do you have an answer,
Mr. Hunter?
You say you didn't
touch the body.
So how did he end up
on his back?
I want to confer with counsel.
ALICIA: If that'll help
you get to the truth,
sure.
(whispering)
Okay, no problem.
Mr. Hunter would like
to adjust his testimony.
Adjust?
Let's adjust.
I did move Jack Arkin's body.
And why did you do that, sir?
Jack was shot
and fell face forward.
I, then, after firing upon
and killing Mr. Gorman,
proceeded to turn Jack over
onto his back
because he was wearing a wire,
trying to nail us.
Where is this wire?
We gave it to Internal Affairs.
This wire will be
supplied to you
at the end of
the business day today.
And guess what, lady?
That wire that was
supposed to catch us-
it shows this thing went down
exactly the way we said.
So I'll be waiting
for your apology.
You know what I would do
if I were you, Alicia?
I'd prepare
for a season of losing.
(three gunshots over recorder)
(men shouting)
(three gunshots)
(shouting continues)
(recorder clicks off)
So they're saying this supports
their version of events.
I hate to say it,
but I think it does.
No, doesn't matter
if it supports it.
What do you mean?
Look at the incident report.
German was lying in wait,
gun in hands.
And within seconds of Arkin
coming through the door,
German was firing.
So it was a setup?
Well, the task force knew
Arkin was the first one
through the door.
They didn't need to kill Arkin.
They just needed
Gorman to do it.
Okay, wrongful death
is wrongful death.
So let's look at Gorman.
Did someone contact him?
Check phone records-
any acquaintance
in common with Hunter.
Please forgive the lateness,
people.
We'll get started.
Just come right in.
There you go.
And grab a seat,
make yourselves at...
At home.
There you go.
Mrs. Florrick.
Pastor Isaiah.
How are you?
Hello.
What can I do for you?
You can leave my son alone.
Won't you come in?
You say you're a man of God;
Then stop making him
feel this way.
What way is that, ma'am?
Like he's a bad man.
He is a bad man.
I'm a bad man. Even
you, Mrs. Florrick.
Who do you think you are?
You think you know people?
You just use the same words
with everyone.
Y- You just say "God"
and you think
you can make people feel bad
about themselves.
Mrs. Florrick, your
son approached me.
He asked advice from me.
I will continue to
offer that advice.
And I will do everything
in my power to stop you.
You don't know my son.
This is a phase.
You are a phase.
Then we'll see.
No, you'll see.
He's running, this year.
He's my blood; and I don't know
what your God does,
but it doesn't match that.
(knocks quietly)
Dinner.
We're never getting out.
Let's do it.
(Alicia and Will laughing)
WILL:
The first time we met?
It was a pool party, wasn't it?
Indoctrination- or
what do they call it?
Orientation.
(laughs)
Yeah, it was a
midnight pool party.
About a hundred law
students trying to
impress each other.
Did you swim?
No, I was too shy.
You were the one
doing cannonballs.
God, that is so embarrassing.
Mm-mm.
It wasn't at the time.
So... what did you think of me?
Ah... no.
What?
Dangerous conversation.
Well, now you have to tell me.
Come on, I'll tell you
what I thought of you.
(chuckles)
So Giada seems sweet.
(laughs)
There's a segue.
Yes, she is sweet.
And third year at DePaul.
Yeah, she's just
getting her retainer out.
(chuckles)
So is it always gonna be
this way, between us?
I want to say yes,
but I want to know
what you mean.
Just... talking.
Being casual and...
Blunt?
I like myself
around you, Alicia.
I don't like myself
around a lot of people.
You do.
It's an act.
It's perfected
over a millennium.
(phone ringing)
(chuckles)
Don't answer it.
It's just life again.
Yes, and that's why I have to.
Hello.
Kalinda, what's up?
No, I'm just with Will.
No.
Okay, I'll...
I'll meet you there.
Kalinda got the dealer
Gorman's phone records.
The night of the shooting,
he had two calls
from a Hank Lydell.
Hank Lydell?
Who's Hank Lydell?
No idea.
Kalinda checked, no priors.
I'm gonna meet her there.
Okay.
Nice dinner.
It was worth the wait.
We always have options, Alicia.
I'm just saying.
(sighs)
(crickets chirping,
dog barking)
We have no idea who
Hank Lydell is? Mm-hmm.
Or why he was urgently
phoning a meth dealer
an hour before he killed a cop.
It doesn't look
like an addict's house.
I don't think there is a look
to an addict's house.
Mm. What were you
doing with Will?
Having dinner.
Thank you for waiting.
Mr. Lydell is
right this way.
That's very unlikely.
Hank has some good days,
but his arthritis keeps him
from dialing the phone.
And you've never heard him
talk about a man named German?
No.
Who else has access
to the phone?
Here? Any of us.
Us?
Nursing care.
Hank has 24-hour
nursing care.
I have the graveyard shift.
Is there anyway to find out
who was the nurse on duty
the night of the
killing, April 15th?
That was... Trish.
Trish Arkin.
Did I say something wrong?
No. It's just that's
the wife of the deceased.
So our client did it?
She apparently warned
the meth dealer
that her husband was
coming to arrest him.
How did she even know him?
Apparently through the husband.
WILL: And the rest
of the task force?
Innocent.
Well, we don't know that
for sure.
But it does look like
it was just Arkin
who was stashing
the weapons and the drugs.
He realized internal affairs
was looking into him,
so he thought
he would make a deal
and turn on his partners.
And Trish?
KALINDA:
She was a battered woman;
Didn't want to enter
witness relocation
with her husband.
Well, that explains the leak.
When we counted
who was in the room,
we didn't count the wife.
Yep.
And you want to hear
an even greater irony?
Cook County wants
to avoid embarrassment.
They just made us an offer
to drop the case.
How much?
A half a million.
So Trish gets her husband
killed, blames the police
and makes a cool half mill.
Are we taking it?
Well, I don't think
we can get them any higher.
No, I mean,
are we taking anything?
She's guilty, and
she'll get off.
She's our client.
It's our job.
And at what point
is our job wrong?
When it fails our client.
So let's advise our client to...
to accept the offer.
(gunshot)
(buzzer sounds)
So I seem to be a suspect.
Apparently, internal affairs
is looking into my connection
with the Arkin shooting.
Yeah, I heard.
This stuff seems to be
coming from your lawsuit.
That's right.
So why all the questions
about what I do for friends?
What, you thought I did it?
Yeah.
Go to hell.
What?
What?!
Nothing. I just, um...
I'm sorry.
What is this?
Who really tipped off Gorman.
(Mic feedback)
One, two. Mic check, testing...
So, is this just an
exoneration victory lap
or is he going to announce?
Gail, you'll find out
in one hour.
Oh, come on.
Mrs. Florrick going to
be on stage with him?
(phone ringing)
Excuse me.
This is Gold.
(distant Mic feedback squeals)
I don't know.
They're not going to leave us
alone- the press.
(sighs) You're right.
You know, I was reading
about these murals in Sienna.
And one of them
showed good government.
People happy.
Buildings going up.
Courts making good decisions.
And on the opposite wall
was bad government.
It was the same people,
but they were...
They were unhappy,
the courts were making
bad decisions.
It occurred to me
that it only works
if people step up...
If you make the sacrifice.
Look, I was just
an okay state's attorney,
nothing special.
But I want to be a great one.
And I can't do it without you.
I don't want the kids involved.
They won't be.
And I want to work.
I want you to work.
(clearing throat)
A little more than a year ago,
I stood at this podium
and apologized to the public
and to my family
about a personal failure.
(phone ringing)
I made a very bad mistake.
I betrayed my marital vows.
Hello. Will?
Alicia, hi.
Where are you?
Peter's press conference.
Is everything all right?
Yes.
I was just thinking-
I don't want to go through life
and think something
didn't happen
just because
I didn't make myself clear.
I can't hear you.
I said I want
to make something clear.
Hold on.
PETER:
All those charges were dropped.
That puts me back
where I belong.
Okay, I just need to say it.
We've been up and down,
back and forth,
and I look at you, Alicia,
and I think that...
Will...
No, I just need to say this.
No.
Show me the plan.
The what?
The plan.
I get the romance.
I need a plan.
Not everything needs a plan.
Everything that matters does.
I have two kids that mean
the world to me.
I have the press.
They're just waiting
for a whiff of a new scandal.
And I have a husband.
Justice is what this job
should be about.
So if you want to cut
through all that noise,
then show me a plan.
Poetry is easy.
It's the parent-teacher
conferences that are hard.
Alicia, come on.
I have to go now.
Come on.
I... Okay.
PETER: Now I realize that
I cannot do this alone.
With your support, I hope to
become the state's attorney
of Cook County once again.
It won't be easy,
but it's necessary.
You're going to make
my life harder.
PETER: Change it we
can, change it we must,
because Chicago once again
needs a change.
Because Chicago once again
needs a new beginning.
I believe I am that change,
and I believe
that I am that new beginning.
Thank you for listening.
(cheering and applause)
(reporters clamoring)
Alicia.