谁管啊
Who cares?
The whole point is,
she never was in the first place, Billy.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
- 是的  - 抱歉 你说什么 大声点
- Yeah. - I'm sorry, what? A little louder?
是的
Yeah.
你说得对 不敢相信我竟然这么入戏
You were right. I can't believe I got so caught up.
我就是这个意思
That's what  I'm talking about.
You know what I mean?  That's it.
这个公园蛊惑人心
This park seduces everyone.
你只是比大部分人
You were just a little more...
更投入而已
enthusiastic than most.
你想当英雄
You wanted to be the hero.
我理解
I get it.
还有
And, hey,
在这儿发生的事
what happens here
就让它留在这儿吧
stays here.
This has been some real bonding shit.
我们即将成为兄弟了
We're gonna be brothers, Billy.
我很高兴
I'm glad.
真心高兴
Really, I am.
- 干杯  - 干杯
- Cheers! - Yeah.
- 威士忌让人们同桌共饮  - 好诶
- Whiskey brings us together. - Whoo-hoo!
西奥多
Theodore.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
你终于把咱带到地儿了 泰迪
You really landed us in it this time, Teddy.
你追踪到了那个婊子
You tracked down the very whore
让她带咱们去见迷宫的守门人
that can lead us  to the gatekeeper  of the maze.
然后你的记忆故障又坏了好事
Then your little  memory glitch fucked us.
嘘
Shh.
你和他们是同伙吗
You're one of them?
你干了什么
What have you done?
怀亚特在哪儿
Where's Wyatt?
怀亚特还没回来
Wyatt has yet to return.
你会在最后见他的地方找到他
You'll find him where you saw him last.
埃斯卡兰特
Escalante.
怀亚特在演习中失踪了
Wyatt went missing while out on maneuvers.
回来的时候
Came back with some...
满脑子奇怪想法
strange ideas.
他告诉我他需要我
He told me he needed me.
我不能反抗
I couldn't resist.
就像是恶魔本人控制了我
It was like the devil himself had taken control of me.
我们就叛变了
We mutinied.
我们杀光了所以士兵
We killed every soldier.
之后怀亚特杀了将军
And then Wyatt killed the general.
然后他准备杀掉我
Then he turned on me.
你确定事实是这样的
Are you sure that's how it was?
看着我 西奥多
Look at me, Theodore.
你记得吗
Don't you remember?
不 不要 求求你 不要
No! No, please, no!
不 不要 求你
No, no, no, please.
求你 不要
Please, no! Please.
不 不要 求你
No, no, please.
不 泰迪 求你 不要啊
No, Teddy. Please, please, no!
不
No.
No, no, I couldn't have.
You did.
And you will again.
这次我们会和你并肩作战
This time, we'll be fighting with you.
等怀亚特回来 你将会在他身边
When Wyatt returns, you'll be by his side
行走于沙海吞没之城
in the city swallowed by sand.
但你还没准备好
But you're not ready.
还没有
Not yet.
也许在下一世
Maybe in the next life.
沙海吞没之城
"City swallowed by sand."
我到过那儿
I've been there.
The maze is taking me  full circle.
The maze isn't meant for you.
But if you like games so much...
why don't you try one of ours?
Whoa, boy.
Okay, now.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, now.
Okay, boy.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Shh.
Good boy.
Ah!
Have you ever considered golf?
Might be easier on your back.
I don't like interruptions, Charlotte.
You know that.
I don't like hiking through the park in civvies,
but there's a delicate matter to discuss.
Theresa Cullen has died.
Slipped down a crevasse attempting to secure our information.
Ruled an accident.
There are no accidents, not in here.
With all due respect, not everything is a part of this game.
Then you don't see the whole game.
Or perhaps you can no longer see beyond it.
Ford's stories are engaging.
For some, downright addictive.
But for all of Ford's obsessing with the hosts' verbal tics
and convoluted backstories,
most of the guests just want a warm body
to shoot or to fuck.
They would be perfectly happy
with something a little less baroque.
- And so would the board. - That's why you're here.
You want my vote to push Ford out.
I like for these things to be unanimous.
After all, it was you who kept Ford in business all those years ago.
The narratives I'm interested in aren't Ford's.
You want to push him out, be my guest.
But no more interruptions.
I know where I'm going now.
I don't want to be disturbed.
Good luck, Charlotte.
What's the problem?
A signal from a system-tethered device.
It belongs to a behavior tech on leave.
There hasn't been employee activity
in that sector for weeks.
I'm guessing it's a glitch.
All right.
I'm heading out to take a look.
And keep monitoring till I check in.
I'm at the location where we got that signal.
Any sign of it?
Control Room, do you copy?
Heya, fellas.
At ease.
Freeze all motor functions.
You're awake.
Good.
You said this place was a game.
Last night I finally understood how to play it.
Okay, Billy.
Let's-- let's talk about this.
You don't call the shots anymore.
I'm gonna go find Dolores.
You're gonna help me.
And don't call me Billy.
Dad?
Listen to me.
Listen.
Charlie?
Charlie!
I don't understand. Why would she do that to herself?
Her cornerstone memory was overwritten
from the trauma
of her child's murder, Bernard.
We must sever that relationship and start over.
But how could she destroy herself over a memory
that you just erased from her mind?
Creatures often go to extremes
to protect themselves from pain.
Living beings.
Not hosts.
It is best
to not obsess over this, Bernard.
It's not good for you.
It would signal a change, a level of empathic response
outside what she's programmed to exhibit.
Something like-- like--
See, Bernard, this is what comes from seeking answers
to questions that are best left unasked.
They were hearing voices, talking to someone.
Simple cognitive dissonance.
They were talking to the same imaginary person.
Someone named Arnold.
Arnold.
With due respect, sir,
I'm not sure you've told me the entire truth
about this situation.
I did tell you the truth, Bernard.
What we do here is complicated.
For three years,  we've lived here in the park,
refining the hosts  before a single guest  set foot inside.
Myself, a team of engineers, and my partner.
His name was Arnold.
Our hosts began  to pass the Turing test  after the first year,
but that wasn't enough  for Arnold.
He wasn't interested in the appearance
of intellect, of wit.
He wanted the real thing.
He wanted to create consciousness.
See, Arnold built  a version of their cognition
in which the hosts  heard their programming
as an inner monologue,