Brought to you by Ramensoupsubs & TIME2SUB!
[Jan 24, 2010. 2PM's Practice room]
Translators: suebee, amirahd2b, hazyfiasco, jennying♥
Timers: jocelyne03, metalguy, rayne86, elle_SJ, ♣ taecmeaway, emilyyt, stg821
Editors/QC: swtsrwlove, melijay, suebee, stg821
[New Family, Ok Taecyeon!]
[Orientation invitation!!]
What's that?
[Invitation] [For the first filming of Family Outing 2, please pick up _____ before coming to Misari]
I don't think this person is going to like me very much.
Is that their place?
[Who?]
There's the address too! I should memorise it!
Really, Awesome!
What's wrong with you guys?
Oh, there's one more person...
[Taecyeon has one more partner?]
I have to pick this person up, too?
That person isn't a big deal. Just tell them to come out.
[The mood for this person is the complete opposite??]
I'm going to pick them up.
[On the same day, at a salon in Kangnam]
[New family, Yoon Sanghyun!]
[The 'orientation' invitation also given to Sanghyun]
Oh, what is this?
[Invitation] [For the first filming of Family Outing 2, please pick up _____ before coming to Misari]
I have really, really liked this person since I was young.
So, I will wake up at dawn and go pick that person up on that day.
[Sanghyun had a crush(?) on this person?!]
Please wait for me! Coming soon!
[On the same day, backstage at M--'s studio]
[New family, Ji Sangryul!]
[Invitation] [For the first filming of Family Outing 2, please pick up _____ before coming to Misari]
Why do I have to?
[Serious face]
[Orientation day, 2:30 AM, Yoon Sanghyun's house]
Sanghyun.
[Woosh~]
Who told you to come here?
Do you know what time it is? Why'd you come to my house...
You have to go now.
I have to go now?
This one?
My cosmetic products.
[Sanghyun's necessities
A variety of toiletries and cosmetics!]
Are you going to wash your face 4-5 times there, too?
You better not ask me to lend you anything then!
Is it that hard to carry these around?!
I will wash up whenever I have time!
[The hopeful dreams of the Variety Freshman...]
[Now he will drive himself to Misari]
Okay...
[The moment of Taebong's first step into a variety program!]
This is amazing...
[Amazed and
Inputing the address...
nervous...]
[2:53 AM, On the way to pick up the other member]
The person that... I'm going to pick up...
She's beautiful...
And she has a lovely voice.
I'm nervous.
[3:18 AM, Arriving at the person's house]
[Who is this beautiful person with a lovely voice?]
[Tense]
Who's this?
You're crazy.
- It's me, noonim.
(TN: "Noonim" is a formal version of noona)
You're crazy!
You're already up?
Wait!
[Triple set of "you're crazy," the haggard noonim]
What?
I said, wait!
-SH: Are you coming out?
-WH: Yes.
[Everything makes the Variety Freshman happy]
[Another New Family's house]
[The legendary first meeting of the Haggard Noonim and Taebong!]
[New family, Kim Wonhee!]
Where is he?
Why?
Come here quickly!
-WH: You have to carry my luggage!
-SH: Bring the luggage down?
Why are you bringing so much?
[Their first meeting, Triple 'You're crazy' + The Porter]
[A symptom of being awake at dawn?
The worrisome Sanghyun's unending laughter...]
My husband is sleeping so be quiet!
[Their first meeting consists of nagging
It's only one night! Why bring all this?
Just take it down already! Why are you here?
+ abuse]
[From the start, a perfect madam + servant relationship!]
Hey, wait for me. I need to put on my shoes.
I am awake way too early.
Hello.
From today onwards...
Hold on! Man, these boots...
[Scatterbrained]
Why are you at my house?
[The effects of shooting at 3 in the morning...]
When you get old...
You end up needing to pack a lot of stuff!
[An unusually large suitcase]
Are you traveling overseas?
[Standard size for overseas travel...]
What the heck did you pack to make it so heavy?
-WH: We have a lot things to do!
-SH: Oh we do?
I just threw everything in because I was short on time.
[Later, this bag will cause the Family's first ordeal!]
Oh, I see. Let's go!
Why did you have to come to my house? I could have taken myself!
What?
You're so weird.
I wanted to be your escort today...
Shouldn't both parties want that...?!
[This is going against the Variety Freshman's dream?!]
It's very cold.
[Wonhee-Sanghyun couple, departing to the first assembly place!]
Ok, before we go.
[What are you going to do]
I burned a CD for you!
[The common sign of a variety beginner, excessive preparing!]
If we think about our age difference...
[However, he's satisfied]
Would viewers really wonder about our age difference?
[In reality, they're 1 year apart
But in variety, their age difference is unmeasurable...]
It's ok, I'm going to win it all.
[Today, Taebong's turbulent life in variety will begin]
Just go straight?
-WH: Yeah, straight.
-SH: Okay.
[3:30 AM, 2PM's dorm]
Let's go.
[Taecyeon also going to pick up his partner...]
Finally, the long-waited Family Outing Season 2 has now begun!
I have a lot of hopes and a lot of worries...
[First attempt in real variety!]
However, I will work hard to make this the best.
[3:42 AM, Teacyeon is on his way to Chungdamdong]
[At the same time, a salon in Chundamdong]
[This person dolling herself up since dawn!]
I want to look like After School's UEE.
[Who?]
Taecyeon is such a handsome celebrity
[Taecyeon's female partner?!]
[We disguised her voice, but her voice is still so loud...]
Everyone in the salon should go down too, to greet him!
[Everyone will greet him!]
[Unnecessary mosaic!?]
Ah, come quickly.
[New family Shin Bongsun!]
[Feeling nervous to meet him...]
Why isn't he here?! Does he think it's okay to keep a lady waiting?!
[The car that's making the lady wait!]
[The lady frantically fixing herself]
Bongsun.
Why the heck are you at a salon when we're just going to Gangwon province?
What are you doing?
[That lady panicking...]
Are you here to pick me up?
Yeah.
What's with all that? Are you going on your honeymoon?
[Her honeymoon fantasy with Taecyeon is shattered]
What the heck is this? Jeez...
Ah, I don't know... I feel sad for no reason...!
[Who did she spend all that time dolling up for...?!]
How much did you pay for your makeup?
I always come here...
[She doesn't want even to answer...]
All the stylists were pressed up against the window thinking Taecyeon was coming...
But now they're all gone!
-Really?
-Yes, they're all gone.
[4:28 AM, SNSD's dorm]
[Bongsun's man, Taecyeon is here...]
[New Family, Yoona!]
It's so cold outside!
Here, coffee.
[Thoughtful~] [Brought her warm coffee..]
Thank you.
-Oppa, you drove here?
-Yeah.
I'm a good driver.
[Up till now, the most beautiful two-shot!]
It's only the two of us?
No, we have to pick up Kwonnie too!
Then should I sit in the back...
[Awkward...]
The two guys should sit up front.
I think I'd be more comfortable that way, too.
[The aftermath of their scandal...]
-TY: Our scandal is killing me.
-YA: Seriously.
Seriously. Because of you...
Do you know how many times I've been cursed out because of you?
I got cursed too. Even from my sister!
Poor you.
[Even her own family is suspicious of their scandal!]
My sister even said, "You're not lying to me and really dating him are you?"
Because so many people have been questioning me that even my sister wonders.
Yoona's sister, that's not the case.
At the moment, me too.
[At the moment, me too?!]
[What does she mean by that??]
What the heck does that mean?!
I think I have to be really careful from now on?
This ring! It's a ring worn by the SNSD members!
[Their biggest scandal, their rings!]
My parents bought me this ring!
[SNSD member ring]
[His parents' present]
-Take a close look!
-They're not the same ring!
YA: It's a ring worn by all the members.
TY: Mine is just a gold band! Hers is different!
[A press conference addressing their scandals in this early hour?!]
This is a Girl's Generation ring.
See! She says it's a Girl's Generation ring!
It's designed with heart.
[Please just let us live our lives in peace...]
Mine is just a plain gold band.
[Born to be single, Yoona?!]
I'm single, forever.
[Neverending music, Sanghyun]
[Her first emotion is embarrassment...]
[Serious]
Your husband doesn't do stuff like this for you, huh?
[What a terrible comment from the Variety Freshman?!]
Do you know a DJ name Lee Hyunwoo?
[The Variety Freshman talking more than the Navigation]
And here's the next song!
[Imitating Lee Hyun Woo]
Requested by Kim Wonhee of Seoul...
-We will now be playing...
-That sounds more like Seo Youngchoon...
Deeper than Love!
-When I listen to this song...
-Please go away!
I'll see you tomorrow. Thank you!
I have another DJ imitation...
[Did he prepare a script before coming today...?]
The song that is playing now is ranked 20 in our charts.
[Imitating Bae Chulsoo]
Richard Marx's 'Right Here Waiting'
[Both embarrassed...]
So embarrassing!
[So he does realize how embarrassing it is...]
Your mouth has talent.
-My mouth has talent?
-Yes it does.
[Sanghyun's mouth is blessed(?)]
It's not my mouth being talented, but when I hear the tone of someone's voice. I can figure out how to talk like them.
That's because your voice is on the same level...
- What level?
- What do you mean?
[Note: Wordplay with 'level' (gwa) and 'dept. of business admin.' (kyung young hak gwa)]
The Depeartment of Business Administration?
-We don't match well.
-What?
We don't match well.
I thought we matched really well, noonim!
Ah, my stomach!
[Has only aired for 10 minutes,
And the Variety Freshman has a character?!]
[5:26 AM, 2AM's dorm]
We arrived at our 3rd member. Jo Kwon. 2AM's dorm.
[2AM's dorm]
He lives in a really nice area.
[Calling Jo Kwon]
Sing a long!
- Hello?
- Hey, where are you?
I'm going down now.
Hurry up! I've been waiting for 20 minutes.
So?! You're in your car!
No! We've been waiting outside!
I'll be there right away~
What the heck!
Hey, why did your voice change?! Hey!
He's here!
Our third member, Jo Kwon!
[New family, Jo Kwon!]
The three of us makes Idol Family.
Idol FO!
Should we just have the three of us do the show?
[Yoona, Taecyeon, Jokwon line has formed!!]
That sounds good!
Everyone, please get in.
This car is nice.
It's my first time riding in Taecyeon hyung's car!
It's my first time, too!
Many people say it's their first time.
Where are we going?
We have to go to Misari now, to meet with the other members.
- You're really taking us to Misari, oppa?
- We're driving to Misari from Seoul?
Yeah, it's not that far.
Still, I've never been there before.
Oh really? We just have to take 880 all the way down...
How do you know it so well?
- You're really good!
- Seriously.
What?
Have you gone to Misari before?
No. Oppa, have you?
- No.
- Me too.
When I was young.
Hyung, but you lived in Boston when you were young!
When I was really young. During elementary school.
Is there also a Misari in Boston?
[Extremely difficult]
Egg...
[Bongson is sharing?
No, thanks. I ate half an hour ago.
No...
No, it's an attack!!]
For FO's season 2!
Big success!
[The bickering siblings, Bongsun and Ji Sangryul]
This is uncomfortable, huh?
[Peaceful Yoona, Taecyeon, Jokwon]
It's no joke.
I'm so uncomfortable now.
You guys please take care of me...
I don't really know anyone there.
Let's do our best from now on.
[Sticking together from the start, YoonTaecJo]
Yes, let's do our best.
[6:05 AM, All 7 Family members arriving at Misari]
We're doing Family Outing season 2 now, but...
[Family members are gathered for orientation]
Hey, you guys...
- Actually, it's hard for us to do this program.
- Of course.
In my case, I always film programs in the studio.
[On behalf of Family members, Wonhee starts...]
That's right! It's your first time doing something like this!
[First challege doing outdoor program!!]
Yes. So this eating fish raw image...!
Like I won't be in a comfortable and warm place anymore...
I'm going to have to suffer a little...
I've reached some kind of... turning point?
[Her words are correct... She's at the turning point of her life!]
We're going to do this together.
But we're going to need someone to lead us.
So we're going to vote on who gets to be the leader.
- Our fate will lie in our chosen leader's hands.
- We're under their control...
Being the leader isn't all good though.
They may have all the power, but they have tremendous responsibilities.
- Since they have to lead the entire family.
- That's right.
So we will choose a new leader each week through our votes.
The person you want to become closer with.
We actually already voted to rank them first to sixth.
This week's leader will be based on those votes.
Taecyeon's choices! First!
[The person who can stole Taecyeon's heart??]
Kim Wonhee!
-And the reason why...
-What the heck...
Because I've never met her before.
[A direct reason fitting for the Beastly Idol(?)!]
That's such a crushing reason!
2nd place is Yoon Sanghyun.
Because I don't know his phone number.
[The strangers that don't know each other's phone numbers?!]
You don't know mine, either!
3rd place, Shin Bongsun.
Because she's funny.
This is fun!
4th place, Ji Sangryul.
Because he's taller than I thought.
[He's only in 4th place because of his height...]
This is interesting.
I don't think he put a lot of thought into his reasons.
[Small thoughts, but big~ impacts!!]
Alright, 5th place, Yoona.
[Putting Yoona in 5th place as a friend??]
Because her fans are scary.
[The reason that goes straight to your hearts!]
Yoona's choice! 1st place!
Kim Wonhee.
-Really?
-Yes!
I met you for the first time at a talk show.
[Reason: A lasting impression the first time we met]
Yes.
You were so beautiful.
Even when we finished recording, the members and I couldn't stop talking about how pretty you were.
[Touched]
Your words are so precious!
Jo Kwon's choice!
-I'm feeling uneasy.
-First place is Ji Sangryul!
Because I feel like he'd tolerate my excessiveness.
Next up is Yoon Sanghyun's choice.
Third place is, Yoona.
Because it might have made her uncomfortable if I chose her for first.
Will she call me oppa instead of uncle?
You'd like it if she called you oppa?
Of course oppa is better than ajusshi!
Please look at her when talking.
- Oppa is better right?
- Yes
Try calling him oppa.
Sanghyun oppa~
Next is Shin Bongsun's choice.
Who has Bongsun chosen for first?!
Not surprising. Ok Taecyeon!
Please take care of me.
Ji Sangryul's vote for 1st place.
As expected, it's Taecyeon.
Next one is the last. It's mine.
Madam Kim. First place is Ok Taecyeon!
Congratulations.
Oh! So that means!
Today's leader is!
Ok Taecyeon!
[Orientation leader, Ok Taecyeon!]
Father, father, father!
we're happy even though we didn't get it.
Ah, my children! We're...
[My children?!]
So he gets to drop the honorifics?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
[The momentary joy of being leader]
No, no. It's okay, it's okay.
Father, show your dance.
[Apologize by doing the leader dance!!]
[The Nation's Idol dancing at 6 in the morning...]
Family outing, let's go!
[Family Outing 2] [A long-awaited departure!!]
[7:50 AM, Taking the bus to Gangwon province]
It's so nice!
[Jo Kwon struggling to talk to Sanghyun]
I don't really have a chance to see actors...
I have this illusion.
-So I...
-Look at his face!
I thought you'd be a gentleman!
Now that you've met him, what do you think?
He makes me uncomfortable!
What have I ever done to you?!
That's just how he feels.
When there's an age difference, you have to keep talking to become closer.
[grumbling] [grumbling]
But it's hard for young people to approach me...
I didn't think he'd whine so much!!
[King of whining Sanghyun?!]
[9:30 AM On the way to the final destination]
[Haven't slept or eaten since 3AM
Or had any food. The starving Family...]
[Wiped out...]
[A bit later...]
[It won't be an ordinary orientation]
[Many things will unfold in the backwoods of Gombaeryeong]
[Their unforgettable orientation...]
[But for now~ they're just sleeping...]
We're here!!
We're here.
I haven't slept like that in so long, my body...
[As expected from Weak Wonhee's condition]
[Yoona the only one still asleep...]
Yoona...
Yoona is unresponsive. She's in a coma!
[10:45 AM, Arriving at Gangwon. Current temperature, -15 degrees Celcius]
Wow, the snow hasn't melted.
[Deep in the mountains of Gangwon province, Gombaeryeong!!]
[An arctic wind blows]
[The Family's tough first step!]
[Wonhee totally covered by clothes]
I thought, 'Are the staff members in their right minds?'
[What did you think when you got to Gombaeryeong?]
What does OT (Orientation) mean to you?
They're normally exciting and happy.
But to drop us off in the backwoods, when it's so cold. For our first time together? I was so shocked.
You are all now in a village called Gombaeryeong in Gangwon province.
[Wonhee's turning point is starting now!!]
From here to our final destination...
[Gombaeryeong
Approximately 1 hour]
[Walking there will take approximately 1 hour]
[The road blanketed with snow]
[Who will be chosen to walk]
[The Family will decide their method of travel!!]
So only three of us will be able to get a ride there...
But there's 7 people in the group...
[3 people get to ride the bikes (vs)
The 4 that have to walk]
Just let the leader choose who gets to ride.
Father~
[Calling out 'father~' from here and there]
Great leader~
[Which 3 will the Leader choose?]
Regardless, it should be 'ladies first.'
There's 3 ladies, aren't there?!
[Ladies first?!]
[3 ladies,
No, there's 2 ladies!
no, just 2...]
There's 2 ladies! Everyone else are men!
[First, make Bongsun walk]
Let's just leave it up to the leader.
[Sangryul as the oldest, pushing aside Bongsun]
If the leader says "ride!" Then just go and ride.
Then just let those three go, then.
[The leader's final decision?]
[Selected for bikes]
[The 2 ladies...
and the 1 oldest member!]
If it was just 4 men walking, it'd be awkward. And it could get crude if it was just all men.
[Why'd you pick Bongson to
walk and Sangryul to ride?]
So, I thought it'd be more fun if Bongsun noona came.
Besides, Sangryul hyung is old and it'd be too hard for him.
So I thought it'd be better if he rode the bike instead.
[11:00 AM, The final destination, a mountain cabin]
[Speed enthusiast, Yoona]
[Shrieking, Wonhee]
[Sending Sangryul ahead in case he becomes a burden!!]
Such innocence...
It's hard looking that innocent when you're forty!
That looks so fun...
[Gloomy...]
[On the way to
Orientation...]
[The mountain road,
and the snow makes your eyes flutter]
[The 4 walkers!]
[Though tiring, exploring what Gombaeryeong has to offer]
[A peek at what Gombaeryeong looks like in the spring...]
[Using the bikes that Gombaeryeong's resident's use to travel...]
[11:15 AM, Arriving at the Family's final destination, the cabin]
-Thank you!
-That was so scary!
We got here fast, but it was so scary!!
Look! It's an igloo!
Did they make this?
[An igloo made from the snow...]
Of course, someone built this.
Yoona, try going inside.
You look good in it!
[Yoona looks good at everything she does?!]
Oh! It's warm!
[It's surprisingly warm??]
You go inside. Why did someone make this?
Oh, it's nice! It is warm!
This is nice. I bet kids hide in this when they come here?
So that's why eskimos live in igloos.
Wow, it's really warm in here.
I have a feeling we have to sleep out here as a penalty for something.
[Sleep in the igloo?!]
No way! Not in this cold weather.
[Wonhee will eat her words...!]
[A proper experience of the backwoods, the 4 walkers!]
HOW ARE YOU?!
I AM FINE!
[Out of nowhere??]
There's an echo here! Let's all shout out 'how are you' in Japanese!
[Bongsun, the only one enjoying herself]
-Why don't we just say it in Korean?
-Ok! Let's do that.
HOW ARE YOU?!
I AM FINE!
[Bongsun's voice fitting in with the backwoods?!]
SOMEONE CATCH THE ABOMINABLE SNOWMAN HERE!
[11:50 AM, Finally reaching the Family's final destination]
Hello!
Ah... snot.
Walking in the cold for 1 hour!
[Did you enjoy
walking for 1 hour?]
My whole body was throbbing and aching.
And my nose wouldn't stop running because it was so cold.
If the orientation is this bad...
I wonder just how bad it will be when we really start filming the show.
[New Family Orientation]
[1. Inspect personal belongings 12PM-2PM]
[2. Outdoor activities 2PM-6PM]
[3. Dinner and Show 6PM-10PM]
But my underwear is in here!
[Jo Kwon, bag inspection!]
Come here. Kwon, hand it over.
But my underwear is in here! Let me just take it out...
What do you think we'd do?!
There's not much to see. There's medicine...
[Backing away...]
What's all that?
Look, just some men's underwear... whatever.
Hyung! Why?!
Ow, the corner...
[The corner attacking Sangryul...]
What the heck is this?
[Wonhee discovering something]
What is that?
BB cream!
He used it all up, so he cut it open...
[Frugal idol, Jo Kwon!!]
-So even idols do that...
-I'll buy you another one!
[Even women rarely utilize every bit of BB cream]
Right, I'll buy you another one.
Someone just please buy me one...
Why do you have so much?!
-What is this? Vitamin...
-Pack! Face mask!
[Embarrassed]
-This is...
-Essence! Control essence!
[Kwon's bag exciting the women...]
Hand lotion!
[Interested]
You must be a BB maniac. He has 2 different types of BB.
That's eye cream.
[In Jo Kwon's bag...
Medicine, Panty, and hundreds of cosmetics!]
It's eye serum...
Men nowadays use eye cream.
[Amazed]
Like this...
[The revealing
Mystery Idol, Jo Kwon!]
Let's look into our leader's bag!
[Leader Taecyeon
Bag inspection!]
-Since I thought it'd be cold...
-Those hats are nice!
Let's all each wear one!
[The neverending spillage of hats]
Wow, so cool.
There's so many.
How many hats are there?!
[Everyone taking one for themself]
What's this?
Long johns! Tight long johns!
[The beast idol's long johns...]
He'll look like this!
Let's see you wear it!
Let's see you with it on!
[A beast wearing long johns?!]
Ok Taecyeon is so cool! Let's see you wear it!
Taecyeon would probably look better than this guy!
Where? Let me see!
His wallet!
[What's inside Taecyeon's wallet...?]
[Crammed with receipts...]
How much?
[How much money is in a top idol's wallet?]
How much money does an idol carry around?
How much is in there?
13,000 won!
(Roughly 13 US dollars)
[Unable to look?!]
[An overwhelming beast energy?!]
How old were you then?
I was 19.
What is this? What's this?
[His American driver's license...]
That's my American driver's license...
You lived in America?
He lived in Boston!
[In Taecyeon's bag...
Abundant supply of hats, long johns, 13,000 won]
Oh really?
He's good at 'shala shala'
(TN: 'Shala shala' is outdated slang for English.)
Really?!
I'm curious about what's in Yoona's bag!
[Yoona
Bag inspection!]
What's this?
-It's a doll.
-There's too much pink!
A book! 'Between Calm and Passion'
[Well-read Idol, Yoona??]
Oh! You read a lot! What's it about?
I haven't read past the first page...
Oh, this is so pretty! Yoona, put it on.
[In Yoona's bag...
Pink doll, unread book, pink ear muffs]
There's not much in here.
Look at Bongsun's. I'm understandable, but why did you bring so much?
Packing this much means she's trying to flee the country!
[Bongsun
Bag inspection!]
[Packing enough for an immigrant...]
Why do you have so much stuff?!
-What is this?!
-It's cosmetics!
-You really put all this on your face?
-Yes!
Wow, it's like wedding makeup.
[Marveling...]
[Focused investigation] [Bongsun's cosmetics]
No it's not.
Isn't this men's makeup?
[Men's makeup?!]
You use men's makeup?
Only when I shave.
It is! It's the stuff they put on my face when I go on shows! Let me see!
Do you use an electric razor?
No, a blade!!
-Stop it!
-I get a closer shave that way.
[Shaving girl, Shin Bongsun]
Sanghyun, bring your bag over.
There's not much to see.
Yeah, I'm done. Look through Sanghyun oppa's bag.
[Anticipating] [Sanghyun
Bag inspection!]
I'm really curious about what's in Sanghyun's bag.
-There's not much to see.
-I feel like he's a health nut. Like he carries around an acupuncture kit.
There's not much to see...
[CSI
The National Bag Inspector agents??]
Those are handkerchiefs. To dab sweat.
[Uneasy]
This isn't normal either. How can there be so little?
[The interrogation of the National Bag Inspectors]
Do you have another bag?
I don't have another bag.
-Really?
-Yes.
You don't have any cosmetics?
It's right there. That gray bag.
Kwon also had that amount.
[Sniff~]
That's... foot spray...
[Foot spray!!]
[The excessive, National Bag Inspector agent Kim Wonhee]
It's for your feet?
Hey what are you... hey!
I just want to see if it's good or not.
Oh, there's lint here...
Get rid of your corn!
Jeez!
That's not a corn!
[Saying whatever's on their minds
Bongsun and Ji Sangryul siblings]
It's a blister from my heels!
Your feet seriously smell!
It's a really good foot spray!!
Oh, it smells good!
What do you have to tell us?
I heard it's important.
[The leader has to tell the Family something??]
Let's just eat first!
-Since we're all hungry...
-Before we eat...
This house is heated through a wood furance...
What? So we need firewood to keep the house warm?
So that's why it's so cold here.
So we need three people to chop firewood.
Because we haven't been properly fed, we're not going to chop firewood.
We're going to chop up the staff.
[The Family hasn't eaten in 11 hours]
Did anyone bring ramen or anything?
I was thinking about packing ramen!
I have ramen!
Unnie, can we eat just one?
Don't we need to get Father's permission for things like that?
Can't we just cook and split one ramen?
[Sad...]
Hey! That's my ramen!
Let's just get our chore done so we can eat.
[The Leader wants to get the work done first]
Who's going to work?
Sanghyun can go then!
[What did I do...]
[The Variety Freshman keeps getting hazed]
You know how usually when there's an actor present, they get a lot of admiration and respect?
[The top actor having a rough time adapting to variety...]
There's no need for that. We play dirty here.
[I'm your sunbae in variety!]
Oh wow, look at him!
[Why, Kwon?]
Just be honest Kwon. What do you think of Yoon Sanghyun?
[Variety Senior Jo Kwon's impression of Sanghyun so far?]
He's a bit trivial!
[Natural enemies line?!]
[Glance]
Wait, why... Why...
It's stuff like this that makes me think that!!
[The harsh terrains of variety?!]
Explain why though.
I don't know if it's because he has such a strong character in his dramas...
Yeah, do that cool part from your drama.
[Perform one of his acts in front of Jo Kwon...]
[Courtesy of MBC] [2009, The role that shook the nation. Taebong!]
Ma'am!
I...
I've never tried to toy with you.
Say your coolest line.
[Try to capture that feel and perform it here!]
Wait, but seriously...
-Look! That's why he thinks like that!
-Stop whining!
Just do it?
Just do it, Sanghyun!
Cue!
Seriously, just do it?
[Whining King, Sanghyun!!]
He just speaks so carelessly.
Reenacting your line from your drama will help lift the mood here.
[Trying to carefully explain to him...]
Ma'am!
[Taebong?
I've never tried to toy with...
Nope, it's Mr. Trivial...]
[Taebong sinking into the variety pit...]
Doesn't Father pick anyways?
Yes, I will now decide who has to go...
Taecyeon. Just say it.
"You, you, and you! Go!"
[The Leader's words are law!!]
Then! First!
-You!
-Wait!
[Wonhee selected!!]
Just don't whine for now! Whine later.
Second!
You!
[Sangryul selected!!]
I'm sick...
[Sangryul had just ordered everyone to not whine]
Don't whine!
[Uneasy]
I'm really nervous...
Lastly!
You!
[Yoona selected!!]
Yeah! It's the Walking Team!
[Relax Group vs Firewood Group]
He's so coldhearted!
Taecyeon. Make your choices again. Quickly.
[Just in case]
Alright. Who?
1, 2, 3! You, you, and you!
[Of course] [Firewood group]
Go go xing! Go go xing!
Father is so cool!
I thought you were all so nice in the beginning...
Father has something else to say.
What?
Can you give us one ramen?
Hold on. I'm going to lock this before I go!
[The precious ramen that her husband packed for her]
Should I just carry this with me?
Don't say anything. They might figure out the combination.
[Serious...]
I know, huh? I feel like they would...
If not, they'll use the axe on it.
[They just end up taking the suitcase with them...]
-You guys are going overboard.
- You're really not going to share?
But we're family!
[At least give us one...]
[They left it behind!! The suitcase with the ramen...]
Close the door! It's cold!
Seriously, it's really cold.
[Good job, Bongsun...]
NO!
[Just steal it for now!]
I LEFT IT UNLOCKED!
[She wasn't able to lock it earlier...]
[The outbreak of the Family's Ramen War]
Get the crackers! Get the crackers!
[It's the ramen!]
[This is what happens when you starve them for 12 hours]
I can only find one!
THAT'S MY RAMEN!
[Struggle]
OPPA! RUN! RUN!
[Sangryun, running into the room with the ramen!!]
That's mine!
[Wonhee chasing after him into the room]
I hid it!
[Coming out after hiding the ramen in the room]
[Bongsun using her whole body to block her]
GRAB HER!
[Saving the cup of ramen!!]
RUN! RUN FAR AWAY!
[fidget] [fidget]
Run far away!
[Naturally weak Wonhee is already tired]
[Positioning on the ramen]
[The FO idols engaging in hand-to-hand combat]
[The intense struggle over the ramen!]
[The ramen at last...
ends up in Sanghyun's hands!]
Oppa! Run!
Put your shoes on and go!
[The ramen cup...
goes to the safe 2nd floor]
[But the war isn't over yet!]
[This time it's the crackers!]
NOT THE CRACKERS~!
[Even the crackers her husband packed...]
[Pained scream]
I wanted to savor that...
[Jo Kwon waiting for a chance to escape]
[No one is paying attention!]
[Time to escape!]
Yoona hurt her hand!
[Yoona leaps to her feet, sprained hand and all!!]
[Will they finally catch at least one person...?]
Kwon! Run away!
[Passing it to same-team Bongsun!]
[Naturally Weak Wonhee, losing consciousness??]
[Bongsun going to hide the crackers...]
[Sanghyun hiding upstairs]
[I will guard the ramen!]
[The 1st battle of the Ramen War ends!!]
Where's the ramen?
It's all gone. Just go chop the firewood, it's cold.
The firewood should be quickly chopped...
Please just quickly chop the firewood! It's cold!
Listen to Father!
[Unaware the battle is over and still guarding the ramen]
-Alright, we'll be back.
-See you later!
[Working Group] [Will now chop firewood...]
[Sanghyun's lonely war...]
What the heck am I doing at my age!!!
[The fight hasn't burned out for these people yet]
I'm going to run inside while they're eating...
Come here. Come and hide in here.
[The Working Group's counterattack]
[Coming soon]
-Yoona, let's go to work!
-Hide in here.
Pretend you're leaving. Don't look around!
Just hide in there.
-Don't go inside?
-No, hide inside. Don't come out.
[Yoona on ambush duty...]
-We'll be back.
-See you later!
[The Working Group pretending to go...]
Where's Yoona?
She already ran up the hill. Ah, to be young again...
[Yoona in the igloo hill?!]
Let's at least get one back!!
They play so dirty!
[The burning desire to fight, Working group]
[The Relax Group winning the first battle of the Ramen War]
I'll go get the crackers I hid.
Good job, everyone.
[All they have to do is eat...]
Let's boil the water now.
[They thought they were at peace...]
Boil the water and eat~
[But]
[Coming closer step by step...]
[The force of disaster!!]
[Totally clueless and running to get her crackers]
Crackers~ Crackers~
[She hid it so well...]
[Just then! Sangryul about to ambush them]
[Sangryul outside the window]
[Happily running back in her clueless state...]
[Caught!!]
HIDE! HIDE!! HIDE! HIDE!
[The outbreak of the Ramen War 2]
[The ramen they had won in war!!]
[Slip]
[The Beastly Idol twisting and struggling!]
[Yoona hears the news of the war's outbreak!]
[Wow! She runs fast...]
[They already have an advantage in this war...]
[The Working Group's perfect sychronized attacks!!]
[How urgent is he to run barefooted?!]
Ow, my feet are cold...
[Sangryul responsible for their win in Ramen War 2]
[Relax Group] [Unable to even chase after them]
They're not open?
[Wonhee even grabbing shoes...]
They're not open.
[Ramen War 2] [Working Group] [Victorious!]
[Dazed~~]
[The top stars even begging for one cracker...]
Can you just give me just one?
Don't come any closer!
[A situation they can't turn back]
Don't! HEY!
What? Where are my shoes?
Hold on! Peace talk!
Just give us one ramen!
We're not going to get anything done this way.
If you don't we won't have the energy to chop up the firewood.
I reckon.
Just give us one cup of noodles! The noodles!
You guys need to get your heads straight...
[Family gone crazy after just one cup of noodles?!]
Do you even remember who's this is?
Why are you guys being like this?
Just give us one, please!
- JK: How can we share that between all of us!
- SR: Okay, we'll split it in half then.
[Leader the mediator settles to an agreement!!]
I'll keep my promise!
Okay, call!
But where did one of the snacks go?
[Whereabouts of one of the snacks??]
- There were originally two.
- Unni's got one.
No... you took it.
You!! Stop lying!
Surrender it now!
[Ashamed...]
- Please just give me one.
- What are we? We're family!
Even if it's half a nut, we still have to share it.
Yeah we have to share.
[What family… I'm hungry...]
The dad goes first!
[When starved for 12 hours, there's no such thing as leader]
More, more!
You have to wait until we get back.
Sanghyun oppa can't even get some of this.
[It looks yummy...]
[2. Outdoor activities 2PM-6PM]
I even had the water boiling!
I reckon!
I was honestly so shocked.
[Deep regret...]
I was walking back from getting the snacks and I saw Sangryul oppa peaking into the house like this.
Even two of you in charge of protecting the food!
[Sanghyun who didn't even get a miniscule piece of the snack]
You guys are way younger than him and you can't even protect that…
[All Sanghyun did was hide upstairs, yet he's the only tired one]
Oppa are you tired?
You were so hyped up just before...
[The orientation hasn't even started yet…]
If it was a drama I was filming today, then I would've been able to sleep fine,
But last night I was up the whole time just thinking of things I could do today.
[Sleepless from feeling burden, the variety newbie]
So you only got 30 minutes of sleep?
Yeah, 30 minutes of sleep and then-
But this is all you've got?
[Variety enemies Yoon Tom & Jo Jerry]
Kwon-ah, do you hate me?
Yeah, we should talk about this truthfully.
What do you hate about Sanghyun oppa?
- I don't really hate anything about him…
- See he doesn't hate you…
Whenever I joke around with him,
[Why make enemies with Sanghyun on your first day of meeting?]
his reaction is just too funny. It's so fun watching him like that,
so whenever I joke around, I can feel his charm.
That's why I'm acting like a prankster.
If we want to keep the fire going all day, I think we're going to have to chop up a lot of firewood.
[After suffering the war, an already tired Wonhee]
Do you think you can do it?
Just get me that one, that medium sized one.
This one?
[Wonhee: Choosing an easy one even if it's only by a tiny bit]
You're really good at picking the really dried up ones.
You have to do it with heaps of force!
[Loose]
No no! You have to do it like this!
Yeah you have to swing your arm up.
[Have you never seen anyone use an ax before?]
I have a feeling the ax is going to fly off.
I'm scared!
Is that how you're meant to do it?
You can't do it like that!
You have a try.
Why are you playing by yourself?
[A sudden disliking for variety shows?]
That's why loners are always the last to be dead...
[A loner]
[I have to sleep...]
Yoona, have you ever done this before?
[First time chopping firewood for Yoona]
No.
Ok, well for the time being Yoona just do this one.
[Yoona also tired from suffering the war]
You have to be careful, just in case the wood flies off.
[Worrisome]
You have to do it slowly; you can't force yourself to do this.
Wait~! Be careful the piece of wood might fly off and hit you.
Just use only the strength you have, not too hard. Slowly.
[Delicate Yoona, will she be able to do this...]
Yes! That's good!
Take it out.
[First time chopping with an ax…]
That's good, really good.
One more time! Go!
That's the way!!
[Whoa!]
[We all thought she was a madam]
That's fine because we're going to burn it anyway.
[But she's got the blood of a servant, Hercules Yoona!]
Whoa she's no joke!
[All in one go!]
Look at Yoona!
She's really good.
Be careful!
Slowly… that's it!
[Hercules Yoona]
[Even just a giving it a little graze it shatters into pieces!]
Yoona you monster!
Ah it's so hot!
[A real servant…]
Take off your jacket.
[A higher level of wood chopping!]
You're a real man!
A man~!
Who cares about beast idols, this is what you're meant to be like.
Go and show us.
[An ax battle?]
Ok Taecyeon you don't even compare.
[If he couldn't use an ax...]
You're my number 1!
[Showing his manliness?!]
[Waddle]
Oppa!
[Alone sleeping, the loner?!]
Right now all the men are fronting up to a chopping battle!
I'm just going to sleep for a bit...
Get up! Get up!
Doing that is normal. You think it turns you into a real man??
Just go show them! Go outside!
OMG...
Right now, Taecyeon and Kwon are no joke.
Whenever I'm next to Kwon, all he does is make fun of me...
[A long~~~ day for the variety newbie]
Let's go!!
[Beast axing!]
If you do it what will I look like?
I just want to try once.
It's not as easy as it looks...
Bongsun-ah!
Yes?
Come quickly!
Ok Taecyeon is showing his manliness!
Wait for me!!
Do it once Bongsun comes!
Wait just wait a minute!!
Thank you for waiting!
[Hoping]
[Admiration]
You're not even a man if you can't do that…
[If he couldn't talk...]
[Anxious]
Wow!! You're the man!!
[A sudden change from Kkab Kwon to beast idol?!]
Whoa you looked so awesome!
[Beast wannabe, Jo Kwon!]
You have to do the rest.
Kwonnie is pretty good at this!!
[I AM BEAST KWON!!]
Sanghyun hyung, you have a try now.
[The Loner's ax skills!!]
Everyone back away, back away.
He's going to cause an accident.
Get away from him.
Sanghyun-ah, be careful!
When I say 1, 2, 3, you hit it ok?
[The loner]
[All day he's been doing variety by himself…]
Ok, 1, 2, 3! Hit it!
One more time! 1, 2, 3!
This is pretty easy!
I think he's annoyed again…
This is easy!
Oppa~! We got cold so we came inside… Do the rest for us okay?
[Solitary family, Sanghyun...]
You're telling me to do it by myself?
I bet he's annoyed.
[The difficult life of variety...]
I feel like I've been lured…
[But because of Sanghyun, they were able to have a warm day]
This is the first time I've felt the feeling of being a loner...
[Feelings when you had to chop firewood by yourself?]
...at my old age. I thought, this must be what variety is like,
and that's when I started to feel it.
And all of a sudden Jo Kwon started coming onto me stronger,
Instead of the talking back contests, but in the games...
I really wanted to beat him in that. Yes.
[So]
[Yoon Sanghyun's challenge against Jo Kwon!
Snowball Chamchamcham!
5 Rounds, 3 rounds to win!]
The winning team gets one wish from the loser team.
Whether it's a punishment…
[If Jo Kwon wins]
We choose giving them a snow rub!
[Sanghyun's team]
[get's a snow rub!]
Over there I saw a stream.
[If Sanghyun wins]
So we choose washing them with freezing water!
[Jo Kwon's team]
[get's a wash with freezing water!]
We'll get the two males for the punishment.
[A snow rub] [vs] [A wash with freezing water]
If it's two males, then you can do it with him!
Ok call!
[Leader gets to choose which punishment he wants!]
Think about it!
If you're talking about the water over there, that's sewage water!
[If Jo Kwon loses, they will use this water to wash]
Yeah exactly, so it's bad for your team!
I choose this team!
[Jo Kwon, because of his pointless talk]
I don't want to get washed with that water…
Okay! First off is Sanghyun hyung. Our team member Sanghyun!
[Finally, the revenge Sanghyun has been waiting for!]
We pick Jo Kwon!
Oppa! You can't lose to Jo Kwon in this fight!
Of course I won't, I'm an actor.
[Icy cold]
[Jo Jerry vs. Yoon Tom]
[Whenever Sanghyun stands next to Jo Kwon, he gets smaller]
I didn't do anything wrong to you!!
[I cannot lose any longer!]
[Snowball Chamchamcham!
5 rounds, 3 rounds to win!]
[Sanghyun vs. Jo Kwon!]
We'll have a staring contest before we start.
[Battle of the energies!]
Okay, 1, 2, 3!
Each of you say something to your opponent.
Kwon-ah...
I don't know why you're being like this.
Do it right.
[Getting pushed around right from the beginning, Yoon Tom]
Ok, let's go. Paper scissors rock.
Paper, scissors, rock!
Ok that's good!
[Flames blazing]
Ok, let's go!
The loser get's a snow rub.
Oppa don't give in!
[Eyes going cross-eyed?]
Kwon's trying to take you on for a battle of the energies!
Don't lose!
Go!
[He said he'll definitely beat Kwon…]
You just lost to someone 16 years your junior!
Ok let's go!
Ah.. it's cold.
[Nervous]
[Composed…]
Kwon keeps playing around with you oppa!
Yes!
It's okay! Kwon-ah it's okay.
You can do it!
This is how you do it.
[Wants to win so bad he's going crazy]
Jo Kwon, I'm going!
I bet this oppa is going to make a mistake out of this.
Yeah!!
[Why always a sad premonition about this…]
Kwon-ah! It's time! The time has come!
[I beg you…]
Kwon-ah, you have to be fast! Fast!!
[Suddenly become more aged...]
I'm liking this!
Okay let's go!
[If he loses this time, it'll be his last]
I beg you!
[Yoon Tom, Reaction is top class!!]
I'm going to get you now Kwon-ah! I'm going!
[Why can't he win just once…]
I'm so nervous!
[Jo Jerry's wall, wouldn't think it would be this high]
Fighting!
[Tries to get over, but stopped by
Jo Jerry's wall!!]
[It's only Yoon Tom…]
[A spectating wild rat?]
[Perfect!! 0:3!!]
[The winner's composure…]
[Now it's time for Team Sanghyun to receive their penalty]
The rules are the males have to get this punishment.
[(Penalty) Rubbing in snow!]
Ok let's go.
We'll just do their back.
[Just a little bit(?) on their back]
We shouldn't let them take off all their clothes, it'll just be too cold.
[(Pointlessly) challenging Jo Jerry…]
Don't take off all your clothes, just raise your top and we'll refreshingly rub it in.
[And leader Taecyeon pointlessly went to Yoon Tom's team]
If you don't like that idea, you can just take off everything.
[No for cheap sympathy!]
[Choosing the wrong team, now receiving the punishment]
[The addition of the wind]
[Even something the beast idol can't do easily]
So cold…
Make it nice and refreshing for him.
[He must be cold]
Kwon-ah when you do the back, you first have to rub on the soap like this.
You have to add the powder soap too.
[Uh…]
Rub it in thoroughly.
[Why did I agree to this...]
[Panic]
Time for Yoon Sanghyun's turn.
[What did I do to be in this situation…]
Get down.
[Sanghyun's first hardship to adapting to variety!]
Why are you doing it so fast!
[Crybaby]
[They haven't even started yet]
Where do you think you're going!
[Taebong, newly reborn as a variety star?]
Yes yes that's good.
We're not done!!
We have this one left!
Bend down!
[Snow: The method for Taebong to adapt to variety…]
[Variety shows…]
[I thought we just had to laugh…]
During the recording, I will show you what variety is all about.
[The words from the beautifully made up Taebong...]
Please look forward to it.
[Taebong's ups and downs of variety adaptation,]
[This is only the start]
[Memories of Gom Bae Ryung]
Do you think they will show this on broadcast?
I dunno.
[New Family orientation]
[3. Dinner and talent show 6pm-10pm]
[The Family who have been on empty stomachs for 15 hours]
I want this! I want this!!
[Generous dinner ingredients prepared in the living room!]
This one is OTL! OTL!
The meat you have is pork meat and one chicken.
One of these will be on your dinner menu tonight.
What?
You're not giving us both of them?
Producer, I am speaking on behalf of our mentality states.
If you are going to make us share this one chicken between the 7 of us, it will cause a riot.
[Impossible for him to manage the aftermath?!]
Even the cameras could eat this is one go.
[Glaring eyes]
The leader will take this challenge.
If the leader gets 5 questions correct, the pork will be on your dinner menu.
[Putting the pork meat on the line leader's challenge!]
You will use your body to illustrate situations animals are in.
Situations animals are in?
What's that?
Stuff like 'a broken-hearted lion'?
Like that?
Yes.
How are you meant to express that with your body?
Since it was our first dinner,
Everyone was on the edge about this since everyone was hungry...
I started to feel everyone's eyes on me.
Like, 'Taecyeon-ah.. you better do well...'
Since I was hungry, all I could think about was needing to do good.
[Leader felt tremendous responsibilities!]
The time limit is 3 minutes.
If the leader gets 5 answers correct, you will get the pork meat.
We will get Yoon Sanghyun to do a practice question.
[Why me of all people?]
[An elephant with pins and needles in its leg]
[Full of energy…]
Elephant?
A crippled elephant?
[Great actor Yoon Sanghyun's elephant with pins and needles in its leg!]
An elephant with pins and needles in its leg!
[Nicely explained and answered!]
Wait we have to arrange our order numbers.
I'm getting a really good feeling from Yoon Sanghyun.
[The hero of the practice question Yoon Sanghyun goes to the front!]
Yoona goes 2nd,
I'm liking this atmosphere!
Our younger friends have a good sense for these things so we'll let them go first.
[Feeling more confident after the practice question…]
I'm so nervous!!
[The determining factor of the Family's dinner menu the Leader's challenge!]
If there's anything you don't know just pass it!
Let's go!
Ready, go!
[A constipated skunk]
[Lost for a moment…]
Skunk!
[The acting is becoming more and more drastic!]
A constipated skunk!
[A hedgehog that's been pricked by its own prickle]
Hedgehog!
Hit by the side…?
A pricked hedgehog!
[Unexpectedly delaying the team, these two people!]
Pass!! I don't know!!!
[Just about to burst into frustration...]
You were nearly there!
[What question will it be this time?]
[A crying tiger because it's hungry]
Tiger!
A tiger with a stomach ache!
No!
[Everyone bursts into laughter!]
A crying tiger because it's hungry!
[Two questions (complete)]
[The queen of body comedy]
[Bongsun's question is?]
[What on Earth…?]
[A bald eagle that has had a hair transplant]
A bald eagle!
[Has half the answer correct!]
[Yoona bursting into laughter after reading the question]
A bald eagle that has had a hair transplant?
[Wow~ Genius Taecyeon…!]
[Ah~ What the heck~!!]
[An encephalitis-bearing mosquito]
T/N: Encephalitis: an acute inflammation of the brain
[After reading another weird question again clutching onto her stomach laughing!]
Mosquito!
[Working hard Mrs. Kim!]
[Still laughing her head off]
[Ones you don't know, quickly reject!]
[A frog with a hoarse throat]
A frog.
An aged frog!
[This is so frustrating they probably will age…]
[A reddening face!]
A frog with asthma!
PASS!
[In the end, getting a hoarse throat himself…]
[A kangaroo abandoning her child]
Kangaroo!
A kangaroo abandoning her child!
[4 questions complete!]
[Only one question left!]
[But time is running out!]
[A giraffe with a herniated disc in the neck]
An ostrich!
[Already 5 seconds gone!]
Giraffe?
[The plentiful pork meat right in view!]
[Leader]
[We beg you, get the answer right…!]
A giraffe with a herniated disc in the neck!!
[He succeeds within a second before the time limit!]
[The last dinner that tops the orientation!]
Head of the household, head of the household!
[Can't even dream of this in the original recording... !]
[You may enjoy yourself only up until this time...]
[As promised, pork is provided!]
Ah, so tasty!
I heard that Yoon Sanghyun is very good at cooking!
[The so called Yoon Chef...?]
[Really?]
I boasted in front of Wonhee noona and Sangryul hyung. "I'm really good at cooking!"
[They say you're confident in cooking...]
[With that one statement, he's become the OT's main chef...!]
Oh, Sangryul getting ready to go now.
How are you supposed to cut the vegetables?
[They're curious about his skills first...]
For the zucchini, cut it in half first.
[With a sincere explanation...]
And cut it.
[However...]
Are you feeling dizzy?
[His cutting skills are a bit off...?]
It's frozen.
[Yoon Chef makes the people that are watching nervous]
Do it slowly, slowly.
Now, for the thickness...
[Different explanation...]
The thickness is different for all of them.
[Different action...!]
Wait just a minute.
I'm working in a very poor environment right now.
It's nice and warm, what're you talking about?
From what I see, Kwon's skills aren't that bad either.
[How are Jo Kwon's cutting skills?]
[Calm and detailed...!]
I think Kwon's better at cutting.
[Perplexed]
It's because I'm excited.
You were in a cooking club?
Yes, cooking club.
[During his high school career, he was in the cooking club!]
Ah, so you were in the cooking club!
[A new side of Jo Kwon!]
Look at this, look at this.
[A comparison of the two skills!]
[Yoon Sanghyun]
[Different sizes]
[Jo Kwon]
[Uniform]
But which one do you think is easier to eat?
Of course the uniform ones!
They are uniform!
[There's nothing going right for him...]
Ah, all he's doing is cooking with his mouth!
[What the...]
Then how about our Taecyeon?
[Head of the Household] [Taecyeon's cutting skills?]
Teach me how to cut carrots.
Eh?
[What...?]
Just try it yourself.
[He's a beginner chef that doesn't know how to cut carrots...?]
Do you want to put the carrots into a salad or into a noddle dish?
[Yoon Chef attempts to help anyway!]
Noodles!
Then for the noodles, you need to cut it into sticks!
Wait, how?
What does Ok Taecyeon think cutting strips of carrots look like?
[He cuts it into sticks for the first time...]
Careful, careful.
[What the...?]
Oh, he's good!
What is this!
[Is he really a beginner?]
Who are you?!
[I'm the head of the household!]
[Smile]
Romantic guy!
First of all, according to the rules, the rules, it's almost like the rules...
[The clear sound of the cutting board!]
The cutting board makes a very steady sound.
[Yoon Sanghyun is nervous right now!]
Next.
He's the one that's called the chef but he's doing it all..
He's good.
[Taecyeon, who once asked how to cut the carrots!]
He's got talent with his hands.
[Does he have a genius gift in cooking...?]
Can you do it like this?
[Pause, Pause]
[Of course I can~ Noona...]
[Hard to believe...]
Do you want to cut it into sticks then?
Easy..
[Although it's hard to believe, they decide to watch...!]
[Shake~]
You could build a house with that!
[Spark]
What, I can't speak now?
[So why'd you say you're good at cooking...]
If you observe him, he's got female hormones in him and a bit of a temper!
He said he'd show us something today.
[Sanghyun, who said he was confident in cooking!]
[With the pork received before, he decides to make spicy bulgogi...!]
He didn't even finish mixing it all up, applause!
I'll mix it now.
He's not wearing any gloves.
[No gloves! There's a bit of an expert aura to him...]
Oppa, have you ever made wraps before?
I haven't.
All you need to do is bring the meat whole and cut into it.
Then how about Taecyeon try.
[Taecyeon attempts to make cuts in the meat...]
Oh, Taecyeon is better than I thought.
[He's definitely gifted...!]
He's good!
[Bitter]
[In Yoon Chef's heart, there is only jealousy and diversion...]
Oh, he's really good!
He doesn't even say a word and he's this good!
When you talk a lot, there's usually no use.
And you spit.
[Of course, Yoon Tom is caught by Jo Jerry]
[Taecyeon's surprising knife skills!]
[He quietly moves aside...]
Wow, looks delicious!
[Ok Taecyeon's meat goes inside the boiling water...]
Now it is time to fry!
Show us something, man!
[When will we be able to see Yoon Chef's skills...]
This is my first time trying this...
[What did you say?]
Wait, what do you mean this is your first time?
You're the one that boasted about your cooking skills.
You said not to worry!
Yeah, you don't have to worry. I can do it, honestly.
[His confidence is still very full!]
You said in front of the women's university, you...
I fried rice!
[He's the CEO of a restaurant in front of a women's university!]
Really?
He said so himself that it didn't taste good, the girls just came to see his face!
How was business?
It was great..
There weren't any other restaurants in the area, right?
There was one on a hill, and mine was right under.
So basically, there was only your restaurant in the vicinity.
Only the starving kids went there!
He's doing this out of anger!
I assure you, Taecyeon's meat will taste better than Yoon's spicy pork.
[It's cooking deliciously!]
[He tastes his own dish...]
[The taste is...]
It's good, it's good?
[Okay...?]
[The family shows sudden interest!]
[Jo Jerry tries first!]
[He's showing awe at Yoon Tom's food?]
How is it?
[What's this expression...?]
I can only taste the hot pepper paste.
[Yoon Tom is attacked once more]
[Bongsun tries this time...]
[Her initial reaction is good!]
Oh!
[But?]
Everything's great, except for the really salty part.
[Housewife Kim Madame's evaluation?]
[!!! It's getting saltier !!!]
[Unable to redeem himself]
[What kind of evaluation will Ok's wrap receive...]
[By looks, it is the best!]
[The taste?]
[Rapid Amazement!!]
Oh, it's good!
Don't cook more of that, stop!
[There's really nothing going for him today...]
Then let's decide who will cook tomorrow.
Let's let one person rest tomorrow morning.
[They all agree on one person...]
[Yoon Chef has nothing to say...!]
Then let's everyone take a bite of the wrap and express the taste in our own unique way.
He's not even ready and he's eating.
[The only thing I can give you, is this wrap~]
[For this moment, it is not 'This Song' but 'This Wrap']
[It goes down, down so well~]
[Bo bo bo bo ssam (wrap)~]
[Even has the sense to smudge a bit of charcoal on her face]
[Yoon Chef is in a daze]
Taecyeon!
What do you want me to do~
Are you talking informally to me now?
[Determined]
[Ah, this is!]
[Heartbeat's 'Wrapbeat!!']
[The taste that seduced even a beast!]
[2PM Ok Taecyeon has completely accepted the variety atmosphere!]
[But this man is still lost...]
[This time, an evaluation of the spicy bulgogi!]
[How will he evaluate his own dish?]
Oppa, how's the taste.
[Salty salty salty~]
[It's very salty~]
[A self torture gag song?!]
[How will Bongsun make everyone laugh...]
Oh man, this is what steals the rice!
Oh yeah, that was good!
[The orientation dorm is met with the night...]
[The family is busily preparing for something...]
[PD: Have you practiced a lot?]
I have to now!
[Who is the owner of this tail?]
[Ah, how surprising!]
[We will be revealing the family's special image now!]
Family talent show!
[Family 2 Talent Show]
[Who's this hobo?]
There is an enormous amount of dishes waiting to be cleaned outside.
During the talent show, whoever receives the most sponges will have to clean the dishes outside along with a partner of their choice.
Our Taec, are you wearing our hanbok?
[Taecyeon's clothes concept is hanbok? (traditional Korean clothes)]
Yes, I haven't prepared an outfit. (ancient tone)
[Why is he speaking in an ancient dialect all of a sudden?]
It somehow suits him!
[Contestant #1]
[Parody Dance Queen Shin Bong Sun]
[This song is... <A Doll's Dream>?]
Isn't this 'A Doll's Dream?'
[Is Bongsun changing her image to ballad...?]
Ballad...
[Huk, it's a Chuckie doll!!]
[A scary doll that is upset with love...]
[Slowly, she walks over to her love...!]
[This is the highlight!]
[She heads straight to him!]
[I was always there behind you~]
[I was always there!!]
[Bongsun Doll's 'Always Curse']
[Then!]
[A song with a strong beat!]
[Preparing to change]
[What is she changing into?]
[What did they see!!]
[Sexy Woman, Shin Chuckie!]
[This is a true sexy scare!]
[(Scary~)]
[It's such a burden to watch!]
[The sexy scare comes closer!]
[I'll make you mine!]
[(It's scary...)]
[She concludes with an extremely cute pose!]
[Loud applause and shouting!]
[She is definitely the queen of parody dances!]
How can you be so good from the start!
It's too much!
The producers are telling me to get dressed quick, they threw my pants!
[If you were to give an evaluation?]
I always thought Shin Junghwan looked most alike to Chuckie but I now think Shin Bongsun does more..
[But...]
Do you feel that you're sexy?
Wasn't it okay?
Well, this side...
My arm pits were a bit folded over, huh!
[Prideful Armpit?]
Ok Taecyeon-ssi, what did you think?
When she was going over to you?
It was a shock itself.
Honestly, did you like it or not?
Of course I didn't!!
Why didn't you like it?
[The person receiving the most sponges is chosen as the dish washer!]
Now, please give your sponges to Shin Bongsun-ssi.
1, 2, 3.
Please open your eyes.
[Comparatively Small]
[She receives 4 sponges!]
Thank you!
[Huk, the doll is bowing too!]
Don't do that, it's gross...
[My little brother says he's really thankful...!]
[The second contestant?]
Jo Kwon and I have prepared...
When we were young, our mothers exfoliated our skins.
[Message]
[To clean your body and remove dead skin cells!]
We will be expressing the love between a mother and her son.
[Contestant #2]
[The variety world's godmother, Kim Wonhee feat. Jo Kwon]
[A, this song is...!]
[A 90's hit track!]
[Cheoli & Miae's <Why Are You>]
[Slowly, they begin to exfoliate!]
[First, the son's restless dance!]
[The old style mother comes out determined!]
[Let's go!!]
[Jo Kwon handles any dance easily!]
[An oldie in her 30's, Kim Madame tries her best!]
[The atmosphere begins to heat up...]
[And Kim Madame begins to get tired...]
[An idea dance utilizing an exfoliating towel]
[Joke]
[Now time to combine dances!]
[But something is off...]
[They don't seem synchronized?]
[(Noona, you're off!)]
[Because of tired Kim Madame...]
[The prepared joint dance goes in a different direction!]
[Now, the conclusion!]
[Bringing up the memories of their mothers exfoliating their skins...]
[Either way, their conclusion is grand!]
[How many sponges will Wonhee receive...]
Ah, that was an impressive stage! However, Jo Kwon shone more than Kim Wonhee, even though it's her stage.
Kwon-ssi, you helped her out but if you were to evaluate her...
Ah, first of all, she got a few moves wrong!
[No wonder it was weird...]
I had to adlib this in.
[Jo Kwon's adlib helped the near failure stage survive!]
Yes, you seemed very surprised.
I was!
1, 2,...
[Now, time to throw in the sponges!]
Wait!
Why?
Is it so wrong that I missed a few moves!
[Trying to receive one less sponge...]
Yeah, you had feel!
1, 2, 3.
Ey, Shin Bongsun!
[You said let's not throw it in for us girls!!]
Okay, let's be honest. Let's not throw it in for the girls...
[It hasn't even been 30 minutes since she's made that promise...]
[But she doesn't want to do the dishes!]
[Tie with Bongsun]
[She receives 4 sponges!]
[And the stage continues!]
[Beast Idol Taecyeon! A transformation into a cute boy!]
[He's doing good...]
[Seo Taiji has arrived at the Family?]
[Yoona's shining dance parade!]
[What am I doing...?]
[He slowly loses confidence]
[As the variety athletes unleash their skills...]
[And the first day of the variety challenge comes to an end...]
[I have to enjoy this...]
[But it stays in my memories]
[There's just so much going on]
[It's my karma I guess...]
Hey, I could've done well but I held myself back.
Just wait for 3 weeks to pass.
I will exceed your expectations.
[Until the day he conquers varieties]
[Please watch over him...!]
[I will conquer variety!]
[However]
[A stricter trial than the first day!]
[What is Sanghyun's fate?]
[We will reveal next week!]