(Seomun Market in Daegu)
(They have various kinds of tasty food.)
Is it only the four of us?
That's right.
- Jong Kook and... - It's very quiet.
- I know. - It's better.
- It's become much more peaceful. - Exactly.
- Right. - That's true.
I'm sure you feel lonely right now.
- Not at all. - What are you talking about?
We don't feel lonely at all.
- I like this better. - Today,
the main theme in the Bromance House.
The Bromance House?
Please come to the Bromance House to find the brothers.
That's where your bromance will grow.
- Do we have to find our brothers? - Our brothers?
Bromance...
(Who will they be?)
- I think... - My brother...
is like a superstar.
He is very wealthy.
Is your brother also rich?
- He is. - I see.
He is quite wealthy.
Why don't all of us have a cup of coffee?
Our brothers are very rich.
Let's order about 20 cups of coffee.
Hello.
I'd like to order iced coffee.
- We need 20. - I want 20 cups of coffee.
- Thank you. - We'll be in the next store.
Our brothers will come and pay for this.
Please come in. Don't worry. It's all free of charge.
- Thank you. - This is on my brother.
Sir, please have a bite.
Open wide.
(Please feel free to enjoy. Our brothers are superstars.)
(Thank you, our brothers.)
- Our brothers will pay for this. - Right.
It's here.
(There they come.)
Hello.
- They are over there. - What are they doing?
(Let's see who Jae Seok and Kwang Soo's brothers are.)
My goodness.
(Jung Seok is Jae Seok's brother and Kyung Soo is Kwang Soo's brother.)
- Hello. - Hello, Kyung Soo.
(It's a dramatic reunion in Daegu.)
(You're having delicious food.)
What are you eating now?
- They're eating a lot of food. - Wait.
- Come have a seat. - Look what they have here.
We ordered these for everyone including the staff.
And you and Jae Seok must pay for these.
- We should pay for this? - Exactly.
Jae Seok, he said it's all on us.
We need to pay?
We both bragged about our wealthy brothers.
- Really? - Yes.
I can pay for this,
but I don't have my wallet with me.
Me neither.
- How much is it? - They didn't say I'd need money.
Actually, we brought your credit cards.
- What is that? - Wait.
(This is really my credit card.)
- Let me see. - This is really mine.
- What is this? - This is mine, too.
Your manager gave it to us.
Really? I lost this card quite a long time ago.
But the problem is...
- Did you really lose it? - Yes.
My credit limit...
I can spend only up to 80 dollars.
- Gosh. - Don't be ridiculous.
I lowered the limit in case I lose my card.
There's no card with an 80-dollar limit.
- So... - Yes?
- What? - Last time on Running Man,
I played that spaghetti game.
- I had to cut the pasta noodle... - I remember.
- as short as I could. - I think we'll win this game.
Aren't you shy, Kyung Soo?
We do such things often.
Yesterday, we kissed each other goodbye as well.
I know Kyung Soo well since we shoot a show together,
- and he's really shy. - Right.
Right. He's a man.
Kyung Soo is more shy than people think.
Why are you all flushed?
- You said we had a kiss. - He's really red.
I'm not sure if I can do this.
Isn't it a game people usually play right after they meet each other?
You're right.
- Then start. - This is...
(Jung Seok bravely moves toward Jae Seok's pouted lips.)
(He's embarrassed.)
(This is the ideal bromance.)
I'm eating now. That's so gross.
(It's only 2cm to Jae Seok's lips.)
(Can I get closer?)
Oh, boy!
Do you have to do that?
You did a good job. It was nice.
Jung Seok. We have good chemistry.
It was great.
- It's 1.2cm. - 1.2cm.
You just stay there. I'll come to you.
(It's Kyung Soo and Kwang Soo's turn.)
(Kyung Soo, just stay there. I'll come to you.)
(Too much pressure)
Kyung Soo. You cut the pasta.
You cut the pasta. Kyung Soo bit it off.
(No, our bromance is still in one piece.)
We kissed before parting.
(We kissed yesterday, too.)
You cut the pasta.
You cut the pasta. Kyung Soo bit it off.
- Kyung Soo bit it off. - Hey!
(We just kissed.)
Kyung Soo bit it off.
- Don't eat it. - Yes, that's it.
(I thought I ate it all. Where did that come from?)
Hang on.
- This is... - Listen.
Did that come out of his throat?
(Is it throat reflux?)
It's cheese. Stringy cheese.
- That's disgusting. - It's not.
- It's just cheese. Stringy cheese. - Stop it.
- This is a dinnertime show. - It's not gross.
- People will switch channels. - Did you have to turn me...
- into a disgusting person? - I had no choice.
- We could've won. - Gosh.
- Thanks for the food. - Thank you, Kwang Soo.
That's just for the food.
- You really did swipe my card. - Of course, they did.
(It's the real-name transaction system.)
We drank coffee, too.
- How much was that? - That bill was separate.
Two coffees, right?
- We all had some. - 20 coffees.
- 20 cups of coffee. - Why?
You don't usually drink coffee.
Let's pick a number, number 1 or 2.
Do you want 1 or 2?
- I'll be number one. - Okay.
- Number 1 and you pay, 2 is me. - Okay.
- The coffee lady. - The coffee lady.
Which credit card do you want? Number 1 or number 2?
(Kwang Soo already spent a lot. Will he pay for the coffees, too?)
- Number one. - Okay.
(Would you like to think again?)
- Did she pick mine? - Yes.
Just a moment.
My credit card...
It's still warm from the previous swipe.
(It's still warm.)
The look on his face... His soul left his body.
Thank you, Kwang Soo.
- Thanks. - 72 dollars' worth of coffee?
Thank you.
You can afford to treat Jung Seok and Kyung Soo.
I feel great. I do.
- You can head to the set now. - Can we?
- Shall we go? - Yes.
- Let's go, Jung Seok. - Okay.
(This is the bromance hangout.)
(This is the Bromance House where boys become tight friends.)
It's empty. No one's here yet.
Seok Jin, I want this.
- You don't even need that. - I want one.
Buy me this.
I will. I'll get you one.
- Sit down, Ji Hyo. - You want everything, don't you?
- You youngsters... - Sit down, Ji Hyo.
(This is my ugly, little brother.)
- Buy me this, too. - Hello.
Kyung Soo and Jung Seok are here.
Brother! Brother!
He's older.
Hello. How've you been?
Hello.
(Today's teams)
- How are you? - Thanks for coming.
Jung Seok.
Hello and welcome.
Please welcome Cho Jung Seok...
and D.O.
- Do Kyung Soo. - He plays a judo player.
- That's right. - "Jealousy Incarnate".
How should I react to that?
Jung Seok, I'm envious.
- You must be pleased. - Not him.
His girlfriend must be pleased.
(He is the ideal boyfriend.)
- Good point. - You're right.
- You shot the movie "Brother". - Yes.
Today's race is about Bromance House and the friendship within.
Bromance? It's a trend.
Each team of two must do their best to avoid the final penalty.
- There's a penalty? - Only one team will go down.
Each team will complete a few, small missions...
and pick a total of four cards in the dealer room behind you.
There are eight different cards to choose from that come in pairs,
so that's a total of 16 cards.
Two of those 16 cards are Penalty Cards.
The team that fails to hand over the Penalty Cards to another team...
will pay the final penalty.
Is it a serious penalty?
The losing team has to pay for the food...
the staff ate with their own money.
- It's usually me. - That's...
That's Jong Kook's thing.
We're okay with that, but Kyung Soo and Jung Seok are guests.
- Do you have your credit card? - Not right now.
- Not right now? - No.
You should pay for him.
- The elder usually pays. - He's doing well these days.
Come on. You're a superstar.
- I'm proud to know you. - You're right.
- I'm proud of you. - You were a superstar for years.
I'm pleased he's here.
- What about you, Kyung Soo? - I'm not sure.
- You aren't sure? - Don't back out.
We'll send the bill to SM Entertainment.
They'll dock your pay.
Get paid the rest.
Before we begin the actual game,
we'll do a little something to find out how each team gets along.
The winner of this game will be given the opportunity...
to check one card before they take a pick.
- The winner of this? - Yes.
It'll improve the odds.
The two members of each team will sing a song together.
Extra points will be awarded...
to public displays of friendship and passion, so do your best.
- Jung Seok is an amazing singer. - He is.
Kyung Soo can sing as well.
- He's a singer. He's in EXO. - He can sing.
- He and I both released albums. - I recorded an album.
- Me, too. - Don't forget Haha.
- Ji Hyo's a pretty good singer. - I can sing, too.
This is the moment
(My brother's a musical actor.)
That's not how you sing it.
- Stop it. - Isn't that it?
- Let's pick the order. - Let's select the order.
Rock-paper-scissors is boring.
Let's pinch each other and the first to scream goes first.
Pinch the person next to you.
To the left?
- To the left? - I can't grab hold...
of Jong Kook's thigh.
I can't grab hold of any flesh.
It's impossible to pinch your leg.
- It's really impossible. - Try again.
- Do something to let me pinch you. - It's so unfair.
How about pulling this?
(How about pulling sideburns?)
That really hurts.
(Instead of pinching?)
- That sounds like fun. - It stings.
- That should be fun. - Do that.
- Let's do that. - Sideburn-pulling.
- Do you mind? - The hair right here?
Do I get to pull Haha's sideburn?
You can't pull anyone's.
(Why did you choose to sit there?)
There's no one to your right so just don't scream.
Come over here.
- Come on. - Grin and bear it.
- Grin and bear it. - I'm scared for you.
Jong Kook's pulling yours.
(You shouldn't be laughing.)
- Jae Seok. - If mine comes off...
- What if it does? - Kwang Soo.
We need glue on standby.
The puller goes first.
You might have a bald spot right here.
Tell me if you pull anything out.
Ji Hyo, tell me if you see him pull anything out.
Your sideburns are so soft.
- Don't do that. - Sorry.
- Let's take it slow. - One...
- Gradually pull harder. - On 1, 2, 3.
(The sideburn-pulling commences.)
(It's coming slowly.)
On 1, 2, 3.
(They feel it now.)
Okay.
(They're about to peel off each other's scalps.)
- I feel it. - Me, too.
(They can't sit still.)
Why you...
(Jong Kook pulled too hard and Jae Seok's out.)
Stop it!
- Shoot. - I didn't pull hard.
- That wasn't hard? - It wasn't.
- How was that... - Jae Seok's out.
Do I have to grin and bear it again?
- I want to pull someone's hair. - What for?
- I'm good at pulling hair. - I'll pull this side this time.
What difference does it make? Both sides hurt the same.
Good luck, Jung Seok.
Are you all ready? Get ready and go.
Get ready and go.
(Kwang Soo takes a deep breath.)
(Haha seems to be doing well.)
Why you...
(Maybe not.)
- What? - I can't stand it anymore.
Did you see that?
Kyung Soo.
- It's no joke. - It's not painful.
Kwang Soo's still...
He pulls really hard!
- Then scream. - He pretends to be nice then pulls.
Then scream.
(Two-faced Jung Seok)
- He pulls really hard! - Then scream.
Just scream.
- Let's switch hands this time. - Okay.
- In the other direction? - Like this?
What? What are you doing?
What are you doing?
(Their friendship runs deep.)
Why... You're just here for one day, but I have to shoot tomorrow.
I like this combination. This should be fun.
This should be worth watching.
- Now... - What?
I'll just grab the sideburns.
Then hold it like this.
- Well done. - What did he do?
Beware of Kyung Soo.
(He's planning something.)
- Let's play. - Are you ready?
(Target acquired)
Go.
(We sense a dogfight.)
Look.
(The giraffe's hunting the tiger.)
I love this. Keep it up.
(It looks like Jung Seok's about to lose a bit of his scalp.)
That hurts. That really hurts.
(Jung Seok's out.)
You got Jung Seok. Well done.
- The switch worked. - Did you see that?
- Couldn't you have kept it in? - Kyung Soo's no joke.
Kyung Soo, you pretended not to care but you're really into this.
- He pulls really hard with a smile. - I saw that.
- He never changed his expression. - Are you ready?
- These two are fun to watch. - Don't forget Kyung Soo.
- He's always smiling. - He's good.
- He has this poker face. - He's scary.
- Don't scream, Kyung Soo. - Ready?
Go.
(Round 3)
(Screaming)
(He screamed as soon as the game began.)
(Is my skin still intact?)
What?
- He pulls like... - I know, right?
- Like what? - We all felt it.
Well done.
Why are we playing this game?
Kyung Soo doesn't even flinch.
What is this game?
(Why are they so competitive?)
- You have to pull hard, Kyung Soo. - It already hurts.
- He's really good at this game. - Ready.
(I'm sorry, but I have to do this, Jong Kook.)
(Get back at him for me, Kyung Soo.)
Ready, set, go!
(Screaming)
(He couldn't get Kwang Soo's revenge on Jong Kook.)
Hey! You were almost there.
You were almost there.
- Jong Kook is so strong. - It really hurts, though.
- How is Ji Hyo doing it? - Ji Hyo is amazing.
Ji Hyo's side hair is about to peel off.
- It really hurts. - I know.
How are we the last two remaining?
One, two, three.
(The final match is between Ji Hyo and Jong Kook.)
Look at Ji Hyo.
- How is she taking it so well? - I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
(Will-power versus tiger claws)
- Oh, gosh. - Don't give up, Ji Hyo.
(She can't take it anymore.)
(Why does it hurt so much?)
- Ji Hyo. - It hurts so much.
I did it.
- I did it. - He's such a...
- Oh, gosh. - I'm sick of him.
- I'm so sick of you. - Ji Hyo's skin is about to peel.
- Gosh. - You sounded like you're swearing.
I won!
(Seok Jin and Jong Kook get to choose the order of the songs.)
Jong Kook is definitely my brother.
Ji Hyo did really well, though.
Which one do you want to listen to first?
- "This is the Moment". - Let's do that.
- You'll go first. - Is it our turn?
- Get up there. - That's our song.
- That's Jung Seok's song, isn't it? - Let's see how good it is.
I want to hear you sing.
You looked cool singing that song.
You have to do it.
You have to sing for us to get a high score.
- Here we go. - Gosh.
What's going on here?
Listen to our song.
- What are you doing? - Can't you see a singer on stage?
- I know that. - This is the moment
(This is the moment, this is the day)
- This is the day - He's got that special something.
Can you put the microphone down, Jae Seok?
- Be quiet. - Stay seated, Jae Seok.
And demons on their way
(I want to sing, too.)
You're going to sing the chorus, aren't you? Take his microphone.
This is nice.
(Jung Seok's sweet voice fills up the Bromance House.)
(Is coming into play, is here and now, today)
(Your turn, Jae Seok.)
This is the moment
(Jae Seok is about to ruin this perfect performance.)
When the momentum and the moment are in rhyme
(It's hard to sing seriously.)
- Give me this moment - Give me this moment
(Jung Seok doesn't mind the disturbance.)
(This is how a singer should be.)
Let's go!
(Get lost, Grasshopper.)
(Let me go.)
(All the dreaming, scheming, and screaming become one)
(They're screaming over here.)
(This is the day, see it sparkle and shine)
Can you give us your microphone?
When all I've lived for becomes mine
(He hasn't given up just yet.)
(Jung Seok's voice captivates the hearts of men and women.)
To prove to them I've made it on my own
(This is the moment, my final test)
(Destiny beckoned, I never reckoned)
(It's a magical moment.)
(He sings passionately.)
(The sweetest moment of them all)
(He tries to take a part at the climax of the song.)
(He's stopped.)
(Can I sing just one note?)
(When I look back, I will always recall)
(Moment for moment, this was the moment)
(The greatest moment of them all)
(We love you.)
(His singing makes a variety show feel like a musical.)
Cho Jung Seok. Cho Jung Seok.
(You're the best, my brother.)
- What's his score? - What's the score?
- It's 86. - What?
- Are you kidding me? - He wasn't his best himself.
What happened?
How is this possible?
There will be bonus points you can earn.
- This doesn't make sense. - They got 86.
- I tried my best. - You did very well.
(A mere machine can't grade the true value of his performance.)
- He's got that something. - He looked so cool.
- I think we lost already. - He was really good.
- Kyung Soo. Kyung Soo. - This is the moment
(Jung Seok left a lasting impression.)
- What are you going to sing? - We picked...
- "I Miss You" by Kim Bum Soo. - Really?
Please. Why are you doing this?
- Come on. - That's what you want to sing.
- What? - Let Kyung Soo decide.
We have the same taste in music.
Please don't sing that song.
- Does he sing it all the time? - What's wrong?
What's with this reaction?
- Just sing it. - Don't do it.
- He has a thing for ballad songs. - Whom do you miss exactly?
- I like that song. - Who is it?
What about it?
I like it, too.
Whom are you missing?
- We'll give it a try. - Go on.
- This is a good song. - Don't get immersed in the song.
Stop it.
(The actor brothers immerse themselves in emotion.)
Where's your bottom, Kwang Soo?
Did you leave it at home?
(They missed the very first verse.)
I think they failed already.
(They should be disqualified.)
- Like a fool - He's good.
(At this moment, he isn't an actor, but the lead vocalist of EXO.)
- That voice. - He's so good.
(She's happy.)
(Kwang Soo looks like the lead vocal judging by the facial expressions.)
(Kyung Soo sings with a sorrowful voice.)
- Why are you singing along? - This isn't your part.
(Kwang Soo sings with a pitiful voice.)
(He's very into it.)
(Stop it.)
(Can we listen to Kyung Soo sing?)
(I want to cry, kneel down for me)
(If it turns out there's nothing we can do about it)
(The others are being mischievous.)
(They have no idea of what is going on.)
(Approaching)
(You didn't see this coming, did you?)
(Keep disturbing us. We'll just get more emotional.)
(They're singing their lungs out.)
(People could listen to Kyung Soo's sweet voice all day.)
(And...)
(people would want to stop listening to Kwang Soo's voice.)
- Eat it. - Swallow it.
What's wrong?
Here it is.
(Kwang Soo and Kyung Soo scored 88 points.)
We got 88.
- How is that possible? - How did they do that?
"Did You See?" by Jeong Sam.
- Jeong Sam. - Let's go.
I wish you a pleasant evening.
This one is called, "Did You See?"
I put my heart into this song.
(What's going on here?)
One, two, three, four.
(Did you see? Did you see?)
(Why are we the ones embarrassed?)
(Is this how variety shows are like?)
(Trust your man)
(I want to say something, but I won't.)
This is how I feel.
What score did you get?
- 88. - Not bad.
- We're tied. - That was the best.
The look on Kyung Soo's face was hilarious.
Kyung Soo was like this.
(What's wrong with that old man?)
- In the end, he was like this. - You were?
- You were like that? - Kyung Soo must've felt like...
he saw his uncle singing at a karaoke bar...
on holiday season.
A drunk uncle.
He was looking at him with pity.
He was probably thinking, "I want to go home."
- Ji Hyo's singing's gotten better. - Let's show them what we've got.
(Coming up next is a stage by an aunt and an uncle.)
("Rose of Betrayal" by Uhm Jung Hwa)
(It's a collaboration between an aunt and an uncle.)
(It's a culture shock.)
(We will come in first place.)
(Haha and Ji Hyo scored 91 points.)
- They got 91. - How did they do that?
How did they get 91?
Honestly, you should deduce that by 10 points.
- Where's your consciousness? - Seriously.
- I said there are bonus points. - Right.
This was the criteria for the bonus points.
If other teams stood up out of joy while you were singing,
you'd receive as many points as...
the number of people who stood up times two.
- Multiplied by two? - Yes.
We should be the winner, then.
- What did you mean by "out of joy"? - These are the results.
Haha and Ji Hyo scored 91 points on the karaoke machine.
The number of people who stood up is...
(How many people in the audience got up from their seats?)
There were none.
You got 91 points in total.
Their performance wasn't fun.
Jae Seok and Jung Seok scored 86 points on the karaoke machine.
The number of people who stood up is...
(Their performance was greatly appreciated by many.)
Everyone.
(Jung Seok's singing received a standing ovation.)
You get 12 bonus points. 98 points in total.
What are you so happy about? It's not like it was because of you.
Kwang Soo and Kyung Soo had three people stand up.
You got 94 points in total.
For Seok Jin and Jong Kook, Haha was the only one up.
Did you stand up?
I did?
(I have no recollection of that memory.)
It was fun listening to you sing.
- Wasn't it? - It was.
I was watching them, but they kept asking if I was looking at them.
- Jae Seok and Jung Seok won. - Okay.
- We sang really well, didn't we? - Okay.
The first card will be drawn by Jung Seok.
Only Jung Seok can go inside to choose a card.
- I see. - Okay.
- Select a good card. - Trust me.
This is great.
(Jung Seok confidently goes into the room.)
(He strides inside.)
Here are the cards.
Since you won the game,
please select one card you would like to check first.
- I choose this one. - Okay.
(The card he chose is showing all of one's special talents.)
Now, please choose a card.
Okay.
(He can also choose the card he checked beforehand.)
- This one. - Please check the card you picked.
(What is the card Jung Seok selected as their first card?)
Please show the card to the camera.
(He doesn't seem happy about his choice.)
(His first card is the Penalty Card.)
(Even if he was in an advantageous position, he seems to be unlucky.)
- Did you choose a card? - Yes, I did.
- It's possible he picked a bad one. - Of course.
He could've picked the worst one out of all.
(This is the penalty card, isn't it?)
Kwang Soo and Kyung Soo are next.
Okay.
(Kyung Soo picks a card since he won second place.)
(Charm Card)
What is this?
(Forehead Kiss Card)
(Highway Card)
(Every team selected their first card.)
(12 cards remain. What will they face?)
The second mission is "Trust in Your Brother".
- What is that? - Now, this is sounds exciting.
The team that wins this mission can check three cards.
The 2nd place team gets 2 cards. The 3rd place team gets 1 card.
- You can only check them inside. - I see.
Younger brothers will solve the quizzes in the front.
Older brothers will sit under the trays and the trays...
will fall on their heads if their brothers give wrong answers.
- Trust in me. - I trust you.
- When you figure out the answer, - If you know it, call it.
you need to ring a special buzzer...
that the staff suggests.
- Okay. - I understand.
Before we start, I'll let you know the special buzzer.
Ji Hyo, be proactive.
The special buzzer for this round is charms.
(They need to show off their charms.)
We're doomed.
- No way. - You have to show your charms.
- Kyung Soo, show your charms. - Come to the front and show them.
- I'm sure Kyung Soo's good at it. - How...
- How will he do that? - Jong Kook.
- Ji Hyo, show us one. - I trust in you, Jong Kook.
Jung Seok is good at things like this.
- Of course, he is. - He's full of charms.
- He does have a lot of them. - Come on.
- It is a picture association quiz. - A picture association quiz.
Yes, I'll show you the first one.
In 1, 2, 3.
(What is it?)
- What is that? - It's a dog.
I think I know this one.
(The first problem looks difficult.)
(What is that dog?)
The dog is standing on a stage.
(They are speechless.)
What is it? I seriously have no clue.
- The dog is the main part of it. - Is that Gary?
(I figured out the answer.)
- Show your charms. - You have to show them.
Show them. I know you can do it.
- One plus one is a cutie pie - Come on.
(She always does that.)
(She's trying her best to show them her charms.)
Darn it.
(Darn it.)
(This is his third culture shock.)
- Look at Kyung Soo's face. - I'm her partner. I'm going crazy.
- Can Jong Kook try? - The answer is...
He can't see.
It's Gary.
(Is the identity of this dog...)
(Gary?)
- Did she say Gary? - How is that Gary?
(It's incorrect.)
(How can it possibly be Gary?)
It's a dog.
Can all the dogs be Gary?
Have you not forgotten him yet?
- No, it looks like Gary. - It's too late, Ji Hyo.
- The answer has three syllables. - What is it?
I think I figured it out for certain.
- Are you sure? - What is it?
"I love you, woof woof"?
- The first syllable is correct. - Right.
- Okay. - We know the first one.
- A cheering dog? - Isn't it individual skill?
Go, Jung Seok.
(They both get up at the same time.)
- Jung Seok was first. - Come on.
(Hello, I'm here.)
- Stop it. - Jung Seok got there first.
(We made this segment to see Jung Seok's charms.)
- Come on. - Why did you go up with him?
Jung Seok was here first.
- What did you say? - He's angry.
I went through all this trouble for nothing?
- Who said you were first? - Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You should've told me earlier!
He even looked scary.
- Jung Seok. - Should I show mine?
Yes, you need to show your charms.
Show them how it's properly done.
I showed them a lot of charms.
(Every woman has been waiting for this moment.)
(Only his girlfriend saw his charms. Now, he's about to show to all.)
- You'll do fine, Jung Seok. - Right now...
- What was that? - Gosh, I can't do it.
- Was that it? - He blew his chance.
- I can only give you one chance. - Jung Seok, just do it.
Why don't you pretend to be cute at least?
(He tries to be cute.)
- What is that? He can't do that. - It's acceptable.
That's good enough.
This is good enough?
- The answer is individual skill. - Seriously?
- Individual skill? - Hold on.
The answer is individual skill.
(Is his answer, individual skill, correct?)
(It's correct.)
(Everyone gets smacked by a tray.)
- Really? - How is that possible?
(He managed to get a point unexpectedly.)
- I see. - It is individual skill.
- Now, I understand. - Right.
It is individual skill. This makes sense now.
Excuse me.
You need to be more objective when you are judging his charms.
- Are you serious now? - He should go back if it's bad.
- Jong Kook's charms were good, too. - What you did wasn't charming!
(It almost made everyone turn against him.)
- I thought I was going to lose it. - I'll show you more later.
What you did was threatening the staff.
(He can get your money back for you.)
The next buzzer will be charms again.
(It's the same buzzer.)
It's a picture association quiz again.
In 1, 2, 3.
(What?)
(The picture is absurd again.)
- Is he skating? - He is skating.
(He's skating and it says "kick".)
- What is it? - Kick?
Kick, kick, kick, kick.
There are ten kicks.
Look at where 'kick' is written.
- The place? It's placed purposely? - Yes.
Think about the written letter and the place.
This is too challenging.
It is hard indeed.
Who drew this picture?
The last syllable is kick.
There must be syllables before 'kick'.
The answer should end with that syllable.
(I figured it out.)
- What are you doing? - What is it?
(Kwang Soo scared him.)
- What did you do? - Why are you so startled?
What's wrong, Kyung Soo?
What did you do to him?
- I didn't blow into his ear. - What was that?
- I didn't blow into his ear. - Hold on.
(He walks confidently.)
I figured it out.
(He's getting ready to show his charms.)
I know the answer now.
This is my charm.
(His charms are very straightforward.)
- What is that? - How can you call it a charm?
You can't accept that.
(He's showing all of his charms.)
- He knows the answer. - What is that?
(Am I not cute?)
Do a little more, Kyung Soo.
- Show them some moves. - This is not acceptable.
(He's trying desperately.)
He's not charming. He's acting out.
This is his best work.
- Okay. We accept. - How can this be acceptable?
- The answer is corner kick. - Come on.
This is the answer.
(It's correct.)
(They are smacked by the trays.)
- That hurts. - You can't allow it.
(He is feeling proud.)
Kwang Soo told him the answer from the back.
(Kwang Soo is teaching him how to cheat as a brother.)
The next special buzzer is dance.
The next quiz will be middle-aged men quiz.
- Is that so? - Ji Hyo's really good at it.
We are all middle-aged men after all.
Kyung Soo will have a hard time.
I don't feel confident about this.
What is another word for a letter of apology?
- I know this one. - I've heard of this.
Another word for a letter of apology?
I should know this one.
What is it? Another word for a letter of apology?
- What was this? - Do you know this one?
I knew this before.
- That's cheating. - You can't tell her.
(They are not hiding the fact that they're cheating anymore.)
- He told her. - That shouldn't happen.
(What is this song?)
(You know the dance moves for this song, right?)
(She dances as she wants to.)
- What is that? Do the dance move. - You need to do it properly.
(Don't you know Twice's dance?)
(It's evident she hasn't seen it before.)
What kind of dance move is that?
What was that?
That was not acceptable.
(Haha gets smacked.)
You're supposed to look cute as you put your fingers below your chin.
Hey, that's not how you do it.
- You only do it with one finger. - This is how you do it.
- Only one finger. - Look at this.
(She's trying to be cute.)
Try to be cute.
You need to do the next one, too.
(Darn it.)
- I'm done! - Come on, Ji Hyo.
- Why can't you do this? - Like this?
Have your fingers like this and move it like this.
- Hey, that's not right. - Give me a break!
- Hey, Ji Hyo. This isn't hard. - I can't do it.
- What is it? - Fine. I'll show you.
(Let's see how well you do.)
- That's not right. - You don't do it like that.
- What is he doing? - That's wrong.
- How can you mess it up? - What can the answer be?
(I figured it out.)
- Hey, that's cheating. - What are you doing?
- Jung Seok, it's time to dance. - Okay. I got it.
Jung Seok.
(He's good.)
What is that?
(His moves are out-dated, but he looks good dancing.)
(He pokes and spins.)
That was lovely.
(He's too enthusiastic.)
- Here we go. - Okay.
The answer is global.
- That's right. - Why is it global?
There we go.
- I understand now. - That makes sense.
(A person writes the letter as the person is being punished.)
- That was the right answer. - I see now.
Now the older brothers will be solving the quizzes.
- Okay. - Great.
- Do it well. - You did well, Jung Seok.
Gosh, look at them. I mean,
everyone out here plays dirty.
They're all gathered here.
(Dirty players are all gathered.)
The next buzzer is charms.
- Charms again? - The rule is the same as before.
- I'm ready for it. - It's going to be hard for me.
You'll see a picture.
You need to tell me the title and the line from the scene.
- Even the line? - The title of the film?
It's going to be hard to tell the line.
In 1, 2, 3. Here it is.
- Got it. - What is this?
- Hold on. - Line from this scene?
Do you seriously expect us to tell you the line from this scene?
- Hold on, the line is... - How is it possible?
It's the famous line.
This scene was...
- This is one of the famous lines. - Jung Seok, which film is it?
- Isn't this "Architecture 101"? - Do you not know?
- I think I know. - It's not fair...
to ask the line.
- You should not ask him. - I'll answer.
I'll answer it. Let me.
This is a famous line.
The buzzer is showing my charm, right?
- "Honey, I dreamed of a ghost." - Go away.
Get out of the way.
(Kwang Soo pretends to be sulky to act cute.)
I dreamed of a ghost.
(This is crazy.)
- Jae Seok, answer, please. - Okay.
You came out first.
- It's the movie "Architecture 101". - Okay.
(The movie is "Architecture 101".)
"What should I do?"
(The line is "What should I do?")
- What was it? - Was it "What should I do?"
- It was "What should I do?" - I thought "I can't understand."
He asked Jung Seok to tell him.
- It's not fair. - Yes, it is.
It's Nap Deuk, isn't it?
Gosh, what's wrong with your hairstyle?
- Spare it for your blind dates. - What's this?
(Then he says...)
What should I do with you?
Take this.
- It's Nap Deuk. - Try it, please.
"What should I do with you?"
I just remember this.
- Me too. That was impressive. - It was very impressive.
"Like this."
- Can he show us again? - Please show us.
- Oh my. - "Like this."
Please show us, Jung Seok.
(Nap Deuk's lecture of Kiss 101 begins.)
When you kiss...
Your tongue and mine slither in naturally...
like snakes. You know what snakes are, right?
And you rub them together.
(Rub the snakes.)
Rub them so hard.
Push forward and backward. Go sideways, too.
- It's fantastic. - "What should I do with you?"
"What should I do?"
(Thank you for your easy explanation of a difficult topic.)
- He's so good. - He is.
He is great.
That was funny.
- Now, it's the last question. - Let's win.
- You'll have to dance this time. - Okay.
What do you think of this picture? In 1, 2, 3.
(What does this picture mean?)
- There is a horse in the ear. - I know.
Is it an ear or what?
I'll try to answer.
I figured it out.
The song you'll dance to is...
(He can answer if he just dances well.)
(What is this?)
(Is it a dance or an exorcism?)
- That's not the right dance. - Get in.
- Why? - Get in.
- This is similar. - Aren't you sorry to Kyung Soo?
- I was doing it right. - Hey.
Kyung Soo.
- Please come here. - Please show us.
Let's see the dance of an EXO member.
Try to dance with Kyung Soo.
- Let's see all five dance. - You'll be surprised.
There will be no big difference.
Show us the original dance, Kyung Soo.
(Go, D.O. of EXO.)
(This is the original dance.)
(He is a mess.)
- Like this? - It is totally different.
- There is a big difference. - There is.
(Isn't this how you do it?)
What are you doing?
- What's he doing? - Didn't you see Kyung Soo?
This is it.
(Kwang Soo wants to hit him.)
- We will dance together. - To "Growl".
- Kyung Soo, watch us dance. - Yes.
Choose the best dancer.
(It's a dance competition.)
Kyung Soo should teach them how to dance.
You're in the way. Get out of the way.
Get out.
(Do you hear the EXO fans growling in anger?)
- Get out of the way. - Okay.
- What is this? - Haha gets the chance.
(What's Haha's answer to the picture?)
A horse riding game.
- What are you talking about? - What?
(It's the wrong answer.)
- Me. - Me.
- Me! - I'll answer.
Let me have a chance.
(The dance battle of "Growl" is getting fiercer.)
- Jae Seok, it's your turn. - Okay.
- A whisper. - Yes.
(Could "whisper" be the correct answer?)
I thought they were earplugs.
I thought it was words.
Everyone had a different answer.
Words, earplugs, a horse riding game,
- and a whisper. - I was wrong anyway.
- It was a whisper. - Did you think it was earplugs?
- We all had different answers. - I thought of a horse riding game.
- You did. - My answer was "words".
Mine was earplugs.
(They all had different yet wrong answers.)
- But it was a whisper. - Since the horse plugged the ear?
Yes, I thought so.
I thought the ear was hanging off the horse.
I went overboard and was mistaken.
(His idea was also creative.)
According to the final score,
the first place is Jae Seok and Jung Seok.
The second place is Jong Kook and Seok Jin.
The third place is Kwang Soo and Kyung Soo.
- I can't believe it. - It's okay, Haha.
(They currently have a Penalty Card.)
We need to pick the same pair, right?
Right. Choose.
Please choose three cards you want to check.
- Then will we be able to check? - Yes.
(If you choose the same pair, you can throw them away.)
You can choose three cards total.
I'll pick this one.
(The paired cards don't include the Penalty Cards.)
I'll choose the one at the end.
(Kiss on the Cheek Card)
(Tour around Daegu Card)
(Another Kiss on the Cheek Card)
(They are the same cards.)
The final mission is like that of Find the Robber game.
All you have to do is throw away all the cards that you have.
- We can throw them away. - Okay.
(The team without any cards will be the winner.)
(They have two Kiss on the Cheek Cards.)
(They have a chance to choose another three cards.)
Shall I pick another?
Please show the card to me.
- We should keep it secret. - I know.
- Let's choose one. - Okay.
(They check two cards and choose three.)
- Try to pick. - If you checked the two cards...
This is unbelievable.
- The cards... - We can avoid the Penalty Cards.
- I see. - This is great.
(They picked three and can throw away two of them.)
Choose the three cards you want to take.
(They checked just one card and try to choose three.)
(It's the Penalty Card.)
(Oh my gosh.)
You're so unlucky.
You should avoid this card.
(They have a Charm Card and a Penalty Card.)
Like this?
(Kiss on the Cheek Card)
(Tour around Daegu Card)
(They don't even have the same cards.)
(Haha and Ji Hyo automatically get the rest of the cards.)
(This is the status of the cards each team has.)
This is round three and it's the last one before the final race.
It's "Night Market Bingo".
- "Night Market"? - Great.
- There are a lot of delicious food. - I was so hungry.
The winner of this mission will get an Exchange Card.
You don't just check them but exchange them.
An Exchange Card?
You can exchange your whole stack...
with the team you want anytime.
- What? - The whole cards?
Anytime? Even right before the end?
Then this is an important round.
To survive...
- "To survive"? - What should you do to survive?
- "To survive"? - Is this the only way to survive?
- What do you mean by that? - Were you dying?
Well...
- You have a Penalty Card, right? - Kwang Soo told me...
to pretend not to have them.
(Kwang Soo is flustered.)
We don't know the result yet.
- Nobody knows. - They have them.
- I think now we all know. - No.
Using the hints of the pictures on the bingo board,
visit the relevant store and complete the mission.
The fist team to complete a row is the winner.
Every time you clear the mission, we'll put the sticker of your team.
You can't challenge the store with a sticker anymore.
- Other teams can't challenge it. - Really?
And from now, while you're racing in this round,
the staff will scatter around, visit stores and eat food there.
- The final penalty is... - Paying the bill.
- That's right. - Oh my gosh.
Before that, as a practice,
we'll let you play a few games with a bingo board here.
As a practice.
- Here. - I'll have an advantage.
Please choose a game that you're very good at.
- Something you'll definitely win. - I'm good at jegichagi.
(Jung Seok is a very talented brother.)
What should I do with Jung Seok?
He is awesome.
It's done. We decided.
- What is it? - We'll do jegichagi.
- Jegichagi? - Is he good at it?
- Yes. - Don't you need that?
What about enduring the pain after hammered?
What do you think?
(Do you want to endure it first?)
(They're practicing hard.)
I think it'll be okay. But it's too fast.
All right. Let's do this.
- Can I practice it? - Yes, you can.
There you go.
It's okay. Don't exhaust yourself. Get some rest.
(You can be an ace with only five in Running Man.)
We're doing jegichagi.
- Is he good at jegichagi? - Yes.
- He is good. - Is he?
This is samgyeopsal.
- This is rolled samgyeopsal. - It is.
In this game...
Isn't it sundae?
(Everyone can't help but stand in awe.)
- This is rolled samgyeopsal. - It is.
It'll be a random choice.
(Who are the hosts of the first game?)
Kwang Soo's team, go first.
- Yes! - It's them.
- It is face to face jump rope. - That's what you wrote.
That's what you wrote. In fact, if you put a snack in your mouth,
- it'll be more fun. - He's right.
- With a snack in our mouths... - Kwang Soo...
Because I'm short, I think it's not a good idea.
Then do as you wish.
We'll just do jump rope face to face.
- That is funny. - Okay.
- He's a new type. - Do something you can do well.
Which team do you want to fight with?
Jong Kook's team.
- We're very good. - Us?
- You're clueless. - You don't know anything.
Start right away.
Are you ready? Ready.
- You can do this. - Ready...
Does anyone want to cheer for them?
- No. - Okay.
No one wants to cheer for them?
- Right. - Why should we?
Ready,
set, go.
(Please get stuck.)
Go.
(Gosh)
(They failed to jump even once.)
This is great.
- It's done. - No. This is not right.
- We didn't even practice. - Okay. You got zero.
- I wanted some practice before. - It couldn't be helped.
- We should have practiced. - Stop being stubborn.
(Jong Kook can't accept his poor result.)
- If they score zero as well... - It can happen.
They may get zero, too. This game is quite difficult.
All right. Will anyone cheer for them?
- No. - I won't.
- He'll hit Kwang Soo with his head. - Get ready.
- Jump once to win. - That jump rope is really short.
Just jump once.
- All right. Ready, - They will fail.
set, go.
(They only need to jump once to win. Will they succeed?)
(Please fall down. I know you will, Kwang Soo.)
Set, go.
(That was a complete mess.)
What's wrong? You were better last time.
- All right. Then... - Please. Give us another chance.
- Another chance? - That's what we asked for, too.
No way. You can't practice before a round.
- Will you swing the jump rope? - Who was it?
- Was it me? - Yes. You got tripped over.
It's really hard to jump even once because this jump rope is so short.
Kyung Soo is really annoyed right now.
- No, he's not. - Let's skip once at least.
- Was it me? Really? - Get ready.
- That jump rope is too short. - Jump like this.
(It's their second time trying. They must be better than the last time.)
Ready, set, go.
We skipped once.
We did it. We did one.
- You sound so happy. - Just do as you did before.
Kwang Soo and Kyung Soo may lose.
You must skip twice to win.
I feel nervous only because I need to skip ropes just twice.
- They only need to skip twice. - Be careful when you jump.
Kyung Soo looks really desperate.
- Jump as high as you can. - Ready, set...
(Will Jong Kook's team win or will it be a draw?)
Set, go.
One. Are you okay?
(Kwang Soo bumps into Kyung Soo.)
What? Did they skip once?
Their knees bumped into each other.
This match is strangely intense.
It's a draw now.
(They sacrificed their knees to get a draw.)
- Are you all right? - I told you...
that our knees may bump into each other.
(It's a really intense match. The third round begins.)
Set, go.
- Gosh. - What was that?
(Gosh)
(Jong Kook's inside is boiling with anger.)
Now is your chance. Chance to win.
This is the biggest chance you will ever have.
It seriously is. Grab it.
- We must get this. We must. - Just do as you did before.
- Ready... - Jong Kook. This isn't easy at all.
- I minded my knees. - Ready, set...
- Seok Jin, please step back. - We don't know the result yet.
- Let's have another match. - Ready,
- Come on, Kwang Soo. - set, go.
(Win and fill the bingo card!)
- Come on, Kwang Soo. - Set, go.
- They did... - Yes.
(They did it!)
(I love you, brother. You are my prince forever.)
(Me, too. Stay with me forever.)
- We won. - Yes.
I never thought this game would be so interesting.
It was really intense.
(They mark one square and enjoy the food.)
Look at that meat.
- That's rolled samgyeopsal. - That is rolled.
- They're in a better position now. - Amazing.
- We can't eat that anyway. - How would it taste like?
This is really delicious.
It tastes different than you might expect.
There isn't any rice in the filling.
- There are vegetables and squid. - Vegetables sounds nice.
- Here comes the next menu. - Goodness.
(Here comes the next menu from Daegu's night market.)
It looks really delicious.
- I'd like to eat that. - We were really close.
All right then. Wait. Jung Seok, whom should we pick?
- Whom should we pick? - Well...
- How about them? - Sounds good.
(Yes? Are you talking about us?)
- I want to take my revenge, too. - All right.
- Are you still resentful? - Yes, I am.
I was avoiding your eyes.
- I was looking at the floor. - You're still resentful about that.
- I didn't know that. - I don't think we can win.
We'll play jegichagi without any practice beforehand.
You practiced really hard over there, didn't you?
- The rule wasn't decided then. - I see.
- You can catch jegi only once. - All right.
- Only one of you... - So we can catch once each, right?
- No. You can catch it only once. - Only once? I see.
- We'll choose your jegi, too. - That silver-colored one...
- Here. - No. Give us that gold-colored one.
- That jegi is suffering hair loss. - What is that?
- What are you doing? - We'll give this for you.
- Hey. That's too much. - Three are too many strips here.
- How can you rip them off? - What's the matter?
- How can you do that? - We're the ones who set the rule.
- Come on, stop it. - Honestly, we're...
- Stop ripping off strips. - All right. I'll stop.
- Here you go. - What is this?
This is as bald as my head.
Remember. No practice.
Look at that. It's so thin.
- Be careful. You may blow it away. - This jegi is really thin.
- There isn't any strip left. - Okay. Just begin.
- I'm ready. - Ready, set, go.
- Two. Three. - Three. What?
(Startled)
- Three. Four. - Three. Four.
- Five? No. - He scored four.
- He scored four. Amazing. - Four? That's pathetic.
It's so thin, so it falls down quickly.
Look at his face.
- It falls down really quickly. - Wait a minute.
- Just give it to me for a second. - Why?
Stop it.
(Stop ripping them off!)
(The jegi now looks pitiful.)
- How can I play with this? - You can't play with this.
(His jegi is ripped in pieces.)
All right. I'll give you another one.
Do you want me to pull out your hair just like that?
- This is thin as well. - Here. This is better.
This is really thin.
- What is that? - That jegi looks pitiful.
- Shall I begin? - Yes.
- This jegi is terrible. - Did Seok Jin score four?
- I'll start. - Okay.
- Five. Six. Seven. Eight. - Five. Six. Seven. Eight.
- Nine. Ten. - You can catch it if you need to.
- 11, 12. - Go on. You're good.
(Staring)
(What are you doing?)
15, 16.
What are you doing?
(Tap)
- I was just standing here. - He did that on purpose.
- I was just standing here. - That's a foul.
- That was mean. - Jae Seok is so mean.
You must step aside.
- You didn't tell me to. - I swear.
If you don't move aside this time, I'll just kick you.
- I mean it. - All right. I get it.
- Jong Kook was good. - I must play well.
Jung Seok. Should we play with this jegi?
- Yes. Play with that jegi. - Okay.
(This is Jae Seok and Jung Seok's turn to play.)
- One. Two. Three. Four... - You're really stable.
(Jae Seok's play seems quite solid.)
(Only 7? Would that be it?)
- Catch it. - Good.
(That was a good catch.)
- That was good, Jae Seok. - Did you see it?
- I caught it with style. - That surprised me.
Now, you're starting over from zero.
- Do we have any more chances? - No, we don't.
(They can't catch their jegi now. Jae Seok gives his second try.)
- Three. Four. Five. Six... - We're here. Don't get near us.
(Jae Seok plays really comfortably.)
- He's good. - Eight. Nine.
(Seok Jin is not happy.)
(He steps forward.)
- Was it 13? - Yes. You scored 13.
Wasn't it 23? I'm confused.
(Here comes the master of jegi.)
(Jung Seok only needs to score 10 to win this match.)
- You only need to score 10. - Go for 10.
- Is Jung Seok good? - Yes. He is really good.
- All right. - He didn't have any practice.
- You only need to score 10. - Go for 10.
- Is Jung Seok good? - Yes. He is really good.
(I believe in you, my brother.)
- One. Two. Three. - Good. There you go.
He looks solid.
(He's outstanding.)
Seven, eight.
(Victory is in his hands.)
- Just keep going. - 10.
(He goes past 10.)
(He begins to show off as he is sure of his victory.)
- Amazing. Keep it going. - 16.
(He catches it.)
Amazing. Keep it going.
(He acts all proud.)
What would happen if we catch it?
(He caught it in his hand.)
(According to the rule, they can only catch it once.)
- He caught it. - You caught it.
- You caught it. Start over. - That's right. You caught it.
He caught it in the end.
- That's a foul. - You caught it again.
We already used our chance. What should we do?
(What would be the referee's call?)
(Jae Seok's team loses.)
(Did we lose? Really?)
(Justice always prevails.)
- We won. - I'm sorry.
- Why did you show off like that? - I'm terribly sorry.
Why did you pretend as if you didn't do it?
He tried to do it again.
- That was close. - Why did you do that?
I was certain that we won and got too excited.
(They lose the game because he showed off after his victory.)
(Seok Jin's team can mark one square and enjoy their bindaetteok.)
- Jung Seok did really well but... - Why did you do that?
I thought he was telling me to eat...
but he's just eating everything.
(It's delicious enough to forget about petty teammates.)
We must win for food.
- That looks amazing. - Let me correct you.
(That was supposed to be ours.)
If we take this square, then they can't win easily.
We should mark this square.
- You're right. - What would you like to do?
(Jae Seok successfully steals a sheet of bindaetteok.)
- We must keep the possibility open. - We'll mark this square.
(Hurry up, Jung Seok. Turn around and eat.)
- What are you doing? - What do you think you are doing?
(Jae Seok is caught at the scene of the crime.)
- What are you doing? - What's the matter?
- What's the problem? - When did you take it?
Won't you spare us some?
Why did you take the sauce?
- To eat with bindaetteok. - It was right in front of him.
You wanted the sauce...
They caught you because you took the sauce which was right here.
I thought they wouldn't be able to notice me.
- All right. - Jung Seok...
- is driving me mad. - Let's eat.
(After that, they have a fierce wrap battle to win drinks...)
(and Kyung Soo finishes first and wins both marks and prizes.)
(Haha's team and Jae Seok's team haven't got any marks yet.)
This place is...
just amazing.
- There are so many snack carts. - It's awesome.
This street is 350m long with about 70 snack carts.
Really? Is it that long?
(This night market is surely big, but moreover,)
(there are tons of delicious food.)
- Are there carts on this side, too? - Yes.
- There are carts all the way. - There are so many of them.
- That looks so delicious. - There are about 70 snack carts.
Find appropriate carts, carry out missions, and mark your bingo cards.
- Let's go there first. - Okay.
(We must stop Kwang Soo and Kyung Soo first.)
- Find sushi cart first. Okay? - All right.
(The second half of "Night Market Bingo" begins.)
Run and scan the carts.
(They need to be quick at finding carts with missions.)
Where's the cart with tornado potatoes?
Excuse me. Where can I find tornado potatoes?
(Kwang Soo's team can almost secure victory.)
- Where's the cart? - Where can I find tornado potatoes?
(I won't let you win that easily, Kwang Soo!)
(Kwang Soo and Kyung Soo are on their way to find tornado potatoes.)
Here's a sushi cart.
- This must be the place. - Hello.
- Is this the right place? - Yes.
(They find fire sushi.)
We just need to find tornado potatoes.
It looks so good.
(A slice of beef is cooked directly with fire.)
It's the flank?
(The cooked beef gets placed on the rice.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(For this mission, they both have to light a match with one try.)
(We'll do the mission after we eat.)
It's good.
It's so good.
(It's got a fiery taste to it.)
(When are you planning on doing the mission?)
It's so good.
It is.
- Thank you. - Did you finish?
- Yes. - This is the mission.
- What? - It's our mission.
- I'll do it. - We have to light it with one try.
- I'll go. - You both have to do it.
- Here I go. - You can't fail.
Let's go.
Set, go!
Mission successful.
I have to do it, too, right?
(Kwang Soo can't afford to fail now.)
(He lights it.)
(Kwang Soo succeeds from a single try.)
Mission success.
- Can you mark it on our bingo? - Okay.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you for the food.
(They're headed to the tornado potatoes.)
- Let's go. - We need to find tornado potatoes.
I'll be with you in a minute.
Where are the tornado potatoes?
- There they are. Is this the place? - Yes.
- Hello. - Hello.
(They finally find the tornado potatoes place.)
What if this isn't the place?
(They got their hands on tornado potatoes.)
There they are.
Can you feed me some?
Hello.
They must be doing a mission.
- Please. Just this once. - We finished it.
Oh, right.
Don't let them see.
What?
(For this mission, they have to juggle 3 potatoes at least 5 times.)
It's a hard mission.
This is difficult than the one before.
They won't be able to do it, either.
How are we supposed to do this?
You have to stop them from making a bingo.
(Haha tries the juggling mission.)
(He drops them.)
What about us?
- Can you juggle, Jung Seok? - Yes.
- Nice. - I'm good at juggling.
Jung Seok is taking his jacket off.
This is so unfair.
You can do it, Kyung Soo. You're on fire today.
I'm not sure.
(If they succeed this mission, they will get the Exchange Card.)
Start!
(He juggled twice.)
- Nice. - Okay.
- It's our turn. - Is it hard?
Give us the potatoes.
- We don't want a lot. - Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for the food. - This one is too good to pass.
It's the only one left to make a bingo.
Jung Seok says he knows how to juggle.
(Jung Seok is apparently an experienced juggler.)
Please.
I haven't done it in a while.
Take your time, Jung Seok.
Is there anything he's not good at?
Jung Seok is an amazing guy.
He's amazing.
(Give me strength, potatoes.)
(I have faith in you, Jung Seok.)
(The potatoes are dancing in the air.)
- He did it. - Mission successful.
(Jung Seok succeeds the juggling mission.)
Yes!
Way to go. That was amazing.
- We're doomed. - Thank you for the food.
- Thank you. - We're done for.
(They prevent Kwang Soo and Kyung Soo from making a bingo.)
There's so much delicious food here.
- Look. It's chicken skewers. - Right.
- Welcome. - Hello.
Is this the place for the mission?
- That's right. - Okay.
(Play a game of palm wrestling against a different team and win.)
It's palm wrestling.
(They fuel up with some chicken skewers.)
Have some more.
It's good.
Everything's delicious here.
Kyung Soo.
We have to do this mission with someone else.
- Help us. - Sure. What is it?
It's palm wrestling.
Let's go.
(Will Jung Seok even be good at palm wrestling?)
(I'm pretty strong myself.)
(Slapping)
Wait, what?
(Jae Seok helps him back up.)
Wait, what? Is that even possible?
- What's wrong? - It doesn't make sense.
What are you talking about?
- Are you Neo from "Matrix"? - I'll show you one more time.
- He's very flexible. - What was that?
He could even get back up from lying down.
That's right. He's flexible.
(They tease Kwang Soo with perfect teamwork.)
- He's flexible. - You're up, Kyung Soo.
- Let's go, Kyung Soo. - Jung Seok.
You can do it, Jung Seok.
Jung Seok.
Kyung Soo.
(We meet again.)
Let's go, Kyung Soo.
- Kyung Soo. - Get him back.
He took the tornado potatoes mission from us.
Jung Seok.
(He dodges.)
(Will Kyung Soo be able to get his revenge on Jung Seok?)
(He hugs him.)
(Kwang Soo and Kyung Soo succeed the mission.)
We did it!
- We won! - That was close.
We did it! We won.
(The brothers were brave.)
- Hello. - Hello, Ma'am.
(They try their next mission.)
(He's good at drawing.)
Marilyn Monroe.
(They succeed the drawing mission with Kyung Soo's drawing.)
Thank you, Sir.
(If nobody gets a bingo, the team with the most missions wins.)
If we block everyone's bingo,
the team with the most missions done will win automatically.
You're right.
We did a lot so far.
We did.
This was a nail salon.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Exchange Card, here we come.)
The way I see it, we're done for.
Just enjoy it, Jae Seok.
Let's do that.
Hurry.
Hurry up.
Let's just...
watch other people shoot.
Jung Seok.
(Cheers, Jung Seok.)
We should eat. Let me know if you find something you want to try.
Do you want some ox blood soup?
Sounds good.
- It's good for upset stomach. - Ox blood soup is the best.
Can we have some ox blood soup?
Ox blood soup is the best.
- Thank you. - Thank you for the food.
- Eat up. - You too, Jae Seok.
(We should at least eat if we're going to lose anyway.)
The game's not over yet, Jung Seok. Who knows?
(What is life?)
I know we're in the worst possible situation,
- but you never know. - Right.
I hope people will watch my movie.
It'll all work out.
(Everything will be okay.)
(Their bromance is hotter than ox blood soup.)
(Kwang Soo's team has the most.)
This is the place. This is it.
- Thank you. - Under 20 seconds,
make the stickers stick on your face or your hand.
Let's go.
Ready, set, go.
Go like this and apply pressure.
Use your nails, too.
(They rub the stickers carefully.)
Please.
Here.
(The stickers have to be printed clearly for both of them.)
Is that it?
Let's take it off.
Oh, gosh.
(You're in our way.)
- What... - I'm sorry.
If you fail, we'll try right after.
I did it.
(Kyung Soo succeeds once again.)
It should come off easily.
(Kwang Soo is the only one left.)
Take it off.
You failed.
We'll try now.
- It's okay. - What are we doing here?
You should've used a new sticker.
It didn't feel sticky.
(This is not good at all.)
If we do this mission, we'll get a bingo.
- Let's go. - You just need to stay still.
- Give us some water. - We have 20 seconds, right?
Ready, set, go.
(Seok Jin and Jong Kook start their mission.)
(If they do this, they'll get a bingo.)
Please no.
(If they fail, Kwang Soo and Kyung Soo could try again.)
If we stop their bingo, we'll win.
- You don't rub it? - No.
Just apply a lot of pressure.
You have to take it off now.
(How did they do?)
Oh, no.
(Seok Jin failed already.)
- Yes! - We'll try next.
It didn't work.
It's more difficult than you think.
If they fail again, we'll try once more.
- Do we both have to do it? - You have to take the plastic off.
Oh, we had to take the plastic off.
(We didn't do that.)
Why didn't you tell us earlier?
Shouldn't you know that?
- The plastic. - Ready, set, go!
(Kwang Soo and Kyung Soo try for the second time.)
You have to soak it completely.
We have to succeed.
(They try even more carefully this time.)
Stop!
- You have to take them off now. - Time's up.
(Will they be able...)
(to stop their bingo?)
(It's a success.)
(Kwang Soo and Kyung Soo did it.)
If we took the plastic off, we would've won.
(Seok Jin and Jong Kook fail to get a bingo.)
- Thank you. - We did it right in front of them.
(Nobody can make a bingo now.)
- We could've been able to do it. - Thank you, Sir.
Thank you so much.
This is so annoying.
(Kwang Soo and Kyung Soo win with the most missions done.)
The final mission is "Find the Matching Cards".
If you have two matching cards,
discard them...
and take one of the cards the team on your left is holding.
When you discard the cards,
you have to do the action written on the cards...
to prove you discarded them.
The team to discard all cards will avoid the penalty.
The team holding the penalty card at the very last moment...
will receive the penalty.
Kwang Soo will get the Exchange Card item.
(The final race gets started.)
- Let's begin. - Do we draw one now?
Kwang Soo's team goes first.
Do you want me to draw first?
Do it.
I will...
take the second one from the right.
- This one? - Yes.
(Which card did the unlucky Kwang Soo draw?)
Can we discard them right after we draw their cards?
Yes.
(They got the Charm Card.)
We'll... Let's see. Then this one should...
This one should...
Do we have to use them?
You should know this.
Throwing cards away can be rather disadvantageous sometimes.
Because you can be a target.
You shouldn't have told them.
I was foolish.
- We don't have to throw them away. - We don't have to?
You don't have to.
- Okay. - You don't need to.
Is it our turn?
You should choose one now.
It's from 1 to 5.
(It's Jae Seok and Jung Seok's turn to choose.)
(Will they be able to avoid the Penalty Card?)
(Jung Seok already has a Penalty Card.)
- I'll designate one. - Go ahead.
- I know you're nervous. - It's 1, 2, 3, 4, and 5.
It's 1, 2, 3, 4, and 5.
(What will he choose?)
I'll pick the third one.
- This one? - The one in the middle.
- He looks disappointed. - Wait a moment.
Wait a moment.
(Good. Think again, Jung Seok.)
- Give it to me. I'll take it. - Give it to him.
Give it to him.
- Give him the one in the middle. - Give it to him.
Jung Seok completely conned them.
- What should they do? - You can see ours now.
(Let's throw ours away.)
We will...
(They can throw away two Kiss on the Cheek Cards.)
(They pretend to kiss each other.)
We will throw them away.
(They threw them away.)
- Okay. - Oh my.
Then let's shuffle them.
I can't tell because they're upside down.
- Gosh. - You hold them.
- I don't want to choose something. - I understand.
(Where is the Penalty Card?)
- Pick one. - Everyone is disguising very well.
- There are two bombs among them. - He may pick a Penalty Card.
We don't know it, either.
You may have to have two Penalty Cards.
- All look like Penalty Cards. - I don't want to choose one.
- I understand. - Let's go with the middle one.
(The card in the middle?)
- Okay. - He hides them well.
It was easy for you to see.
I'll let you know.
Pass it to me. I'll look at it.
(Let's see.)
(We can't tell from Jung Seok's face.)
(The card Seok Jin and Jong Kook brought is...)
Please let me see.
This is insane.
(It's a Penalty Card.)
(It is a Penalty Card.)
Oh my.
(They want to laugh out loud.)
(Show Your Individual Skills Card and Tour around Daegu Card)
We're heading toward the end.
They were Forehead Kiss Cards.
- I'll use the Exchange Card. - Okay.
Give it to me.
- Suit yourself. - I like the exchange.
We're almost heading toward the end.
- It's almost the end. - Does it end if you have two bombs?
Among 1, 2 and 3.
Pick one.
(Haha and Ji Hyo have to choose one.)
I'll choose number three.
Here.
Take a look.
(Haha and Ji Hyo only had a Penalty Card.)
(What did they choose?)
Good job, Haha.
Did you see that? You can do it, too.
You haven't tried that yet.
Right?
You look desperate.
I thought it would be over soon.
If you have two matching cards, you can throw them away and end it.
(Will it be a Penalty Card or the same card?)
- But it can be a Penalty Card. - Right.
(Haha and Ji Hyo actually have two Penalty Cards.)
(They're anticipating.)
Look at Kwang Soo's expression.
(They got the Penalty Card again.)
It must be a Penalty Card.
(It must be a Penalty Card.)
(Your misery is our joy.)
His expression changed suddenly.
- I'll shuffle them. - I saw your expression.
We're in trouble now.
(Jung Seok might pick the Penalty Card.)
They need to throw the cards away.
The upper one is 1 and the lower one is 2.
- That's right. - Jung Seok, pick one.
- One or two. - I'm so unlucky. You saw me, right?
- I can see your cards. - Take what you want.
- One or two. - Should I pick one again?
- Do it. - I feel anxious.
- Suddenly, I feel anxious. - One or two.
(It's a 50 percent chance.)
I feel so worried.
Your nails are so pretty.
(What's Jung Seok's choice?)
(What is the last card Kwang Soo and Kyung Soo has?)
Look at Kwang Soo. I can read your mind.
(They glance at it.)
(It's the Penalty Card.)
(How unfortunate.)
- This is 1 and this is 2. - Did you see it?
One and two.
(The Penalty Cards go around and around.)
They're 1 and 2.
- We'll take the upper one. - The upper one?
- Yes. - Let's see.
Okay.
(In whose hand is the Penalty Card?)
(He takes a deep breath.)
(What Jong Kook picked is the tenacious Penalty Card.)
(He got the Penalty Card.)
You can choose the card this time.
Why? Did you tolerate a lot?
"What should I do?"
- I get to think a lot. - What should I do with him?
- What should I do? - What should I do?
- What should I do with him? - Look.
- It's 1, 2 and 3. - Okay.
- This one? - Number one.
Let's not look.
- I won't see it. - I won't, either.
- Let's leave them as they are. - There must be something important.
There must be something important.
If I win, let's choose that one. And if you win, pick this one.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- The left one, please. - This one?
- I didn't see it. - Me neither.
(The Penalty Card can make it back to square one.)
- Look at that. - Is this the end?
(Will the fortune be on Kwang Soo and Kyung Soo's side?)
Yes.
(He screams.)
(Show Your Individual Skills Card finally meets its pair.)
Did you find the pair?
- They must be a pair. - They seem so.
This is incredible.
(They're the first ones to escape the penalty.)
In 1, 2, 3, 4.
A huge mosquito bit me at night
It was itchy so I scratched a lot
(They look cute.)
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
(Kwang Soo and Kyung Soo placed the first.)
(The brothers were brave.)
- Congratulations. - We're done, too.
- Congratulations. - It's over.
- My gosh. - Well done.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
You're finished consecutively.
We're finished, too.
- We are. - Finished.
- Here. - Here.
It's over. We're done.
- You should take this. - Yes.
If you take this, it's over.
- If you take this. - They finish consecutively.
It's over.
(They pass the Penalty Card to Haha and Ji Hyo.)
We should have done that before.
- Kyung Soo's Exchange Card was... - That was awesome.
- He did very well. - We made it.
We were unlucky until the end.
I'm relieved.
We had ox blood soup together before.
I feel bad for them.
They pay for it straight away.
(The prompt and sacred ceremony of paying the bill)
- How much? - It's 446 dollars.
- Since he owns... - Since he owns a store...
(He's used to that device.)
(The total is 446 dollars.)
- Thank you. - They paid 446 dollars.
Jung Seok and Kyung Soo, you did a good job, too.
Thank you.
(Thank you for your great bromance.)
(Twice will be here next week.)
(Every member of the group is pretty.)
(It's Twice.)
I'm just happy.
(They're cute, little girls.)
(The girls with great singing skills and beauty will be on this show.)
(However,)
(they are not the Twice that we know.)
(There is no more Twice that we're used to.)
(Don't be blinded by their beauty.)
(Stop the sweet girls from committing brutality.)
(Suspicious Busan Trip will be aired next week.)