Subtitles by DramaFever
[Let's summon the legendary heroes!]
[Heroes appear in a turbulent age!]
[A battle between the heroes!]
[Find the experts of different fields]
[and unleash the heroes' powers!]
[The battle between heroes'
unbelievable supernatural powers!]
[Who will be the first
to conquer the world?]
[The fourth battle for the strongest.]
[The Battle of Heroes.]
[The waterfront of Han River]
- It's summer!
- It's a hot summer.
It's like Miami weather.
Today, you will be having
a race with heroes.
It's the Battle of Heroes Race.
Before I announce the rules...
Maybe we're heroes.
You will meet the heroes first.
[Today's guests are heroes.]
- Ha Ha, please step forward.
- Do we have partners?
Is it partners?
[Each member will get
a hero as a partner.]
Oh, hero!
I don't know who you are...
but please come out, my hero!
[He looks like an expert
of martial arts.]
[Who is this man in a bamboo hat?]
[The immortal dunk expert!]
Is he the Super Power?
(His nickname from 'Infinite Challenge')
- Ninja turtle, the Super Power!
- Oh, Hyun Joo Yup?
Really?
[The immortal dunk expert,
Hyun Joo Yup.]
The Magic Hippo, Hyun Joo Yup!
[The vanguard that helped basketball
achieve popularity in Korea.]
[His outstanding sense of shooting!]
[His beast-like ability
to break through!]
[And strong enough
to break the back board!]
[The power forward
that represents Korea!]
[Hyun Joo Yup's rebirth
as a hero on 'Running Man.']
He was a hero when
I was in middle school.
Nice to see you, ninja turtle!
[It feels like we should shout
'cowabunga!']
- I love him!
- Raphael!
[The first hero is
a legendary basketball player.]
Who are you, my hero?
[This time, it's soccer!]
[The invincible
Crown Prince of soccer.]
[He looks like he's about to
do a free-kick at any moment.]
Who is it?
[She wants to find out who it is.]
[Oh my!]
[Smile]
It's Song Jong Gook!
[Suddenly it feels like
it's the World Cup.]
[The Crown Prince of soccer,
Song Jong Gook.]
[The one who defended
Korea's defense line to the last]
[the national treasure,
Song Jong Gook!]
[Now, even a soccer hero
joins the battle!]
[Respectful treatment
for the legendary man.]
It's really powerful!
[I'm powerful, too.]
[Song Ji Hyo and Song Jong Gook
are the double Song couple!]
This is awesome!
We have Song Jong Gook today.
Basketball, soccer, and... baseball?
- Is it baseball?
- My super hero...
please come out!
It's a woman!
[A slender woman in a bamboo hat?]
[The strongest spiker]
I know who it is!
[This posture is volleyball?]
Volleyball!
Oh, Kim Yeon Koung!
[The volleyball empress's visit.]
- Kim Yeon Koung!
- She's the best!
[The strongest spiker,
Kim Yeon Koung.]
[Women's volleyball MVP
at the London Olympics.]
[Kim Yeon Koung,
the world's best!]
[She conquered Turkish league,
and became the MVP!]
[The Messi of
women's volleyball.]
[Everyone wants to high five
the number one sports star.]
[Deeply moved]
Be quiet before she spikes you away!
- Give me a high five, really hard!
- Go away!
[I was going to give you one...]
[Bodyguard Yoo's block.]
Did you finish your season?
Yes, it's finished and
I'm just taking a break.
She's the best!
- The volleyball empress!
- The world's best!
The world's greatest!
- Rhythmic gymnast?
- No way!
[Who is Kkuk's rhythmic gymnast hero?]
Oh, it's a woman!
[Graceful]
[An eye catching figure!]
[The rhythmic gymnast, Shin Soo Ji.]
It's very magical.
[She bloomed to represent Korea,
the rhythm gymnast fairy!]
[A well-rounded sports star that
excels in bowling and golf!]
[Full of men and women sports stars!]
She must have been hot...
You sweat a lot!
I thought it was a sauna!
[They have to bear the heat,
because they're heroes.]
There's only one left...
[There's one hero left.]
Out of the three...
[The people who don't have
partners are worried.]
- Kwang Soo, step forward.
- Okay!
No way...
My hero, please come out!
Who is it?
[Swirl]
It's a man!
Genius wits expert!
[They can't make any assumptions yet.]
[Huh?
This motion?]
- Who is it?
- Oh, it's him...
It's Hong Jin Ho!
[Hong Jin Ho?]
Hello!
- You're going to place second today!
- No, first place!
[Genius wits expert, Hong Jin Ho.]
[The legend of 'StarCraft,'
during the first generation of eSports!]
[He conquered eSports world
with his wits and desire for victory]
[and even excelled in
a smart game show!]
[He has won second places
more than first places though!]
[He's a little different
than the other guests.]
- Gary, please step forward.
- Do I go up?
- What about me?
- Is Suk Jin alone?
My hero, please come out!
[My hero... where are you?]
Ji Suk Jin!
[No way...]
Are you serious?
[Big Nose is Gary's hero for today.]
Why is Suk Jin my hero?
The bamboo hat suits him
really well, though.
The hidden hero of 'Running Man.'
[They forcefully had to
come up with something.]
If you make today boring,
I won't stay still!
- Is the punishment a slap?
- Don't think of it as a slap.
This is the spike of love.
This is a spike of love.
I will give you a taste of it.
Give me a high five.
- High five him!
- Hard?
I'll just wait here.
[Crack]
[An intense spike!]
[Why did you ask for one...]
It was really hard!
My hand flipped backwards.
[The world's strongest high five.]
In today's race, you will be using
your heroes' super powers
to eliminate name tags.
The last team standing
will win the race.
How would these guests come to...
The 'Running Man' member who wins
will receive the title of the
strongest hero and a prize!
- It's a battle for the strongest?
- Really?
The hero will get a prize.
[Everyone wants to be the strongest.]
- We only do it once a year.
- Oh, really?
I really want to win!
Before you begin
the name tag elimination
your heroes have super powers,
but they are withheld at the moment.
- What's your super power?
- I don't know either.
- You don't know?
- Hurry and tell me, what is it?
Why did you speak informally
all of a sudden?
He's older than you!
- I was in a rush.
- There are...
experts that know how to
unleash your heroes' powers.
You will need to find them
and complete a mission.
And only then,
your heroes' powers will be unleashed.
[Heroes who want to
bring peace to the world.]
[Find the experts and
unleash the heroes' powers!]
[Who are these experts?]
[The six heroes have separated.]
[Who is the expert that Jae Suk
and Yeon Koung went to?]
[They arrived at a
residential area in Seoul.]
Where?
Is it here?
This is just a house...
[A two floor city-type
hiding place of the expert.]
This looks like... they live here.
[What kind of expert
is waiting for them?]
[Unlock]
Oh, that surprised me!
What is it...
This person's rich...
This looks like a house
from the dramas.
It looks like one of the
rich houses in dramas.
You really don't know this place?
Isn't this your house?
I have no clue...
[Just come on in.]
Who is it?
[Who is this expert?]
Oh, sir!
It's mister Cho Hoon Hyun!
Hello!
[Korean Go's living legend.]
[The Go master, Cho Hoon Hyun.]
How did you get him to come?
We filmed an ad together, recently.
[They have been attuned already.]
[He came back to see Grasshopper.]
I had no idea!
I didn't know Yeon Koung was coming,
and now Master Cho's here.
So is everyone else
also meeting an expert
like Mr. Cho?
- Oh, wow.
- I'm no expert.
[What other experts are there?]
[Kwang Soo and Jin Ho
came to a coffee shop.]
- Hello, hello!
- Hello, what is this?
What is this?
- Hello!
[Mysterious]
Expert, please come out!
[Who are you?]
Hello!
[This person is...]
[webtoon artist, Cho Suk]
[His cartoon has 2400 million
views over 10 years.]
[Ranked first as the most loved
webtoon artist by Korean teens.]
[The webtoon artist, Cho Suk.]
I love his drawing style!
It's a relief, I thought you
wouldn't recognize me...
This is so... sketchy.
Are you sure he's an expert?
[Expert]
He's not a celebrity...
[The aura of a real expert.]
[The world's best profiler is here!]
A profiler?
I might know him!
I don't know him personally,
but I'm his fan...
[The best criminal Profiler?]
The expert of mystery solving!
[Pyo Chang Won]
Hello!
[Approaching in a scientific manner,
he's an expert criminal psychologist.]
[The Criminal Profiler, Pyo Chang Won.]
I spent 30 years of
my life solving crimes.
I regret some of the things
I've done in the past...
You've met the right person!
[Who is the expert that is
waiting for Kkuk and Soo Ji?]
I think the expert is
going to come out.
[The Goddess of Korean Folk Singing,
Song So Hee.]
Oh, hello!
[The most expected prodigy,
the rising star of Korean folk singing.]
[The Korean folk singer, Song So Hee.]
I thought she was an elder...
[What is the mission they have to do]
[to unleash the hero's powers?]
Hello!
[The expert that Ji Hyo and Jong Gook
will meet is a global expert!]
[Oh, this person is?]
Hello!
Michael!
[A star chef who came from Bulgaria,
who is the expert of Western dishes.]
[The Chef, Mihal Ashminov.]
He's very good at cooking!
Hello!
Wow, nice to meet you!
[Ha Ha and Joo Yup went to
a university to meet their expert.]
- Expert!
- Yes?
His voice isn't celebrity-like.
[Who is the expert waiting for
them at the university?]
[The expert of all sounds,
Bae Myung Jin.]
[The number one
sound analyst in Korea!]
[The sound analyst, Bae Myung Jin.]
[What will the six heroes' task be
in order to unleash their powers?]
[Before they unleash any powers...]
These are nothing,
but they're very precious to me.
What do you mean they're nothing?
This is incredible!
The throne... this is really...
The 'King's Throne' of
Joongang Daily Go tournament.
That's probably the Ing Cup.
It is a tournament
sponsored by Ing Chang Ki.
- Do you know him?
- No, I don't.
- It's been too long.
- When was it?
- It's a world cup for the game of Go.
- It was the first world-wide tournament.
- I heard there was an enormous prize?
- 400 thousand dollars...
It was a lot.
I was one year old in 1989...
[Kim Yeon Koung had just turned
one when he received his award.]
You were born
in the year of the Olympics?
You're Hodori generation.
(mascot of '88 Olympics)
[It's interesting how they all
got to meet together, now.]
But why your house?
I heard you had do something,
so you should probably see this.
- Oh, sir...
- Have a look at this!
[The Go master?]
The Go master...
The way to unleash your powers.
You can unleash your powers if you
have a match of Go with the expert.
When you get the
'unleash stamp' from the expert
the withheld powers
will show in the book.
You don't mean winning
match of Go, right?
- Do you know how to play?
- Only 'Five in a Row.'
Five in a Row!
I can do that too, how about you?
A super newbie!
[What will they win the expert with?]
I don't know what we're
battling against
but we need to win to unleash the
powers, so please understand us.
- Yeon Koung, pick one.
- What if it takes too long?
Then we need to battle
until tomorrow morning.
If we don't win, we can't leave.
It needs to be
something like stone fight.
Jackstones using Go stones.
This is possible.
Even though he's the master,
I don't think he's good at everything.
- This is Jackstones...
- This is a complete defeat.
[Kwang Soo and Jin Ho vs. Cho Suk.]
Team Kwang Soo and Jin Ho
can draw together.
We just have to draw so that
the people can recognize it, right?
We just have to win one more than him.
I'm really detailed when I draw,
so I usually take a long time...
Just draw one, and
make sure people can tell.
Speed is important.
Do you draw fast?
Just because I'm an artist,
it doesn't mean my drawings are great.
- Draw with your left hand.
- Hearing this now...
if I knew what we were doing,
I wouldn't have come...
He looks so worried.
My job is a webtoon artist...
Then, we will start
with the first topic.
The subject is animals, starting now!
Animals are hard to draw!
I'll draw the animals on the right,
you draw from the left.
The left side is super hard!
[He finishes drawing the sloth
as soon as he started.]
[He finishes a penguin in a flash.]
Oh, that's a sea lion?
[He even finishes drawing
the sea lion speedily.]
Is a skunk's head white or black?
- Is the middle black?
- A skunk?
- I don't know...
- Where's the white part?
Just draw him farting!
That's a squirrel!
- I don't know where the white part is...
- Just draw him farting.
[Cho Suk leisurely
finishes drawing a mole.]
- Which part is red on a crane?
- I don't know!
Don't color, it's black anyway!
Where's the red part?
Is it the middle?
- There red somewhere... the eyes?
- Just draw the key parts.
Jin Ho, what do you have left?
I'm drawing an anteater, right now.
You're drawing all the ants one by one?
[Relaxed, relaxed]
[Time is up!]
It's a meerkat.
[Kwang Soo's monster vs.
Cho Suk's meerkat.]
This is a hydra for sure.
[Jin Ho's hydra vs.
Cho Suk's anteater.]
[Hyena]
[Sloth]
[What is Kkuk and Soo Ji's mission?]
- Please take this.
- Yes.
What is this?
'You must compete
by singing a verse and'
'if you win once,
you can unleash your powers.'
'You must each sing a verse from
children's songs by taking turns.'
'It is important to sing your song and not
get confused by your opponent's song.'
[One verse karaoke]
We sing a different
song by taking turns?
But we have to sing our own.
I think we'll get confused...
Then I'll go first.
Here, miss expert.
Oh, you must like the color blue.
Pick one.
Pick your favorite color.
The expert's song is...
'Little Calf.'
- Oh, 'Little Calf.'
- You know the song, right?
[The children's song that everyone
knows is the song for the expert?]
Should we open ours, then?
[Then what song did
Kkuk and Soo Ji draw?]
'Icicle.'
Icicle, icicle.
- You don't know it?
- No, I have no clue!
- Why don't you know it?
- What song is that?
Did you spend your
childhood exercising?
- Yes, I did.
- Really?
[Kkuk will be starting
first as their rep.]
Little calf, little calf.
Spotted little calf.
Ici... cle.
[Super low-pitched]
[Head shot]
This is hard... this is really hard!
- Did it hurt?
- It was too hard!
It was too hard!
Can I do this instead?
This hurts so much!
She can raise her leg
instead of her hand.
Me, me!
[It's hard to sing different
songs and taking turns.]
Icicle, icicle.
Wait, that's not it.
[That's butterfly.
Are you going to make the icicle fly?]
[Second try]
Little calf, little calf.
I... cicle!
[A gymnast's defense]
It's right!
[It's not i.. cicle, it's icicle.]
We sang it like this
in our neighborhood!
[Which neighborhood adds a
groove in a children's song?]
It's a variation!
[No improvisation allowed
for a strict evaluation!]
Well, here is the mission
you have to complete.
The sound master.
If you find a student that can replicate
the voice that the expert shows you
you can unleash your powers.
[You want us to find a
voice doppelganger?]
If that student's voice
is over 90% accurate
then you will get a stamp, and
your powers will be unleashed.
[What is this...]
Can you do it?
You must not be on good terms
with the producers...
[Otherwise, this kind of
labor is unnecessary...]
I will let you hear the
first voice for the mission.
You have to listen to it carefully.
You unmannerly bastard!
It's Yoon Mun Sik!
'You unmannerly bastard!'
But they have to be really old...
As long as their
speech pattern is the same.
You know T.O.P is really good
at imitating this, too!
[Accuracy is 98%, Yoon Mun Top!]
Ha Ha, on the move!
- We have to do it together!
- I need to save energy.
Hurry!
I'll be here.
Who is able to imitate Yoon Mun Sik?
- Show them once.
- Who can do 'you unmannerly bastard'?
[Many challengers are coming to them.]
You unmannerly... sorry!
- You unmannerly bastard!
- Wow!
- Louder, louder.
- Raise it by one octave.
- It's too low.
- You unmannerly bastard!
- He has a possibility!
- He's good.
[A challenger with a
bowl haircut is here.]
Oh, you look like you can do it well!
Start!
- You unmannerly bastard!
- Make it longer.
You unmannerly bastard!
This bastard...
[It was my style of acting.]
Try it one at a time.
We need to vote.
- Ready, set!
- You unmannerly bastard!
- They're going to fight!
Thank you!
See you again soon!
- You need to make it clear.
- And higher.
Like this, you unmannerly bastard!
It's Yoon Mun Sik!
[They enter proudly with the
assumption that they're going to win.]
[Jang Man Gil, 25 years old.]
- There wasn't much time.
- It's 100 percent!
- It was a little easy...
- It's exactly the same!
- This person sounds exactly the same.
- Are you sure?
You... you... unmannerly bastard!
[What kind of results will they get?]
Wow, it sounds the same!
[Anticipation]
We won, we won.
[They listen to the original again
to make sure it's accurate.]
- You unmannerly bastard!
- It was this long?
It's so long!
Did it stretch out all of a sudden?
Wow, this is too long.
[Long vs. short]
First of all, the length of
the sound is different.
The most important thing
is the speech pattern
but the speed of the sound here...
- the problem is...
- Will is be over 90%?
No, probably around 75%.
[Finding the voice doppelganger,
first attempt fail.]
[Finding Kim Hee Ae's voice.]
Who can imitate it?
This is a top compliment.
[Not similar]
[Similar to the person before]
This is a top compliment!
[Extremely not similar]
[Finding Kim Jong Kook's voice.]
You only play the guitar, right?
[Promise me that you'll
only play the guitar...]
Just challenge!
Anybody!
Start!
Five, six, seven, eight!
- There's a man
- What are you singing!
There's a man
Sorry, I got a little angry.
[Will he be able to]
[complete the mission?]
What is this?
The cooking master.
We wouldn't be making a dish, would we?
Tasting challenge with the chef...
how is this possible?
How do we compete against the expert?
With your eyes and nose covered,
eat different ingredients.
You have to guess the ingredients
the staff call out, in order.
Please go easy on us!
[Gives up as soon as
he hears the mission.]
The first mission is types of powder.
[With the eyes and nose covered,
eat three similar ingredients.]
[Guess the ingredient
before the expert to win.]
[First, is coffee.]
Here's the second.
[Next is brown sugar.]
[When the nose is covered]
[the taste buds become dull
because the smell is part of the taste.]
[The last one is salt.]
[He takes a big mouthful of salt.]
[Yuck]
[It must be salty!]
It's yummy, is there any tequila?
[He must have realized what it was.]
Why isn't there any left?
I'm scared.
[I'm ready]
Answer!
Coffee, then sugar, then salt.
Correct!
[How do we beat the chef?]
[Gary and Suk Jin's mission.]
Play 'catch the thief' with the
expert, and if you win once
you can unleash your powers.
The cards have to be divided
evenly among three players.
Then, throw away any cards that
have the same numbers.
Going in order, take a
card from your opponent
and collect all the same numbers
and if you become empty-handed
you can win. The last one who
has the thief card loses.
It's a psychological game.
- He's an expert...
- We're playing this with Pyo Chang Won.
I would like to help you,
but I can't lose on purpose.
Sorry, please understand
even if we win.
Yes, go ahead.
[Will Big Nose and Gary be able
to beat the crime solver expert?]
We will now start 'catch the thief.'
Please divide the cards.
- Yes.
- Wait a minute.
It's a little suspicious,
so I will shuffle it.
Well we never know if
you did something with
the cards before we got here.
That's a very good attitude.
He doesn't get drawn
into what you said.
Being suspicious is a good
start to solving mysteries.
[Big Nose divides the stack and
hands out 10 cards to each player.]
[Let's see...]
It would be beneficial to have
many of the same numbers.
You really divided them well.
[Gary's cards are 1, 2, 3, and 4]
[and the thief card.]
[Why are you hiding there?]
The person who has the thief card
will probably put it in the middle so that
the next person can pull it out easily.
[Shiver]
Pick one, please.
You have one more card than us.
- Right?
- Yes.
- So you have a higher chance...
- Yes, very high.
Very high.
I don't have it.
Don't try to be psychological!
I'm being drawn in, right now!
I'm doing it so we don't get drawn in.
I don't want to get drawn in.
Do everything you can.
You said the thief card is
placed usually in the middle.
I will daringly take
the one in the middle.
- Thank you, you gave me a seven.
- Lucky seven.
[He picked a seven and cleared a pair.]
Then I will pick...
[Lame psychological battle]
I will go with the far left.
Do you want this one?
Take it.
Hmm...
[His face is pretty relaxed.]
You and I are in the same boat.
Then I will clear this pair.
[Gary made a pair of nines.]
Here, pick one.
Gary, your eyes keep
shifting to the left.
When I'm with my girlfriend
I always look to the left.
- Is that the truth?
- No, not that one!
[An intense psychological warfare]
Can you even tell by feeling it?
Hmm... is that?
[Look at his reaction...]
[30 years of experience
in solving crimes.]
[The realistic analysis
based on statics.]
[What's the safest card
that all the data tells?]
[The thief came.]
[Oh no...]
[What just happened?]
[Embarrassed]
I picked it precisely.
[It's too precise...]
Do I keep looking on my left?
I can't normally lie...
I can't lie at all in front of you.
You seemed happy.
I wonder if he picked the thief.
You have seven cards.
I don't think you'll keep the thief
in the middle.
Well...
[He's lured!]
[Nod]
Wait, why did you nod?
It means you want me to pick it.
[We thought you're an expert,
but you're docile.]
Then, I'll pick the one beside.
Oh, I see.
[Total failure]
- He just nodded.
- It's getting better.
[He has dealt with criminals, but he
might not have dealt with cards.]
Who has the thief?
I wanted to pick the card
in the middle for a while.
I think you've noticed that
I like to pick the one in the middle.
So, I think if you have a bad card...
- you would have put it in the middle.
- Is that so?
Yes.
[Preserving the equilibrium]
And the result is...
He isn't very happy.
Then I'll pick this one.
[Suk Jin looked at his face
and pick the card.]
[Dizzy]
Number one!
[He picked number one
and made a pair.]
- Then it means...
- You'll pick this one, and I'm done.
[Big-nose finishes his stack.]
[Huh?]
[Suk Jin's last card was 10?]
[Gary finishes the game, too.]
It's destiny!
Naturally, this card
will be given to you...
[That's how the crime solver
ended up with the thief.]
We won on our first try!
[Bitter]
I had the thief at first...
he picked it when he
made his first comment.
[Detective instinct?]
[He never let the thief go.]
He's perfect for variety shows!
[Gary and Suk Jin's
ability is unleashed!]
Have you played Jackstones before?
- Not with Go stones...
- It's the same.
I never thought Master Cho
would play Jackstones with Go stones.
It's the first time.
The world renown go master
is going to play Jackstones...
I'm in trouble.
How can I win this?
[The one who gets
5 points first will win.]
[Master Cho Hoon Hyun
kicks off the game.]
If I were younger,
I think could play this.
[His moves are pretty fast.]
[It seems that he's played
Jackstones a lot.]
It's the second stage.
Oh no!
[The high pitch voice of his!]
You were really cute.
You must be disappointed.
[The master of Go reveals
his cute scream for Jackstones.]
Ready.
If she can finish...
[Her big hands might be helpful.]
[It's up to you, Yeon Koung.]
[Absent-minded...]
Nice!
Good!
That's right!
- Great!
- This is the critical moment.
[They're going straight into
grabbing two stones at a time.]
- It's nice!
- Very good!
[His fanning is accelerating.]
- The way you grab the stones...
- Oh ho!
That's it, that's it!
[The position of the stones is great.]
It's perfect!
Great!
[An advanced skill, 'the railroad'!]
[Continue the winning streak]
[and sweep all four stones!]
[Now there's only one more left!]
I need to grab all five.
[Wow]
[All five stones at once!]
[They will succeed the
mission if she grabs all five!]
[Fail!]
That was so close!
[Now, the expert needs
to grab four stones.]
[High pitch scream]
[The expert's scream
is quite addicting.]
You are very disappointed.
Because I almost made it.
On your fan,
it's written 'absent-minded.'
But, I'm actually greedy inside.
The fan says 'absentmindedness'
but you're greedy inside?
Wow, you are very..
[Being competitive]
We need to win this.
[It's Yoo Hyuk's turn to snap.]
Three points!
Great!
We gained three points first.
[They need to get two more points.]
Look at the position!
[Who's that person at the back?]
[While Yoo Hyuk passed the first stage]
[Master Cho's wife
is watching their game.]
[The stones are little too close.]
[Yoo Hyuk fails at the stages.]
Oh, she's watching?
Maybe she can try.
- I have small hands.
- I'm not good at it, either.
[The ringer joins the game.]
[The wife of Master Cho
will start from snap.]
- Wow!
- Keep playing.
Start from the first stage again.
- Oh, from the first stage?
- Yes.
It's been a while since
I've played Jackstones.
- She's good...
- Aren't you an expert, ma'am?
[She reassures them
with her modest words.]
[She's plowing through]
[If this continues...]
[Ho ho ho]
This is bad...
[She failed at grabbing two stones.]
She's so good!
She's really good.
[She has the presence of an expert.]
[Jae Suk and Yeon Kyung just need
to get two more points![
[If he gets two or
more stones, he wins.]
[The speed of his fan
is at maximum speed.]
I'm sorry ma'am,
I need to finish it here.
[Three stones survived.]
[Will they be able to
finish it this round?]
[Young fellow...]
[They succeeded in
getting five points!]
- Thank you very much.
- Well done.
[They can now unleash
the hero's powers!]
I get it now.
I understand the game.
[The high jump]
[Figure skating]
[Shot put]
Who will go first?
- Would like to go first?
- I'll go first.
Does it have to be a person?
[Well, I guess a dog
can't really guess...]
- What about the woman over there?
- Oh, us?
Oh, thank you very much.
- Hello.
- Do you have five minutes?
- Can you solve this quiz?
- Do you like sports?
- Yes.
We'll give you one minute.
Ready, set!
You can write it below.
Just write the ones you know first.
[This is a horse?]
[Horseback riding]
[Weightlifting]
[Taekwondo]
[That's interesting...]
[The high jump]
[Fencing]
What's the name of this?
[Bobsled]
You ride it... a bobsleigh!
- You have 15 seconds.
- Hurry, hurry!
There aren't many things
to do on the ice...
Oh, figure skating!
Is this right?
[Worry, worry]
What about this?
[Time up]
[They got eight questions right.]
There are different
types of sports drawn.
You just need to write the
sport in the empty space.
Ready, set!
[Horseback riding]
[It's easy because they're well-drawn.]
[Taekwondo]
[Fencing]
[Bobsleigh]
[Satisfied]
Jang Mi Ran...
[She's stuck on this drawing?]
[No way]
[She couldn't remember the
sport, so she passes.]
[Shot put]
Five, four, three...
two, one!
[They got six questions
right in total!]
[The final score]
[They picked the right people.]
[They won the drawing battle
with expert Cho Suk!]
There's a little calf,
sitting upon some coal.
He begins to cry.
There are three bears,
under the same roof...
[He keeps copying the
melody she sings.]
[It must hurt.]
[It's more confusing because
it's a similar melody.]
He begins to cry.
There are three bears, under the same
roof. Daddy bear, mommy bear, baby bear.
Waa Waa, my bottom feels so hot.
Daddy bear is fat.
Mommy bear is thin.
- Sitting upon some coal.
- Baby bear is so cute.
Shrug, shrug, very good.
[They succeeded the one
verse karaoke mission!]
She's really good.
It was the battle of experts.
[Lee Ryul, age 20.]
Ah, this is frustrating.
- Oh!
- It's the same, right?
[The graphs looks very similar.]
The similarity is about 91%
[They succeeded the voice
doppelganger mission!]
[They retry the tasting
challenge, with three]
[three different jam flavors.]
Strawberry jam, apple jam, grape jam!
[That's correct!]
[They succeeded the tasting challenge!]
[After signing on the book of secrets]
[they need to get
a stamp from the expert.]
Unleash the powers!
[Premium benefit after
battling with the experts!]
[The heroes' powers are unleashed!]
[How will these powers be used?]
[Finally, the final match.]
[The gate of turbulence.]
[No one can enter without the
unleashed powers of the book.]
[The door to the city of heroes.
The gate of turbulence.]
[Jae Suk enters with
the book of secrets.]
Huh?
[He walks through the
passage with green lights.]
You need to open the book
that you received
shout 'summon the hero, '
then place the book down.
Summon my hero!
[Name cloning power.]
[He summons
the Goddess of spikes, Yeon Kyung.]
[Ji Hyo enters next.]
Summon my hero!
[Temporary sending-off power.]
[She summoned the soccer
Crown Prince, Jong Gook.]
Don't leave my side!
- Summon my soul!
- It's hero, not soul.
[He was going to summon a ghost.]
Summon my hero!
[He summoned the historic dunker,
Joo Yup.]
Summon my hero!
[He summoned the game genius, Jin Ho.]
I was gaming, why did you call me?
I was winning...
[He summoned the ribbon fairy, Soo Ji.]
Yes, you have summoned me.
[He summoned the
'Running Man' hero, Suk Jin.]
- We meet again!
- I'll give it all I've got for victory!
I'm going to win today.
- But do you know about this?
- No.
I don't know even after I've read it.
This race is to pick the strongest.
It's the fourth battle.
From now on, you will be using
your hero's unleashed powers.
You need to eliminate the
'Running Man' members' name tags.
- Only 'Running Man' members?
- Yes.
Even if the hero's name tag is
eliminated, they can't be ousted.
And they can't eliminate
any name tags, either.
This is important,
the other teams' name tag
can only be ousted by
'Running Man' members.
That means Song Jong Gook
can't eliminate name tags.
- But I can hold them down?
- Yes, you can.
So the one physically eliminating
it should be Ha Ha.
So because we are one, if my name tag
is eliminated then my hero also...
- Correct?
- I'll be ousted?
Yes, if Ha Ha is ousted,
you are also ousted.
When Jae Suk's name tag is eliminated,
Yeon Koung will also be ousted.
Do well.
- Okay.
- We're in the same boat.
The important thing is the
power you've unleashed.
I will tell you how you can use them.
There will a bamboo case
that has an orange 'R' sticker.
If you open it, there
will be a golden glove.
You need to wear that
and scream 'Name cloning!'
For example, if it's Kim Jong Kook,
slap his back with a spike.
From that moment on, Jong Kook's
name tag will be on Jae Suk's back.
This is hard!
She has to hit Jong Kook's back,
but how is she going to do that?
You have to yell 'name cloning!'
So Jong Kook's name tag
will be on Jae Suk's back.
You have to ask someone else
to eliminate it within a minute.
After the minute passes,
your name tag will return on your back.
For one minute...
However, if your team and
Jong Kook's team are left
then, you can eliminate it yourself.
Only if you're the last two.
[The power of name cloning.]
[Kim Yeon Koung can clone
other Running Man's name tag.]
[If the name tag is eliminated,
that member will be ousted.]
Find a red bamboo case
which will have a red card inside.
When you have found the
person you want to oust
blow the whistle,
yell 'temporary sending-off!'
you need to place the red card
on the 'Running Man' member's sock.
The hero will be kicked out of
the building for 15 minutes.
Don't place the sticker
on a hero's foot.
[Temporary sending-off power.]
[Sending off a hero by putting
a red card on Running Man's foot.]
Find the green case, and inside...
- what do you need to reboot?
- Ctrl alt delete?
'Ctrl, ' 'Alt, ' and 'Delete.'
The keys will be in three
different cases.
You have to find all three
and find the only computer that
you can use the keyboard with.
Find it, connect the keyboard
and yell 'keyboard attack,
oust Kim Jong Kook!' press enter
then Kim Jong Kook will be ousted.
- Can you type five people in a row?
- No.
- Just once?
- Yes, you can only oust once.
Only one at a time.
You can try and find
more keys after that.
[The keyboard attack.]
[Complete the keyboard and oust!]
I will explain about the
ribbon teleportation.
Find the bamboo case
with a purple 'R' sticker
and there will be a ribbon inside.
In a dangerous situation,
yell 'ribbon teleportation!'
swirl your ribbon in the air
there will be a shield, so you can
teleport without anyone knowing.
- It means that they have to act, right?
- That's right.
They will have to stay still
and we'll move you.
[Ribbon teleportation.]
[Teleportation by swirling the ribbon.]
The memory extinction power.
I think you played with this
when you were younger.
You know the fart bombs
that have a nasty smell.
Everyone who smells it
will lose their memory.
- I have to blast it?
- At a critical moment.
If the hero uses his powers
after Gary is ousted
the people around him will lose
their memory and go back to the past.
How many are there?
Give me two thousand bombs!
Whoever ousts you won't be able
to remember that they did it.
Gary might win this battle again!
He's Mr. Random Capable.
[He won the first and second.]
Should I be randomly capable today?
[He's full of energy.]
Let's be randomly capable.
[The memory extinction power.]
[Erase people's memory.]
The important thing is the
powers that you have unleashed.
- It's the soul exchange power.
- What is that?
This is a power that can
switch your name tags.
Ha Ha can become Joo Yup,
and Joo Yup becomes Ha Ha.
If you use it, then that means
Joo Yup can eliminate name tags.
- That's a pretty great power.
- It is great.
- Is there a time limit?
- It's for three minutes.
You can't even go to the
bathroom in three minutes.
You can use it three times.
So you can use a total
of nine minutes.
However, there's a spell you have
to say to activate the power.
This is how you do it.
Shake it, shake it.
Let's shake it up, soul!
Let's shake it up, exchange!
After this...
I'm not going to use my power!
- What is this?
- Don't be angry.
- You have to do this.
- You want me to do that?
You're definitely going to do it.
Shake it, shake it.
Let's shake it up!
Be careful of your pronunciation!
Oh, I'm drooling.
[The soul exchange power.]
[Joo Yup becomes Ha Ha for a while.]
[The Battle for the Strongest, start!]
We need to hurry and
find the bamboo case.
I'm nothing without it.
I'm totally useless.
- Let's go this way.
- This is Jin Ho's hero item.
[The attacking keyboard.]
It's a real keyboard.
We need to find the computer
more than anything.
Keyboard attack!
Oust Kim Jong Kook, enter!
You're really fast!
Kim Jong Kook, Kim Jong Kook.
I can do it with my eyes closed.
[Kim Jong Kook, Kim Jong Kook.]
Do we start looking for it here?
- We can look anywhere?
- Yes, ours is the purple sticker.
Purple sticker...
It's hard to find...
Oh, there's an 'R' sticker.
This is what it looks like.
Come, I'll show you.
It's Green Team's case.
This is easy, isn't it?
It's here!
Never mind, it's orange.
[How come it's so easy
to spot others'?]
Where could it be?
- We need to find it...
- We're doomed if we don't find any.
We have no strength whatsoever.
[Team Green and Orange met
while looking for their cases.]
Why are you following us?
I think our two teams are the weakest.
- Where?
- Who?
Us?
Why?
I'm really sorry, but let's look at
this in a realistic point of view.
If we just look at the heroes' powers
you're either last place
or second to last place.
Do you even know what my power is?
- What are you saying?
- Do you want some of this?
Should I put your teeth
instead of keys in here?
- Just be careful!
- Do you want to use your power, Jin Ho?
Look at me, Jin Ho.
If I punch you...
- you'll lose at least three teeth!
- Just show him your power!
If Yeon Koung spikes you...
your teeth and his teeth
will be switched!
They will be switched in the air!
I hope you'd survive till the end.
- Yeon Koung, show them your jump spike.
- How can I do it here?
[A long provocation]
[A short provocation]
[The provocation in perfect harmony!]
Then, I'll gently do it.
[Wait, really?]
[This is how she plays.]
[Will they be okay?]
Don't hit me!
[Scared]
[He's cute.]
You know what you did?
[I think I'll have nightmares tonight.]
Should I use my power?
Should I?
We can use our power, too!
Are you a referee?
[What's the whistle?]
[Everyone is nervous to see his whistle.]
I'll stop here.
His power must be really powerful.
If you keep doing that, we will...
[Shake it, shake it?]
Don't do it.
[They don't know each other skills,
so they're making up their movements.]
You know what happens if
I blow it one more time.
- I was really surprised!
- Me, too.
He's good at bluffing.
My nickname is Song Bluff.
Why did you blow it so hard?
I'm sweaty, do you see it?
[Everyone is fooled.]
[Song Bluff doesn't stop.]
[Their target is
Kwang Soo and Jin Ho.]
What are you doing?
Let's not do this.
[They're puzzled to see the whistle.]
Please calm down.
- What do I do?
- It's so much fun!
Don't do it to us!
We should've found at least one by now.
They usually hide around
desks like these.
[They found a green bamboo case.]
You scared me!
[In this bamboo case,
there's an 'Alt' key.]
'Ctrl,' 'Alt,' and 'Delete'
are separated and hidden.
You have to find all three.
Then find the only computer
you can connect your keyboard.
[They must have found it.]
[They become confident
by finding the 'Alt' key.]
Something might come out!
Run, run away!
[Stop there!]
I can't see it!
- Write his name!
- I need to see it first!
[We don't know what it is,
but it's scary.]
[Good riddance!]
[After finding the 'Alt',
they feel they've all but won.]
Look, it's a golden color.
That's for the 'Ctrl' key.
[He puts the 'Alt' key in its place.]
What's that?
This is amazing!
I think it happens
every time you put a key.
Two more left!
Are we in a mysterious world?
I found the red case!
- Wow, amazing!
- It's the red one.
This is ours!
It's awesome!
[Inside, there're red cards.]
What do we do now?
We need to find it quickly.
- Did you find it?
- Yes, I did!
[Jae Suk and Yeon Koung find the case.]
- What's that?
- Let's go.
They're all dead!
Let's pretend we didn't find it.
- All we can do it is nothing.
- Yeah, me, too.
If we reveal our power,
it's too disadvantageous for us.
Ji Hyo... I'm serious.
Let's just...
- Should we attack them?
- Attack?
It's about time
anyone should be ousted.
[We need to do that?]
[The spell is too corny
just to watch...]
I'm not going to use my power!
[At that moment, it seemed
I didn't need the power.]
- Should we?
- Let's do it.
Quickly, shake it, shake it!
Let's shake it up!
Soul!
[Joo Yup, this is the moment!]
No...
[How can I do this?]
Shake it, shake it!
Let's shake it up!
Exchange!
[He did it perfectly!]
[Soul exchange!]
This is a power that can
switch your name tags.
Ha Ha can become Joo Yup,
and Joo Yup becomes Ha Ha.
If you use it, then that means Joo Yup
can eliminate name tags.
- That's a pretty great power.
- It is great.
[Joo Yup's name tag
is on Ha Ha's back.]
[And Ha Ha's name tag
is on Joo Yup's back.]
[Joo Yup is reborn as Ha Ha.]
It remains for three minutes.
Don't be too aggressive.
Should I eliminate Gary?
[The Giant Haroro is on the move!]
That's too harsh...
- Raphaella?
- Isn't that a girl's name?
[Now, who should I attack?]
Should I eliminate Jae Suk?
[Their first target is Yoo Jae Suk.]
- Who?
- Soo Ji found their case.
Look, she has it.
[This is the chance!]
[Grab]
[Yeon Koung defends in a flash!]
[The sudden attack fails!]
[What's going on?]
I was just kidding!
[Should I try?]
I'm sorry, my body just moves.
- He wanted to see.
- You're not supposed to!
[Heroes can't eliminate name tags,
but he's Ha Ha now.]
- Just kidding.
- Mister, put it back!
Don't joke around.
- He scared me!
- Me, too!
I was thinking what's going on?
Why don't you use your power
on Kwang Soo?
[His second attempt.]
[What is he doing?]
What's wrong with you?
[He moves in slow motion.]
He's weird.
Stop it!
[Slow and naive,
Brother Turtle]
- We don't have to stay here.
- Let's separate now.
Don't we need to decide
on the next target?
[They step backward
for hiding their name tags.]
What are you doing?
[He lured him successfully.]
Please don't do that.
[They're alone.]
[Grabs]
[He seals off the hero.]
[Go, Giant Ha Ha!]
- What is it?
- Attack Gary!
[What is he doing?]
[What just happened?]
He's a hero.
What is he doing?
What is it?
[They wouldn't know they're switched,
would they?]
Gary is ousted,
Gary is ousted!
[The other teams are agitated.]
It must be Ha Ha.
You mean Ha Ha ousted Gary?
What do you mean I'm ousted?
No, Joo Yup did it.
What is it?
[You should have checked his name tag.]
[That was his power?]
I'm sorry, let me
explain the situation.
[Suk Jin, I think it's time...]
[Yes, this is the moment!]
Ji Suk Jin's power
is the memory extinction.
You know the fart bombs.
Everyone who smells it
will lose their memory.
If the hero uses his powers
after Gary is ousted
the people will lose their memory
and forget Gary was ousted.
[This is the moment
for the fart bombs!]
The memory extinction!
[Huh?
The memory extinction?]
[You'll see what it is.]
The memory extinction!
[Whoever smells this
will loose their memory.]
The smell!
It's awful!
[What a terrible smell!]
[Everyone is surrounded by
the odor of the fart bombs.]
- Hello!
- How have you been?
We need to be careful
because we're in a battle.
- Did anything happened?
- You're sweating a lot.
Where did you come from?
- From that side.
- You're Ha Ha, right?
[Wait for us...]
I thought I saw three letters.
No, I'm Ha Ha.
What was that?
[Three minutes passed, and the
name tags are back to its place.]
[Don't be too relaxed,
we have two more chances.]
[Kwang Soo and Jin Ho
are still searching.]
Here it is!
I found it!
There are 'Alt' keys everywhere.
It's the control key!
Please, please!
I hope it's not 'Alt.'
[But it's the 'Ctrl' key again.]
- Jin Ho!
- Did you find it?
- Where are you?
[Hope it's delete key...]
[Joy to the world,
the 'delete' is come!]
[They've completed
the attacking keyboard!]
Wow, it's done!
[Their acting gets better.]
Let's find the computer now.
[There's only one computer
in this huge building.]
- We shouldn't go to the other building.
- It's Jong Kook!
[Nice to see you!]
Where are you going?
[They make a u-turn.]
- Where are you going?
- We're searching.
- What are you searching?
- A computer.
- I know where the computer is.
- Let's go together.
- Tell us where it is.
- Don't oust us, then.
- Of course not!
- Why would we oust you?
You know me.
Then, follow me.
I found where it is.
I saw the computer.
Don't write my name.
[They follow Jong Kook,
but what's going on?]
Kwang Soo, come over here.
- Open the door.
- It's here?
On your left.
[There it is!]
How come we couldn't find it?
I told you!
- Connect the keyboard.
- Don't force him.
- Don't push me.
- Sit down.
I'm only going to watch him.
- People treated us unfairly.
- Just connect it first.
Let us boss around others.
[When they don't listen,
he starts threatening them.]
- Do you want to boss around?
- I'm untying my keyboard.
I'm un... untying it!
Hurry up and connect the keyboard!
Hold him tight.
[I've never been in front of a tiger.]
Why are you shaking?
How can you be actually scared?
He's not even acting!
What do you think is faster?
You writing my name, or me eliminate him.
[What should I do?]
I feel much better
sitting at the computer.
You're not sweating any more!
- He's just practicing.
- I'll eliminate his name tag!
- He's not that fast.
- I'll rip this tag when you type 'Kim.'
This is it.
[Ha]
I think we should start using the item.
Wear your glove.
Shout the spell here.
- What was it?
- 'Name cloning!'
After shouting it
for example, if it's Kim Jong Kook,
slap his back with a spike.
From that moment on, Jong Kook's
name tag will be on Jae Suk's back.
You have to ask someone else
to eliminate it within a minute.
After the minute passes, your name
tag will return on your back.
Within a minute...
[Who will be the one
to feel Yeon Koung's spike?]
Loud?
'Name cloning!'
[Now she needs to slap someone
to clone their name tags.]
[The two teams are allied.]
I think someone has 'Reflection.'
I think so, too.
[There're people near here.]
I think someone has
the reflection power.
[Jae Suk and Yeon Koung
were hiding at the door.]
[The two teams attack them
since they outnumber the two.]
[Ha Ha bravely approaches.]
[This is the moment!]
[Volleyball spike!]
[Yoo Jae Suk has Ha Ha's name tag.]
[They have one minute!]
Eliminate me!
Eliminate me now!
[Ha Ha and Joo Yup
don't know what's going on.]
Are you sure?
- Hurry up and rip it off!
- You're sure?
[The name cloning worked!]
What's your power?
It worked!
[What just happened?]
- Run, run!
- Wait.
- What is it?
- You're ousted.
What?
What was that?
Ha Ha is ousted.
[That's my hero's power.]
What is that?
- When I slap your back...
- Did you slap me?
Thank you for your hard work,
Super Power.
It's full of betrayal.
[Ha Ha is ousted.]
What?
Well, you have less choices now.
Then I'll write Gary's name.
Let's work together.
- Don't betray us!
- Don't you know me?
I'll write Gary's name for sure.
[He wrote 'Ga' this time.]
[At that moment, Gary is...]
[stopped by Ji Hyo and Jong Kook.]
Temporary sending-off.
- What is it?
- Sending-off!
[Lift]
[If they place the red card
on the Running Man member's sock]
[the hero will be
kicked out for 15 minutes.]
Run away!
- No!
- I took off his shoe!
[Jong Kook put
the red card on his foot!]
[Suk Jin has been sent off.]
I had no choice.
What just happened?
You followed us
thinking we don't have any items.
It's fine.
You need to oust me, Ji Hyo.
Here, Ji Hyo.
Eliminate me!
[I can be resurrected
at a cost of fart.]
Our power is to send off your hero.
[Huh?]
[Wait a second...]
Your hero is out of the building.
He can't come back for 15 minutes.
- Where is he?
- He'll be outside.
[He realized the situation.]
Wait!
Where did my hero go?
No!
[Gary is ousted.]
Ji Suk Jin!
I'm so sorry, Gary.
[I want to smell the fart...]
Gary is ousted.
It's because we've been
facing each other.
We've kept our pose for a while now!
[This time, he wrote 'Yoo.]
Now, we've reached Yoo.
- Okay, I'll write it this time.
- Really?
- Who are the survivors?
- Ji Hyo's team and Jae Suk's...
What's going on here?
[As soon as he enters the room,
they start threatening them.]
[Yoo Jae]
Don't provoke me!
Calm down.
- I'm going to type 'S!'
- Why us?
- It's either Ji Hyo or Jae Suk...
- But you can't type here.
Jin Ho, you need to escape.
Yes, Jong Kook.
If you can't escape,
I'll eliminate his name tag!
What situation is this?
[I want to go home!]
Show your will to escape, at least.
Who orders that around?
Wait, both of you're afraid
if I'm going to write your name.
I'll write Ji Hyo's name.
Then the three teams will be left.
[They've come to a conclusion.]
[Song Ji]
Should I really eliminate her?
We're gathered here.
What else can you do?
[I'm sorry.]
I'll act if there's no announcement.
- I'm serious.
- I can't give up on you.
[Jin Ho, look at my tongue.]
[Do you want me to write Kkuk's name?]
[Kim\Jo]
[He was going to write
Kim Jong Kook quickly.]
[He keeps making typos.]
What are you doing?
Wait, wait!
[Song Ji Hyo]
[He goes back to Ji Hyo's name.]
- I saw you typed my name.
- Just to make it fun.
Just kidding!
Why are you so bad at typing?
[Former Professional gamer
makes so many typos.]
Because it's not my keyboard.
How many times did you practice?
You wrote it with your
eyes closed before!
- Keep your promise, Jong Kook!
- Of course!
She's going to be ousted!
Keyboard attack!
[He presses the enter key.]
Keyboard attack,
oust Song Ji Hyo!
[Oust Song Ji Hyo!]
Song Ji Hyo is ousted.
Lee Kwang Soo...
- Is this how it is?
- Lee Kwang Soo!
[This is a scary place.]
[Only three teams are left.]
- We're the only teams.
- Oh, really?
The survivors are all here.
Let's just separate.
[Jae Suk, you know what I mean?]
Kwang Soo, did you
just look at Jae Suk?
I caught him!
[Launch the plan!]
[Seize the tiger!]
Hurry up, Yeon Koung!
[Yeon Koung was about to spike Kkuk...]
Ribbon teleportation!
[They can teleport
when she swirls the ribbon.]
It was really close!
I knew it.
[Thanks to Soo Ji, he survived,
but they attacked me together?]
[Kwang Goo and Jin Ho
are searching for the keys again.]
[They found 'Alt' key before.]
[Where are you, Ctrl, Del?]
[Jae Suk and Yeon Koung
help them, too.]
[The only way to oust Kkuk.]
[Jae Suk and Yeon Koung
find the green case.]
[Now... how should I attack them?]
[Please, please, please.]
- Jin Ho!
- Did you find it?
[They acquire the Ctrl' key!]
[Go that way!]
[Thanks to Jae Suk and Yeon Koung,
they found the 'Del' key.]
- Keep your promise.
- Don't worry.
[They made another attacking keyboard.]
[Now, go straight to the computer!]
I think they're trying to oust us
by making another keyboard.
Let's just go back
to the room with the computer.
It should be around here.
[He found it.]
There's no one!
- Why did they lock it?
- Why?
Are you trying to write my name?
[Open the door!]
[Oust Kim Jong Kook.]
Did you write it?
[I'm on my way to eliminate you.]
If you write my name,
Jong Kook will win this battle.
- One of the teams will be left.
- Yes, let's just spend the night.
One will be eliminated eventually.
I don't have to go home.
I have nothing to do tomorrow.
[Just fight each other.]
[Jae Suk and Yeon Koung
changed their mind.]
They locked the door.
They're waiting for you to eliminate me.
Then, they just write your name.
- Is that so?
- Yes, they locked the door.
- Are they fighting?
- I don't hear any sound.
Maybe they already left.
If they fight somewhere,
one team will remain.
Then, they will announce the result.
- I need to go to bathroom.
- No! Just pee here.
[Use that.]
[An empty water bottle]
[Quiet]
- Just take a peek.
- No!
- I'll come back quickly.
- Just use the water bottle.
You can't hold it any longer?
I can't really pee in here...
Let's just take a peek.
Then close it right away.
What are you doing?
You don't have to turn it.
I pressed it when I locked it.
You can just open the door.
[Kkuk is here!]
[Jae Suk and Yeon Koung join him.]
[Open the door!]
Write Kim Jong Kook's name!
[Write Kim Jong Kook's name!]
[He already typed Kkuk's name.]
[He only needs to press enter and shout.]
I'll block them.
Type Kkuk's name!
[No way!]
[He presses 'Enter' and shouts!]
Oust Kim Jong Kook!
[Oust Kim Jong Kook!]
Keyboard attack, oust Kim Jong Kook!
I shouted first!
I should have caught Jin Ho.
[Kkuk and Soo Ji fails
on the threshold of winning.]
- Hello.
- Just talk to me for a second.
[Kwang Soo and Jin Ho vs.
Jae Suk and Yeon Koung]
[While Jin Ho blocks them
Giraffe runs away.]
I can't never let you go!
[Kwang Soo runs
straight to the washroom.]
- Kwang Soo, run away!
- Where are you going, Yeon Koung?
[Do you feel better now?]
Jin Ho, come here!
[I can't go...]
Kwang Soo!
You should come here!
[She keeps giving him spikes.]
- Jin Ho!
- Turn around!
[I'm busy!]
Jin Ho!
[You said you'll protect me!]
[Lee Kwang Soo]
[Kwang Soo's name tag is cloned
and attached on Jae Suk's back.]
[Why does Jae Suk has
Kwang Soo's name tag?]
[If there're only two teams left,
Jae Suk can eliminate it by himself.]
Lee Kwang Soo is ousted!
Lee Kwang Soo... is ousted!
[Jae Suk and Yeon Koung
win the battle.]
What happened?
[I placed second again...]
Therefore, the strongest of all...
are Kim Yeon Koung and I!
Wow, the book of secrets!
[With a golden label]
[Envy]
The fourth Battle for the Strongest
on Running Man
the winners are Kim Yeon Koung and I!
I'll win the next battle.
[Thank you for playing for the battle!]
[The reality even more
dramatic than a movie.]
[Hwang Jung Min]
[Jung Man Sik]
[Jang Yoon Joo]
- I can't remember anything?
- Are we police men?
[They have lost all their memories.]
[They don't even know who they are.]
[The clues are like puzzle pieces!]
[A suitcase full of gold bars]
[A sharp conflict between
the police and the Mafia.]
This is just like a movie!
Did you betray again?
[Finding the identity:
Police vs. Mafia]
Subtitles by DramaFever