It's a son.
I have a new product.
That's the right amount right?
- Count it if you'd like. It's probably right.
- Bye.
Sol it's been a while! Four of these and that one please wrap those up for me.
Hello.
You're working hard.
I wanted each letter to be perfect.
We don't have much time until opening.
Ahjusshi please do this over.
Yes. I will do it over.
Thank you.
Hello Oh Daesan of "Total Fashion Doryunnim" speaking.
Sky of Masan?
Where?
I already paid for that.
I'll send it through the dawn shipment so just be prepared to play till you drop.
Of course. It's a waste of time to repeat myself.
It's amazing just amazing. It's the best!
Of course. I'll talk to you later then.
Success!
What the...?
Closed at this hour?
Did this guy drink too much again yesterday?
Hello. This is Oh Daesan of "Total Fashion Doryunnim" speaking.
What...?
Yoojin. Yoojin... What should we do? Yoojin.
Yoojin...
Daesan.
Daesan... What are we going to do..
Mom!
- Mom!
- Madam!
- Ahjumma! Yoojin's mom!
- Mom wake up!
Madam! Madam!
- Madam!
- Wake up!
Hurry! Move!
- Move!
- We have to take her to the emergency room!
What a poor man... He took such good care of his wife and daughter.
Anyways what will happen to her if something bad happens to her mother?
I heard she was studying at a designing school in France.
Studying will have to fit around her situation not just her wishes.
What is going to happen to the store?
They'll just have to sell it off.
Young Master!
Joonhee Young Master.
If you had just arrived a bit earlier...
Where is my car?
It's ready but if might be better if you were to go in a different car.
Young Master.
At least change your clothes.
Mom I just arrived.
No I'm a bit tired so I'm going home.
I'll visit my old teacher at Elegance in a few days.
I'll see you at home.
What the...?
We should get going now.
Grandma we should go.
The road is very rough grandma.
Alright.
Thanks.
Do you call yourself human? How can you miss your own father's death?
You didn't purposely call me late?
What are you saying?!
Once is enough.
You're not the only one that's sad.
Did you forget that I'm an orphan now?
You little...
May I begin?
Then I will now reveal the will of the deceased Lee Kangil.
First I just want to let you know that the deceased edited and signed the will the day before his death with me.
Thus it is different from the will from last year.
For time's sake I'll just read the inheritance part which was changed.
First 80% of Sopia Apparel's stocks will be split evenly between the oldest son Lee Jaemin and the youngest son Lee Joonhee.
The remaining 20% will be given to my mother Kang Juok.
Second the mansion at Sungbok will be given to my wife Oh Sunyoung.
The house and land at Icheon will also be given to my mother Kang Juok.
Third the remaining lands will be distributed evenly to the three rehabilitation centers that I have been supporting.
Fourth inherited stocks cannot be transferred or be sold to a third party for five years. However it can be transferred and be sold among family mem
That is all.
It seems like we're finished so I'll just take a shower and rest a bit. I still need to recover from the jet lag.
Show me the back too please.
Man...
I just can't seem to pick one since I've never picked out women's clothing before.
You can't take pictures.
I just want to ask my girlfriend about it.
Hang on.
Oh my pretty.
Did you see the picture I sent you?
Do you like it?
Really...?
Oh well...
Okay.
She doesn't really like it.
What should I do?
I can just delete the picture right? Deleted.
Yes.
It seems great to me but women are so picky.
You're pretty too.
Please come again.
My pretty? It's me.
Velvet it's me Oh Daesan.
Yeah you got my picture right?
Of course you are the pretty one who else would it be?
Have I ever gotten in trouble before?
Anyways that picture is a newly released product so print out a good copy for me.
Ten copies in color okay.
It looks better than I had imagined.
However the risks are still high so she should stay in the hospital and receive treatment.
Okay.
Hey wake up! You should be selling not sleeping.
- Hyung do you have anything new?
- Yeah that one is good.
Miss how much is this?
I'm the owner of "Little Bear" shop in Incheon. You can ship these to my shop in four days right? Do you think you can have them deliver to me quickl
Huh?
I... You see...
Nevermind. I'm going to die from waiting.
Noona wait.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
You've never heard of us have you? We're "Eastern" thirty year veterans of the Great East Gate. "Eastern". Choose choose!
Are you the owner?
She just doesn't seem to understand...
She's a new worker. Hasn't been here too long and is a bit slow. Don't worry about her. Choose choose!
Then start by giving me ten of Carvillu small and medium for the sizes.
Okay my noona who is pretty and knows how to spend I like how you work! I'll throw an extra one in.
That man...
He's not the owner of this store.
If you buy from him I can't guarantee returns so do what you like.
What kind of business is this?
Noona!
Just kick me... Do you want to close the store down?
And how does a salesperson's daughter not know sales terms?
You could have just sat still why did you have to interrupt?
I was just trying to help you out.
Who are you?
I've been buying from Mr Seo for a few years. I'm Oh Daesan of "Doryunnim".
You don't remember? I carried your mother from the funeral home.
So?
- It looked like you were a bit lost so I thought I would help considering the owner and the store.
- Liar.
Huh?
Then you could have just helped why did you have to go acting like you're the owner?
That's just a technique not lying.
You were failing as a salesperson so I stepped in.
Do you think running a store is a game?
From now on I'm the owner of "Eastern" Seo Yoojin.
So don't use that kind of technique ever again.
How humiliating...
You're here.
Yeah.
Are you here to stay?
I can't just leave the office empty forever.
Someone needs to sit in that room.
You might hurt yourself again.
Dr Song even told you to rest.
If I'm going to fall I'll fall in the office.
A will for business.
How great is that?
The shareholders will also be happier.
Where is Joonhee?
You should know.
We found him a place to stay in the city.
One that doesn't come and one that doesn't bother to stop him.
Jaemin!
Hey Jaemin!
Did you know grandmother was going to start working again?
I had a feeling she would.
She has enough will power and responsibility.
He's been saying you were going to be the inheritor what kind of situation is this?
If I suddenly take over Father's place the shareholders are not going to trust me.
Grandmother probably has a plan.
It's because of Joonhee.
With Lee Kangil dead you and I have no blood relation in this family.
Mom.
I worked so hard.
It's got to the point where Sopia Apparel can't run smoothly without me.
Joonhee doesn't even care about running the business what are you so worried about?
Please go downstairs.
Why you... Make certain you do it right.
It was my family that brought the business up from failing.
They accepted you as a son? I took in Joonhee and cared for him.
You and I we have no more debts from this family do you understand?
Yes I understand.
I have to prepare for the designers' meeting. Go and rest.
- Jaemin Jaemin...
- Go rest mother.
It's pretty organized even though the head of the company was missing.
Lee Jaemin organized it everyday. You know he's just like the president in his work habits.
Show them that even with a new president Sopia Apparel is fine.
Oh and I have something to say to Ahn Seukhwan so please leave the room.
Huh? Oh okay.
Is it true that Jaemin's mother's family is secretly buying our stocks?
Yes I'm sorry.
They're just planning to take it all aren't they?
It seems as if we need to get Joonhee to take over.
Check up on Joonhee's conditions from his caretaker in Paris.
Yes ma'am.
Weakling... he had to take after his mother.
Nevermind that one.
Do you have something you're looking for?
I'm looking for something I can wear comfortably but there isn't one that I really like.
There doesn't seem to be one that will look good on you either how about you try another store?
What?
Don't risk damaging the clothes while you just browse and just go to another place.
I think they're having a sale at the national department store downstairs.
You're telling me that you want me out of here because my standards are low?
What are you doing? I told you to keep these kinds of people out from the entrance.
Please show him out before another customer comes in.
Lady you must be crazy.
Where are you grabbing? Call the security!
- What are you doing to a customer? What's this store's number?
- Sir you left this behind. I was looking all over for you.
This... isn't...
You must be confused because you bought too many things. Should I just send it to Daegoo with the rest of the things?
Forget it.
I'll just carry this.
Please visit our store again next time.
Sure. I'll do that.
I'll just stick to the stores that I've been going to.
Sir... I think I made a mistake...
Anyways... There isn't much to wear in this place no matter how much I look... Nothing nothing...
Sir... Sir...
That was close so unkind.
Anyways... Okay! I got it all.
What is this anyways?
Feels so nice!
So there are people who buy things like this.
Crazy... He must have a ton of money.
This is great!
I'm going to go crazy. Why is this so nice?
These are so my clothes.
The clothes make the person.
Does that even make sense?
I'm right here and you gave my things to who?
I'm so sorry but she made certain that she checked the face.
But it really was the same. I thought you just took your sunglasses off.
Do you have a twin?
I'm sorry. Since it's our fault we'll find the same clothes and send it to you as soon as possible.
You know that suit is a limited edition right?
There was only one left in Korea but I'll leave that in your hands.
This is a lie right?
Maybe you don't get this.
But your father handed over the store then borrowed money from us.
So don't waste time and hand it over.
Why should I?
Why? Are your ears blocked or something?
This store isn't yours anymore.
Don't touch that!
What are you going to do? Huh?
I said don't touch it!
Are you kidding?
Get in there and do something!
Who are you?
Isn't it embarrassing for a bunch of guys to hit a girl? Let's just stop this.
Okay. Who are you?
Are you her husband?
Do you want to pay for this store's debts?
It's not that...
Wherever we go there is some idiot trying to interfere.
Hey don't embarrass yourself and just leave. Before I beat you..
That's enough.
I'll just leave you for today but don't regret today when I come and tear this store apart next time.
I don't have regrets... I've never looked back on anything in my life.
Just leave. Go!
Let's go.
Yoojin are you okay?
Daesan!
Stupid perm loser!
Thank you.
Scary huh?
I'm fine.
There's no reason to be surprised. You see a whole lot of things when you come out to the market.
Do you want some coffee?
It's best to just forget things like this with coffee.
I'll get you the best coffee in Seoul.
Let's go!
How are your legs so weak? How do you expect to work in the market like that?
What kind of coffee is it?
We're almost there let's go.
Do you see that way over there?
This is where I come when I'm tired or stressed out.
I've never shown this to anyone.
I'm letting you in on this just because the situation has been bad recently.
You're mine!
Even if I die you will be mine!
You just wait!
Great East Gate you will be Oh Daesan's! Success!
Try it.
Huh?
Say whatever you want.
You keep everything inside yourself but what would happen if you wanted to let it out and aren't able to?
There's no one to listen anyways. Try it!
I hate you.
Because of you I'm hurting so much.
Because of you...
How dare you...
Coffee sugar and cream. Even thought it seems the same it's different here.
After screaming when no one is around cold hands and sore throat... The coffee tastes different.
That's why I never drink coffee from other places.
You studied in Paris?
Yeah.
What school? Studio Bercot? Or ESMOD?
ESMOD.
You might not believe me but I wanted to go study abroad in Paris too.
I barely graduated from high school so it may not be easy. But I want to go study and succeed in the Great East Gate things like that.
Don't worry too much. Things like this happen all the time. Shops close down in a blink of an eye.
Honestly we have to move out of the house too.
There seems to be a lot of other debts and I don't even know how much there is and my mom doesn't know anything.
What am I going to do if "Eastern" is lost too?
I'll help you.
I owe a lot to your father.
He took me in when I left the orphanage and was wandering the markets fed me clothed me and gave me jobs.
He saved a kid that was almost dying.
So I'm going to repay the debt.
Thanks for your helpful words.
First let's sell the leftover stock since we need to save the store.
You may not know but "Eastern" is a famous store in the Great East Gate.
It's not something you hand over for a little debt.
And I also know of a place that's hiring designers you might like it.
Do you want to or not?
I don't know if I should be bothering you so much.
Let me see your phone.
Hurry!
If you need any kind of help don't hesitate to call me.
Since I always called your father "Uncle"  just think of me as an older cousin.
You seem younger than me so you can just call me oppa.
Go back to Paris.
Save the store save money for school then return to Paris and become an amazing designer.
Then when I go you can help me out. Okay?
Rock on.
I always wanted to serve you the food I made.
But you didn't wait for me this time either.
Rest in peace.
Ahjusshi.
Young Master.
What are you doing wasting money out of the house?
Hurry and return to the house in Seongbook-Dong.
You couldn't wait to get me out of the house before. Why?
I lived alone for ten years. It's uncomfortable to live with others now.
Others?
You have to fill your father's place.
If you lack education go study. And if you lack the business skills we can fill them with clever assistants. Know that and give up your life in Pari
Does Jaemin know?
Why? You don't want to hand the company over to someone of another blood?
I've never been treated as a grandson from you nor been acknowledged as the inheritor of the company.
It's a bit uncomfortable to be treated this way.
Just take it when it's given to you. Your father did that.
Is that why he was just watching when you took me from him?
Ten years ago you said to my father...
"It would have been better if Jaemin was the grandson. If I knew he was going to be weak like this I would never have taken him."
You probably thought I was sleeping then but I wanted to die at that moment.
It's a sin for a person who has to take care of 3000 people to be weak. That's why.
Also if I had left you in your mom's care do you think she could have afforded your artificial heart valve?
Father left me a message. He said he told me my mother was dead because he thought I might get hurt but she is still alive.
So I want to find her and ask her the reason she left me.
When that's done I'm returning to Paris.
Joonhee I'm sorry to reveal the truth as I leave this Earth.
Yoo Junghee she is your real mother.
You may have thought she was dead but no one knows of her whereabouts.
Life is short and regrets are never ending I wonder why I didn't realize that before.
Please seek her forgiveness for your grandmother and me.
There is nothing else that you know about Joonhee's birth mother?
You instructed me to forget the dead. I haven't done any more or any less than you've instructed.
If I think about it sometimes I wonder if she is really dead.
Because she might return to claim her son I did it while Kangil was abroad.
If she was alive she might have came to Kangil's funeral.
Find out if she is alive or not and let me know.
Yes ma'am.
You can drink now?
It's pretty crowded today. I can handle one or two cups.
Did grandmother come to see you?
Do as she says. It doesn't make sense to follow another career when there is a perfect job at home.
I can always use your help too.
How long has it been since we saw each other?
Four years? Do you even remember my face as you're saying that?
I'm on your side whatever you do.
I'm not going to stop you even if you're returning to Paris. Grand Chef nice isn't it?
But if you're planning to leave the company hand over the stocks you received.
And if things work out I can even pay you for them.
For what? I can just leave it like the will said then sell it in five years that would be easier.
Do you think you can sell Sopia to another person with your own hands?
Just like father said four years ago you're the only blood-related inheritor.
Take time and think about it I'll wait for you.
Clean up at the hotel and come home don't ruin the mood at the house.
ESMOD students from France's ESMOD are different. Her sense of fashion is so much better.
Well if you studied designing it shouldn't be too hard. If you can do patterns that's good and if you can even make the basic shape I'll multiply
What did I tell you? Good feel and good skill too. You're lucky too.
And that it's a new product so if she can copy that it'll sell like mad.
I'm sorry but I don't think I can do it.
What?
Even though I'm not working right now I'm going to become a real designer later.
I think I'll be furious if someone copies my work like this later so I just can't do it.
Okay. I'm not going to hire a person who doesn't want to work. I was going to help you out because of your situation.
I'm sorry.
Being picky... She isn't really suffering yet.
I guess not.
Hey hey! Hey!
What's your problem? You said you wanted to run the store and work part time too.
If you want to gather that kind of money you don't really have a choice.
So you're making me steal?
What? Steal?
For you copying the design might be nothing but designers spend days – no months – to come up with those designs.
Even if I am on the verge of dying of hunger that's something I should never do.
Acting so elegant...
What?
How about you? You studied with the money your father sent you by doing things like this didn't you?
That...
You may think the people in the markets are little people that survive on ramen everyday
but there are lives that have to carry on by doing whatever it takes even if it means stealing.
It's even more embarrassing to act all elegant then come begging after you lose everything. Do you understand?
One second.
I'm sorry I must have forgetten to get money from the bank sorry.
What...
- Since yours is the only one with bigger size I'm charging extra.
- Oppa!
Is this really original? I haven't really worn much of this but this seems a bit weird. Isn't this a copy?
Let's stop this. I Oh Daesan have lived so far on trust. Your distrust is like cutting me open and tearing out my heart.
What did I do? Oppa can't I joke a little?
Sign it.
Aeran this is real.
Done for the day! Be careful not to drink too much and you know to be careful in smoking rooms right?
Of course!
My unnies! Don't forget next week is the last week for sales. Don't forget to collect all the tips you can! Success!
Success!
Go in it's cold.
Be careful bye!
Park Seungjae you can leave now.
Next person please enter.
Seo Yoojin?
Yes.
It says that you won at a designing contest in France. Have you studied abroad?
That...
I thought you weren't going to ask about education.
That's true. A simple certificate isn't really important. But doesn't it make sense that we check your acceptance into the school?
I was at ESMOD in Paris.
You should have said so earlier. Did you graduate this year? Or not yet?
Seo Yoojin.
Actually I'm on a break.
Then it's the same as not going to the school.
But I'm confident in my love for design.
I hope you consider me not on my education but my skill.
Thank you. You may leave we will contact you shortly.
Hold on.
The portfolio you turned in seems very fresh. Was this fifth piece Rokkoko Avant Garde the design you won with?
Yes it is.
Lee Jaemin?
Ahjusshi that's you right?
Your ahjusshi isn't here at this interview. Please leave.
Ah okay.
Do you know her?
No please call in the next person.
That's definitely him.
Welcome.
Who is this? You look nice.
Did you get a good deal?
What are you talking about? These are my normal clothes. Do I look good?
If you were Cinderella the prince would be able to find you instantly. Such small and beautiful feet.
Such a liar.
This is pretty is it new?
Consider it a gift from your oppa for the newly opened store.
Really?
- Hey hey. You heard that I'm opening a new store right?
- Yeah.
We're going to fill it up with shiny new products from Paris. How about it? You won't be just any customer but a real VIP.
Just look the clothes are on a whole different level.
Oppa!
Hey.
It's been a while Daesan.
Yang Madam it's a bit sad to see you like this.
Oppa. Look listen to me...
- Hey!
- What? What?
- Don't touch my clothes.
- Come here!
I didn't know this was your area.
Do you think I would come here if I knew?
Let's go talk outside.
Fine I've been doing badly recently. So I happened to walk in because I've been running around a lot.
Hey it's not like there's a line here showing that it's your district. Why do we people like you and I need business districts?
It's not like we just met let's share the wealth. Good boy.
Are you kidding me? You little weasel.
What did you say?
- He went that way.
- Which room is it?
You little... Are you messing with me?
You little bastard.
Who are you?
You're so dead.