Previously on "Lost"...
I was in a wheelchair
paralyzed for four years.
This island-- It changed me.
It made me whole.
I'm so thankful for you, John.
You stole my kidney.
You needed a father,
and I needed a kidney,
And that's what happened.
Get over it.
I don't care what Jack said.
They've got him, and we have to
get him back. I owe him that.
- How did you get onto this island?
- They brought me on the submarine.
So your people-- They can just
come and go whenever they want?
You never know when a little
C4 might come in handy.
Jack--
Name?
John Locke.
Marital status, Mr. Locke?
Uh, single.
Girlfriend?
No.
Are your parents living?
Uh, I was raised in foster care.
I never really knew my parents.
Have you ever considered seeking
out your biological parents?
Uh, uh...
I don't see how that's relevant.
It's relevant, Mr. Locke, because if the
government's gonna continue paying your
disability insurance,
I have to figure out whether or
not your condition has improved.
So... how's your appetite?
Fine.
I see you stopped submitting your
therapy bills for reimbursement.
It's 'cause I stopped going.
Waste of time.
It's just a temporary suspension,
Mr. Locke.
As soon as you resume your sessions,
you can reapply.
You think I'm
temporarily disabled?
Depression can be
temporary, yes.
And since you see fit to
stop going to therapy,
I guess you're all better.
Guess I am.
Next!
What is he doing?
Good hands!
Jack!
She's the one who helped
me and Sawyer escape.
- What's up?
- I think it's gonna be a while...
- Hey, what?
- Danielle.
John, Rousseau's gone.
This is gonna be more
complicated than we thought.
Synchro: Travis
Transcript: Raceman - www.forom.com
So what exactly
are you saying--
We simply start shooting
people and hope for the best?
We came here to rescue Jack,
and that's what we're gonna do.
But obviously the circumstances have
changed. He may not want to be rescued.
That is not him.
That's not Jack.
They must have done
something to him.
When they captured us,
they drugged us.
He didn't appear to
be drugged, Kate.
They kidnapped him, held him prisoner.
He wouldn't just forget that.
I agree, but until we know why,
we're putting our lives at risk.
- I'm not leaving him, Sayid.
- We may not have a choice.
It's Jack.
The first time I saw him,
he was risking his life
pulling people out of
burning airplane wreckage.
If he's shaking hands with the Others,
I'm sure he has a good reason.
We just have to go down there
and find out what it is.
What do you suggest?
We wait till it's dark.
We approach Jack when he's alone...
And if he wants out,
we get him out.
Here's what we know, Crystal.
The bolivian coal deposits were
stolen last night around 2:00 A.M.
Oh, that means the Cobra--
He's back.
Has he been shot?
I can't find him!
He's armed! I can't get up!
Hello. John locke?
I'm sorry. No solicitors.
I have a sign.
Oh, I'm not--
I'm not trying to sell you...
Listen, my name's Peter Talbot.
I-I just need a couple
minutes to talk to you.
- Talk about what?
- My mother, actually.
I think she might
be in some trouble.
You got the wrong John Locke.
How many kidneys do you have?
She met him two months ago.
"Love at first sight," is what she said.
The guy was charming,
sweet, funny.
His name's Adam Seward.
He's a retired computer
entrepreneur from Ontario.
Anyway, Adam had
something... special.
My mom just went gaga for
him right out of the gate.
After two months of knowing him,
she agrees to marry the guy.
And something about him, it...
Something in my gut told me that he was
after something, so I had to check
him out.
Well, i'm not sure I know what
any of this has to do with me.
Well, what this has to do with you,
Mr. Locke,
is that you donated one of
your kidneys to Adam Seward,
Only his name was different back then.
He used to be "Anthony Cooper."
All I could find were
his medical records,
and I saw that he was the recipient
of a kidney transplant from...
you.
So I figured, hey, someone gave the
guy his kidney. How bad could he be?
Right?
Well, it-- It was an anonymous donation.
I never met him.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I can't help you.
Sayid, you guard the front.
I'll go around and cover the back.
- You head in through the side door.
- I'm going in alone?
It's better if you're
the first one he sees.
All right.
Hi.
- What are you doing here?
- I came to get you.
Get out of here right now. Go.
Jack-- Kate,
they're watching me!
- Get out of here!
- I'm not leaving you.
Yes, you are!
Get down! Get down!
Don't hurt her! Don't hurt her!
Step back, doc. Step back.
- Jack!
- Hold him still.
Jack! Jack!
Who else is with you?
- Jack?
- Just answer the question, Kate.
Okay, one more time--
Who else is with you?
Nobody.
Nobody else. It was just us.
Alex?
John!
- Shh. Keep your voice down.
- All right.
It's all right, John.
You don't have to point the gun at me.
I can tell you where Jack is.
I'm not looking for Jack.
I'm looking for the submarine.
The submarine-- Where is it?
I'm not sure what you mean, John.
What submarine?
The one you use to travel
to and from the island...
The one your man
Mikhail told me about
Right before I killed him.
- Dad? Who are you talking to?
- Alex, don't come in here!
- Tell her to be quiet.
- Alex, please.
Ben, you awake?
No!
I'm coming in.
- What is it?
- It's Austen and Jarrah.
They're here.
Somehow they found us.
Where are they now?
We captured them.
We're holding 'em over at my place.
Want me to help
you get outta the--
No. Separate them.
I want to know how they found us.
What about Juliet and
Shepard? Tomorrow--
Let me worry about that.
Just go.
Got it.
Richard, wait a minute.
I'll wait outside.
I want you to bring me
the man from Tallahassee.
- What do you need him for?
- Just do it. Now.
Okay.
"The man from Tallahassee"?
What is that...
Some kind of code?
No, John, unfortunately,
we don't have a code for
"There's a man in my closet with
a gun to my daughter's head,"
Although we obviously should.
Sayid-- He had a pack with him.
I want her to retrieve it.
Okay.
But you should know, John,
my daughter currently hates me,
so i'm not sure holding me
hostage is your best option--
Dad.
I'll get your bag.
Honey? What do you
think of this one?
Oh, it looks good.
What do you think?
I like it.
Maybe just a little larger.
Yeah...
Larger would be good.
Um, i'll go over
there and take a look.
Hello, John.
Gonna be a big to-do
or just the two of
you and a preacher?
I guess you couldn't invite me, huh?
That would make for...
awkward introductions.
- How did you even know that i was gonna--
- I know because her son came to me
And asked why I
gave you a kidney.
He's on to you,
but he doesn't have any proof.
So he came to me hoping
I would vouch for you.
What did you say to him?
You're conning her, aren't you?
You're gonna marry her
for her money, right?
What is it you want, John?
I want you to end it.
I want you to call
off the wedding.
- Why are you doing this?
- Because-- Because it's not fair.
You make people think
that you're their family,
and then you leave
their life in ruins,
and i'm not gonna
let you do it again.
You're gonna call off
your engagement and go,
or I'm gonna tell
her the truth.
I want to hear you say it.
You say you're gonna leave.
Okay, John. You got it.
Would you mind helping
me get into my chair?
No tricks, I promise.
I just want some dignity.
You of all people should understand
what it means to want some dignity.
Thank you.
So tell me, John,
how do you expect to
pilot our submarine?
I mean,
it's a complicated piece of machinery.
You don't just
press "submerge."
Oh, I'll figure something out.
For all you know,
I was a commander in the navy.
Put your arm around my neck.
I'll lift under your knees.
What's in the pack, John?
If you've met Mikhail, that means you
were in the communications station...
Which means you
found the explosives.
So you're not planning to pilot
the submarine anywhere, are you?
You're planning to destroy it.
I know you, John Locke.
You don't know me at all.
I know you were
born in California.
I know you were raised
in foster care.
I know you wasted a big
part of your life in Tustin
pushing papers at a company That
manufactured industrial boxes.
I know you spent the four years Prior to
your arrival on this island in
a wheelchair.
And I know how you
ended up in it.
Tell me, john...
Did it hurt?
I felt my back break.
What do you think?
I didn't think I'd see
you again so soon, Kate.
- Be careful in here.
- Thanks.
Did they hurt you?
No. Did they hurt you?
No.
What is all this?
This is where they live.
And the people they took?
The kids?
They're all safe.
"Safe"?
So you're with them now?
I'm not with anyone, Kate.
- What did they do to you?
- Nothing.
Then why are you
acting like this?
There's no way-- You--
There's no way that I could--
I came here to help you. So why
don't you tell me what's going on?!
I told you not to come
back here for me.
I didn't think you meant it.
What did they do to you, Jack?
I made a deal with them.
They're gonna let me go.
Where?
Home.
When?
First thing in the morning.
I can bring back help.
It's our best chance.
You trust these people? They are liars.
Why would you believe a word they--
I trust them because
you told me to, Kate...
When you asked me to
save Sawyer's life.
Jack... What did they tell you?
Jack, we need to go.
I'll be right there.
I asked you not to come back
here for me, and I wish...
I wish that you hadn't.
But I will come
back here for you.
John Locke?
Yeah?
Detective Mason. That's Detective Reed.
Do you mind if we ask you a
few questions?
No, of course not.
Do you know a man
named Peter Talbot?
No, I don't think so.
Thin, brown hair, 20s?
If it'll be helpful, we believe he was
here in your apartment two days ago.
Oh! Oh, oh, yeah.
Yeah, he was a solicitor.
I-I, uh, i sent him away.
Mr. Talbot's family is worth somewhere
in the neighborhood of $200 million.
So I'm curious.
What exactly was he
selling you door-to-door?
Well, I--
Look, I told you I don't know him.
Then why was your name and address on a
piece of paper in his pocket, Mr. Locke?
Why were you-- Would you be
looking through his pockets?
Because Peter Talbot's dead.
It wasn't easy, you know...
Being in that hatch with
you all that time...
Knowing you had no
business walking around,
Knowing I couldn't even ask you about it
without telling you who I really was.
So ask me now...
Now that I know
who you really are.
Was it immediate?
It started the
moment you got here?
- Yeah.
- And you were just walking--
The feeling returned right
after the crash, that day?
That's what
"immediate" means, Ben.
You're wondering why it
hasn't happened for you.
You're not recovering
as fast as you'd like.
How long's it been
since Jack fixed you?
A week?
Now that I think about it,
how did you get sick
in the first place?
Are you afraid
it'll go away, John?
Is that why you want to
destroy the submarine--
Because you know if you ever leave this
island, you'll be back in the chair?
You got anything to eat?
Hey!
Go on home, kid.
You know you're not
supposed to be here.
My father sent me
to get his pack.
Why?
I don't know, Ryan,
but he told me to get it.
All right. Here you go.
You're Alex, aren't you?
Hey! Can it.
How do you know my name?
Because you look
like your mother.
My mother is dead.
I'm sure that's
what they told you.
Get going, Alex!
Keep your mouth shut.
Where do you get electricity?
We have two giant hamsters running on a
massive wheel at our secret
underground lair.
Yeah, that's funny.
There's leftovers in the refrigerator.
Help yourself.
I ate most of the
dark meat. Sorry.
Mmm. I never really appreciated
chicken until right now.
I know you think you
need to do this, John,
but if you blow
up my submarine,
I'll have a big
problem with my people.
Is that supposed to be an
incentive not to blow it up?
I was born on this island.
Not many of my people can say that.
Most of them were
recruited and brought here.
And as much as they
love this place,
as much as they would do
anything to defend it,
they need to know they
can leave if they want to.
The sub maintains
that illusion.
- So you're lying to 'em.
- No.
They're here because
they want to be here.
Some of them are just not ready
to make a full... commitment yet.
But you, John...
You've already made
that commitment,
and now you have a choice.
Because if you stop
and if you think,
I can show you things--
Things i know you want
to see very badly.
Let me put it so
you'll understand.
Picture a box.
You know something about boxes,
Don't you, John?
What if I told you that
somewhere on this island
there's a very large box,
and whatever you imagined,
whatever you wanted
to be in it,
when you opened that box,
there it would be.
What would you say
about that, John?
I'd say I hope that box is big enough
to imagine yourself up a new submarine.
- Why are you so angry, John?
- Because you're cheating.
You and your people
communicate with the outside
world whenever you want to.
You come and go as you please.
You use electricity and
running water and guns.
You're a hypocrite, a pharisee.
You don't deserve to
be on this island.
If you had any idea what
this place really was,
You wouldn't be putting
chicken in your refrigerator.
You've been here 80 days, John.
I've been here my entire life.
So how is it that you think you
know this island better than I do?
Because you're in
the wheelchair,
and I'm not.
Did you have any problems?
Okay, here's how
this is gonna work--
She's gonna take me to the sub.
Once we're there, I let her go.
John, she's done enough.
Let me take you.
I don't want you
to slow me down.
Come on. Let's go.
John, before you go,
you should know...
Jack and I made a deal.
In less than an hour he's leaving
this island on that submarine,
and it's a 1-way ticket.
The anomaly wiped out our
communications. We have no way of
contacting the outside world...
Which means when that sub leaves,
it can never come back.
So whether you destroy the
submarine or whether you let it go,
the end result is the same--
No one will find this island.
Let's go.
Come on.
You know he's
manipulating you, right?
How's that?
That's what my father does.
He manipulates people.
He makes you think it's your idea,
but it's his.
I'll have to keep that in mind.
Submarine's down there...
At the end of the dock.
I'm sorry I had to
involve you in this.
Look, I know you
don't owe me anything,
But I need to ask you
for one last favor.
You don't knock?
I need you to let my
friends go after I'm gone.
And if I said no,
would that stop you from leaving?
Of course it would.
Your friends are only
here to rescue you.
But you seem to be doing a good
job of rescuing yourself, so...
I suppose there's no
reason to keep them here.
Do i have your word on that?
You have my word.
I'll let them go just as soon
as you've left the island.
Well, I guess this is it.
Thank you, Ben,
for keeping your promise.
Hey!
Hold it right there!
Get your hands up!
Get down! I said get down!
What are you doing here, John?
I'm sorry, Jack.
Sorry for what?
What did you do?
John?
Tell me you didn't do it.
- What are you talking about?
Tell me that you
didn't kill that kid.
What?
You think I had something
to do with Peter's death?
I tell you to end things with his
mother, and the next thing you know,
he's dead!
John, now calm down, please.
Think about what you're saying.
- Why would I kill Peter?
- He was on to you!
John, I've been doing this for a long
time. I'm not sweating some rich kid.
Then why are you still here?
- What do you mean?
- I tell you to leave.
You tell me you're gonna leave town.
Why are you still here?!
Now listen, John,
I'll be honest with you.
I didn't end it.
I was looking for an angle.
I wanted to make some
money before I skipped out.
But then all this happened.
Peter died, and everything just
went straight into the tank.
She's devastated.
She's called off the wedding.
There's no profit in it, John.
I'm a con man, not a murderer.
She called off the wedding?
She said she couldn't
deal with it.
She needs to be alone.
So if I were to call her right now,
that's what she would tell me.
Phone's right over there, John.
What's her numb-- Aah!
Mr. Locke, we know this isn't
what you want to hear, but...
Your father's gone.
We know he fled to Mexico
shortly after your... encounter,
then he disappeared.
I'm sorry, but he could be
anywhere in the world right now.
All right, detectives,
that's enough.
Mr. Locke has work to do today.
We'll let you know if
anything develops.
John, John, John, we have got ourselves
quite a day ahead of us, my friend.
It's finally time to get
you up out of that bed.
No. I don't want to.
I don't remember asking.
Now...
Most people struggle with this at first,
but don't worry.
You'll get used to it.
No, wait. No, please.
I-I-I can't do this.
John, you fell eight
stories and survived, okay?
I don't want to hear
about what you can't do.
Now let's go.
It's gonna be all right.
- No, I don't--
- No. It's gonna be fine, John. Come on.
No, I can't...
You're fine.
There we go.
There you go, buddy.
See? Wasn't that bad, was it?
Be right back, buddy.
Well, John,
you've really gone and done it now.
You don't have to pretend
to be disappointed anymore.
We both know you
wanted it to happen.
You left the C4 in Sayid's bag
because you wanted me
to make it happen.
Uncuff him, please, Richard.
You gonna do anything stupid?
No, sir.
Do you remember earlier, John,
when you called me a cheater...
When you said I didn't deserve
to live on this island?
Well, get this--
There I was, shaking hands with Jack
and thinking I'd give almost
ything to come up with a way
to stop him from leaving,
because to let him go would be a sign
a weakness, of failure, of defeat.
My people would see that.
They would know it,
and that, John,
would be the end of me.
But to kill him...
That would be cheating,
because my people also
heard me make a promise,
and to break my word...
That would be the
end of me, too.
And then you came striding
out of the jungle, John...
To make my dream come true.
You're not gonna start talking
about the magic box again, are you?
No, John.
I'm gonna show you what came out of it.
When I asked you
earlier if it hurt
When you suffered your injury,
I think you misunderstood me.
It seems fairly obvious that
when a person's back smashes
into a hard surface after being thrown
from a building, that that's gonna sting
a little.
But I really wasn't asking
about the physical pain.
What, do you want to know
if it hurt my feelings?
No, john.
I wanted to know what it felt like
When your own father
tried to kill you.
He's the reason you destroyed
the submarine, isn't he?
You're afraid.
You're afraid of him,
and this is the one place
he can never find you.
This is the one place
he can never get to.
What do you want from me?
I don't know how it happened...
But you seem to have some
communion with this island, John,
and that makes you very,
very important.
You have no idea what you're
talking about, of course,
but in time you'll have a
better understanding of things.
- So what do I want?
- I want to help you, John.
Why?
Because I'm in a wheelchair,
and you're not.
Are you ready to see?
Dad?
Synch: Travis
Transcript: Raceman - www.forom.com