In case you just got here, I'm Spider-Man
And I'm in a race against the clock
So much to be responsible for, so little time
Like weird energy readings coming from a lab
Doctor Octopus abandoned before he went tentacles up
But a good leader like me knows to bring good backup
Spider, we got company here
Engaging at the east entry
Ava Ayala, White Tiger
Cat-like speed and reflexes. She's on this
Power Man, Iron Fist, Tiger's down
Any visual on an adversary?
Yeah, I can't believe it, but he's alive!
And movin' right for us
Or is it we who move for him? Perspective defines reality
Luke Cage, the super-strong Power Man
And Danny Rand, Iron Fist
he of chi-powered fist and haiku shout outs
They're on this
Nova, light us up, now
You don't have to yell in my earpiece, bug breath. Sheesh
Sam Alexander, Nova, Loud mouth with a mega-helmet
He's a flyer, a fighter, and a great big flashlight
Whoa. Doc Ock alive?
Reports of my demise were greatly exaggerated
This would be really bad...
if I wasn't rocking the latest SHIELD technology
Now, I'm on this
You shouldn't have followed me
I didn't. But I'm glad I found you
No web fluid? Ah, yikes
This is SHIELD! We have you surrounded!
No! Not now!
Nice to see you're keeping up on your training
Training? Maybe you didn't notice, Fury
but my web shooters jammed and Ock got away
P.S. Did you guys even know he was still alive?
We heard rumors. But at least he didn't leave with his prize
Have to give credit where it's due, Spider-Man
Your team has been on point lately
The SHIELD helicarrier may not be back up
and operational yet
but you're doing us proud
I couldn't agree more, Agent Coulson
Securing Ock's experimental DNA compounds?
Incredible work
Want to stay and lend me a hand
testing these samples, Spider-Man?
Do I? You bet, Doctor Connors
Sorry
We gotta jet
Teenagers
Assume position Alpha 3, hurry!
We must hurry. Proceed with haste
C'mon. C'mon. C'mon. Time!
I'm home
Oh. Hi, aunt May
Hey, Mrs. Parker
Hey, guys. What's up?
Any excitement today?
Who has time for excitement?
终极
蜘蛛侠
Welcome to "Casa de Parker"
浮空母舰杯具之后
After the helicarrier went kablooey
"蜥蜴"
我的小队搬进了我家
my team moved in with me
SLOMO动画组
我时常好奇一个大家庭会是怎样
I always wondered what a bigger family would be like
现在我知道了
And now I know
It's been fun, but it's also take a lot of you can used do
Can I get on the computer, Ava?
I'll be off in just a sec
I knew that was coming
Everybody has their own way of adjusting
I'm just going with the flow
And lookin' for a place to work on
my broke-down web shooters
Sorry, Danny
Luke? Again?
Takes a routine to look this good
These days, the basement is the only place I can be alone
A small price to pay for family. I guess
C'mon, aunt May. No pain, no gain
- Who kicks butt? - I do
And cue my exit music
Want to stay and lend me a hand
testing these samples, Spider-Man?
A hi-tech lab plus a super-scientist mentor?
That equals the best idea I ever almost forgot
No web slinging would be a problem
for an average Spider-Man
But an ultimate Spidey just says
"hello SHIELD-issued Spidey-cycle."
Goodbye gridlock
Hello solitude
Ah, see? There's your clogging problem
The intake-canister's cracked
Causing the web fluid to leak
Hah, you're a life-saver, Doc
Me? No, no, no, no. That's your job
I'm just your friendly neighborhood one-armed scientist
From the day I first joined SHIELD, heh
Doc Connors was 100% cool peeps
A fellow "science-geek"
and if I'm being completely honest, a real mentor for me
I still feel responsible for him loosing his arm
There, good as new
Better. Tap twice
Flash webs? Cool
Simple upgrade. Us brains have to stick together, right?
Speaking of which
I want you to see what Octavius was after
I think you'll find this particularly interesting
considering your power set
Whoa. Is this animal DNA?
Do you see what he was getting at?
He wanted to open an evil petting zoo?
I believe Otto was inspired by you to try and create
a group of people powered by specific DNA sequences
Ah, the old "build an animal army world domination" gag
I'm glad we put the kibosh on that
But place this technology
in the hands of a scientist who isn't a madman
and then what do you get?
He's not thinking what I think he's thinking... is he?
I think these animal compounds could
regenerate a damaged human body
I know it sounds far-fetched, but
look at how you turned out
I... got lucky
But look at Venom or Goblin if you want
the usual results of Ock's genetic guesswork
Of course. You... you're right
I shouldn't rush into anything
Hey, that doesn't mean
we can't dig deep into his notes
Have to be super careful
Don't want to trip any of Ock's nutso security
Just leave that to me
Welcome, intruder, You want my tech? Have at it
- Hey, what is that? - What's going on?
- Wilcox, call for back-up! - That might be my fault
The sample vials!
Science later. Saving now
Look out!
- Oh, no. No! - Intruder alert
Spider-Man!
Oh, really? After all I've lived through
it ends on a steel slab and a laser?
What the what?
Whoa! Thanks
- Remarkable - Doc?
Uh, high five?
- What'd you do? - I saved you with science!
Doc, did you just? I appreciate the hand...
Help... help. I mean help
But you shouldn't have taken the serum
Perhaps
- But I feel incredible - Uh, yeah?
Well, my Spidey-sense just started ringing like a firehouse
and I'm guessing you're the alarm
Well, it can't be me, I'm fine. Look. Look out!
He brought friends
We can handle this, Spidey. You and me, together
While impromptu team-ups are a norm in this biz
I can honestly say I did not expect...
Spider-Man and Man-lizard
Combating evil with the forces of nature on their side
We make a good team, huh?
Team? Doc, are you feeling all right?
You look a little green
Doc Ock puts the "mad" in mad scientist
Who knows what his lizard juice is doing to you?
I'm great
I do have a slight itch at the back of my brain
but... maybe more?
Hey, Doc! A little help here!
With some fine tuning
Otto's work could cure me and thousands like me
I need to ask him
if he has more of this substance hidden somewhere
Imagine what other advances the world might have
if we could pull him back from the brink of his madness
Other advances? I don't think you're in the win column yet
I get that you and Ock were friends back in college
but the only mind that could even begin
to make sense of Ock's weird work is Ock's
Exactly! But not if we don't give him the...
Chance
Doc?
Oh, boy
Oh, no
What happened to you?
If Otto is the only one
who can perfect my change, then I must find him
His great power? Heh, now my responsibility
Doc, wait up! You need a jurassic intervention
Oh, don't lizards have ears?
Whatever's happening to you needs to be looked at, fast
Besides, finding Ock is a needle in a haystack
It's impossible
No. I can smell him. Like lizards do...
With my tongue. He's in the sewers
Ew. That is gross on every level
You need real help before you start spending all
day eating flies and looking for hot rocks to lie on
Spider-Man to SHIELD. Need backup...
I can reach Otto
SHIELD will just lock him up. Take all this from me
I can't lose it again
Maybe too late for that, but it's not too late to tail you
Heh, "tail." I slay myself
Web-brain, where you at?
Sam, I'm... is that limbo music?
May pulled it out. It's killer
No, killer is a lizard-y Doc Connors
on his way to find Doc Ock
Meet me in the sewers at these...
Sewers? Sounds like a dream come poo
I mean true. No, I mean poo
Trace my coordinates. Get here
You got it, big guy. And we'll bring the air freshener
What do you want me to say? "You're welcome"?
You took an untested formula that wasn't even yours
You deserve what you got
Don't mock me, Otto. Perfect this and it help millions
You laugh at me?  Your saver-er?
Can you hear yourself, freak?
You've taken the mind of a genius
and turned it into a pea brain
I'm just as smart as I ever were
Was... ever was-er
I know how to fix you
but I do like what my serum has done
with your skin, monster
You want monster, Octopus?
I'll show monster
I need options
Plan 1: Let 'em rip each other to shreds
Plan 2: Call the team again
Ah, no signal here in "Smellville."
Plan 3: Out-matched and alone like in the action movies
Three it is.
And here I am without my popcorn
Spider-Man, protect me
Spidey, can you hear me? Web-head, are you there?
Web-head, do you copy? Hello?
Doctor Connors, please, don't do this
See, I knew there was still a good guy inside that lizard skin
Stay out of my way!
We have to stop meeting like this
This is no time for your puerile attempts at humor
Puerile? I don't know what that means
But when I find out...
Hey! You are not gonna hurt my friend!
- You said you could fix him - There's no him to fix
- It's 100% reptile now - He's not an it
Your serum is making him irrational
It could have happened to any of us
Stop!
Connors! No!
I'm not giving up on you. I know you're still in there
And Ock knows how to get you out
But you have to help me help you
Say cheese for flash webs
Sorry to use your own tech against you, Doc
Neither one of us will escape here alive unless...
Please don't say it
We team-up
Spider-Man super-villain team-up
My brain goes to some strange places sometimes
This way, I have a plan
You ever feel like the title Doctor might
be slightly undeserved in your case?
It worked, didn't it?
Yeah, you'd make a solid dogcatcher
What did you put in that serum, Ock?
Okay, Ock, plan "B"?
Have you ever heard the term "sacrificial lamb"?
Spider-se...
Hey, no one rang the recess bell
快回来. 告诉我解药!
Come back here. Tell me the cure!
你何不去我的实验室偷一份呢
Why don't you just go steal it from my lab
就是他偷我血清的地方
where he stole my serum?
拜托, 你认识我的
Come on, you know me
我, 蜘蛛侠. 你, 康纳斯博士
Me Spider-Man. You Doc Connors
喔, 踢你鼻子不好意思了, 但我得跑了
Ooh, my bad on the snout kick, but I gotta run
嘿, 你何不跟着我呢? 这边, 来呀
Hey, why don't you follow me? This way, come on
- 来呀, 有种你来 - 打猎么? 好啊
- Come on, I dare you - Hunt? Yes
打猎? 不. 计划? 可以有
Hunt? No. Plan? Yes
蜘蛛大逃亡 2
开始游戏
载入游戏
嘿, 我这走路呢
Hey. I'm walkin' here
啧啧. 这年头超级英雄啊
Sheesh. Super-heroes these days
一点都不尊重老者
No respect for their elders
这就是你的计划?
This was you plan?
不. 这才是我的计划
No. This was me plan
小蜘蛛, 你叫我们?
You called, Spidey?
博士是一条蜥蜴? 哈, 冷血动物
Doc's a lizard? Heh, cold blooded
已经吐槽过了. 而且吐的更棒. 现在, 你们都规矩点.
Already did that one. And better. You all play nice, now
在那可怕的鳞之下的仍是我们的朋友
He's still our friend underneath all that scaly scary
一会儿见
Back in a few
一定要管用啊
Please let this work
希望我的科学技术能胜任
Now, let's hope my science skills are up to
我的拳头未能完成的任务
the task my fists haven't been able to solve
- 牵制住他 - 正在呢
- Keep him distracted. - Trying
但他越来越...强壮了
But he's getting... stronger
你有大概两秒钟, 小蜘蛛
You have about two seconds, Spider
一定要成功
Make it count
- 康纳斯博士? 你还好吗? - 嗯. 我在哪?
- Doc Connors? Are you ok? - Yeah. Where am I?
我...我在干嘛?
What... what am I doing?
哥们, 你变成了一条又大又丑的...
Aw, dude, you turned into a big, ugly...
你刚才在试图帮我
You were trying to help me
事态只是有点失去控制
Things just got a little out of hand
呀, 不好意思. 用错词了
Ooh, sorry. Wrong turn of phrase
不. 不, 只是...
No. No, it's...
康纳斯博士被你发现是他的幸运, 蜘蛛侠
Doctor Connors is lucky you found him, Spider-Man
我们必须帮帮他, 科尔逊. 他是我们的责任
We have to help him, Coulson. He's our responsibility
他是咱们疯狂的神盾大家庭的一份子
He's part of our big crazy SHIELD family
啊哦. 我们得溜了
Uh-oh. We gotta skedaddle
他有进展请告诉我, 好吗?
Let me know how he is, okay?
别担心. 你的责任尽到了. 我们也会尽责
Don't worry. You did your part. We'll do ours
晚餐时间到
Dinner
在今天这样的日子的末尾
At the end of a day like today
很多事情都会成为焦点
A lot of things can come into focus
比如独行并没有吹得那么好. 至于我的小队?
Like solitude's not all it's cracked up to be. And my team?
我应该尽可能的多跟他们在一起
I should get as much time with them as I can
黏在一起, 就像一家人
Stick together, like a family
喔, 彼得. 你来得正是时候. 萨姆做了晚饭
Oh, Peter, you're just in time. Sam made dinner
- 萨姆...做饭? - 他十分有天赋
- Sam... cooks? - He's quite talented
一只火鸡, 加加热, 小事一桩
A bird, some heat, no biggie
喔, 别担心, 丹尼. 专门给你做了些烤豆腐
Oh, don't worry, Danny. Made some grilled tofu for you
就像真正的一家人
Just like a real family
我的神奇家庭
My totally amazing family
欢迎关注@Slomo-Lu小鱼
Weibo.com/2092509395
翻译 FnGs Lu小鱼
特效 Lu小鱼
校对 FnGs
压制 东尼 魔芋
时间轴 小河