(Singing) And you need
some love and care,
And nothing,
nothing is going right,
Close your eyes,
and think of me,
And soon I will be there,
to Brighten up,
even your darkest night,
Winter, spring,
summer or fall,
All you have to do is call,
What the hell
are you doing here?
Is this it?
Thanks for bringing me.
I had to come
to London anyway.
It's worth the detour
to make sure you're not
still hanging around.
Now get out.
I'm sorry,
I just needed to see you.
You needed money, that's all!
Well you won't
make me pay any more.
Never again.
You're scum,
Jane, that's all.
I don't want to know you.
No one does.
Sooner or later
everyone's just going to
think you're dead anyway.
It would be
better if you were!
Now piss off!
Are you all right?
It was just a row, you know.
I thought he was
going to hurt you.
(Doorbell)
More and more bills.
Yes, who is it?
I'm round the back.
Oh, it's you George, is it?
I thought it was the
bloke they send round
to test the front door bells.
We've got a body.
I've been trying to ring you.
my phone is not off.
It's never off.
My phone's off,
where's your mobile?
Yeah.
Let's see.
Ridiculous this is.
I've been filling in forms
so I can get cheap calls
on the numbers I use the most.
Oh, yeah, Indian takeaway
was top of the list.
Quickly followed
by the Chinese.
Oh yeah, they've got
all that on the computer.
Yeah, that's fine.
When it actually comes to
giving you a phone that works,
oh no that's... Hello?
Yes, I want to report a
phone that's out of order.
Yes.
Denton 764323.
And it would be very
helpful, you know,
if you're going
to disconnect people
you inform them
first so that...
What?
I see.
All right.
Yes, yes, I'll see
to it, thank you.
All sorted Jack?
Where's that ruddy bill?
Good day, Inspector.
Yes, good day.
Life extinct early
hours of this morning.
Sometime between
midnight and two a.m.
How old is she?
Between fifteen and sixteen.
Cause of death?
I'm pretty sure the post
mortem will show drowning.
But you'll notice
some recent bruising
around the neck.
That needs to be
examined in more detail.
I thought you should
have a look, at least.
Any means of identification?
I gather not.
All too predictable if
she's been living rough.
No bills, no credit
card, no check book.
None of the stuff of life
which is so indispensable
to most of us.
What about needle marks?
There are no obvious
signs of drugs abuse.
Are you sure?
It's a grim statement of
where we are, Inspector.
I'm called out to the dead
body of a teenage girl,
and like you,
my first thought
is to look for signs
of heroin addiction.
He's back again.
Sorry Mr. Barber.
Didn't know you were
inspecting us again.
Slight problem, Mr. Ryan.
I know, I've got a
pile of forms upstairs
for the Min of Ag.
I'll sign them today.
No it's that Environmental
Health Officer,
he's wandering round again.
I'll call you back.
What does he want now?
I don't know.
He just turned up.
He's obsessed!
Mr. Barber, I'd appreciate
it if you'd inform me
when you arrive
on my premises.
I might be able to help you,
besides the issue of safety.
I'm following
up some complaints
from local residents.
Incinerator dust
on their cars again?
Or is it unpleasant
odors this time?
There may still be a problem
with your incinerator.
I've had that incinerator
serviced twice this year.
And what's it got to do
with you roaming about
the operation anyway?
Just doing my job.
No you're not.
I've a Meat Hygiene Service
inspector here full time.
If you want any information
about this area, ask him,
right, Dave?
I've got nothing relevant
to the Environmental Health,
I've been back for
the figures on your
(Unintelligible)
of meat twice now.
Get off my back
or I'll push you off.
You're wasting
your time on this.
And you've been here too long.
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't have to keep
my head down, do I?
You wouldn't be the
first Meat Inspector
to look the other way.
Look, the meat trade's
had a rough time lately,
and blokes who work here
don't like anyone
who's sniffing around,
especially someone
who's just out for trouble.
They think their jobs
might be on the line.
They get very
stroppy about it.
You'd better
watch yourself, Barber.
The more I get threatened,
the more I think
I should look harder.
Come on, there's
no need for all this.
There were
problems last year,
but Ryan's put money
into new equipment,
a lot of money.
No one's covering
anything up here,
believe me.
You'll want to do
something about that car.
That's a real
environmental health risk.
George, give me one of
those photos, will you?
Spare a bit of change please.
There you go.
Thanks.
That's all right.
Have you seen this girl?
No.
You don't know her?
You're a pig, right?
You got nothing better
to do than to bust me?
She was living
rough in Denton.
Now she's dead.
I can see that.
I'm trying to find
out who she was
and what happened to her.
If she's dead,
it doesn't matter.
Spare a bit of change please.
There's nothing
you can do, Warren.
They definitely don't want
me looking round the place.
They're hiding something.
If I am going to
find out what it is,
I need to get
in there at night,
when there's no one around.
Don't you think you're taking
this a bit too personally?
That's no good reason to
let them get away with it?
And anyway,
there are better things
we can do at night.
Just a kid.
Yeah.
We've got no ID
but if she's been
reported missing
she'd be on the
National Register somewhere.
I imagine you notice
if your fifteen-year-old
daughter goes missing.
I mean, who knows?
She's been living
on the streets
for the last few months.
Anyway, there's the rest.
Ah, Jack, good.
Preliminary autopsy results.
Jack?
Sir, yeah?
Hold it.
We seem to have
a bit of a problem
on the communication front.
Ah, well then you'll
want the CAD room, sir,
that's where all
the communicating
is done round here.
Very hi-tech it is.
I'm referring to the fact
your phone is out of order.
A number of people have
been trying to contact you,
myself included.
Well, that's because there's
been an engineering fault.
My information is
that it's been cut off.
Because...
Excuse me, sir.
Because the bill
hasn't been paid.
Now what sort of
example do you think
it sets the rest of society
when senior police officers
who can't pay their bills
have to have their
facilities cut off?
That could be
rather painful, sir,
when you think about it.
Just, just sort
it out, will you?
Sir.
How did he know?
How did he find out?
Now give me my coat.
I didn't say a word.
I promise, honest.
Joys of owning your
own home again, Jack.
Don't tell me about it.
Have you seen these bills.
Look at this lot.
I've got electricity, gas,
telephone, council tax,
you pay one and there's
another one on the way.
If this carries on much longer
I'm going to end up
delivering pizzas
in the evening.
I might be able to
help you out there.
Why?
Had a win on the lottery?
Or are you selling
lost property
at the car boot sales again?
No, I've got a new
constable starting today.
Tom Haliday.
He did have his
digs sorted out
but they've just
fallen through.
It would only be short term
until he finds
something permanent.
Does he speak only
when he's spoken to?
I'd say so.
Yeah.
Right, sold.
I've got a spare
key here somewhere.
Hang about.
There it is.
Right, he can let himself in.
Oh, Jack, there's just...
As long as he leaves me
alone and pays his rent
I don't care if
he's got two heads.
She was definitely
sleeping rough.
Probably sixteen,
small, young for her age.
Something odd,
given the background,
she'd recently used cosmetics.
They've been wiped away,
but there are
traces of lipstick
at the corners of her mouth,
mascara on the lashes.
Any evidence of
sexual assault?
No.
Drugs?
Her stomach contained alcohol.
And quite a lot of
what I think tests
will prove to be aspirin.
That could be suicide?
I can't speak
for her motives,
but it wasn't
enough to kill her.
Anyway there is no doubt
about the cause of death.
Asphyxia by drowning.
However I would point out
the bruising McKenzie
mentioned in his report.
It's quite extensive.
On the arm and as
you've seen on the leg.
Inflicted by fists,
I'd say, and feet.
She was kicked and punched,
and with considerable force.
Jack,
the computer's
come up with a match.
She was a Jane Owens.
Parents Geoff and
Christine Owens.
Living in Bridgend.
She'd been missing
nearly six months.
Anyone reached the parents?
Yeah, South Wales
have been in contact.
They'll be here
in the morning.
What a journey.
I'm late, I'm late,
Julia, I'm sorry!
I don't care about you Gerry,
so long as you've
brought the first course.
Three dozen oysters.
Fresh in Ostend this morning.
Guaranteed not
to kill the guests.
I'll see to these.
You can get me a
glass of champagne.
I'm just going to go
and hop in the pool.
They'll be here
in half an hour!
Yeah, and the boys will be
home from school tomorrow.
the last chance I get it to
have it to myself for a month.
Don't worry,
I'll come and
answer the door,
even if it is in my trunks.
I don't believe it.
Now what!
That'll do, Kai!
Sit.
Inspector Frost,
I'm Tom Haliday.
Constable Haliday.
And your friend?
This is Kaiser,
but I call him
Kai for short.
You know, Kaiser,
as in the
First World war,
the German?
Yes, all right,
I am aware of that.
But before we
get too involved
in 20th century
European history
maybe you'd like to tell me
what that bloody dog
is doing in my house!
He's with me.
Well, I didn't think he was
with the Jehovah's Witnesses.
I'm a dog handler.
Didn't the Sergeant tell you?
No.
And why aren't my
ruddy lights working?
I had a look at your fuses.
They're OK.
I'd say there's
been a power cut,
unless you haven't
been paying your bills.
Slow.
Tools, Joop!
(Noise)
Shit.
All set?
I'll be reconnected
this afternoon.
No problem?
No.
I've given them two hundred
and sixteen quid for the bill,
quid for the deposit.
And they have
given me nothing off
for good behavior.
So, come on George,
I've done the housekeeping,
I'd like to spend the rest
of the day as a copper.
What do we have to do?
I'll take you
through that later.
I'm afraid that
Jane can't be moved.
Just yet.
We just want to take her home.
Yes, I know.
I think it's best
if we have a little
chat down at the station.
I'd like to talk to you
a little bit about Jane.
What she was like.
It just might help.
When you're ready.
Come on, Geoff.
There's no Jane here.
I have made a
note, Mrs. Barber.
Name, description.
There really is nothing
we can do at the moment.
It's only a matter of what,
fourteen, fifteen hours?
Now, you might find if you
were to ring his office...
I know where he
went last night.
Ryan's Meat Processing.
And he didn't come home.
I want him found.
We'll see if we can
get you a cup of tea.
You go on ahead,
I won't be a minute.
I know that this is the
last place you want to be.
I am not here for pleasure.
I know my husband.
I know something is wrong!
George?
Got a minute?
Could you just hang on,
please, Mrs. Barber.
Yeah?
When the next relief goes out
make sure uniform
have got photographs
of the Owens girl,
you know the body.
Also get a set of these,
they've been brought
in by the parents.
Get them copied.
I want to know who she knew,
where she hung out,
you know.
Where she slept.
Must be somebody out there
who'd seen her
in the last few days.
These kids are invisible
as far as most
people are concerned.
When you have
finished in here.
I can see you're busy.
Husband went AWOL last night.
Don't envy him
when he gets back.
Do I look as if I'm so stupid
that I'd walk into
a police station
just because my husband's
been out on a piss?
Thanks, George.
Thank you.
Well, she did ask to
see someone from CID.
How long's he been missing?
Last night.
He's an Environmental
Health Inspector,
she reckons he
was trying to get into
Ryan's Meat Processing,
on the quiet,
thinks they're up
to something dodgy.
Now Jack, do you
think that's likely?
I reckon he's gone
over the side.
Come on.
That reminds me I've got
a bone to pick with you.
It's a room I'm
letting, not a kennel.
Jack, I would have told you.
Yeah well.
Look why don't
you send someone
down to that meat place.
And while you're at it
get someone to check out
with traffic and hospitals.
First we thought
it was accident,
then at the mortuary,
they talked as if
she'd killed herself.
Well, we don't know.
We're trying to put
together a picture
of the last few
days of Jane's life.
Especially her last evening.
Is there anything that
you could help me with?
We haven't seen
or heard from her,
not from the
day she walked out.
She didn't tell
us she was going.
She just left a note to say,
she had to go.
I see.
Did she know anyone
here in Denton?
No.
We've never been here.
We thought she was in London.
There was a description
of someone like her,
a few days after she went.
It was a service
station on the M4.
We tried everything.
We put adverts in papers.
We went to London
for days on end
and just walked round.
We still do, did.
It was the only
place we could think,
it's where people
go isn't it?
Have you any idea
why she left home?
No.
You know, we didn't
even argue much,
not considering
she was fifteen,
the way teenagers...
we thought we were so lucky.
Her brother was
very different.
He's older,
and he was a
nightmare at her age.
She was doing so
well at school, wasn't she?
She enjoyed it.
She had good friends,
people we liked.
And what about her brother?
Mark.
Has she had any
contact with him?
No.
I'm sorry there isn't any
answers in all of this.
Is just that I'm trying to
build up a picture of Jane.
You know,
what she was really like.
At least we can
talk about her.
The only thing
that did happen
was a friend of hers died.
Angie.
It was eighteen
months ago now.
It upset her a lot,
and I'm not saying
she'd forgotten,
but it wasn't...
She was an very
ordinary girl,
who was enjoying
growing up, we thought.
We were close, Mr Frost,
very close,
all of us.
We've never understood.
Inspector, where did she die?
We found them
somewhere to stay?
Yeah, it's all done.
So far we know
precisely nothing.
We don't even know how
long she'd been in Denton.
If she'd just got here,
maybe nobody did know her.
Well somebody did.
Who brought those flowers?
Mrs. Barber, I really don't
know what this is all about.
The police have been
here this morning.
I've told them
everything I know.
He came here last night.
He'd no reason to
be here last night.
The place was shut up.
There was nobody here.
There's nothing
else I can say.
You could tell me the truth!
I don't pretend
your husband and I
didn't have our differences.
Frankly I felt he
had a personal grudge
about me and my business.
I even went so far as
complaining to his superiors.
But what you're
suggesting is, ridiculous.
That's it.
I really would
like you to leave.
My husband is
missing, Mr. Ryan,
and I know he came here.
The police may not
want to listen to me,
but they will.
Because I am not going to
stop shouting until they do.
It's no good having
a go at me, love.
You're just protecting Ryan!
But let me tell
you something.
I know you're
in on it as well,
and I'm going to be back!
(Truck horn)
I'll see you.
Thanks.
One of ours, Sergeant?
No one of mine.
Your lodger.
Oh, really, what happened.
Kaiser bite him did he?
Constable Haliday
tripped over the dog
and down the stairs.
Oh dear.
Wait 'till you
hear the best bit.
The dog was only trying
to arrest Mr. Mullett,
who was going up the
stairs at the same time.
Trying to arrest Mullett.
I love it.
That dog grows on me.
Ah, well I hope so because
the dog's in your office now.
He what?
Haliday asked if you
could look after him.
What do you mean he asked,
what do you mean,
Oi!
Excuse me gentlemen.
If you would
like a cup of tea
there's plenty of time.
Come on boys, I'll show you.
Hello, Inspector.
Bit of bad luck,
What's this about the dog?
I'll be back before
you know I've gone
they've only got to
put the ankle in plaster.
Now listen to me, Constable.
I am not babysitting your dog.
There are handlers
in this station,
he can go with one of them.
That's the problem.
What is?
He's not...
Kai's not exactly
on top of the job yet.
do you known what I mean?
I know exactly what you mean.
It looks to me as though
you two have got
something in common.
We both scraped
through the course.
I can sort him out,
but I reckon if any
of the other handlers
try and work him,
he could get kicked out.
Look, all you've
got to do is feed him,
give him a bit of a walk.
I had set up with the bank
to pay you a month's
rent in advance,
but if Kai can't stay on,
maybe I'll have to
look for somewhere else.
How long's this going to be?
Like I said, I'll
probably be home tomorrow.
Tonight, maybe.
I expect to be
hearing from your bank.
Are you two going
to stand there
swilling tea all day?
or are you going to get
that man to hospital?
All right, come on,
settle down.
Settle down.
Come on.
Okay, so we've got no
record of Jane Owens.
She hasn't been
picked up for anything.
A couple of uniform think
they could have seen her.
So they'll be trying
to talk to people
who might have known her.
You don't reckon she's
been around Denton long?
No that seems
very unlikely.
Uniform have got
a pretty good idea
who's sleeping
rough on their patch.
The problem is you'll
be talking to people
who don't want
to talk to you.
'Cos any time we
want information
they think they're in trouble
and when they're in trouble
they don't know anything.
And they haven't
seen anything.
Are drugs involved?
No, not as far as we know.
Drugs have been fairly
quiet since our last push.
Jane wasn't a user,
and she certainly
wasn't selling.
No, but she was
out on the streets.
So she must have known
people who were on drugs
or maybe even
dealing in them,
you know muggers,
thieves,
prostitutes.
All of them not
very talkative.
How many of them are
there living rough out there?
Sergeant Brady reckons
30, 40 at any one time,
across the area.
Isn't this a job for uniform?
I mean they know these people.
Yes, uniform.
This morning I had to go
and identify the body
of 'one of these people'
with her parents.
Now until proven otherwise,
this is a suspicious death.
And no address does not
mean no investigation.
So you take those
photographs down to the DSS
and see if she was on
benefit, all right?
Sir.
Thank you.
All right,
now what we've got here
is a list of places where
kids were known to doss.
Uniform leave
them alone mostly
because there's nowhere
to move them on to
except a police cell
and there's not
much point in that.
All right that's all.
Go out and see
what you can find.
Chop chop.
Told you, Jack.
What?
Invisible.
Once you get beyond
Mr. and Mrs. Owens,
Jane's not very high on
anybody's list of priorities.
She is on mine.
Jack,
Mullett.
You what?
Jack.
Sir?
I don't know if you
recall the expression
'read my lips'.
My lips are saying
'crime figures'.
Now I don't know how many
times I have to say the words,
but I really must insist...
Is that dog still here?
Yes, yes sir.
He's on a detection course.
Well I hope he can teach
you something, Inspector.
Teach me.
Very good, Mr. Mullett.
Now Jack, there are limits.
Limits to the time I can
wait, every month...
(Dog growling)
Good boy.
Kai.
Stay.
Good boy.
Get that animal in the
kennels immediately.
Good boy.
Now that's what
I call a police dog.
Anyone thought of making
him Chief Constable.
Yeah, good boy.
All right,
what have we got?
Boy called Rickie.
He's opposite
the shopping center.
I think I saw him with
the girl, only once.
I spoke to him,
showed him the pictures.
Nothing.
I thought you might
want to have a go.
All right, where is he?
He's sitting on the
library steps, begging.
There were a
few others around,
but they cleared
off when I turned up.
All right, thanks.
Hello boy.
Rickie?
Look,
I told the woman pig,
I don't know who it is,
I never saw her.
Her name is Jane,
it's Jane Owens.
You were seen with her.
Someone else.
No not at all.
Look there's no hassle here.
Jane is dead.
Someone hurt her,
maybe even killed her.
Anything that
you know could help.
Even if it's just
where you saw her last,
where she was dosing.
Something,
a time, a place, a start.
You do want to
help her, don't you?
It's too late
to help her now.
Look.
Look at this.
That's how we found her
when we dragged her
out of the canal.
And before she was
thrown in there
someone had beaten
the hell out of her.
I keep my head down,
that's all I do.
If you don't know anyone,
then people leave you alone.
That's all I want.
But you do know her, Rickie.
And you do care
about her, don't you?
Come on.
So how long you
two been together?
Three months.
We met up in London.
Just dossing.
We tried to look
after each other.
You don't know anyone
here in Denton?
No.
We wanted to
get out of London.
This is as far as we got.
We wanted to get
to the West Country,
earn a living
busking and that.
Jane could sing you know.
I mean really sing.
I need to know what
happened that night.
We had a row, okay.
About money.
She said she'd get some.
She disappeared
for a few days
and came back
with a couple of quid.
She said...
Yeah?
Go on.
She said what?
She said she'd seen what
went on at Bedford Park.
She said there was
only one way left
and that she'd get
some money that way.
Prostitution.
I didn't think she was in the
market for that sort of thing.
There's blokes who go
for crusty, believe me,
male or female.
Crusty?
What do you mean, crusty?
Dirty, filthy.
As long as
you're young enough.
Look, I tried to stop her.
She said there was
only one way left.
Oh, so, she went
to Bedford Park?
I followed her.
There were
prostitutes all over.
They told her to piss off.
I was going to make
her come back with me.
Then this bloke stopped,
in a black BMW.
It was a just a few
seconds, that's all,
and she got in.
They drove away
and that was it.
I never saw her again.
Were you close enough
to see this man?
Come on.
Hey, hey, come here!
Now wait.
Heel!
Heel, will you.
Hey, will you.
I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, about that.
Just a minute.
Has there been any news?
Not yet.
Well, you know,
it's early days yet.
It doesn't seem to
mean much when you say
someone's missing in a
police station, does it?
Sooner or later someone
is going to listen to me.
Sooner would make it a lot
easier to get to the truth.
Look, we have been making
enquiries, Mrs. Barber.
I don't know whether
there's any news come back...
It's not likely to.
A policeman went
round to ask Gerry Ryan
whether he'd seen
my husband last night.
When he said no,
I think that was about it,
apart from the
apology for troubling him.
I went round to see
Gerry Ryan myself
and I would say he was
very troubled indeed.
We are not ignoring this.
Good.
I intend to make
damned sure you don't!
You'll need some photographs.
I've left them
at the Front Desk
and I will be back
to see how you're getting on.
Well, there's no doubt now
that the man is missing.
You chased up the hospitals?
Yeah.
Nothing there.
Right.
Well, get a description
out to all areas.
Also details of his car.
If he has done a runner
he's got to
turn up somewhere.
Come on Kai.
Oh, Jack.
Mr. Mullett's been
on to me about the dog.
What are you talking about.
Haliday will be out
of hospital tomorrow.
Kaiser can stay with him.
Tomorrow?
He'll be in till
the end of the week.
What are you talking about?
What with a broken ankle?
And a torn ligament.
A torn...
he never told me that!
Well, he's not as
daft as he looks.
What is it girl?
Come on, come on, come on.
Morning, Jack.
Morning, sir.
You got that fax from
Humberside Police?
Yes.
It's a long way from Denton.
A very long way
if you're dead.
Quite.
And of course a severed arm
is hardly identification.
Yeah I know.
A lot of things you
can get from it though.
You know, age,
height, weight, sex.
Right color for Barber.
Yeah, and a million others.
Frankly Jack, I think
it's all rather far-fetched.
Mmm, I know, I agree.
The odds are against it.
But supposing,
supposing it's true.
Supposing this Barber,
he goes to this
meat factory, right,
for reasons that
we don't know.
Gets himself killed.
There's no evidence
that anything actually
has happened to Barber.
No, I know.
I do think I ought to go to
Hull and check it out though.
Jack, I cannot have
you gallivanting
across the country on expenses
for something
as fanciful as this.
If there is anything to find
out about this severed arm,
I'm sure that Humberside
will let us know.
All right.
Could be embarrassing.
What do you mean
'embarrassing'.
Well look at it this way.
A woman comes into
Denton Police Station
saying her husband
has disappeared, right.
She thinks he's in danger.
Well, to put it
at its politest
she's patted on the head
and told he'll come
home when he's sober.
I mean,
supposing it is him,
well, part of him.
I've got a feeling
that this Mrs. Barber
is the sort of woman
that would take this
to the Police
Complaints Commission.
Well, I wouldn't
want her to feel
that we weren't doing
everything we could.
You're absolutely right, sir.
I'll get up to
Hull straight away.
Meet this DI Alice Beale.
All right?
Don't worry sir,
there must be a limit
to what a night in
the fleshpots of Hull
can set you back.
Keep up surveillance
on Bedford Park.
Follow up the BMW.
Any news from the tarts.
Several of their
descriptions match Rickie's.
And there's at least one
sighting of that car
on the night in question.
The man's certainly not
a stranger up there.
Mostly a looker,
not a doer, apparently.
Well, not any more.
Hey, have a word with traffic.
We've got security cameras
on roads either
side of the park.
We might just catch
him going through.
And Warren Barber?
Well, go with his
wife's instincts.
Find out if there
was a problem with
that meat factory.
You know, what
was he looking for?
Also have a
word with the owner,
what's his name, Ryan.
Just gentle
questioning, you know.
Find out what
time they closed.
Who was there last that
night, that sort of thing.
Barber's just missing as
far as Ryan's concerned?
Unless I can get
an ID from Hull,
which seems to be unlikely.
Oh, and have a sniff round
the meat trade will you?
Just anything,
find out if there's BSE or
something in the meat pies,
that sort of thing.
Jack, meat
processing's not exactly
a specialty of my snouts.
All right, if you
don't get anywhere
I'll get Kaiser on the case.
Kaiser's an expert in
the meat department.
I mean why keep a
dog and bark yourself?
See you in a bit, George.
Chop chop!
I really can't think of
anything else I can tell you.
To be honest,
I'm surprised
that these questions
are being asked again
I did speak to an officer.
Mr. Barber is missing.
We obviously have
to do all we can
to trace his last movements.
His wife is saying
some pretty wild things.
I thought I was going to have
to call the police myself,
to get her out of here.
She just burst in.
Well, she is
very upset, Mr. Ryan.
I'm sure you can
understand that.
Of course I can.
That doesn't mean
I take very kindly
to being accused of
God-knows what by the woman!
This is just routine, sir.
Questions are raised,
we have to answer them.
Obviously your
guests will be happy
to verify the details of
the dinner party that night?
I am not lying
about where I was!
As I say, sir, we
just have to check.
Afternoon, Inspector.
Good afternoon.
The pathologist's over
at the Coroner's
Court in Beverley.
If there's anything
we can't answer,
he'll be available later.
What there is,
is in the report.
Thank you.
What's the blood group?
It's 'O, page five, in there.
It's the right group
but it's too common.
Other than to
give us verification.
Right profile, wrong place.
Any evidence to suggest
that this arm was dumped
where it was found.
It's hard to say.
What we do know is
that it had been in the
water for some time.
Not enough to do much damage,
no more than
24 hours, probably less.
That's even why it's less
likely to be Warren Barber.
I mean, what on earth
was he doing in Hull,
Iet alone the North Sea?
According to the coastguard
it was just good luck
the current brought
it ashore at all.
Or bad luck if you were
trying to get rid of a body.
Just tell me something,
could this have
happened in the water?
You know, I don't mean Jaws,
I mean a propeller.
Someone falling off the back
of a ship, or an oil rig,
something like that?
No, the pathologist said
the limb was severed
before it entered the water.
It was cut off by some
kind of blade or saw.
Tell me something,
is there any evidence
that this man
was ever near a meat factory?
You know, animal hair, blood,
underneath the fingernails,
anything like that?
There's no forensic at all.
No, but it would be a perfect
place to cut up a body,
wouldn't it?
What about this wedding ring?
It's back at the station.
I doubt it'll give you
more than the blood group.
It's like ten million others.
Really, let's see.
Thanks.
No latent prints?
Not a hint.
Funny thing to do when
you come to think about it.
You go to all that
trouble to cut up a body
so it won't be recognized
and then you leave this on it.
Still doesn't
help much though.
The man's wife would be
hard pushed to recognize it.
There's no
distinguishing features,
it's absolutely plain,
there's not even a
hallmark to give us a date.
It's eighteen carat
but you could find a million
rings that look the same.
No you couldn't.
Not without a hallmark.
It's against the law.
It's probably not English.
Right.
This is for you.
Sergeant Toolan.
Says he's got a name
and registration for,
says, 'Bedford Park Bertie'?
Oh, right.
Thank you.
I'll tell you what.
I'd like to take this
with me if I could.
I'd like to show
it to Mrs. Barber.
As long as you sign for it.
All right.
I will.
George.
Yes, well done.
We'll pull him in first
thing in the morning.
Of course I will,
I'm on my way now.
All right,
Oh, ok.
Come on, come on then.
Where is it.
(Phone ringing)
Hello.
Oh, hi Gerry,
you just caught me,
just been down to Kent
for a game of golf.
Who?
Well, what do I know about
Environmental Health?
I just drive your meat around
it's none of my business.
I've had the police
here and the man's wife,
making all sorts
of crazy allegations.
You can't have
hysterical women
running around the place,
it's not safe, is it?
Hang on a minute.
Joop,
you drive the cargo
over to Amsterdam,
when you get
there stay for a bit.
I'll give you a call when
I want you back here.
Okay?
Okay.
Yeah, Gerry, listen if
this bloke's done a runner,
he's probably
got good reason.
His wife sounds bonkers.
You take care now.
I've got to go.
Another round
of golf at the club.
I had hoped that you
were going to tell me
that this wasn't his.
That his had a hallmark.
We went on a
package tour to Mexico,
the year before
we were married.
Warren had the
rings made there
from the same piece of gold.
He said it would remind us
that some people look for
El Dorado all their lives,
and never find it,
and that we had found it
just by meeting each other.
I said it was because
it was half the price
he'd have paid in England.
I'm going to have to
take some fingerprints
from the house here,
in order to confirm identity.
I'm not afraid
to identify him.
It's not that
straightforward.
I understand.
But I'd still like
to say goodbye.
There's no easy
way to say this,
but we don't have your
husband's body to identify.
All we have is...
(Doorbell)
Open the door.
I'm looking for
a Mr. Allen Deering.
I'm Detective
Inspector Frost,
Denton CID.
I think there
must be a mistake.
Is your husband at
home, Mrs. Deering?
Yes, but I don't think...
All right.
I think you ought to take
the children upstairs.
Marjory, what is it?
I don't know Allen.
What is this?
Mr. Allen Deering?
Yes, I'm Allen Deering.
What do you think you are...
I want all
Mr. Deering's clothing
taken for
forensic examination
including his dirty laundry.
I also want his car searched
and sealed for investigation.
You can't do this!
You can't just walk in here
without some kind of warrant.
Oh, yes I can, Mr. Deering.
I am entitled to
seize anything I want
on these premises
if it relates to an offence
which I am investigating
and I find it
necessary to seize it
in order to prevent
it being concealed,
Iost, altered,
damaged or destroyed.
What sort of
gobbledygook is that?
The correct gobbledygook.
What offence, for God's sake!
I'm investigating the death
of a young woman
called Jane Owens.
Who was last seen
getting into your
car two nights ago,
when you stopped to pick up
a prostitute in Bedford Park.
Now I'm sure you don't want
to discuss the matter here,
so Denton Police
Station, Mr. Deering.
I'd like to make a start.
There is no doubt
about identification.
A number of women
saw Jane Owens
get into your car.
Whores.
You think that what a bunch
of whores have got to say
is going to...
Mr. Deering,
we have traffic cameras
that saw your car on a loop
from the bypass
round to Bedford Park.
You went round six times,
now can you explain that?
We all know what
goes on up there.
Mr. Deering
refuses to respond.
The women know you.
They know your car.
You drive up and
down that road
several times a month.
What do you think
they are, blind?
Same man, same car.
I've driven up there.
I've looked.
That's all.
A few times.
I don't know why really,
it was stupid,
I didn't...
Mr. Deering, it would
not be true to say
that all you did was look.
That's all.
I swear it.
Really?
Then why did you stop
and pick up Jane Owens?
I didn't stop.
I have never stopped.
Oh, yes you have.
And when you've stopped
it's always for someone
who looks like a young girl.
Very young.
I don't have
to listen to this!
Yes you do.
Because I know you
picked up Jane Owens.
I've got witnesses.
And three hours
later she was dead.
Now what have you
got to say about that?
Mr. Deering refuses to...
All right.
There was a girl.
I did pick her up.
It was a mistake.
We drove off.
I knew that I
shouldn't have done it.
I just dropped her off,
I said that I'd
changed my mind.
You didn't hit her?
Of course I didn't.
Oh, yes you did, Mr. Deering.
You hit her.
Let's be blunt about it.
She was a sixteen
year old child
and you beat the
hell out of her.
Jack, Jack, Jack,
come on, come on, come on.
Yes, all right, okay.
Ryan, was he nervous
when you spoke to him?
Uncomfortable.
What about the alibi?
He was definitely
at home that evening.
All right.
So what happens here then?
The animals are cut up
and then carted off
to the supermarket.
Is that it?
Oh, no, it's a bit
more than that, Jack.
Ryan's in partnership
with this bloke,
Jim Scott, hauler.
This is one of
his trucks, here.
They export to Europe.
Mostly lamb, pork,
it's processed
and chilled here.
So, was anybody here
the night that
Barber was killed?
According to Ryan, no,
nobody here after
about seven O' clock.
He was here with Scott
and Ryan locked
up when they left,
separate cars but
at the same time.
Tell me, if someone
wanted to break into
this place at night,
would it be difficult?
Not that difficult I suppose.
Why, no real security?
Well, when I say
someone could get in,
I don't mean a truck
I mean just someone
on their own.
We've got alarms.
But if a bloke got round them,
Iugged a side of
meat over the fence,
well, good luck to him.
I bet he wouldn't
go back for two.
Tell me,
what was it that Mr. Barber
thought that you were up to?
He did think that you were
up to something clearly.
Don't ask me.
He had it in for me,
and I don't pretend to have
taken very kindly to it.
But this place is clean.
We have a meat and hygiene
inspector here full time.
I know about the night of
Mr. Barber's disappearance.
What about the following day?
The day after?
Yes, the day after.
That would be
the following day.
You see Sergeant Toolan here
didn't have the full details
when he spoke to you last.
He didn't know that
we'd found Mr. Barber.
Dead.
That's terrible.
So, where were you
the following day?
I was out with Jim Scott.
What were you doing, working?
No, we were flying.
Jim's got a plane, a Cessna.
We were going to play golf
but we didn't
land in the end.
The weather closed in.
Do you often fly round the
country just to play golf?
Often enough.
Jim Scott's a golf fanatic.
Often thought about
doing that myself.
Not the golf thing,
the flying.
Must be a wonderful
feeling that, you know.
Being up there
above the clouds.
You know, no worries.
God's great creation
spread out beneath you.
Where did you go?
Up towards Norwich.
Now that's real freedom.
Oh, yeah.
Flying up high with
nowhere special to be, eh?
Well,
I tell you what
I don't know much
about this business,
but there are those who say
that if you eat meat
then you shouldn't
be squeamish
about watching an animal
being killed and cut up.
Perhaps you'd like
to show me round?
I've got work
to do, Inspector.
So have I.
That's why I'm here.
So how did you
get into all this?
My father was a
butcher in Ireland.
I came here to get
away from all that,
but I started doing odd jobs,
making more
money than I expected.
I ended up managing
a rundown slaughterhouse
by the old cattle market.
Oh yes, I know, that's all
gone now though, hasn't it?
Most of the business
has gone with it.
But I built up new trade
and eventually
I moved over here.
What about this
partner of yours?
What's his name, Scott?
I've got a lot
of meat to shift.
He's got a fleet of
refrigerated trucks
and contacts in Europe.
That reminds me.
I never told you how
we found Mr. Barber, did I?
Well, the bit of him we found.
It was enough though.
You see his body
had been dismembered.
No, that's not quite
the right word, is it?
He had been cut up actually.
You won't mind
shutting down this place
for the day, will you?
What do you mean?
I'm sending in
a forensic team,
to examine this lot.
George, I'm going off to have
a word with this Jim Scott.
I want you to wait here
until forensic arrives.
I've already
given them a call.
Ryan's shutting
up shop for the day.
Just make sure nothing
leaves the place, will you?
Forensic why,
what have you got?
Think about it.
We've got a butchery,
a butchered body,
and the means of delivering
the pieces to the north sea
without the aid
of extra terrestrials.
Well, okay, a
plane would solve that,
but where's the motive?
Well I don't know, do I?
Maybe Barber found
what he was looking for.
Anyway, just
keep your eyes open.
Come on!
Come here!
Come on, we've got to go.
Come on, where are you?
Come on!
Kai.
Heel!
Come on!
One word from you, eh?
You ever tried feeding him.
I don't know.
You're like a kid in a
candy store, aren't you?
Will you come on!
Hey, Kai!
Come on!
You've got to admire the way
these police dogs are trained.
Come on!
Is tomorrow soon enough?
No, tomorrow won't be
bloody soon enough at all.
So you spent
the evening alone.
Yeah, I watched television,
had something to eat, a couple
of whiskeys went to bed.
If I'd known you'd
wanted an alibi
I'd have arranged something.
Do you live on
your own do you?
Yeah, me and the
wife are divorced.
Look,
I left the factory with Gerry.
I drove out before him,
he was behind me on
the bypass for miles.
But you could have gone back.
You had a set of keys.
I didn't go back.
And as for this man Barber.
I'd never heard
of him till yesterday.
If I wanted to murder
a government inspector,
I'd go looking at the Ministry
of Transport, wouldn't I?
You find Mr. Barber's death
amusing then, do you?
No, of course not.
I'm just running out
of ways of telling you
I don't know
anything about it.
Only the circumstances
of his death are peculiar.
In particular
about where he died
and where we found his arm.
Oh it is his arm, by the way,
we've identified
his fingerprints.
Well, I can't
say I knew the man.
But obviously a tragedy
like this, it's awful.
Was it an accident
of some kind?
Less of an accident,
more like a ruddy miracle.
A miracle?
I'm not with you
there, Inspector.
Well, it's very
possible that he did die
within or around Denton.
But then he turned up some
hours later in the north sea.
In pieces.
They do say that
souls sprout wings,
his gave up
somewhere around Hull.
If this is your sense of
humor, Inspector Frost,
I really don't understand it.
No, neither does
my superintendent.
Tell me about your plane?
Oh my god,
it's alibi time again.
Cos I think it's time
I took a closer look at it.
A fine tooth comb
is what I had in mind,
with forensic
on the other end.
This is getting out
of hand, Inspector.
That's after they've been
to the factory, of course.
Now you can believe this
or believe it not.
But every knife or saw
has it's own signature.
Something unique
and a weapon
can be identified
by the mark
it leaves on a wound,
or on a cut.
Gerry, Jim's called in,
I think I should
get you out of there
before you do
yourself an injury.
Will you stay for
something to eat, Jim?
No, it's just business.
I won't keep him long.
We'd better talk
then eh, Gerry.
Well, forensic have
used everything they
can find at Ryan's.
If it cuts they've tested it.
On pigs.
Apparently their skin's
the closest to human flesh.
Well, looking at
you I can believe it.
But the top of
the arm's too damaged
to make
comparisons conclusive.
Does that mean they
can't even tell us
that it was meat cutting
equipment that was used?
No, not even that.
Uhh, come on.
The cut was
probably a lot cleaner
when the arm
went into the water
but that's down to crabs.
You what?
They were in the
process of eating it.
Are you telling me you don't
know anything about this?
You're telling me Barber
didn't break into the place?
I don't believe you.
All right, Gerry.
If you really want to know,
I'll tell you.
Yes you're
environmental officer
decided to do a little
bit of undercover work.
Your fault.
You can't even run a straight
operation convincingly.
What happened?
He got in.
Joop and I were just about
to start moving the stuff.
We spotted him, he ran,
we got him outside.
We didn't know who he was,
how much he knew.
Joop knocked him out,
we took him back in and...
And what?
He ended up dead.
You've been a
front for this stuff
coming into the country
for nearly ten years.
They'll put you away
a long time for it
so just remember that
and keep your gob shut.
I'm not getting
in any deeper, Jim.
You're in this as
deep as I am Gerry,
and if it blows up,
don't think the police is all
you've got to worry about.
Cheers.
I don't know,
some bloke sees
a plane go off,
another bloke sees
a plane come back.
Scott writes a few notes
in a book about the weather
and that's it.
I mean I thought flying
was supposed to be
like brain surgery.
Well, it's hardly
Concorde, is it?
Is there anything
on the mileage?
Well we can probably
show the total distance
could have taken them
to the North Coast of
Lincolnshire and back
but that doesn't
prove they did it.
There has to be some way
of tracking them surely.
There was a lot of cloud.
If they stayed in that they
wouldn't have been seen.
If they'd have
kept radio silence.
Have you been down
that library again,
Sergeant, or what?
All I'm saying is what we end
up with is a possible plane,
in a possible area,
that might have
been Scott's plane
or might not.
All right.
What about forensic?
I think you'd better
have a word there, Jack.
Okay, okay, I know
what you're after.
Come on.
Here you are.
Here.
Hey, what are you doing?
I've already given
him his breakfast.
Oh, he was asking,
I thought you hadn't.
Hey, a devious
little devil you are,
come on, down.
No, get down!
Really!
Anyway, that's the last laugh
you're going to get today.
Forensic have
come up with nothing.
No human blood,
hairs or fibres.
All very tidy.
He must have been
very well wrapped.
We know exactly
what happened
and we've got exactly
nothing to make it stick.
(Phone ringing)
Yes, CID?
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah okay,
thanks I'll tell him.
Mr. and Mrs. Owens
are off back to Wales.
Jane's body
has been released.
Her brother's come down
from Leeds to pick them up.
I suppose I'd better go
over there and say something,
though I don't know
what I'm going to say.
He must have beaten her up.
Of course he beat her up.
That's where he stopped,
because my gut feeling
tells me he didn't kill her.
Then how did she die?
Jack?
I've got a Mrs. Waldren here,
information about Jane Owens.
Did she see her that night?
No, this is two
days before she died.
She saw her
having an argument
with a bloke in a black car.
A BMW.
Come on.
Stay Kai!
Yes.
All right, thank you.
As soon as I saw the picture
I knew it was the same girl.
I stopped and asked her if
she was all right, you see.
Let me get this straight.
You said that this happened
on the Wednesday 27th.
It couldn't have
been a mistake.
It couldn't have happened
like the next day?
No.
I'm sorry.
Please carry on.
I'd been cycling
down by the canal,
and there was a car parked
in the old brickworks.
A BMW.
She was standing there.
A man was shouting at her.
As I cycled up to them
he was shaking her.
I thought he was
going to hit her.
As soon as he
saw me he stopped.
Did you hear any
of the argument?
No, nothing.
Did you get a good
look at the man?
Oh, yes.
I see.
How old would you say he was?
I don't know, 20, 22.
Are you sure?
Well, it's
difficult at that age.
I find more and more that
young people just look,
very young.
Did you speak to Jane?
I asked her if
she was all right.
She clearly wasn't,
but she wasn't
hurt or anything.
He'd driven off,
and she just went.
I could see how
she was living,
I felt...
but there's not really
anything you can do, is there?
No.
Well, thank you very
much Mrs. Waldren.
You've been a great help.
Sergeant Toolan here
will take your statement
a little later on.
George, would
you come outside?
Well, it certainly
isn't Deering.
No.
It's also someone else you
wouldn't expect Jane to know.
Well heeled, expensive car.
Someone who's
about to attack her.
You think she was
lying to Rickie,
she was already on the game?
I don't know.
Find out all you
can about this bloke.
If Deering isn't the
reason why she's dead,
we've got another one.
Ah, there you are.
Where have you been?
There's a good boy.
Jack?
Yeah?
You want a lift?
Yeah, all right.
Mullett's on the warpath.
Oh, yeah?
What now?
Forensic overtime.
Come on, good boy.
Good boy.
In the last two days
you've used up the allocation
for the next two months.
And still no results.
No.
Did you manage to get that
photo-fit from Mrs. Waldren?
Yes, it's in the
file by your feet.
You know he could be local.
There's something
about him I recognize.
Don't know what it is.
I do.
But it's not
because he's local.
Remember the photos
Jane's parents brought?
I think I know who it is.
We're taking her home.
Yes, yes of course.
Well I'll say goodbye.
The Funeral Directors'
van's coming later.
Mark's driving us.
That's your son.
Where is he?
He's here.
Time we were off.
We'd best get our things.
We'll see you before we go?
Yes, of course.
You're Inspector Frost.
Yes.
And you're Mark,
Jane's brother.
Yes.
Look, thanks for all you've
done for Mum and Dad.
We still don't
know what happened
the man you're questioning,
do you think he
really killed her?
Well, all the evidence
points in that direction.
However,
I do have a witness
that puts you in Denton
with your sister Jane,
two days before she died?
Perhaps you'd like to tell me
why you failed to tell
the police about that,
Mr. Owens?
I dropped her
by an old factory.
She said she was living there.
Near a canal.
I drove off,
that was it,
we were arguing,
I was angry.
So two days later you
hear from your parents
that Jane has died
in circumstances
that require a
police investigation.
You don't tell them
that you've seen her
and you don't
tell the police.
Would you describe
that as normal?
What was I going to say?
That my sister hitched
up to ask for money
and told her to piss off.
Look, if I hadn't said that,
if I'd tried to help,
maybe she'd still be here.
I still can't face
myself, Inspector,
Iet alone mum and dad.
You had contact with her.
You knew where she was,
despite what your
parents were going through.
How sick they were.
They were going
to London for days,
Iooking for her, everywhere.
And you let them
do that, knowing!
Look, the only time
she ever came near me
was when she wanted money.
She wouldn't let me tell them
what was happening to her.
I went along with it,
what else could I do?
Oh don't give me that.
They couldn't have
handled what she was.
So you kept quiet for your
parents' sake, did you.
Despite what they
were going through.
I don't buy that either.
You know why she
left home, don't you?
Look, I didn't want
this to happen!
No, but it did!
And if you'd done things
differently she'd be here now!
I know that!
What's this got to do with the
death of her friend, Angie?
Angie died after she
took an ecstasy tablet.
I think Jane
dared her to do it.
I was the only
one who knew that.
Jane couldn't
handle the guilt.
She went on like she'd got
over it, but she hadn't.
One day she just walked out.
And you said nothing.
Even though she needed all
the help that she could get.
She got that ecstasy tablet
from you, didn't she?
I didn't know.
She just took it.
That's why you paid up.
That's why you
kept your mouth shut,
to protect yourself.
I thought she'd come
back in her own time,
when she'd
sorted herself out.
Kids don't sort themselves
out from living in the gutter.
It felt like she was trying
to drag me down with her!
Because down was
where she wanted to go.
Nothing was going to stop her.
I wanted to...
I wanted to
protect them from that.
You're going to
have to tell them.
You owe them that.
And her.
Rickie?
We need to talk, Rickie.
She came back here
that night, didn't she?
When?
Ten, eleven.
All right.
Come on.
What happened?
She'd been off
with this old bloke,
the one in the car.
The one that you identified.
She couldn't go
through with it.
When she told him,
he went ape-shit.
He threw her out of
the car and laid into her,
punched and kicked her,
And she was badly hurt?
Bad enough.
Inside was worse.
I didn't really know
how much worse.
We talked.
I tried to tell her
it was all right.
I thought she was OK.
We went to sleep.
In the morning she was gone.
Look, I didn't want to talk
to you in the first place,
but I started.
I wanted to make him pay,
for what he
made her feel like,
he might as well
have killed her.
But he didn't.
She left this.
It says, 'See you on the
other side of the starlight.
Goodbye 'till then'.
I'm sorry.
She had a friend who died,
she didn't talk
about it much,
but she said that afterwards
she used to look
up to the stars
and think her friend was
there, behind the night,
Iike if you
turned it inside out
there'd be no more darkness,
just stars and light.
I loved her.
Leave us alone for a
minute will you Sarge?
You know better
than that, Jack.
Oh, I'd like to, believe me.
He's perfectly safe with me
it's just I've
got a piece of news
I want to deliver personally.
Yeah, well, I'll
still be outside.
Well Mr. Deering,
it appears that
you're free to go.
Sergeant Brady has
your personal effects.
I told you that
I didn't do it.
Yes, yes you did.
You also told me
that you didn't beat up
a sixteen year old girl
when she refused
to have sex with you.
But because she's
dead I can't prove it.
But we both know that you did.
And after that
she killed herself.
You said that I'm free to go.
Yes, you are, go on.
By the way,
we will be pressing ahead
with the curb
crawling charges.
And don't you go
being a shrinking violet,
because I've got friends
in the newspaper industry
who are going to make
sure that's well covered.
Oh, and don't expect to
find your wife and kids
when you get back home.
Apparently you'll be hearing
from Mrs. Deering's
solicitor at some point.
I still can't believe it.
You cut a man's body up,
put it in plastic bags and,
for God's sake...
We had to get rid of it.
The plane was
the obvious answer.
You try putting a
body in a Cessna
without anybody seeing it.
It had to be in bits.
Fine.
If I'd realized that
I never would have
questioned it.
Jim, will you listen
to what your saying!
Joop knew what he was doing.
I left him to it.
We didn't have any choice.
But it didn't work did it?
It wasn't foolproof, no,
but it did the job.
If they had anything on us
we'd be in Denton nick by now.
They took this
place to pieces.
And your bloody plane.
If they can't prove anything,
Frost can write
a book about it
and it wouldn't mean
a thing, would it?
You thought you
were so clever.
Just clever enough,
that'll do me.
You keep a lid on it
and it'll do you
(unintelligible).
Jack?
Yes?
I think we're in business.
Why's that?
Bloke stopped in
a stolen car on the M4.
Wrong plates,
the plates from
Warren Barber's car.
Where did he get them?
He worked in a scrap yard
for a couple of weeks,
here in Denton.
(Sirens)
Hear that?
It means we're closed.
I don't know whether
you recognize these,
Mr. Radcliffe?
Yeah, they're number plates.
And you're coppers.
Well, that's two right.
These plates came
off a stolen vehicle.
The driver said he got
them from this yard.
No way.
I keep a record of everything
that comes through here.
Do you know
Gerry Ryan, Jim Scott?
I know Jim.
Any reason why I shouldn't?
Originally these
plates came off a car
that Mr. Scott asked
you to get rid of.
Now the owner was killed
the night before your
chum brought you the car.
Now you might call that
doing a favor for a mate.
I call it accessory to murder.
And so will the judge.
Hold on.
Jim Scott said it was nicked.
He needed rid of it, quick.
How involved are you
with Scott and Ryan?
I'm not.
I owe Jim some
money, that's all.
Well I do hope that
you're a close friend
because you see
accessory carries with it
a lot of years.
And as this was a
particularly nasty murder
that'll up the ante.
Look, I told you.
I don't work with them.
I'm not into
that sort of thing.
What sort of thing?
Look, work it out.
This is Amsterdam
we're talking about.
Nobody smuggles beef
from Amsterdam, do they?
Will you tell me
about it, Gerry?
I don't know where to start.
You've been a
thousand miles away.
The boys have seen it too.
I can't help
if you won't tell
me what's wrong.
You remember when the
business was going to fold,
when it looked like we were
going to lose everything.
We didn't.
We're going to now, Julia.
We'll manage.
Only now it's worse.
Much worse.
We'll lose everything
and probably...
I'm probably
going to go to prison.
What are you talking about?
It's a long story.
It seemed it was only
like turning a blind eye
to something that
couldn't touch us.
There was money
no one could trace.
Jim Scott and I.
Now there's a man dead.
I didn't know.
Oh, Gerry, why?
Why didn't you talk to me?
Oh, darling.
I'm sorry.
Poor old Barber mislead us.
It wasn't the meat,
it was the transport.
Get Customs and Excise
down to Scott's yard.
You know, with our lot.
Mullett going to
be happy about this?
Mullett!
Leave Mullett out of this.
These blokes know
what they're doing.
Our jokers will take all
night to take a truck apart.
Yes, I know,
you're a good boy.
You tried to tell me that
the lorry was full of drugs,
and I didn't listen to you.
All right, I'm an idiot.
So, where will you be?
Well, Ryan's not at home.
I reckon he's
down at the plant.
We've got a lever.
If we can keep
Scott and him apart
it won't take long
before we can break him.
So I want you to stay
here for Customs and Excise
and I'll meet you down there.
Umm, no sugar!
Come on Kai, off we go.
Good boy.
Let's go.
Come on.
I told you Frost
wouldn't leave it.
I told you.
Why the hell you
had to kill Barber?
Joop knocked him out.
We brought him in here.
He tried to make a run for it.
I stopped him.
With a meat hook.
He was dead.
It just happened.
Come on George!
We haven't got all night.
Kai, stay.
You stay.
Good boy.
Kai.
You weren't going to
send him home, were you?
He had to be killed.
I wasn't going to
do ten years for him.
It's going to be a
lot more than that now.
You're out of control, Jim.
Yeah?
Like I was out of control
when I saved your business
from going down the tube?
Yeah, it all seemed so easy.
And it still is.
It's over, Jim.
Can't you see that.
Frost knows and he's
going to get there.
No.
Not if we stick it out.
We're in this together,
Right!
Together.
We're mates, Gerry.
Do you know what this is?
It's a record of every payment
you've made me over
the last ten years.
I'm going to give it to Frost.
Let me show you
something in the truck.
Whatever you've
got to show me
it's not going
to change my mind.
It started with a bit
of dope being brought in.
Now it's ecstasy,
cocaine, heroin, you name it.
I told you it
was time to stop.
I wanted to stop.
The people who set us
up won't let us stop.
They're not a Savings Bank,
They own us.
No.
I'm not going to look
the other way any more.
I'm going to Frost
with the truth.
You're a clown, Gerry.
Always were.
I mean it.
And if your brain
wasn't so altered
with the stuff
you're smuggling in,
you'd know I do.
Bastard.
You Bastard.
All right, that's enough!
I said that's enough, Scott!
You think I'm going down?
You can sod off!
No!
That's him.
Come on.
I'll be about ten minutes.
I don't know why you don't
leave it till next week, Jack.
If the doctor
says take it easy,
you should take it easy.
If I take it
easy for any longer
they'll have to carry me
out in a straight jacket.
Anyway I've been
a burden enough
to the National
Health Service.
Right, come on, out you come!
Better go and do
what a dog's got to do.
You must be bursting.
You better give him a hand.
What?
Well it's obvious.
He can stand on three legs,
but when he's
got to cock a leg
that leaves him just two,
with the inevitable result.
Come on Kaiser, out you go.
Will you get out!
Well, no one's pushing
you to get back to
work you know, Jack.
No, I know, sir,
but if I stay at
home any longer
I'll have to buy
a television license.
No, no, I'd rather
be back at work, sir.
The Regional Crime Squad
will be investigating
the Ryan Scott
network now, you know.
With Dutch and German police.
I'm sure they'd be very
happy to have you in on it.
Should pull in
some major players.
No, there's
plenty of work here.
It's not as
though it's getting us
anywhere though, is it?
Well, it's another
drug route closed.
Yes, that's right.
And then another
one opens this week,
and then next week,
and the week after.
If it is a war,
we're not winning.
Well, come back as you like.
All right, thank you very...
oh, by the way, this is for
you sir, it's the vet's bill.
Oh, yes.
Did a marvelous
job, didn't he?
Oh, yes.
Good grief, Jack.
Is this right?
Oh yes.
It says prompt payment
would be appreciated.
Best not get behind with
these things, eh, sir?
Come on.
You got in, you can get out.
Come on!
Haven't you got him out yet?
Well, either he
doesn't want to go,
or he's not as keen
to get back to
Denton nick as you are.
What is it Kai?
Hey, now don't over do it!
Kaiser!
Hello Kai.
They'll probably
give Kaiser a medal.
He didn't get his by
falling down the stairs.
Go on take him inside.
He'll tell you all about it.
Come on, Kaiser.
It's true what
they say, George.
Yeah?
The more you
know about people,
the more you appreciate dogs.