Did you ever really plan on going down South?
How could you ask that?
This just came up.
You can alWays get another job at a grocery store.
I can't just Walk into an ad agency.
I can't believe you.
All you do is complain about that place and those people.
That's not true.
Well, I’m going.
I guess I’ll just hop in Billy Kaplan's bus
With ten strangers.
Why can't it Wait?
1 9th Street.
This Was all supposed to be ours.
I keep thinking What Would have happened if Dad had lived.
He'd be on his knees to us.
What about all that money Dad gave to Lincoln Center?
Get that back.
You can't take a donation back.
Listen, I’m as upset as you are.
We're about to finally buy in Millbrook.
How long can she afford to live?
By golly, Pete, maybe We can get rid of her tonight.
RemberRope?
Well, look, all We have to do is go over there, get her signature,
mourn over the loss of our birthright, and move on.
I hate going there.
The smell.
To the end of the line.
Does Judy Want kids?
We have a five-year plan, although secretly I think Judy hopes
We're that childless couple people invite over.
Trudy?
We've tried.
That must be disappointing.
Adoption.
People do that.
They do.