Running Man Episode 538
No Guests
Today's special is
Running Man Rewritten.
We will rewrite...
some of the content on Running Man's
website that has stayed the same...
- for 10 years now.
- Really?
Does anyone know the production
objective that Cho Hyo Jin wrote?
Isn't it "Don't walk, run."?
It's "From landmarks
stuck in the city..."
"Landmarks that represent Korea."
"Running Man will let
you know about them."
"They will do missions
everywhere to win games..."
and escape from that place
before the next morning.
- It was like that in the past.
- This really must be changed.
- It was still like this.
- But there is a need for change.
There's also something else.
"MC Yu" is the nickname,
and there's a one-sentence comment.
I wore that for Episode 100.
"He has a charm where strength
and softness exist together."
- Where is his softness?
- That makes no sense.
It says "He has a strange charm."
"Unlucky Rising Star"?
You must have not had any nicknames.
That's really written
carelessly. I really hate you.
So if you write everyone's nicknames,
one-sentence comments,
and production objective
from your ideas...
The winner's content will
be posted on our website.
We will spin a roulette at the
end of today to decide a winner.
The entire website will be changed?
- The whole thing will be changed.
- This is hard.
We must pay some attention to this then.
"Variety shows are
disappearing these days."
- Gosh.
- Gosh, Jae Seok.
- The introduction is good, right?
- That's right.
"Beyond Korea" is too...
It sounds too much like
bragging. Isn't that right?
- But we need that.
- It's kind of our pride.
- Right.
- We need that.
"The pride of Korea's variety shows."
"Based on a worldwide
fandom beyond Korea..."
"A giant scale."
"A tremendous amount
of production cost."
That's cool. That's like a blockbuster.
Here's the production objective.
"The eight people who grew up
on love will make you laugh."
"'The fruits of studying hard
will show themselves later.'"
"Do you all know that saying?"
"It means something good."
"Open your eyes. Fun on
a big scale will come."
"Open your mouth. Laughter
on a big scale will come."
"Open your heart. A
great lesson will come."
Bravo!
"Growing the long hair
on his ear to live long,"
"he's a hard-working man
who is soon-to-be 60."
I don't have a long hair.
"He's Protein Monster who's
got the surprising ability..."
"to make people uncomfortable
with his excessive love."
"He doesn't care about B Class actors."
"He only cares about A Class actors."
What's wrong with him?
He's "Mr. Dirty Mustache
Who Pretends to Be..."
"the Youngest Among the
Celebrities Born in 1979."
He's "Mr. Dirty Mustache
Who Pretends to Be..."
"the Youngest Among the
Celebrities Born in 1979."
That's his nickname.
His nickname is "Mr. Dirty Mustache".
"Keeping its place for 10 years."
"It's the gateway to becoming a star."
"Running Man is the best man out there!"
"It involves all of the above."
"It's beyond amazing.
Get ready to have fun."
"Song Ji Hyo."
"She once had a crush on
Haha and was heartbroken."
"But being a cool guy, Haha
asked her to be his sister."
"Now, she and Haha are
the cutest Mapo Siblings."
You are crazy, aren't you?
"He went from a gangster
to a Grand Award winner."
"He went from a gangster to a
Grand Award winner." Love it.
"He's cute and sexy. It's crazy."
"He's popular but humble."
"Haha is cool enough to let
Jong Kook win the Grand Award."
"What will he do next?"
What is that?
- What is that?
- He says that all the time.
- Kim Jong Kook.
- Kook Jong.
Me? I didn't write a lot.
It's okay. Make it short.
Gosh, I think this is too formal.
"With the global fandom beyond Korea,"
"Running Man has become the
center of Korean variety shows."
He must be shy. He seems anxious now.
"It's the gateway to becoming a star."
"Through talks and games that
attract viewers of all ages,"
"Korea's representative variety
show spreads K-Culture."
This is real. He is serious
about this. I love it.
It sounds like SBS wrote it.
We also need things like this.
"Yu Jae Seok. His nickname
is 'Unchanging Goofball'."
Is that all you wrote?
The thing is...
- I wrote the others first.
- I love it.
- I was going to come back to this.
- I like it anyway.
- You like it.
- I do.
- "Unchanging Goofball".
- Good.
"Jee Seok Jin. The Lynx of talk
shows called 'Jee-rasoni'."
"He's burning the last embers
of his variety show career."
- Good.
- Hey.
When will your last
passion come to an end?
Last? It's not like...
- "The Last Leaf".
- It's like eternal youth.
- Good luck.
- Go, Jee Seok Jin!
"Kim Jong Kook. 'Anyang Tantrum'
who throws a tantrum when he's mad."
He admits it too.
"He's a singer. He sings
well and has many hit songs."
"But he's better known
as an entertainer now."
Okay.
- That was about him.
- Gosh.
"Haha. Short Guy, Small Guy,"
"Haha PD, A Guy Who's Short but Happy".
"He's an indispensable
seasoning in Running Man."
"But he's more focused on
his YouTube these days."
Is he a seasoning?
- Seasoning.
- "Lee Kwang Soo."
"Just Crazy, Forever Star Butler."
Why do you keep saying "Star Butler"?
"He's ugly, but he finds it
hard to accept the fact."
"His fans spoiled him."
What?
- Exactly. His fans spoiled him.
- That can't be my introduction.
It's the fans.
They didn't spoil me.
They say he's handsome, so
he thinks he's handsome.
"He finds it hard to accept
the fact." It's hilarious.
- My gosh.
- He can't accept it.
- This is crazy.
- "Yang Se Chan."
"Yechani, Yang Sebastian,
and Gum Angel."
Good. I like my nicknames.
"Kim Jong Kook's favorite doll."
"But he badmouths me behind my back."
"He's pretending to be innocent, but
once there's proof, I'll kill him."
This is a declaration of war.
I didn't badmouth you.
- Who's up next?
- I made it short.
- It's simple.
- Good.
Make it short.
I was serious about the
production objective though.
This stuff can last a while.
"It's spreading to the whole world
beyond Korea? No, to outer space."
"The members make up for
each other's deficiencies."
"The piller of Korean variety shows
that the whole family can enjoy."
- Okay.
- Good.
"Piller?" Does it say "piller"?
- "Piller?"
- What?
It's "pillar", you punk.
- It's a typo.
- It's not a typo.
You also said "piller".
"The piller of Korean variety shows
that the whole family can enjoy."
- Okay.
- Good.
- It's a typo.
- It's not acorn jelly.
It's not a dialect.
It's "pillar". Do you even
know what a pillar is?
- What?
- Do you know what it means?
It's like a support.
That's it. Just move on.
- Please change the spelling.
- It's okay.
If Kwang Soo wins, you
should go with this.
Member introductions. "Jee
Seok Jin. I'm still vigorous."
"I'm still vigorous."
"Yu Jae Seok."
"Bring it on."
"I will stay ranked eighth by
looks no matter who comes."
Gosh, that was...
- I love it.
- He's crazy.
"Kim Jong Kook. My heart
is like a soy sauce dish."
"My heart is like a soy sauce dish."
Are you saying he's petty?
- Good.
- "Haha. Old Fossil".
"Come to me if you
want to get an earful."
I'm talking now!
- Good.
- "Song Ji Hyo."
"Go ahead and text me."
"I'll ignore it anyway."
I love it.
"Jeon So Min. It's me who
made Running Man PG-15."
"I'll make it Rated R in 2021."
- Good.
- "Yang Se Chan."
- "Poop".
- Hey!
Hey!
What's that?
I lost my concentration toward the end.
It doesn't mean anything.
It's just one word.
- I lost my concentration.
- It's funny though.
- I like it.
- How could he say that?
I like it. It's short and good.
"Lee Kwang Soo. We didn't know..."
"how charming he was."
Gosh, I hate him.
It makes me want to vomit.
Mine is short too.
The production objective.
"Variety shows are..."
"disappearing these days."
"Running Man is Korea's favorite
variety show that's been..."
"on Sunday nights for over 10 years."
"The members play games and clear
missions with various guest stars,"
"as they go around to different places."
"Among various fun factors,"
"this show only focuses on laughter."
This is the true production objective.
I hope this will go on the website.
This is how Jae Seok
thinks of Running Man.
The writers are giving him a big hand.
Why are you clapping your hands?
"We only care about laughter."
- Cool.
- Right.
It's not like you're
submitting a report.
"Jee Seok Jin. He was going to
leave the team in the first year."
"But now he says Running
Man is the best."
- Jae Seok!
- That's just a message to him.
- "His behavior is frowned upon..."
- Hey.
- That's basically a letter.
That's just something
we say among ourselves.
This is my introduction. It's mine.
It's like...
It's like an article for the tabloids.
Yes, that's right. The tabloids.
It's just how I feel about him.
"His behavior is frowned upon by many."
- It's excessive.
- It's totally for the tabloids.
- You praise the show excessively.
- He's right.
- I'm not excessive.
- And everyone hates it.
My goodness.
"Yu Jae Seok."
"The official prankster of
Running Man, Yooruce Willis."
- Okay.
- Jee Seok Jin.
"Kim Jong Kook."
"Called 'Kim Nipple' during summer
and 'Enema Kim' in other seasons."
"Also known as 'Go Large' and
won the Grand Award in 2020."
- Congratulations!
"And won the Grand Award
in 2020." Congratulations!
- Congratulations!
How long do we have to
congratulate him for the award?
"Song Ji Hyo. Real name is
Cheon Seong Im, Cheon Su Yeon."
"Nickname is 'Jeoktoma'."
"We can't say that she gets
along well with the members,"
"but we also can't
say that she doesn't."
"To cut a long story short,
Ji Hyo is funny these days."
Next is...
"Haha. He's the dad of three kids.
He's officially an old fossil now."
- "But he still doesn't know it."
- Why am I an old fossil?
"He doesn't want to admit it."
"Recently, he sent me
half-dried herring".
- "He sent me half-dried herring."
- Why tell us that?
Is it necessary to write about
that in his introduction?
I wanted to write about
things the viewers don't know.
Who is "me" in the introduction?
- That's me.
- It's you?
- You can't write about yourself.
- All right.
"Lee Kwang Soo. He can grow
taller but he doesn't try harder."
- He doesn't try harder.
- Hey.
You keep saying that.
- Then try harder.
- Yes, drink some milk.
- He's right.
- Why won't you try harder?
- Drink milk and play basketball.
- What are you talking about?
Next is Jeon So Min.
"I've seen her for a while
and she really is crazy."
"Yang Se Chan. Yang Se Hyeong's
brother. Has handsome gums."
"It seems he has a girlfriend."
- I don't.
- That's all I have.
- Okay.
It was good.
- It was very neat.
- It was, wasn't it?
I thought it'd be better to
write a lot about the show.
You wrote a lot. It's very long.
"A show that makes the entire
country, and beyond, run as one."
She's actually right.
"Running Man carries out missions
like we only live today."
"Eight members with different
colors go through many troubles..."
"to deliver a great deal of joy
and extraordinary entertainment."
She used all the fancy words she knows.
"Stay tuned for the charm
of the eight members..."
"which we will show you
anywhere and in any situation."
- Ji Hyo, I love that. "Stay tuned".
- "Stay tuned!"
- Stay tuned.
- Okay.
Next is...
Who's the thug?
- "Kim Thug."
- Okay, "Kim Thug".
"You'll be sorry if you judge
him only by his muscles."
"No one can catch up to his
good sense and witty words."
- "All Mighty of all higher beings."
- She's right.
"He likes to reveal his
adorable side sometimes."
"He is unexpectedly charming."
- You're so right.
- Yes.
You know exactly who I am.
"Small business owner."
"President Ha, small
business owner in Mapo-gu."
That is funny.
- Small business owner in Mapo-gu.
- That is funny.
"How capable and resourceful is he?"
"He's capable of both running a
business and running on the show."
"President Ha is a greedy
man who wants it all!"
Do you think it's appropriate...
to write that in the
member introduction?
You can't write about
his personal business.
"He's capable of running a business."
- Well, he does a lot of things.
- Hey.
It's my business.
- I wrote "a small business owner."
- She can't compliment him...
for running his business well
in the member introduction.
- What about Song Ji Hyo?
- "Song Ji Hyo."
Well, I wasn't sure what I should say.
So I wrote, "Finally, she's trying
to step out into the world."
Maybe that's how you feel.
"She's learning how fun it
is to be out in the world."
"Song Ji Hyo is stepping
out into the world."
Congratulations!
"Song Ji Hyo is going
out into the world."
Congratulations!
Yes, you should communicate with others.
You're finally stepping
out into the world?
Finally.
Song Communication.
Okay, Song Jeoktoma!
- Song Jeoktoma.
- Yes, come on out. And call me.
Let's have a meal together.
We're supposed to be social distancing.
- Seok Jin.
- In spirit only.
- Be with her in spirit only.
- Sure.
- In spirit only. My apologies.
- All right.
Next is Jee Seok Jin.
"He doesn't know himself."
"He's the Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong
who pretends to love his family."
I love it.
- "The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong."
- Today...
Ji Hyo is stepping out into the world.
"The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong."
It was great.
"Find yourself falling for his charm."
"The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong."
What's that?
- It's kind of ambiguous.
- Hugh Grant.
I'm not offended but
can't say I'm pleased.
It's good since it's Hugh Grant.
Hugh Grant is amazing.
Yes, it's good that
she compared me to him.
We got two amazing nicknames today.
- "The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong."
- And "Mr. Dirty Mustache".
- Yes, "Mr. Dirty Mustache".
- That's right.
"The Hugh Grant of
Jamwon-dong" is funny.
All right.
Hello, everyone.
- Hi.
- The production objective.
"The funniest show ever in Korea
and in any country in the world."
"The only show you can enjoy
both the old and the new."
"You can bite, chew, and
taste. We are the real deal."
"The one and only
semi-real variety show."
- "Semi-real variety show".
- "Semi-real".
- It's a bit more than half.
- Actually, it's 100 percent real.
- "The dealer of semi-real variety".
- "semi-real".
"We guarantee your laughter, longevity,"
"love life, marriage,"
"and success in life."
Shouldn't it be "the
leader", not "the dealer"?
Oh, right. It's "the leader".
Shouldn't it be "the
leader", not "the dealer"?
Oh, right. It's "the leader".
- Wait a minute.
- It's "the leader".
- He's right.
- Wait a minute.
- What is "a dealer"?
- My goodness.
How can you make such a mistake?
How hard is it to make a
PowerPoint? Am I right?
- No, no. It's a typo.
- What is "the dealer"?
It's "the leader".
I knew the correct word.
I wrote "piller" as a typo too.
I thought it was written correctly.
"Piller" was a typo.
I confused "the leader"
with "the dealer".
- Whatever. That's what you wrote.
- It's "the leader".
- It's "the leader," everyone.
- Okay, what's next?
- Let's move on.
- I knew the actual word.
Next is Jee Seok Jin,
known as "The Senior".
- Gosh, it says "Jee Seok Ji".
- What's "Jee Seok Ji"?
- Gosh.
- You can't fix it now.
She can't fix it.
What's "Jee Seok Ji"?
She can't fix it now.
No, she can't.
- If she wins, I'll be "Seok Ji"?
- Sure.
You're "Jee Seok Ji" even
if you say it backwards.
It's the same even if
you say it backwards.
"The lucky charm, the adorable,
the youngest Jeon So Min."
"No one knows who she really is."
"Running Man unveils
her mysterious charm."
"She's good at acting,
comedy, writing, and cooking."
"The perfect entertainer
this generation wants."
"The best entertainer. How
much more can she be charming?"
"We're lucky to have her!"
All right.
- It's Seok Jin's turn.
- I think...
everyone's good enough to be picked.
- Yes, everyone's good.
- Right.
- They're not bad.
- If I win,
- mine will be posted, right?
- Yes.
All right.
The production objective.
"The new hearth of Running Man,"
- "Jee Seok Jin leads the new show."
- "Hearth"?
"The new hearth of Running Man,
Jee Seok Jin leads the new show."
- "Hearth"?
- Running Man.
- Wait.
- What?
- Are you nervous?
- No.
Wait a minute.
- Well, I think...
- I'm not nervous.
it's been a long time since he
was in the center of attention.
You said, "The new
hearth of Running Man."
- "Every week, Jee Seok Jin..."
- Don't be nervous.
"fights against the seven losers."
Don't be so nervous.
All right.
Just hang in there.
Hugh Grant!
- Hugh...
- Please be quiet.
"He can't be fooled, but
he pretends that he is."
"His name tag can't been ripped..."
"but he lets them rip it off."
The word spacing is terrible.
It's not "can't been ripped".
It's "can't be ripped".
Other words are wrong too.
- Just let it go.
- I can't believe him.
His grammar is terrible.
Just let it go.
"I sacrifice myself to giving
hope to the younger members."
"I is the Giving Tree, Captain Jee."
Shouldn't it be "am" not "is"?
"I is"?
"To giving hope"?
He wrote, "to giving hope".
It's because...
the keyboard arrangement is
different from my generation.
Is it a regional dialect?
Your generation didn't
even have a keyboard.
- "The Giving Tree, Captain Jee."
- What's wrong with you?
"It's not just a variety show anymore."
What's wrong with him?
"In the endless cold
betrayal betrayal..."
Why did you write "betrayal" twice?
What does that mean?
- I'm sorry I wrote it twice.
- What does that mean?
My goodness.
You're unprepared.
Why would you write "betrayal" twice?
My goodness. This is making me cry.
- Gosh, this is so funny.
- That's not it.
- Gosh.
- This is...
He was surprised too.
"Endless cold betrayal betrayal..."
- He was like a broken record.
- Wait a minute.
I'm sorry that I wrote the word twice.
Okay, member introductions.
What's this? "Jan Seo Min"?
I'm so sorry.
- My goodness.
- Why so many typos?
- Seok Jin.
- "Any litle?"
- It's just the order.
- It's "Any little thing."
"Any little thing can make her go
crazy. No one can control her."
- "The biggest fool on the show."
- Why did he make so many mistakes?
"Buckteeth Se Chan"
"The ugliest."
"He's all talk but no sincerity."
It's witless.
Song Ji Hyo. I named
her "Zoned-out Girl."
Song Ji Hyo. "Zoned-out Girl."
I named her "Zoned-out Girl."
It's not witty.
"Zoned-out Girl," the next "Young Gu".
- "Running Man's new fool."
- Wake up, Haha.
We're still filming.
Wake up, Haha. We're still filming.
Wait a minute. Wake up, Haha.
Jae Seok, Jae Seok!
- Jae Seok!
- We're filming.
Jae Seok, wake up!
Jae Seok, wake up.
- What?
- We're still filming.
Okay. Look alive, guys!
I fell asleep.
Hang in there, guys. He's almost done.
- Gosh, I fell asleep.
- He's no fun.
- Okay. "Lee Kwang Soo."
- He's not done yet?
"Now he's 350cm tall."
- "He entered the Guinness Book."
- It's already morning.
- Haha!
- "How tall will he get?"
Okay, next.
- This is exhausting.
- "Kim Jong Kook."
- Another typo?
- "The starter of the new rase."
- There's another typo.
- "Experienced much muscle loss."
"He suddenly lost so much muscle."
"His thighs are as slim
as Seok Jin's arms now."
"Now he's the weakest
member of Running Man."
It's like the principal
is giving a speech.
- Seok Jin.
- What?
- Your face turned red.
No, no. I'm fine.
It's not funny at all.
- Seok Jin.
- Just keep your mouth shut.
- It's really not funny.
- Don't say a word.
- "It's really not funny."
- Next is Haha.
I laughed so much my stomach hurts.
I'm talking about Haha, you punk.
Seok Jin, are you upset?
Yes, I am upset, you punk!
- He's embarrassed.
- Are you all right?
I'm fine.
- Okay, next page.
- My mouth hurts.
Gosh, my cheekbones hurt.
"Jee Seok Jin, known as 'Jee-rasoni'."
- "He's there."
- Seok Jin.
Seok Jin noticed it.
He just scanned the entire room.
- Hey.
- He sensed it.
Stay quiet.
"There is no need for
further explanation."
- Is that it?
- "Yu Jae Seok."
It says dirty.
"Yu Jae Seok announced
his retirement this year."
"This is his last work."
- "Pay attention to him."
- He's Jee Grant.
Give me a white towel.
- We don't have a white towel.
- Get him one.
Get me a white towel.
Seok Jin is about to cry.
It's hilarious.
Gosh, it was so funny.
Seok Jin, is it over?
What?
Why are you swearing?
- Why are you swearing?
- Why are you taking it off?
- Why are you swearing at us?
- Why are you upset?
Why?
What's wrong?
- Fine. Do what you want!
- Come here.
- It's so funny.
- Seok Jin.
- Come here.
- Don't be upset.
- Seok Jin.
Why are you swearing?
All right. You can watch
Seok Jin swear on YouTube.
It's called "Spicy
Version Jee Seok Jin".
It's so funny.
I'm sorry I lost my temper.
I laughed a lot.
It's hilarious.
It's killing me.
This is so funny.
I want you guys to pick...
the worst introduction each.
- Can I say it?
- Hey.
- Don't do that.
- You're really mean!
- There's no need to say.
- Do you really not know?
No need to say it.
- Why do you even ask?
- Do you really not know?
You should pick the worst one.
- 1, 2, 3.
- I can't pick.
Who picked Seok Jin?
- Me.
- Me too.
- Four people.
- 5 people.
- There are 5.
There are five.
Jae Seok, Se Chan, and
Kwang Soo got one vote each.
And Seok Jin got five votes.
Like I said, today's special
is Running Man Rewritten.
The winner's content will
be posted on our website.
I'll have mine go on the website.
We have two kinds of roulette here.
The first one has your names on
it, and we will spin it at the end.
It has 40 spots with 5 name tags each.
We will spin it to decide the winner.
And the other roulette
is about benefits.
The winners of each mission
will spin this roulette...
and win the benefit they pick.
According to the roulette,
you will have more...
or less name tags on the roulette.
And you will get paid
as much as the number...
of your name tags on the roulette.
- Really?
- Good.
If you have more name tags on the
roulette, you'll get more money.
It increases the amount of money.
We will start the first
mission once you get changed.
- What is this?
- What's that?
What is this thing?
It's getting more advanced.
I'm really curious. Who comes
up with games like this?
This is amazing.
- My goodness.
- There's flour. Is this flour?
What? Is that flour?
- I think this one is better.
- What's that thing?
- Are they marbles?
- Marbles.
It might break my head.
- It can't break your head.
- This is the worst.
I might break my head.
This one is...
It's like jelly. It's called frogspawn.
- That's just...
- It's not hard.
How can someone be so untrusting
of our production crew?
A member like that...
I can't believe this.
You should have a
meeting and rule him out.
The production crew wouldn't
put metal marbles in there.
Hey, stop it.
I saw Seok Jin punch the
wall in the restroom earlier.
- I almost cried now.
- Why?
Seok Jin just kicked me,
but it didn't hurt at all.
Come on.
Seok Jin just kicked me,
but it didn't hurt at all.
Come on.
- Jae Seok, that's so sad.
- Hey.
I just kicked you gently.
- I just kicked you gently.
- What should I do?
Kook Jong, it makes my heart ache.
I know how you feel.
This camera is only for me.
- Hey, it's not for you.
- It's not for you.
It's for all of us.
It's for a full shot.
Jong Kook should be on the camera too.
This is for a full shot. Lean back.
We can be on the camera too.
- Don't block the camera.
- She's right.
My goodness.
We're rewriting the production
objective for the year 2021.
So we prepared missions
that require a good hunch...
and good wit which are necessary
skills for Running Man.
This is what I'm good at.
I have a good hunch.
Goofball is acting up again.
- What are you good at?
- Goofball is acting up again.
I really want to see
you do something well.
- A good hunch and what?
- I'm good at this.
I'm sure you will be covered
in a floury mess in 10 minutes.
- Hey, stay quiet.
- I'm pretty sure.
I can imagine that.
The first mission is...
Know How It Feels to Run.
You will give it a try one by one.
You will lie on the cart
and stamp your feet once...
to get as close as possible to the wall.
And you will see...
the yellow zone, green
zone, and red zone here.
- And the cart has an arrow.
- There's an arrow.
If the arrow stops on red,
the water balloon will burst.
If it stops on green, the
marble balloon will burst.
If it stops on yellow, you succeed.
If you fail to control the
speed and bump into the wall,
the bell will ring,
and the whipped cream
balloon will burst.
That's the worst.
It'd be better to try it later.
- No.
- No. That's not true.
Why are they being like that to me?
- Why?
- You two should sit apart.
- But why?
- Just sit apart.
Why do you think it'd
be better to try later?
- That's not true.
- Why is that?
What?
I mean, I can see how
hard it should be...
- Kim Grand Award. You're right.
- All right.
- I know. Why would it be better?
- This is crazy.
Only the 1st and 2nd places will...
- get to spin the roulette.
- Only the 1st and 2nd places?
- Okay.
- The order is important here.
Who will go first?
Seok Jin said he'd go first.
- Really?
- When did I say that?
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- He told me that.
- When did I say that?
- Before we got in here.
- When did I?
- You did.
- I didn't say that.
- He said that.
It would be disadvantageous
for me to go first.
- Will you go first?
- Jam Hugh!
Do I get any advantages?
- Advantages?
- Any advantages?
- I need something.
- Show us what to do.
- You're the oldest one here.
- I'll go first then.
- Okay.
- Are you serious?
He's cool.
I will give you a chance to practice.
- A chance to practice?
- Okay.
I'll go first then.
I'll do it.
I want to go first.
Hey, this is... It goes like this.
- I get a practice round, right?
- Yes, you do.
Let me push it back for you.
Look at this.
This is more sensitive than I thought.
This is for practice.
- It's a practice.
- You can practice it only once.
Right.
It's red.
- It doesn't slide well.
- It's water.
- It's red.
- You should push it hard.
In this case, the water balloon bursts.
If it were a real round, the
water balloon would've burst.
Did you get the hang of it?
He has no idea.
You should stop on yellow.
Are you trying it now?
No. I'll do it later.
- Why?
- I'm not doing this.
- You practiced it already.
No. I'll do it later.
Why?
I think we should
decide the order again.
- I'll go first.
- Okay.
I'll go first.
- Do you want to go first?
- Yes.
- I knew it. He's Kim Grand Award.
- Kim Grand Award.
Kim Grand Award steps up.
He's setting a good example
after winning the Grand Award.
A gangster to a Grand Award winner.
He's "Protein Monster".
He's the Grand Award winner indeed.
His heart is like a soy sauce dish.
- You're amazing.
- Since it's the new year,
- You're the best.
- I should change my life pattern.
- I should stop waiting.
- That sounds good.
So I should stop there.
I can look at it, right?
- You can practice once.
- Yes. This is a practice.
- What was that?
- Why?
- Soy sauce dish.
The practice is over.
- You should start now.
- Start.
- Here I go.
Can I start?
- It should be twice as hard.
- It slows down quickly.
It's water.
- Is it marbles?
- Okay.
This is the best one.
What was that? It wasn't so bad.
It just feels bad.
It just hurts your feelings.
He did a good job though.
- This is pretty.
- Okay.
- Feel them.
- Didn't I succeed?
- No.
- These are the marbles.
Who's up next?
- I'll go next.
I'm ready now, so I'll go first.
You should stomp your feet hard.
You're right.
Jae Seok, you should start immediately.
- All right. Here I go.
- Let's go.
Will he make it to the whipped cream?
Let's go.
Oh no.
Gosh, this is...
What's that?
- Oh no.
- Gosh, this is...
What's that?
You pushed it too hard.
You can't do that already.
What should the rest
of the members do now?
- You can't do that already.
- Are you all right?
You shouldn't have pushed it too hard.
It splattered all over.
It was too hard.
What should the rest
of the members do now?
- Hey.
- You pushed it too hard.
Didn't someone kick the cart?
You pushed it too hard.
You should've done it in moderation.
I mean, I thought...
I pushed it at the speed of Mach.
- You just pushed it too hard.
- It exceeded the speed of sound.
- It was fast, wasn't it?
- He's really strong.
Didn't someone push it?
- It just feels that way.
- You have strong legs.
Gosh, I'm afraid to go next.
Seok Jin.
We shouldn't commit a foul anymore.
- "Anymore"?
- We can't play the game this way.
We can't play the game.
- No one should stand close.
- We should play the game.
I think someone kicked me.
Me?
Ji Hyo, did someone kick me?
No. You just pushed it yourself.
Is it just my feeling?
- It's your feeling.
- You just feel that way.
I think someone kicked it.
No, you pushed it too hard.
- Really?
- It was really hard.
- Did I push it too hard?
- Yes.
So you mean it's my fault.
How many times do you have to ask that?
Next up is Seok Jin.
I feel sad as I see
him lie down on here.
Eternal youth.
I hope you live young forever.
You need to kick a
little hard to succeed.
- Okay. Got it.
- Okay.
It's hard to reach the wall. See?
Oh, no. That was so close.
He almost succeeded.
- Is this how we'll play this game?
- Come on, Jae Seok.
- Really?
- What's the point?
I'll just volunteer to get
the whipped cream on my face.
That's a shame.
I didn't know it was a
downward slope from here.
Oh, I think you're right.
It must be sloped here.
- It's flat. Trust me.
- It seems...
Did you push me?
No, I didn't push you. I
was standing over here.
- Really?
- You kicked too hard.
Hold on. We can't...
Let's all sit on the cart from now on.
- Right. That's a good idea.
- Someone pushed me, right?
- Hey, someone...
- This isn't fair.
- He did kick hard.
- Did someone push me?
- No one pushed you.
- Seok Jin.
- Are you sure?
- Sorry?
- You kicked hard, Seok Jin.
- Did someone push me?
By the way, my hunch was right.
I didn't know why, but
I wanted to go first.
- Exactly.
- Isn't it strange?
- Right? It's strange.
- He kicked too hard.
Did no one push me? I
think someone pushed me.
I can't get mad because I'm not sure.
Seok Jin, you never lose your temper.
That's true.
True.
- He never gets angry. It's amazing.
- Exactly.
- I wonder why.
- Why do you not feel anger?
If I were him, I would've gotten
angry earlier at the opening.
Seok Jin would never get
angry over things like that.
- You see...
- He has a big heart.
- It's not that I hold back...
- Let's keep provoking him.
- my anger. I don't feel anger.
- Let's make him angry.
He has such a big heart.
He plays along with
any jokes. He's great.
I would've thrown my
coat and made a scene.
He's so cool. I would've
sworn harshly at everyone.
- He's a man with good manners.
- Indeed.
- He really has a big heart.
- Absolutely.
- You know I didn't get angry.
- Of course, we know.
- I wasn't angry earlier.
- He's so cool.
- Why would you swear?
- Why did you take it off?
Why would you get mad?
I just did it to make you laugh.
- I know.
- He should publish a book.
- Are Seok Jin and Jae Seok out?
- Yes.
- Hang on.
- Can't you give us another chance?
It's because you guys
tried it in the beginning.
You can give us a disadvantage instead.
- Deduct our score, for example.
- Sit down, will you?
Jae Seok, we'll give you
another chance if you want.
- I'll try again.
- Because there was cheating.
Didn't anyone really do
anything when I tried it?
- No.
- No one did anything.
- Be honest with me.
- You should kick hard, Se Chan.
Are you serious or what?
Honestly, I'm not sure.
There wasn't cheating.
I guess there was. There was cheating.
I didn't see anything.
If Bo Pil says he didn't
see it, he didn't see it.
Next up is Song Jeoktoma.
Here comes Song Jeoktoma.
She said, "Here comes Song Jeoktoma."
She called herself Song Jeoktoma.
- That's good, Song Jeoktoma.
- She's so funny these days.
- Song Jeoktoma, good job.
- Where? Here?
Right, Song Jeoktoma. Let's go.
Push it hard, Ji Hyo.
- Hard? Should I push it hard?
- Yes.
- Ji Hyo, this isn't a practice run.
- Okay.
- Go, Song Jeoktoma!
- Ji Hyo, kick hard.
- Here goes Song Jeoktoma.
- Kick hard.
- Gosh.
- Oh, boy.
She'll stop at the water
balloon. She's the first.
She got the water balloon.
Gosh.
- Song Jeoktoma.
- It's a water balloon.
It's a water balloon.
- Hey, Song Jeoktoma.
- The water fell on her belly.
- On her belly.
- That was funny.
- Gosh. My belly...
- I told you to kick hard.
- It fell on her belly.
- Song Jeoktoma.
- It hit her belly.
- It hit my belly.
- I know.
- Did you hear the sound?
- Song Jeoktoma.
It fell right on my belly.
Good job.
No way.
Did he succeed?
If Kwang Soo succeeds,
the 1st and 2nd places may be changed.
It feels...
- Kwang Soo, go down a little.
- Go down.
- A little more.
Kwang Soo, go down. Go down.
- Hey, stop it.
- Go down.
- I'm just giving him a signal.
- That's enough.
- Stop it.
- To tell him to go down.
- That's enough.
- Darn it.
- Okay. You're almost there.
- Stop it.
You're almost there. Okay.
- Kwang Soo, come up a little.
- What?
Move up a little.
- Go back down.
- Gosh. What are you doing?
- Go down.
- We're trying to help you.
- So you won't hurt your head.
- Exactly.
- They're helping you.
- You should trust us.
- All right.
- Kick harder than you think.
Whenever you're ready.
- Trust me.
- Kwang Soo, kick hard.
I have a feeling that he'll succeed.
- Me too.
- I think he'll do a good job.
You may begin.
- That's good.
- Because he has long legs,
he's at an advantage.
Look at him. Because he has long legs...
He looks so ugly. His face is annoying.
My gosh.
Kwang Soo has a well-proportioned body.
Goodbye.
How could it fall right on his face?
It fell right on the target.
That was perfect.
- It was placed in the right spot.
- Nice.
- Good shot.
- Kwang Soo, go back to your seat.
Good shot.
You did such a great job, Kwang Soo.
- Go on.
- I did that, right?
- Yes. You did it perfectly.
- Yes. No one touched you.
- I'm next.
- Now...
Oh, right. Jae Seok
will try again. Okay.
- Right.
- We'll give you another chance.
- Of course.
- It wouldn't be fair.
- We won't touch you.
- Right.
He's a cool guy.
Here. You should wear a nose clip.
Hey, I don't need it.
- Hey, that's okay.
- Really?
- You're such a weakling.
- But if whipped cream...
- Stop it.
- Your nose will run.
- I don't care.
Jae Seok, go down.
- After the shoot, he'll say,
- Go down.
- "The cream keeps coming out."
- Go down already.
- Go down. Come on.
- Hurry up and go down.
- Go down. Put your head on it.
- Your head.
- Go down more.
- A little more.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Watch me.
- Are you ready?
- Go, Jae Seok.
Show everyone your accuracy.
- Watch how I do this.
- That's great.
Let's go. Oh, my. He looks so skillful.
- I think he's calculating.
- Watch me.
- Watch me closely.
- Is he calculating?
- Watch me.
- He's playing with the cart.
- Watch this. Watch how I do this.
- He's playing with it.
- Here he goes.
- Watch me.
Let's go. Bounce off of it. 1, 2, 3. Go.
Here I go.
- Come on.
- What's that, Jae Seok?
- That's disappointing.
- Come on.
- Gosh.
What's this? It's neither
funny nor impressive.
- That's disappointing.
- Try again.
- What was that?
- Gosh.
- He's the Grand Award winner.
- He said...
I focus solely on laugh.
I'm so disappointed.
- Neither whipped cream nor success.
- It's hard to get what you want.
It was boring.
Why did he have to try again
if he would make it so boring?
He's disappointed in himself.
- Gosh.
- I'm so upset right now.
- Oh, man.
- It wasn't funny or impressive.
- Jae Seok failed.
- Is someone in there?
Bo Pil, edit this part out.
Gosh. That was disappointing.
I'll announce the result.
- Se Chan is in the first place.
- Oh, yes!
- Haha is in second place.
- All right!
Let's move to the next location
to continue the second mission.
- Okay.
- It was disappointing.
- Shall I call your stylist?
- Hey, can you...
Can you bring a fresh team uniform...
and a T-shirt to wear under it?
Because it's wet. Hurry
up. Thank you. Okay.
- It's sticky.
- Do we have extra uniforms?
I'll call your stylist again
to tell her to come back.
- What did you say?
- Come again?
- Who pushed you?
- I heard that you pushed me.
- Yes, I pushed you at the end.
- I know.
Who pushed me? Was it Kwang Soo?
Yes, Kwang Soo did it.
It looks like your stylists...
stepped out together
and are coming back now.
- They'll be back in 5 minutes.
- 5 minutes?
- Really? We should wait then.
- Yes.
- I didn't know.
- I was surprised...
Or would you like to
continue dressing like that?
Like this?
Hey... My gosh.
- I wouldn't mind, but...
- Don't they look pitiful?
- Hey!
- Don't we look awful?
- You guys look great.
- Wearing this stained shirt?
- But you look great in it.
- Answer me.
- My gosh. We...
- Then can I borrow a towel?
- To cover the neckline?
- Okay. All right. Let's do this.
- You guys look great.
- Let's do this.
- You look great.
- Those shows you direct.
I'll see how successful they will be.
It's not like that.
You want me to be on the show
when it has yellow stains?
You're on Running Man, so
put on your running shirt.
- "Running Shirt Man".
- Gosh.
- Did you throw up while lying down?
- Why is your shirt clean?
- The clothes are here.
They're here.
Where have you been?
- Why hasn't my stylist come yet?
- I brought you fresh clothes.
Where have you been?
I'm worried.
Could I be the only one
without fresh clothes?
Seok Jin, you should...
I'll change my clothes so
we can start the shoot.
- Wait.
- Run, Jae Seok.
Let's hurry up before
Seok Jin's stylist comes.
- Come on. Hurry up.
- Change your clothes.
- Hurry up and give me the shirt.
- I look like a beggar.
Let's hurry up.
I should hurry up to prevent Seok
Jin from changing his clothes.
This is driving me crazy.
- Hurry up!
- What did you do?
- Come here.
- Ji Hyo is in there?
What is wrong with you?
- Ji Hyo is in that room, Jae Seok.
- Gosh, Jae Seok.
Jae Seok, why did you come in?
- You're unbelievable.
- You startled me.
- What's wrong with you?
- Goofball.
- Are you out of your mind?
- You punk!
- Beat him up!
- Come here.
We should teach him a lesson.
- She had her clothes on.
- We'll punish you.
- Why did you do that?
- Playful Child.
- He screamed after a long time.
- I'm relieved, Ji Hyo.
- He startled me.
- Ji Hyo, I'm relieved.
- You startled me.
- She had finished changing clothes.
- Gosh, seriously.
- He hasn't screamed like that...
- in a while.
- He screamed when he opened it.
- Hurry up!
- What did you do?
I was the one who should be
screaming, but he screamed.
- Gosh, Goofball.
- What is taking my stylist so long?
Seok Jin, why are you wearing a
cartridge belt during a shoot?
- Oh, this is...
- Let's begin the shoot.
- I need to change my clothes too.
- He's wearing a cartridge belt.
- Kwang Soo, isn't that my shirt?
- My stylist, where are you?
Look at Seok Jin.
Seok Jin, your uniform just arrived.
What is it? This is what I wore earlier.
- Just put it on.
- My stylist!
Just put it on, Seok Jin.
We'll begin the shoot now.
- Where are you, my stylist?
- Let's go.
- Where are you?
- Let's begin.
- Wait. I haven't changed...
- Good. The semi-real variety show.
- That's great.
- This is a semi-real variety show.
This is unfair. You guys
changed your clothes.
- That's why I told you to wear it.
- My stylist!
- The next mission is...
- Excuse me.
The next mission is...
Excuse me.
- Hey...
- The semi-real variety show!
- This...
- Seok Jin, wait.
- This is true entertainment.
- Nice.
- Nicely done.
- Right?
This is of a similar color.
It's Chan Hee's.
- But...
- There you go.
Unbelievable.
I love it.
- But...
- I love it.
I look like an old man who lives alone.
I love it.
- Live forever, Seok Jin.
- Nice.
What's that?
- It suits you.
- Live forever, Seok Jin.
It suits him, doesn't it?
It's time to spin the
wheel for the first time.
Se Chan and Haha, you
will spin the wheel.
If the wheel...
lands on the section
labeled "swap name",
you'll swap others' names
for yours on the big wheel.
The one that says "absorb
all seven names"...
means that you can swap out
one of their names each...
for your own.
Land on "2 left and 2
right of the selected",
and you'll be able...
to swap the name in which
the big wheel lands on...
as well as 2 on its
left and 2 on its right.
Some will land you at
a disadvantage though.
If you're told to add the
name of the worst member,
the worst member you
selected earlier today...
will have his or her
name replaced with yours.
Seok Jin, stop trying to look good.
- Wear it like you did earlier.
- Why?
Why did you make it look cool?
I had it on backward earlier.
The tag was on the outside.
- Gosh.
- Are you all right?
- Are you okay?
- No, and it's no thanks to you.
I can still smell the whipped cream.
You should just head home today.
I will if you do.
- Go home.
- Haha, you're up first.
Okay, let's do this.
- Here we go.
- Sure.
Let it be the worst one.
Okay, here we go.
No way. Not that one.
Is it mine?
Three slots in my name!
- How boring.
- Could it be more boring?
- He got one of the best ones.
- How bland.
Swap out the names of the ones you hate.
- You've gotten all boring.
- The one you hate.
Yes, the one I hate.
Why would that be me?
You called me Mr. Dirty Mustache.
- He's right.
- Darn it.
Mr. Dirty Mustache!
- Yes, take out Se Chan's name.
- Right.
- Take out Se Chan's name.
- He called me B-rated.
There's one over here.
- No, it's better over here.
- Of course.
- Why are you taking out my name?
- Of course, he should.
Se Chan, go!
- Go.
- Let's go.
Nice!
Go round and round.
Land on the one with seven slots.
That's what you'd
expect from a comedian.
Go round and round.
Did you see that?
- He's just like Se Hyeong.
- You're more like Boom.
- No, not that one.
- Just one slot!
He only gets to change one slot.
- This is what I get for winning?
- Nice.
Take one of Haha's slots.
But it's better to have my name up here.
Why would you take my slot?
Of course, he should.
Seok Jin's the one you hate.
- Right.
- Take both off.
Why would you take my slot?
- Take Haha's.
- He has the most right now.
Haha has the most.
- Is this you being angry?
- Of course not.
"Of course not."
That was never the case.
- I'll take this one.
- That's the correct choice.
Don't listen to others
and go with your gut.
- Okay.
- All right. Nicely done.
- How are we supposed to sit?
- What's this?
We should sit in two rows.
Here's the last game.
Just like the previous games,
this one will require your wits,
your concentration, and gut feeling.
- Again?
- Concentration too?
This is the Joint Responsibility Quiz.
- Joint Responsibility Quiz?
- A quiz?
- I'm doomed.
- Gosh...
- Okay!
- Hold on.
- All right!
Don't touch me.
I'll make him be more active.
Okay!
He's showing more excitement now.
- That's the spirit.
- Let's do this.
None of this makes me angry.
- Okay!
- Get him excited.
- I'll get him to be more active.
- All right.
Like this.
That tickles!
Seok Jin's loving it.
- There. You're all good.
- You can sit back up.
- You're to stay later on.
- All right.
Why are you only saying
that to me though?
Jong Kook can just go.
The last game...
will be played in groups of 2.
You and your partner will
answer the questions...
given by the staff.
Get it right and you'll earn 10 points.
The team with the highest
score will win this game...
and get a chance to spin the wheel.
I should at least get
a chance to spin it.
Team play is required, right?
So we must answer one each.
I won't be favored then.
You can't discuss with your partner,
so choose your partner wisely.
- We'll select the teams then.
- Sure.
We ranked you...
by how well you did on the quizzes...
throughout 2020 on Running Man.
- Really?
- You never know.
I'll reveal the ranking
starting from up top,
so raise your hand if you wish
to partner up with that person.
The person will choose who
he or she wants as a partner.
- Okay.
- Good.
Let me reveal who had the highest score.
I should raise my hand every time.
Getting the most answers
on quizzes in 2020 was...
It has to be Jae Seok.
Getting the most answers
on quizzes in 2020 is...
Do you know what hyeongseoljigong means?
Well...
Something complex...
An area!
He's demonstrating
hyeongseoljigong right now.
I mean...
1, 2, 3.
- Quail eggs.
- Being hungry!
Being hungry! Did you say quail eggs?
And you'll make it out alive.
Be a nutjob!
What's the name of the vice-president?
- Kamala Harris.
- Jeoktoma!
Getting the most answers
on quizzes in 2020 was...
It has to be Jae Seok.
- It's Yu Jae Seok.
- Okay.
Me!
- It's Yu Jae Seok.
- Okay.
Me!
Everyone raised their hand.
Seok Jin...
- Everyone raised their hand.
- Me.
Seok Jin...
Seok Jin reluctantly raised his hand.
Seok Jin raised his hand too late.
That can happen, you know.
He was late to raise his hand.
Seok Jin raised his hand late.
- That can happen, you know.
- It can't.
- Seok Jin, lower your hand.
- Lower it.
- Lower your hand.
- We all raised ours instantly.
I raised it before hearing your name.
Our team will be too hard to beat.
- We shouldn't team up.
- Exactly.
Jong Kook is on the smarter side,
- so we shouldn't team up.
- But...
I'll probably win if I
team up with Jong Kook.
- That's a high possibility.
- We'll be unbeatable.
You should take him then.
- 1 or 2...
- It makes better sense.
Take me or Ms. Toma.
Ms. Toma or...
I should team up Ssaebssaeb,
- Ms. Toma, or...
- Kwang Soo.
- I'm not as bad as them.
- Or Haha.
- But...
- I'm not as bad as them.
There's also Haha.
- What about So Min?
- He's not as bad.
- And Haha.
It'll be either Ssaebssaeb or Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo isn't as bad,
- so take Empty Head.
- Empty Head?
- How cool of you.
- Empty!
I love your confidence.
Shouldn't you take me with you?
Team up with me,
and if I get to swap five slots...
Three?
Take Se Chan instead.
I was wrong just now.
I need to take a short break.
I need to rest a bit.
Okay, raise your hand!
- 1, 2, 3.
- Me!
- I'll take Se Chan then.
- Okay!
Why didn't you raise your hand?
- Why can't you raise your hand?
- You should've raised it.
- Kwang Soo...
- Call me Kim Jong Kook.
- I choose Se Chan.
- Okay.
I want to team up with Seok Jin.
- Okay, good.
I want to team up with Seok Jin too.
I want to team up with Seok Jin.
I want Seok Jin as my partner.
- I want to team up with Seok Jin.
- I want Seok Jin...
In second place...
is Jong Kook.
Why did you stand up?
Why on earth did you stand up?
- Sit back down.
- His legs must be numb.
I don't understand why you stood up.
Director Choi.
- Sit back down.
- Are you sure he's in second place?
We counted all of the questions.
- But...
- This is hilarious.
Why did you stand up?
In third place...
- is So Min.
- What?
- I'm in third place?
- Really?
Are you sure you counted this correctly?
- I'm in third place?
- Are you kidding me?
- Me?
- Hold on.
I remember her getting
a lot of them correct.
- Seok Jin's in fourth place.
- That's not so bad.
Haha's in fifth place.
In sixth place is Kwang Soo.
In seventh place is Ji Hyo.
And in eighth place is Se Chan.
Why? I already knew.
Se Chan's in eighth place?
Jae Seok, isn't it obvious?
Don't pretend to be okay with this.
- What do you mean? I'm fine.
- You're upset with the result.
Why am I in third place though?
- I...
- Se Chan, my gosh.
- So raise your hand if you want...
to team up with Jong Kook.
If you want to team up with Jong Kook.
- Because...
- Teaming up with me though...
- Seok Jin.
- We'll be a tough team to beat.
Don't choose those of a higher ranking.
Come on.
He's right. Don't choose
anyone of a higher ranking.
- Then...
- Choose someone in the bottom.
The one in third place
should give others a chance.
- I'll swap for you.
- Hold on.
- Choose one of these two.
- Exactly.
Either Kwang Soo or Ji Hyo.
These two are my only choice?
Kwang Soo or Ji Hyo.
Choosing Ji Hyo will humiliate me.
Jong Kook, I got Jeoktoma right.
- Jeoktoma?
- Jeoktoma!
That's what you're bragging about?
- Why can't I?
- "I got Jeoktoma right."
That happened weeks ago though.
Team up with Mr. Mullet.
- Okay, I'll take him.
- Okay!
It's a good choice.
Please put on your
vests and sit in rows.
All right.
- Let's go.
- All right.
Out of the many categories,
- I'll reveal the first one.
- Sure.
The first...
- will be the song quiz.
- Yes!
- I love quizzes like these.
- You're good at this, right?
Yes, I am.
- I'll count on you then.
- Two songs will play...
and you will name the artists
and titles respectively.
You will hear three seconds
of the first song's intro...
and then three seconds of
the second song's outro.
- The outro of the second song?
- Yes.
The intro and outro will be...
from two different songs.
When you say that you'll answer,
I'll choose the one who'll answer first.
- Randomly?
- Yes.
You will name the two songs...
- in that order.
- Okay.
Artist or title?
The first one is to name the first song.
What's this?
- It must have a purpose.
- It seems that way.
We don't know...
- who he'll pick first.
- All right!
The first song must be named first.
Here's the first song.
Cue.
- Let me answer!
- Okay.
- I don't know the second song.
- Let me answer.
Ji Hyo.
"Beautiful Restriction" by Kim Jong Seo.
PSY's... You know, this dance...
- Wrong.
- Let me answer.
- We were faster.
What's the song title, Ji Hyo?
- Let me answer.
"Beautiful Restriction" by Kim Jong Seo.
"New Face" by PSY.
- Let me answer.
- Wrong? Really?
"New Face" by PSY.
- Let me answer.
- Wrong? Really?
"Gangnam Style" by PSY.
- Let me answer.
- Wrong?
"Gangnam Style" by PSY.
- Kim... You said the wrong one.
- Let me answer.
"Beautiful Restriction" by Kim Jong Seo.
- You said the wrong one.
PSY's "Gangnam Style".
- No?
- Let me answer.
Is the first song wrong?
No, I'm sure it's the one.
No. We all got the first song right.
We got it right.
The song was so popular.
We used to sing this song
whenever we went to a club.
- We sang it so many times.
- Hold on.
- The song ends like that.
- Exactly.
- We danced to the song too.
- Yes, we did.
- That's why.
- A strange woman
- I think it's PSY's "New Face".
- I think so too.
- Let me answer.
- Isn't it "Gangnam Style"?
Haha, you go first.
PSY's "Face".
- What?
- What's that song?
You should've said Kim Jong Seo's song.
- Is it an old song?
- Let me answer.
"Beautiful Restriction" by Kim Jong Seo.
PSY's...
- "Hwitturu Matturu".
- "Hwitturu..." Gosh.
Let me answer.
- "Hwitturu Matturu".
- "Hwitturu..." Gosh.
Let me answer.
- Hey.
- Wait.
Let me answer.
"Beautiful Restriction" by Kim Jong Seo.
What's the point when I
don't know the second song?
Can we hear it again?
- Let's hear it again.
- We need to hear it again.
- Can we hear it again?
- Let's hear it again.
- We need to hear it again.
- PSY's "Gentleman".
Yes, we should.
- No.
- This is driving me nuts.
- I think it's the correct answer.
- Jae Seok.
Let me answer.
- I heard off-beats.
Do you know the answer? Let me answer.
Se Chan goes first.
"Beautiful Restriction" by Kim Jong Seo.
PSY's "New Face".
What are you doing?
Why did you even raise your hand
when you didn't know the answer?
How many times did they tell
us it wasn't the answer?
- Why did you do that?
- Why did you say the same song?
If you didn't know the answer...
They already told us
it wasn't the answer.
I thought you knew the second song.
- But he let me answer first.
- Hey.
I still think it's the correct answer.
- Try to guess the song.
- I have no idea.
It has been changed.
- What are you two doing?
- They're discussing.
That's not allowed.
- What are you two doing?
- They're discussing.
- You shouldn't do that.
- Is it not allowed?
- Hey, what are you doing nay?
- You knew that.
"What are you doing nay?"
- Hey, what are you doing nay?
- You knew that.
"What are you doing nay?"
- "What are you doing nay?"
- I mean, what are you doing now?
- Pardon?
- You must've lost your mind.
- "You must've lost your mind"?
- What did you say?
Don't be disrespectful
to your senior comedian.
- Why would you...
- You were whispering to each other.
- Why would you speak thoughtlessly?
- I didn't speak thoughtlessly.
Seok Jin, you've crossed the line.
How dare you?
- He played with my glasses.
- Come here.
I hate it the most.
How dare you do that?
- You've crossed the line.
- I hate it the most.
- Is that so?
- How could you...
- If you...
- Please sit down.
- You lose points if you discuss.
- I was so surprised.
- They shouldn't get to answer.
- Let me answer.
From now on, if any team
gets caught discussing,
- the team will lose points.
- Understood.
We're not allowed to whisper
to each other in any case?
- Correct.
- Let's just say it out loud.
It's obvious.
You really shouldn't do that.
- Here goes Level Four.
- I'll go first.
- You should.
- He picks the one to go first.
Let me answer.
- Let me answer.
- Kwang Soo, you go first.
- But we were faster.
- Me?
- Yes.
- 3, 2,
- Kim Jong Seo's...
One.
- Okay.
- "Beautiful Restriction".
Let me answer.
Okay. Jae Seok, you go first.
"Beautiful Restriction" by Kim Jong Seo.
"Up and Down" by EXID.
- Okay!
Let's get ready to dance.
Gosh. Hey.
- That's not how they dance.
- What is this?
- This is...
- That's not how they dance.
It sounded like "New Face" earlier.
This is their dance move.
He's annoying.
Gosh, I'm so upset.
Gosh. He's so...
- That was good. Great.
- We did great.
Up, down, up, up, and down
I thought it was "Like a Cat" by AOA.
Here goes the second question.
Aren't there any common
knowledge questions?
- Level 1 of the 2nd question.
- Here we go.
I love this game. It's fun.
- I love this game. It's fun.
- Let's do this.
Let me answer.
- Jong Kook, you go first.
- I know the first song.
Sharp's...
3, 2, 1.
- Let me answer.
- I don't know the second song.
- Okay.
- Jae Seok first.
"Tell Me, Tell Me" by Sharp.
- I don't know the second one.
- Let me answer.
- Gosh. That startled me.
- What's this?
- What's that?
- Let me answer.
- I don't know the second song.
- What's that?
- Gosh. That startled me.
- What's this?
- What's going on?
- What is that?
- Happy birthday
- What's this?
- To you
- Wait.
Is there something inside the balloon?
- What is it?
- That was so sudden.
Is there something inside the balloon?
- What is it?
- That was so sudden.
He found something inside of it.
There's something in the balloons.
- He found something inside.
- What is it?
What is it? What is this for?
- What is this for?
- Can we just stick it in there?
- The singer and the song title?
- What is this?
- The first one...
- What's this?
The 1st one should say the 1st song.
- It must have a purpose.
- You're right.
- What is this for?
- Can we just stick it in there?
Hey, wait. Wait.
- What is it?
- Just stick it in.
- What is this?
It doesn't fit in the slot. Come on.
What? It doesn't fit in the slot.
I think we got the wrong swords.
There are real swords too.
See? I popped the balloon
as soon as it fell.
- I'm sure it's the right one.
- Right.
- What is it?
- What is this for?
It doesn't fit in the slot. I
think we got the wrong swords.
- I popped it right away.
- It's a real one.
- I'm sure it's the right one.
- Right.
- You can't try several times.
- You can do it just once.
You have just one chance.
I thought... I found one...
- I didn't know... I thought...
- It doesn't fit, right?
- You have just one chance.
- Does yours fit in the slot?
- Does it fit?
- It doesn't fit, right?
It fits in the slot.
Okay. Stop it. Hey, you punk.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Gosh, you.
Okay. Stop it. Hey, you punk.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Gosh, you.
You little...
- I'll stick mine in it.
- Okay.
If it pops out, do I get something?
Then you'll win.
Stick it in and see what happens.
- Do we get a hint?
- Maybe there's a hint.
Please. Please come out.
- Please.
- Maybe there's a hint.
Will it pop out?
It won't pop out anyway.
Just get it over with.
- Please pop out.
- He's right.
- We didn't put in many swords.
- So this is how it works.
- Gosh.
- I told you so.
So we need to stick a real
sword in the right slot.
The person who makes
it pop out will win.
- Okay.
- The quiz doesn't matter.
- They tricked us.
- This is so difficult.
You get 10 points when
you get 1 question right,
and you get 50 points
when the pirate pops out.
This is a faster way to win.
Oh, boy. I should find out
what the second song is.
- Now,
- They must be waiting upstairs.
we'll play Level Two.
Wait. I'm sorry.
- I think someone just farted.
- What?
- Why are you looking at me?
- Gosh, Seok Jin.
- Hang on a second.
It can't be just a fart.
Do you have a diaper by any chance?
I'm serious.
- I mean...
- You guys...
- Due to extreme nervousness...
- He must be embarrassed.
- He was laughing to hide it.
- Honestly, I don't think...
- Don't try to set me up.
- it was you.
- Okay.
The breeze is coming from that side.
It wasn't me.
- Was it really not you?
- No.
- What are you doing?
- Gosh.
It wasn't me.
- What are you doing?
- Gosh.
- Ji Hyo, what's wrong with you?
- I didn't do it.
You've been saying I smell bad
since last week, but it wasn't me.
- It wasn't you?
- Trust me. I didn't do it.
By the way, you've become
so good at improvising.
It wasn't me.
Let's move on. Play the music.
Let me answer.
- Kwang Soo first.
- All right.
- This must be the correct answer.
- I know this song.
Kwang Soo first.
- This must be the correct answer.
- I know this song.
- I know this song too.
- I listen to it very often.
"Tell Me, Tell Me" by Sharp.
"One Man" by Kim Jong Kook.
Okay!
- This is...
- I can't believe this.
- This is unfair.
- I recognized it right away.
I did great, right?
Thank you.
- You can't play his song.
- He's right.
What's wrong with playing my song?
- Play my song too. "I Know".
- What's wrong with it?
It was advantageous for him.
Your song wasn't a hit
song, but mine was.
- What does that have to do with it?
- No wonder it sounded familiar.
Exactly.
Darn. It's a fake sword.
- It's a fake one too.
- Hey, why did you do that?
You punk!
- It's a fake one.
- Is it a fake sword?
- I didn't find any.
- Like I said,
don't get too excited when
you find a sword. Okay. Good.
This is a fake sword, right?
It didn't pop out.
She stuck it right into the slot.
I did it. I made it pop out.
- We made it.
- This is unfair.
- I'm so excited.
- This is so pointless.
It's not bad.
We're doing all right.
We won 50 points.
- Nice.
- Oh, man.
Let's take our time.
Song Jeoktoma is the best.
- What a shame.
- Song Jeoktoma made it.
You see, this is like dog training.
I can't help but look up.
Just like Pavlov's dogs drooled
when they heard the bell ringing.
- Like dog training.
- It'd be funny...
if they throw balloons in front of us.
I don't understand.
What was the point...
of ranking us for our quiz?
It's pointless.
You didn't choose him
for the quiz anyway.
Jae Seok.
You chose me for the quiz, right?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
We won a lot of points
thanks to the game.
Please sit down. You're
blocking Kwang Soo.
Was he hidden from view all this time?
- I didn't know.
- Sit up straight.
No wonder. I couldn't see anything.
Kwang Soo is better suited
for group shots anyway.
Come on!
There's no such thing.
Here comes the next quiz.
Play the music.
- Hang on.
- I know the first one.
Then answer it.
I'm not sure about the
first song. Hold on.
Can you play it longer?
Level three. Play the music.
I know this song!
You do? I know the second song.
- I know the song.
- All right. I know the second song.
- I know the 2nd song too.
- You know the 2nd one?
- We got the 2nd song.
- Let me answer.
"I Have a Girlfriend" by Park Jin Young.
- "A Winter Story" by DJ DOC.
- Let me answer!
- "A Winter Story"?
- Let me answer. I was faster, no?
Go ahead, Jong Kook.
"I Have a Girlfriend" by Park Jin Young.
"Eve's Warning" by Park Mi Kyung.
That's not it. Let me answer!
- Park Jin...
- Haha, go first.
Park Jin Young's "That House Is Mine".
Let me answer.
- What kind of song is that?
- "My House Is Yours".
- Let me answer.
- I thought he knew.
- "Your Baby Is Mine Too".
- Two...
- Let me answer!
- Se Chan, go first.
- You'll all be surprised.
- Hurry up.
- 5, 4, 3,
- It's Rain's...
- 2, 1.
- "How to Avoid the Sun".
- 3, 2, 1.
- Let me answer.
I know this song!
You do? I know the second song.
- Let me answer!
- Se Chan, go first.
- You'll all be surprised.
- Hurry up.
- 5, 4, 3,
- It's Rain's...
- 2, 1.
- "How to Avoid the Sun".
- 3, 2, 1.
- Let me answer.
"Eve's Warning" by Park Mi Kyung.
- That's it! Jae Seok!
- You gave them too much time.
- They were too slow!
- That was fantastic.
Come on.
Don't throw the balloons just
yet! Watch our performance first.
Don't throw the balloons just yet!
Watch our performance first.
Give them to us now!
- Watch us, Seok Jin.
- Throw them now!
- Gosh.
- That one was...
- Seriously.
- You counted for too long.
- Give us a break.
- You're playing favorites.
- Don't count the second one.
- We didn't discuss at all.
- Let's not count it. It's absurd.
- You went too easy on them.
- Don't count it.
- Who didn't know the answer?
Then let's have the Grand Award
winners play rock-paper-scissors.
- With whom?
- The Grand Award winners.
Gosh, you want me to play
rock-paper-scissors with him?
So if I win against Jong Kook,
everything will be settled?
That's not it. Listen.
If Jong Kook loses, let's
not argue against it anymore.
- Okay.
- Make sure to win, Jae Seok.
- All right. Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- All right!
- It's the best of three.
- Come on! Stop it!
- We lined up behind him.
- All right!
- It's the best of three.
- Come on! Stop it!
- We lined up behind him.
- Stop it.
- He said they lined up.
We even lined up!
- Goodness.
- Yangsebari, come here.
Yangsebari, come here.
- At least two people should play.
- I'm sorry,
- but did you win the Grand Award?
- No...
- Then he's not qualified to play.
- That's not it.
He's just a research subject.
I'm one to get vaccinated first.
You're the first one to get vaccinated?
- If you want to play, come closer.
- You have to win one more round.
If you want to play, come closer.
- If you want to play, come closer.
- You have to win one more round.
- Why do you want to play it?
- You must come closer.
Why do you suddenly want to
play rock-paper-scissors?
Come closer if you want to play.
- Just play one more round for him!
- I mean...
- If you want to play...
- Come this way.
- I mean, if you want to play...
- If you want to play, come closer.
If you want to play, swallow
your pride and come closer.
I'm going to you.
If you want to play, follow us.
- He can win it, you know.
- It's so funny...
- He can win it.
- Seok Jin is following them.
- Let's play it.
- Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- All right, I won. I won!
- Darn it.
He lost. Goodness.
All right, I won against him.
- He even threw away his pride.
- How annoying.
The protruding mouth
brothers are getting ahead!
- Okay.
- Just give it to them.
- But this is absurd.
- Here come the next quiz.
- Okay.
Kwang Soo, you have to
listen to the rules.
Kwang Soo, you're in
charge of the balloons.
- Okay.
- This time,
you'll be playing the Guess Who Quiz.
We'll show you a picture
of a foreign celebrity.
You'll have to guess their full name.
- Gosh, this is...
- Okay.
You have to take turns
saying syllable by syllable.
We have to say the syllables?
For instance, if I tell
Haha to go first...
That's how you should say the answer.
You have to take turns
saying syllable by syllable.
We have to say the syllables?
For instance, if I tell
Haha to go first...
Let's catch the balloons instead.
- Gosh, this is hard.
- It is.
- We have to say the full name?
- Yes, that's right.
- We excluded the middle name.
- Okay.
- There's a middle name too?
- Yes.
There's a middle name too?
- Okay.
- Here comes the first question.
If you call your answer,
I'll tell whom to go first.
Then you'll have to say
the syllables right away.
- Say it right away.
- We have to call to answer first.
- I'll do that.
- Let's begin.
- Let me answer!
- Go ahead, Haha.
- You know who he is.
- Mister...
- Let me answer!
- Go ahead, Jae Seok.
- Jo.
- E.
- Let me answer!
- Go ahead, Kwang Soo.
- Joe.
- B.
- Kwang Soo.
- Ji.
- Darn it!
- Let me answer!
Go ahead, Se Chan.
- Joe.
- B.
- I.
- Den.
Darn it, you punk!
- We stole their answer!
- Darn it!
- It's Joe Biden!
- "Joe Ji"?
"Joe Ji"?
"Joe Ji".
- What's happening? We missed them.
- What's happening?
- Darn it.
- That's our target.
- That's ours!
- Did you get them?
- Kwang Soo, we got it.
- What was that?
- Have you lost your mind?
- We got it.
- Give them to me. Hand it over.
- No.
- Okay.
- Kwang Soo got the chance.
He even used his teeth.
- Hold on.
- Hey, we got it.
Who put their hands in my underwear?
Someone hit me from behind
regardless of the balloons.
We have to give it a try. Hand me one.
It was already over.
Why did they hit me?
Gosh, how unlucky of me.
- Are you upset right now?
- No, I am not upset.
I forgive you for not getting Joe Biden.
- I got this for us.
- Yes, you did.
- I forgive you.
- The pirate will pop up.
It's a relief that you're
contributing to our team.
- All right.
- This is worth 50 points.
- You can stick one in.
- Okay.
I forgive you for not getting Joe Biden.
- Gosh.
- I think it will pop up.
- You have one, right? Let's go.
- Yes, I have one.
- It'll be a relief if they fail.
- Give it a go.
Go ahead, trust your gut.
- Have you forgotten who you are?
- No, I'll give it a go.
You're Lee Kwang Soo,
for goodness' sake.
I should've caught one.
Just stick one in indifferently.
He's timid with things like this.
- That's it. Just stick one in.
- He has no luck with it.
- Just stick it in.
- It didn't pop up! Okay!
- Darn it.
- That was...
- That was cheap of you.
- Let's go, Kwang Soo.
- All right.
- I'll catch the next one.
- Let's move on.
- This is too much.
- Well done.
- This is too hard.
I... We...
I knew he was Biden, but I didn't
know his last name was Joe.
We weren't in a good position
to catch the balloons.
Hey, his last name is not Joe.
There's no such last name as Joe.
Then what about Joe?
His last name is Biden?
Then is Michael Jordan's last name "Ma"?
Do you even know who he is?
Do you even watch the news?
- I mean...
- Then is his name Biden Joe?
I know he's the president of the US.
- That's right.
- He's the president-elect.
You all know who Joe Biden is, right?
I knew who he was, but I didn't
know his last name was Joe.
I didn't know his last name was Joe.
That's not it. His first name is Joe.
- Biden is his last name.
- Oh, it's the other way around.
- Okay, I got it.
- "The other way around"?
Oh, it's the other way
around. Okay, I got it.
Why would you pronounce it like that?
You should memorize the
name of the US president.
- President Joe.
- President Joe, got it.
"President Joe".
- Then how do we call him?
- It's not President Joe.
- It's President Biden.
- Biden? Okay.
Let's settle with that.
Here's the next question.
There are two ways of reading his name.
We'll accept both.
Of course you should.
All right. 1, 2, 3.
- Let me answer!
- Kwang Soo, go ahead.
- A.
- "A".
- Let me answer!
- Go ahead.
- A.
- B.
- Let me answer!
- Why?
- A.
- B?
- Let me answer!
A.
- Bu.
- Let me answer!
- I got it!
- What?
- A.
- Why is it wrong?
- "A".
- B.
- Ra.
- Ham.
- Lin.
- Coln.
- Correct.
- All right!
But I said the same thing!
I said "A" also.
- He didn't say that!
- That wasn't correct.
- He didn't say it.
- A, "A".
A, "A".
You can't pronounce it like that.
You pronounce it that way!
It's just another way of saying it!
- You have to say either...
- Abraham, Abraham.
"A"!
Do you have a daughter in the US?
He probably said it with a Texan accent.
My accent is a little Texan.
According to the Korean dictionary,
there are two ways of saying it.
Why did you pronounce
it that way, you punk?
- Good job.
- Okay.
- You know,
- We did a good job.
Kwang Soo and I thought...
- Who did you think he was?
- We were like,
"Is he Einstein?"
- Einstein.
- I couldn't see the photo well.
- Me neither.
It's confusing since it's
a black and white photo.
Empty Head.
The next person.
- There must be one Korean in there.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Let me answer.
Jong Kook.
- Three.
- Let me answer.
- Jong Kook.
- E.
- In.
- Let me answer.
- Se Chan.
- 3, 2.
- What?
- Let me answer.
- He wouldn't know the first name.
- E.
- In.
- It's incorrect.
- Let me answer.
Al.
E.
- Let me answer.
- Ji Hyo.
Al.
F.
Me!
- Let me answer.
- Haha.
- Al.
- Ber.
- Ji.
- Let me answer.
Jae Seok.
- Al.
- Ber.
- T.
- Loan.
- My goodness.
- Let me answer.
- Al.
- Ber.
- T.
- Loan.
- My goodness.
- Let me answer.
- Empty Head.
Let me answer. Let me answer.
- Jong Kook.
- Al.
- Ber.
- T.
- E.
- In.
- S.
- Te.
- In.
- Okay.
For goodness' sake.
What in the world is Albert Loan?
Albert.
Do you think...
he is from the financial circle?
- Okay. Grab it.
- Here.
- We sat down.
- We get to go.
- Here I go.
- Come on, Se Chan.
What is it?
The chance is high this time.
- It will come up.
- There are four slots left.
It didn't pop up.
It was shaken up earlier.
This is driving me crazy.
Push in another one. We
need to win 50 points.
- Please let them fail.
- The last one.
- How many knives are left?
- None?
- Let's get over this.
- There are 7 slots.
- 1 out of 7.
Then the probability is only 15 percent.
1 out of 7.
- Okay!
- That was insane.
That's so annoying.
- I didn't want to see that.
- That's so annoying.
Nice!
- Nice!
- That's so annoying.
We won with Albert Loan.
Albert Loan sounds like a stock item.
That's so annoying.
Is it a biotech stock?
Nice!
- You changed the seats, right?
- Yes.
Do you want to change the seats?
- Okay.
- Do you want to do it?
- Yes.
- All right.
Let's change the seats. Move.
Stay there.
- They changed the seats.
- Kim Grand Award,
- change seats with him.
- All right then.
Why did you listen to him
when you didn't listen to me?
- He is a senior.
- For goodness' sake.
- A junior who won the Grand Award.
- Come on.
Jong Kook didn't even
budge when he kicked him.
You won't budge?
He is a junior who won the Grand Award.
So you won't budge.
It looks like you won, Seok Jin.
I am dusting the cushion.
He is provoking Jong Kook.
Thank you for sitting still.
We are set.
It will be funny if we end it here.
Don't air my apology.
I wondered what I should do...
if you got up. Thank you.
Seok Jin hit him with
his hands trembling.
- All right.
- Let's go.
This time, you will have
a quiz on capital cities.
- Capital cities.
- Capital cities?
- Yes. Capital cities.
- Okay.
I am good with capitals.
- Let's go.
- When I give you the country name,
- say a syllable...
- Let's go.
- each.
- Come on.
The first country is...
- Mongolia.
- Let me answer.
- U.
- Lan.
- Ba.
- To.
- R.
- Isn't it "Ulaanbaatar"?
- Is it correct?
- To.
- R.
- Isn't it "Ulaanbaatar"?
- Is it correct?
- Ulan Bator.
- It was too easy.
Is it "Ulan Bator"?
Is it?
- Ulan Bator.
- It was too easy.
Is it "Ulan Bator"?
"Ulan Bator" is a
correct way of saying it.
- Is it "Ulan Bator"?
- Yes.
Jae Seok, we got it right!
Is it "Ulan Bator"?
I have good pronunciation.
Ulan Bator.
- That was great.
- It was a clean answer.
How could he be so annoying?
- That was so much fun.
- The next capital.
- Iraq.
- Let me answer.
Haha.
- Kwang Soo.
- What?
- For goodness' sake.
"What?"
- Let me answer.
- Se Chan.
- Ja.
No, no.
- Let me answer.
- Iraq.
B.
- Io.
- Let me answer.
Bio.
- Ba.
- Gh.
- Da.
- D.
Nice!
- We are on a roll today, Jae Seok.
- Bio!
Here come the protruding mouth brothers!
- Let's go! Nice!
- Nice!
- It was amazing.
- We are getting everything right.
I was the master of the quiz.
Jae Seok,
I am no longer Empty
Head when I am with you.
Kwang Soo's answer was so funny.
He said "Bio".
- Seriously.
- My goodness.
Baghdad.
The Iraq War.
I remembered the Iraq War.
You are doing great today.
I wasn't Empty Head.
Bio.
Here comes the next question.
Don't you know "Baghdad
and the 50 Thieves"?
That's Ali Baba.
It isn't "Baghdad and the 50 Thieves".
It's "Ali Baba and the 50 Thieves".
Empty Head.
The next capital.
Se Chan is really good at this.
- Norway.
- Let me answer.
- Haha.
- Van.
Das.
- Let me answer.
- Se Chan.
I don't know.
Let me answer.
- Seok Jin.
- My goodness.
Let me answer.
Seok Jin.
- Van.
- Hel.
Sing.
- That's a movie.
- Isn't "Van Helsing" a movie?
- Is it a movie?
- Isn't it a movie? Let me answer.
- Se Chan.
- Wasn't it something like that?
Van.
- Is it incorrect?
- Are you going to be like that?
- Let me answer.
Jong Kook, go ahead.
- O.
- Sl.
Ram.
- What?
- Let me answer.
You said it's Oslram.
- Se Chan.
- What?
- O.
- Sl.
- Bi.
- For goodness' sake.
- O.
- Sl.
- Bi.
- For goodness' sake.
Oslbi.
- Hey. Hey.
- Oslbi.
What kind of an answer is "Oslbi"?
Let me answer.
- Oslbi.
- Give me a chance. Let me answer.
- Let me answer.
- Haha, go ahead.
- O.
- Sl.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- It was Oslo.
- It's okay.
- It's okay to make a mistake.
- "Oslbi" was a funny answer.
- Oslo.
When Oslbi falls early in the morning
- Three umbrellas walk
- Side by side.
I knew it was Oslo.
Here they come.
- All of them popped.
- For goodness' sake.
All of them are fake!
Okay, okay. I sat down!
All right.
- You can't do that.
- We sat down.
- Hold on.
- So Min.
- We sat down.
- I received a tip-off...
about the bad odor that came...
- when the balloons popped.
- No, no.
No, seriously. When
the balloons popped...
No!
Okay, okay. I sat down.
Jae Seok, why do I
smell something sour...
after the balloons popped?
No, seriously.
- When the balloons popped,
- No!
- I smelled something sour.
- No.
- So Min.
- It really wasn't me.
- It wasn't me.
- So Min.
- My goodness.
- I smelled something sour.
We sat down.
- Hurry up.
- We need to catch the culprit.
There's someone who
smells sour among us.
Okay. Let's try this slot.
Yes!
This is the last question on capitals.
- Hungary.
- Let me answer.
- Haha.
- Bu.
- Da.
- Pe.
- S.
- T.
They got it right. Budapest, Hungary.
My goodness.
- The balloons...
- What?
Where are the balloons?
Hey, these are fake.
No.
Jae Seok!
I figured it out.
It's the smell of someone's
feet. I figured it out.
I figured it out.
I figured it out. It's the
smell of someone's feet.
- Someone has stinky feet.
- It's the smell of someone's feet.
- Throw it.
Haha!
It popped out!
Did it pop out?
We were fighting.
Seriously.
Okay, okay.
Find the person who has stinky feet.
- Who is it?
- It isn't me.
- Find the person.
- Who is it?
- It isn't me.
- Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo's feet were stinky last week.
It isn't me. It wasn't
me last week either.
Let's have Bo Pil smell
our feet for fairness.
That's right.
- That's right.
That's right. Bo Pil.
- Gosh.
- No!
- Stinky feet.
- Really?
- No!
- Stinky feet.
- Good job.
- Come here.
Come here.
- For goodness' sake.
- Gosh.
Hey, it smells like fart.
- Take them off.
- Hey.
Throw them outside.
Hey.
- It was Se Chan.
- It was you.
No wonder the sour smell...
kept circling me.
I wondered where it was coming from.
It was coming from my feet.
- I am sorry.
- Hey.
Don't you wash your feet?
Wash your feet!
- Gosh.
- It wasn't me.
So Min and Ji Hyo, I am sorry.
- It was the smell of his feet.
- That was funny.
I suspected you guys for a short while.
It wasn't us.
I came to my senses.
- His feet don't stink now.
- Hey.
My goodness.
There we go.
Please sit down.
The result is out.
Haha and Seok Jin placed
last with 30 points.
So Min and Ji Hyo placed
3rd with 90 points.
The other 2 teams are
co-winners with 130 points.
The two teams will have a
question of the Guess Who Quiz.
We got a lot of questions right.
We got a lot of questions right too.
For goodness' sake. Don't
be like that, Jae Seok.
You should know better.
You have won a good award.
- You will lose, so sit down.
- Sit down.
All right. I will be
objective with this question.
- Okay.
Guess Who Quiz.
Let's go.
Let me answer.
Kwang Soo.
- Let me answer.
- Kwang Soo.
Hul.
Does that work?
No, he has a name.
His name is... Hold on.
- I don't remember.
- Let me answer.
Mar.
- Is it right?
- Kwang Soo.
- Mar.
- K.
- Wal.
Come on.
- Let me answer.
- I got it.
- Jae Seok.
- Mar.
- K.
- I don't know.
- I will answer. Let me answer.
- Do I go 1st?
- Kwang Soo should go 1st.
- Mar.
- You should have let me go first.
K.
Long.
Let me answer.
Kwang Soo, go first.
Mar.
Is he going first again?
- You should give us a chance!
- Hey!
- Mar.
- Mark.
- Back.
- Again.
- Let me answer. Mar.
- K.
Ru.
- Pa.
- Let me answer.
- I figured it out.
- Mar.
- K.
- Ru.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
- He doesn't know the answer.
- Kwang Soo should have gone first.
- Seriously.
- Phi.
Phi.
- Is it Mark Loan? No, no.
- Mark Loan?
Why do you like loans so much?
- Mark.
It sounds like macaron.
Let me answer.
- Mar.
- K.
- Ru.
- E.
Let me answer.
- We are set.
- What's the answer?
- Mar.
- K.
- Ru.
- Ffa.
- Lo.
- Okay.
Okay!
I knew the name.
- Ruffalo.
Mark Ruffalo.
- We did it. Okay.
- Mark Ruffalo.
- Jong Kook and Kwang Soo won.
- Okay!
- Mark Ruffalo.
- Decide who will spin first.
Okay.
- Mark Ruffalo.
- We fought well.
Ruffalo.
Who will spin the roulette first?
If you add it...
It's time to spin the
roulette one last time.
The chosen one will have his or
her comment on each member...
and project objective on the website.
- So this is the final decision.
- Yes.
The chosen one will also
receive the prize money...
of 100 dollars per name
tag on the roulette.
It will be like a writer's pay.
I have a chance.
I have a few name tags on there.
Why don't we have a staff
member spin the roulette?
Then Sun Myung should spin it.
- Sun Myung.
- Yes.
- This is the last roulette.
- Spin it hard.
Sun Myung, let's see it.
Here it goes.
- Sun Myung!
- Let's go.
- You followed me a lot.
Get mine.
It all depends on luck.
That's right.
All right! It's me!
It's me!
- It's me!
- Is it Jae Seok?
Jae Seok.
- What is this?
- Hey!
He didn't put his name tag once.
- This is absurd. I feel cheated!
- How did this happen?
This is ridiculous.
I feel so dejected.
Sun Myung, thank you.
How did this happen?
This show must be Yu
Jae Seok's Running Man.
It suits the production objective.
It's 100 dollars per name tag,
so he will receive 400
dollars in gift cards.
Jae Seok's production
objective and comments...
will go up on the website. If
you want to add something...
I will combine what everyone wrote...
- and use the comments I like.
- Okay.
- My production objective was nice.
- What?
- My production objective.
- All right.
Please use "Mr. Dirty Mustache".
I will add it. Don't worry.
Se Chan's feet continue to
stink even without the socks.
He needs to wash them.
Come here for a second.
I will wash your feet.
No.
- You are a celebrity.
- My shoes...
Variety shows are
disappearing these days.
Running Man is Korea's favorite
variety show that's been...
on Sunday nights for over 10 years.
The members play games and clear
missions with various guest stars,
as they go around to different places.
Among various fun factors,
this show only focuses on laughter.
Open your eyes. Fun on
a big scale will come.
Open your mouth. Laughter
on a big scale will come.
Open your heart. A
great lesson will come.
Yu Jae Seok. The Unchanging
Goofball of variety shows.
He is the pride of Running Man.
Jee Seok Jin. The Hugh
Grant of Jamwon-dong...
who pretends to love his family.
Kim Jong Kook. In
summer, he is Kim Nipple.
In other seasons, he is Enema Kim.
Haha. Mr. Dirty Mustache who
is the worst at acting young...
among celebrities who were born in 1979.
Song Ji Hyo. Her real name is
Cheon Seong Im, Cheon Su Yeon.
Her nickname is Jeoktoma.
Lee Kwang Soo. The
butler of A-list actors.
Jeon So Min. The Crazy Poet.
Yang Se Chan. Yang Se
Hyeong's younger brother.
Has handsome gums.
Yu Jae Seok's production objective
and the comments on the members...
can be seen on Running Man's website.
Isn't this a delinquents' school?
The guitarist.
We are in the dance club.
- Turn off the music.
- Be quiet!
What does your father do?
Look at these students!
Why would you swing that in school?
Loyalty.
- Loyalty.
Let's go.
- There we go!
- Did he take a bribe?
For goodness' sake!
Get your acts together, okay?
I can't do this.
Friends should help each other!
Student guidance club is the worst.
- Why did you come here?
- I came...
- to protect.
- Did you find it?
- Kwang Soo.
- What are you doing?
I will never visit this show again!
Let's go!