Previously on Cleverman.
Gota get out of here. Go!
- Just get rid of the Namorrodor.
- Just stories Waru
- Like sand in claws.
- More people are going to die.
- Unless you act.
- It's spoke to Koen again?
What you want you me to beg?
Will take a few minutes
the drug to make effect.
You are so close to loose everything.
We work to hard and too long for you
mess it up now.
Help us.
Call an ambulance.
What's that?
Woman: Charlotte Slade.
- Hi.
- How are we today?
A little bit nervous. I've been
through this quite a few times.
We've managed to harvest and
fertilize very impressive embryos.
I have full confidence.
Oh, this is my husband.
Jarrod Slade.
- Pleased to meet you.
- And you.
Come through.
Thinking of England. (sighs)
Think boy or girl.
All right, Charlotte.
I'm just gonna ask you to relax.
Okay, keep steady.
Here we go.
Oh!
I love you.
"Take Me Home" playing
(man singing in native dialect)
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
♪ Take the head
and the body will follow ♪
♪ Take the head ♪
♪ Take the head
and the body will follow ♪
♪ Take the head ♪
♪ Take me home ♪
♪ Take me home. ♪
I can't imagine what it must be like
to look at this view every day.
No, a couple of years, a few
more melted polar ice caps,
then we'll be the ones with waterfront.
Perhaps we should be selling, Charlotte.
Yeah.
It's a lovely meal.
Oh, thank you, but Jarrod
takes the credit for lunch.
- No.
- Oh, you can cook, too?
Waruu here can't boil an egg.
I enjoy the alchemy of the kitchen.
I'll be back in just a tick.
(vomiting)
(flushes)
Need a GPS to find yourself around here.
- Is everything okay?
- I'm pregnant.
- Oh!
- Oh, my God.
Okay, well, that was about
three months premature.
I won't say a thing.
Oh, is it something you want?
Oh, God, yeah. I just...
- I didn't think I could.
- Oh.
Well, I'm really happy for you.
(both laugh)
Congratulations.
Oh, God. I hope it sticks.
Sorry, I'm just after the bathroom.
Oh, God, I'm sorry. It's just down here.
Great.
(horn honking)
Cops should be crawling
all over the place.
(speaking native dialect)
Blair, wait. Blair, we
don't know who's in there.
Blair!
Blair: Grab something to hold her.
We got to go, brother.
I'm not leaving her here like this.
So why are we here?
Charlotte's filled me in with what
you're trying to do in the Zone.
The issues you're facing with
a lack of basic amenities,
the ongoing accommodation crisis.
I'd like to help you out.
- You offering me money?
- Mmm.
I'm always on the lookout for
worthy philanthropic projects.
Yours is a good cause.
Right in my own backyard, too.
Well, not quite your backyard.
Come on, you tell me how much you need
to kick-start some real
improvements in the Zone.
300,000.
From what I understand of the situation,
300 won't touch the sides.
Three million.
You're a man of vision, Waruu.
Why don't we add another zero to that?
Can't take that much money.
30 million.
Now you can leverage off that capital.
Turn it into 300 million.
Build a citadel.
I'm giving you the chance
to have a real stake
in your people's future.
Before people like Matthews
take that away, too.
I would feel comfortable with less.
Moses led the Israelites
out of the wilderness.
He didn't just drop them off
at the bus stop midway.
Take the money, Waruu.
Let's stop mucking about.
And what do you want in return?
Your brother.
(speaking native dialect)
I still don't understand
a word you're saying.
Let's go.
If we go into the Zone half-cocked,
we will lose personnel.
Then do your job properly.
You promised me air support, tear gas.
For three kids? Come on.
- (groans)
- What happened to you?
Subhuman encounter.
Send a couple of cars in.
I don't care about collateral damage.
I can work with that.
But three Hairy boys
loose in the streets
tearing people's hearts out...
They didn't. I did.
You killed Dickson?
No, I just made the best
of a bad situation.
That symbol on the wall, that was you?
Your approval rating
went up 10 percentage points
after your press release,
after that image went viral.
Now, did I do the wrong thing?
- Hey!
- Hey, dickheads.
Look here.
Get me those boys.
- Come on, come on.
-  (sirens wailing)
(laughs)
- (crowd chanting)
- Boy: Welcome to the Zone.
- The savage. Stop! Show us your hands.
- Stop!
Wait! Don't shoot.
That's assaulting an officer.
- Stay down. Get down.
- (screaming)
Get off! Get off me!
Don't touch a CA officer, you rug bastard.
Okay, Max, I'm gonna need you
to keep your eyes open.
Okay? Can you try? It's gonna hurt.
Okay, let me just get the milk in there.
- Okay? Oh, I know it hurts.
- (groaning)
I know it hurts. Just try and
keep them open. What happened?
We were just fooling around and
the guards pulled out their guns.
Then they went Uncle Max. Kicked
him on the ground and stuff.
- You all right, Uncle?
- (groaning)
I've got to go, brother.
Come on, we can't stick around here.
Let me drop you somewhere.
Getting rid of me?
It's not safe for you where I got to go.
Dump and run time?
I've got shit to deal with, Blair.
And it doesn't involve you.
- It's a bit late for that.
-  Blair.
- You knew what was gonna happen to Ash,
didn't you?
(laughs) That's why you had the gun.
(liquid pouring)
You knew and you didn't tell me.
Did he know?
(speaking native dialect)
See? Kora knows you're an ass.
- Don't you, Kora?
- Ass.
I remember when I first met him.
I was 13
sleeping rough under a bridge.
But it was better than sleeping
at home with a randy old man.
It was cold.
Freeze a witch's tit off cold.
And this guy comes up asking
for somewhere to sleep.
- But he didn't have anything.
- I just split the Zone.
He was full of the same old Koen shit.
Telling stories, making us laugh.
You're a funny bastard when you
want something, aren't you, Koen?
Then he wanted my sleeping bag.
Later he wanted my girlfriend.
-  I knew.
- No.
No.
Come on, brother, you got that wrong.
That's not what she's saying.
Kora, do you concur?
(speaks native dialect)
Kora concurs. So that's three
against one says you lie.
We need to go.
I'm not going anywhere until
you say you screwed Ash.
(knock on door)
- We're not open!
- Say it.
- Okay, whatever.
- Not good enough.
Say "I screwed Ash."
I screwed Ash.
How many times? Lose count?
It didn't mean anything.
So you screwed my girlfriend
and it didn't mean anything?
Is that what you're saying?
Ass.
Cleverman.
Blair.
(engine starts)
(announcer) Coming up...
(woman) You dirty animal!
(protestors chanting)
(electricity buzzing, painful groaning)
(shouting)
(announcer) Stay tuned
for more "Cleverman."
Rowena: Didn't you hear me? I'm at work.
Okay, he has to call me back.
No, no, listen to me.
He has to because I can't 'cause
my phone's almost out of credit.
Jesus, Jordan!
(mutters)
(sighs)
Okay, that's both hands.
You're good to go.
(door closes, lock clicks)
(crowd chanting)
Hairies out, Hairies out...
(speaking native dialect)
- Man: They're a bunch of savages.
- Woman: You dirty animal!
Guard: IDs, please.
- Charlotte: Hey!
- Woman: You filthy rug!
Hey, which one of you used
capsicum spray on an unarmed man?
- Ma'am, you need to calm down.
- Was it you?
No, I'm not gonna calm down.
I want your name and I want your rank
- and I want them right now.
- Guard: Mam you need to back off.
-  I'm not gonna back off.
- Excuse me, sir.
We have a slight situation on our hands.
Charlotte: I'm not gonna back off.
McIntyre: No one is to
touch a hair on her head.
- Do you understand me?
- Uh, yeah.
Firing on innocent children.
Macing old men.
You people are a disgrace.
The Zoners, they're
no different from you.
They're just trying to raise their
families as best as they can.
And now you stop
food trucks from getting in.
There's children in there.
Whatever happened to live and let live?
Man: Get a real job.
- Whatever happened...
- Woman: Stop helping savvies.
- You're the ones that are subhuman!
- (man laughs)
- Hey, hey, monkey!
- You're the ones that are subhuman.
You're the ones that are subhuman.
Man #2: Get back inside,
you Hairy lover.
Welcome to the Zone.
(knocks on door)
Just push it.
Well, here's trouble.
Blair: Hey, I'm Blair.
This is Ash.
We're operating under the
idea that her name is Kora.
But we've got no idea.
_
You understand her?
Where'd you say you know her from?
- We sort of picked her up.
- Picked her up where?
_
Ass.
Suck it up.
No.
That's not good.
She's not from here.
This is old spiritual stuff here.
She's like some kind
of ancestral spirit.
You didn't screw her, did you, boy?
He screws anything that moves.
(distant siren wailing)
Where's my phone, you Hairy bitch?
You're gonna regret this.
Get up.
Get up!
If I find out that
you are lying to me...
you're lying to me about this...
What's the problem?
She's got my phone.
I had it on me when I
was doing her nails.
She must have hidden it someplace.
I'll ask you once.
Do you have her phone?
- You're lying.
- Shut up, Rowena.
If I find out you're lying
to me about the phone...
Who would I call?
You're off your face.
- (electricity crackles)
- (groans)
How many times do we have to
have this conversation, Rowena?
- (sobbing)
- No doing drugs in Frankie's house.
(crackling)
(Rowena whimpering, mutters)
(door closes, lock clicks)
Here.
_
(sighs)
(scoffs)
You got to send her back, Koen.
- Back?
- To her home, her dimension.
(scoffs) Yeah, go on, Cleverman.
Send her home.
Use your fancy stick.
Do your magic thing.
You want another drink, buru?
Hey, don't be a smart-ass.
You need to take her
to the old fig tree,
where Jimmy used to take you and Waruu.
All I know is she got to get home
and you're the one make it happen.
I don't know shit.
Pretty accurate.
(announcer) Coming up...
(panting)
(grunting, groaning)
(announcer) Stay tuned
for more "Cleverman".
(winces, groans)
Waruu: Clean functioning housing
for everyone in the Zone.
It's everything we've ever dreamed of.
More.
It's big money you're talking about.
How much is Slade offering?
Enough to get a business plan together,
to redevelop, to approach
the bank for a loan.
How much?
$30 million.
(laughs)
And, what, Jarrod Slade's just gonna
hand over the money just like that?
It's already in our bank account.
What?
When a white man gives a black
man that kind of money,
he wants something back.
What does he get?
- He's a philanthropist.
- What does he get?
I'm trying to create a viable
future here for our people
- and you're asking me questions?
- It's a simple question.
- What does he get?
- What options do we have?
Hey. What are you doing up?
You all right?
You want something to eat?
No, I'm good. I'm here
to speak with my son.
Who won't even look at me.
What do you want?
Some bad shit's been going down.
Jimmy... he's messed things up.
What are you on about?
Koen.
He needs your help.
Koen's here?
In the Zone?
Right next door.
Linda: Says he found her
in some sort of laboratory
tied to a bed with tubes
sticking out of her.
Mean anything to you?
- No.
-  Jimmy, did he mention?
Jimmy stopped making
any sense a long time ago.
(people shouting)
How did you find this place?
She called me.
Got inside my head.
Calling over and over.
What else?
I grabbed her, took her to the bar.
Then nothing till...
this guy came around looking for her.
He had a gun.
He killed my friend.
-  So I shot him.
- Now, that was smart.
-  There was this other dude.
- Shoot him, too?
Different bloke. Tall.
Spoke with his head up his ass.
Coming offering condolences for Jimmy.
Told me he was a friend of his.
Offered me a job, too.
Straight out of the blue.
What'd you tell him?
Told him to get lost.
You seen a guy like that?
Well, Kora needs to be sent back.
First things first.
We have to get rid of the Namorrodor.
That's your job...
Cleverman.
It always comes back to that.
Killing it's the only thing
that's gonna save the Hairies.
- We should do it tonight.
- Now?
Why not?
Before more people get killed.
Your call.
And leave her at home.
I was thinking...
maybe it's time you wound up
your work in the Zone.
At least till after the baby.
That's eight and a half months away.
What am I gonna do instead?
- Stay home and crochet?
- There's a thought.
I intend to work until the day I drop.
If you were working in an
office or a GP practice, maybe.
Oh, come on.
It's a dangerous place.
It's not your battle.
Someone needs to take a stand.
Those CA animals used capsicum
spray on an unarmed man today.
Exactly, a volatile situation.
It's not just you to consider.
Ah, you thinking about your heir?
You are, aren't you?
Our baby is in rudest of rude health.
Okay? I did an ultrasound today.
Its development is off the charts.
Must be my good genes.
(laughs)
What you gonna be like
in eight and a half months, eh?
A monster.
So we lure this thing.
Say it comes.
Then what?
Then you kill it.
And it goes back
to wherever it came from?
And Kora?
You'll be in your full powers.
You open up the portal,
you send her back.
That's not gonna work.
You bring the nulla nulla?
It's in the boot.
You better go and get it.
So, what, I just club it to death?
I guess.
Is that all the advice
you're gonna give me?
It's quick and it goes for the heart.
(chuckles)
(chanting)
(beeps)
Go, go, go! Go!
(screaming)
(grunts)
(gasping)
(chanting)
It's not working.
It's not coming, Waruu.
Something's wrong.
- It's probably your chanting.
- You want to do this or not?
'Cause you don't look like you do.
Looks like you want to run.
Stuff you.
Go on, then. Take it.
Go on, take it.
Uncle Jimmy stuffed up. This
is your chance to unstuff it.
Take the nulla nulla, Waruu.
Go on, be the Cleverman.
(trills)
Take it.
That's not how this works.
What?
Am I supposed to die first? That it?
That's what you're waiting
for, isn't it, you dog?
I know I die.
I've seen it.
What you see and what eventually...
So how does it work, then, brother, huh?
Tell me, do I get mauled to death,
and then you take over?
Be the man you've always wanted to be?
Take it.
Yeah, run.
That's what you're good at, boy.
You're a sellout, Koen.
Sell your own mother if you could.
Even when we were kids,
it's always been about my mother, eh?
Koen's a coconut.
Koen's got a white slut mother.
Well, I never had a chance to meet her,
so I don't know how
you're such an expert.
Huh?
Your mother was a whore.
You're the living proof.
Bastard.
Oh, do you want to keep
going, then, brah?
It's not over yet, brother.
- (boy groaning)
- Maliyan: Shh.
-  (distant baby crying)
- (speaks native language)
(boy wheezing)
- Shh.
- (boy groans)
Go to sleep.
- (speaks native language)
- (boy groaning)
Shh.
Hey, little one.
How about I make the pain go away?
I know a special way.
You interested?
I'm gonna let you in on a secret.
I can fly.
When we fly,
the pain just goes away.
You want to try?
- (imitating airplane)
- (boy laughing)
Djukara.
Okay, bud.
Djukara's out of fuel now.
Mungo.
It all go down how you wanted?
What's happened to you?
I can explain.
No need.
I saw the tape.
You killed that guard
with your bare hands.
No, no. It wasn't like that.
I saw how it was.
Nerida, I swear I had no choice.
- You have to believe me.
- Believe you? How can I?
Well, come on, then.
Give me your reason.
Level with me.
Tell me what's going on.
Hmm?
Tell me about this deal
you've got with Slade.
Tell me.
Must be pretty freaking bad
if you can't tell me.
Is it worse than killing a
man with your bare hands?
It was him or me.
I thought I knew you.
I've no freaking idea who you are.
- Look, Nerida.
- No, don't you touch me.
(train rattling)
(people chattering)
Hey.
(grunts)
It's your fault my sister's dead.
You have destroyed everything.
Shoot.
Go on.
Do it.
- Do it!
- (gunshot)
- (dog barking)
- (people shouting)
(gasps)
Linda: What happened out there?
Koen: Nothing.
Never was going to.
I'm not the one.
I'm just a stuff-up.
Don't say that.
I couldn't save Ash.
And a kid.
Little Hairy girl is dead because of me.
I sold her family out
to the CA for some extra cash.
CA might have pulled the trigger,
but it's my fault that she died.
Doesn't sound so clever to me.
(sniffles)
She was just a kid.
And the last thing
that she said to me...
she thanked me.
Okay.
Come here, love. Come on.
Minister.
Your man McIntyre needs
to be pulled into line.
He's refusing to send down
squads into the Zone.
The brief has always been
one of containment.
Situations change, therefore
responses must change.
You go in there armed
and it'll be carnage.
That's the idea.
Assets will be destroyed.
The general public won't like that.
Right now we have the Zone
population like fish in a barrel.
What are you guys up to in there?
Don't worry. Our interests
are not mutually exclusive.
I want the Zone cleared.
If your company won't do it,
I'll find one that can.
And risk losing the support
of my network?
Do we have to keep playing this game?
The public want to feel
safe in their homes
and on the streets and I'm
gonna make that happen.
The Zone will be cleansed.
(sighs)
And after it's empty...
this.
Top-floor penthouse I've set aside.
Wonderful, isn't it?
Sweeping 360 views of the city,
the harbor.
(sighs)
I reckon you're gonna
be happy living there.
I've been talking to Frankie
about purchasing you.
Outright.
Okay, so you take these twice a day.
(boy wheezing)
And some Valium while you're at it.
Okay.
(boy moaning)
Eve.
There's something weird on his skin.
Scratches.
They're getting bigger.
Charlotte: Hey, are you okay?
Ooh, doesn't look good.
Hold on...
When did this happen?
I don't know.
Shh.
Come on, lie back.
Alinta, go get Koen now.
Eve, you still got them
eucalyptus leaves I gave you?
What do I tell him?
Tell him to get here now
or I'll kick his ass into tomorrow.
Go on, get him.
Do you know what this is?
Yeah. I'm afraid there's nothing
in your bag of tricks to fix this.
It's not a what, it's a who.
You've been to a smoking
ceremony before, haven't you?
Yeah.
Good. You're running this one.
There's a young boy in there
in a whole lot of pain.
Something wrong about it all.
Go and get your dad.
He should be doing this.
Nah, time for you to step up.
I'm not the one. Get Waruu.
We don't always get a chance to do good.
If I was you, I'd grab this
opportunity with both hands.
(boy moans)
I know, right?
Okay, everyone's got to get out now.
Okay, clear out.
Go on, get, now.
All of you, go on.
You, too, darling.
It's not safe for you.
You have to go.
- Over to you.
- I can't.
(singing in native dialect)
Whoever's in there,
it's safe to come out.
Follow the smoke. It will set you free.
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me.
The smoke will lead you
where you need to go.
(singing continues)
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com