Keep it down. Don't back it up.
(LIONS ROARING)
Lying on its back, keep going.
ON RADIO: Come in. Do you read me?
Having waited days, well, it's pretty grim now it's happening, it's...
Yeah, I mean, it's something we really wanted to film,
but it's not... Not very tasteful.
It's quite rare behaviour and we didn't think we were able to get it on film,
but now that we're here, it doesn't feel like a privilege to watch.
It just feels like a bit of an ordeal.
ATTENBOROUGH: It's never easy for anyone to watch a hunt,
especially when the odds are stacked like this.
But the sequence that the crew managed to shoot
is a valuable record of a very rarely seen behaviour.