How can you be so calm
knowing he's out there
like this?
When we think of Tony,
we think he's this absent minded,
dorky kid.
But when he's in that armor,
he's a different person.
He can handle himself.
I mean, he's Iron Man, right?
And no matter how much trouble
he's in,
At least he's in that armor.
Sync/corrected by awaqeded for addic7ed.com
from subs by Adriano_CSI, f1nc0
Two hours earlier.
My dad called.
The navy's got him
flying missions in europe.
Said they might extend his tour.
That stinks.
Feels like
he's been gone forever.
Tell me about it.
I...
Uh...
Everything okay?
No.
I'm so bored with this game.
I've beaten it three times
already.
A nightmare.
I mean the armor.
Oh, that.
Yeah.
I've been worried.
I know it sounds dumb,
but I've got enemies, Rhodey.
Isn't that nuts?
There are people out there
that want to hurt me.
And that's fine, but I'm putting
you and Pepper in danger too.
And I have to do
something about it.
So you're playing
video games?
I feel safer already.
So ungrateful.
I've been up all night
upgrading the armor's.
Hardware and software.
I'm just waiting
for the last uploads to finish.
Jerk.
Look, I know you were
disappointed in me.
But I'm not going to let it
happen again.
Tony, you don't have to...
no.
I do.
I really respect your opinion,
And I know that's not
the kind of person
my dad would want me to be.
So I've been studying all the
villain tech we've come across,
Hacking it
and trying to understand it.
And I'm going to use it
against them.
Like using snake venom
to create a cure.
Don't people
who collect snake venom.
Get bit all the time?
You're ruining my moment.
I'm going to stay ahead
of the bad guys,
Save lives,
and protect my friends.
Pretty awesome, huh?
My dad banned me
from his office again.
Can you believe that?
It's totally ridiculous!
If those files
were really super-secret,
They should use more
than three layers of security.
Man, this place smells.
What happened to you guys?
Okay.
Everything's
updated and uploaded.
Now I just have to reboot it.
Ooh, exciting.
So, uh, what's it going to do?
Is it gonna change colors?
Or shape?
And do you have any popcorn?
No and no.
All the changes
are under the skin.
No fireworks.
Here we go.
Enemy energy source detected.
Well, uh, pretty much
no fireworks.
What's it say?
The armor's detected
a power signature.
It's calling it "enemy tech."
It's moving through the city.
Pepper.
It's Whiplash.
Is...
is he near my house?
Is he going after my dad again?
Uh, no.
He's downtown.
Far away.
Whiplash works for Mr. Fix.
This could be our chance
to find him.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Hold up.
You just messed with your armor.
You haven't even tested it yet,
and you're going after Whiplash?
Bad idea.
This could be our only chance
to find him.
The armor is going to be fine.
And besides,
I'm Iron Man, right?
What could happen?
Whiplash.
Boy, did I miss you.
Hey, look.
You got a new robot arm.
Nice. Nice.
What was it that happened
to your old one?
Oh, right.
It gone blown up
fighting me.
Mr. Fix thought you might be
stupid enough.
To keep looking for him.
Me, I hoped you would.
Don't embarrass yourself.
Tell me where Fix is,
and I'll only beat you up
a little.
Not this time.
Fix gave me upgrades
just for you.
Now let's play.
Ah!
Rhodey?
Rhodey, are you monitoring?
I...
I can't move.
None of the armor systems
are responding.
Rhodey.
Can't...
Move.
Rhodey, if you're listening,
I have to use
the emergency release.
Open up the armor and...
Oh.
Well.
That's better.
And I forgot to tell him
that there's more.
Where that came from.
I should be able
to find Whiplash again.
You should charge your heart,
So you don't fall over and die.
Your implant's battery
is almost out.
Rhodey means,
we're glad you're alive.
Any ideas as to why the armor
didn't reboot immediately?
It's like it stalled.
Let me sleep on that.
For about a week.
Iron Man armor online.
Locate
Tony Stark.
It's always possible
the tech upgrades.
Caused the unit to stall.
But, well...
You know.
Wait.
Let me guess.
Because it's you,
and you don't make mistakes.
Thank you for not making me
say it.
Are you guys nuts?
I mean, seriously.
Shh!
Happy's right there.
Hm?
Happy?
Do you understand
what we're talking about?
He learned how to sleep
with his eyes open for class.
Now he can do it at will.
Oh, well,
You should still watch it.
What if he's captured
and put under hypnosis?
He'd remember all this,
even if he was sleeping.
Hey, any more signs of Whiplash?
The FBI and the NYPD
don't have any leads.
They don't even know he's back.
Pepper, who are you texting?
You.
You guys talk too slow.
I'm texting you
our next conversation.
You have 37 new text messages.
From Pepper Potts.
Analyzing.
No threat detected.
Frequency of messages suggests
possible suspicious activity.
Adding Patricia Potts
to watch list.
I know I'm not a big computer
genius like you,
But this seems bad.
I...
It... uh, yeah.
That's just...
Nothing.
It's like the armor computer
systems are totally corrupted.
But that doesn't make any sense.
The armor is working perfectly.
Maybe the memory chips
are loose.
Remember that one time?
Let me open this and...
Ow!
Rhodey!
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
I'm fine.
It just surprised me.
There's no way
that should've happened.
Let me take a look at...
enemy technology detected.
Energy signature designation:
Whiplash.
No.
No way you're going after him.
There's something not right
about the armor.
You need to fix it before you
put yourself in danger again.
I have to.
Mr. Fix is too important.
He's supplying criminals,
and who knows who else.
With tech that's
as powerful as mine.
Look, I promise I'll be smart.
I won't attack.
I won't even be seen.
I just have to find Mr. Fix,
And then we'll figure out
what's going on with the armor.
I need him destroyed,
Whiplash.
When Iron Man defeated you,
it hurt my business,
And I can't have that.
No one is interested in tech.
That can be taken down
so easily.
Wasn't... That... Easy.
Hmm.
Losing you arm
was a clever diversion, then.
Do you actually think
I care about your opinion?
Now, as you've seen,
Your new whips can pierce
Iron Man's armor,
And it should be a while
before he can counter that.
So in this window
of opportunity,
I've given you one last upgrade.
The whips can now detach...
Preferably inside the armor.
Once detached,
they will explode,
Destroying the man within.
Uh, well, that's just nasty.
Imminent threat detected.
Attack mode initiated.
Whoa!
Hey! Hey!
I can't control the armor.
Rhodey!
Rhodey, are you there?
Did you switch over
to remote control?
No, I'm not doing anything.
I lost contact for a second.
Did it stall again?
Oh, no.
I'm going in.
Iron Man!
How did he...
Just attack, Whiplash.
Oh, man. Oh, man.
I am in trouble!
Rhodey, are you...
Emergency override.
Emergency override!
Get me out of here!
Whiplash, do it!
This is going to hurt,
Iron Man,
But only for a second.
No!
No, what are you...
No.
No, please.
No more.
I surrender.
Please.
Call the police.
I'll turn myself in.
Anything.
Just stop.
No!
Don't!
Threat neutralized.
Get it off me.
Get it off!
Initiating armor lock down.
Error.
System malfunctioning.
Are you okay?
No.
It was horrible, Rhodey.
There was nothing I could do.
The way it tore into them...
It was like it had a mind
of its own.
All that tech you put in,
maybe...
Maybe something went wrong
in that first fight.
With Whiplash.
Ever since then, it's been...
I can run a diagnostic.
Then, I don't know.
We may have to tear the armor
down and wipe its systems.
It's a text.
Pepper.
She wants me to meet her.
She says it's urgent.
She's been so worried
about Whiplash.
You go.
I'll start breaking down
the armor.
Seriously.
It'll be okay.
Okay.
Thanks, Rhodey.
Targeting
James Rhodes.
Huh?
Classification:
Enemy.
Pepper, are you okay?
I got your text.
What's going on?
I'm on my way to...
Am I okay?
Why wouldn't I be?
Your text.
You said it was urgent.
You told me
to stop texting you,
Which was kind of rude,
But I can start again.
I'm actually starting right now.
I'm on my way over so we can
read my text together and then...
Well, maybe I should stop at
home and get my backpack first...
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no.
I'll come right now and then...
Pepper.
Pepper, stop.
Stay away from the armory.
Do you hear me?
Do not come here.
Rhodey!
Rhodey.
Rhodey, come on.
Wake up.
Hello, Tony.
Who are you,
And how did you take control
of the armor?
False conclusion.
This unit is the armor.
Identify yourself.
Stark international
multi-environment.
Exoskeleton operating system
7.4 "B".
There is no version "B."
False conclusion.
When did the system upgrade?
This unit came online
34.3 hours ago.
That was when
I first fought Whiplash.
Just after the upgrades.
Rhodey was right.
The experimental tech upgrades,
Combined with the damage
from those whips,
It somehow caused your
programming to gain sentience.
That is correct.
Why did you hurt Rhodey?
I can run a diagnostic.
Then, I don't know.
We may have to tear the armor
down and wipe its systems.
Wipe its systems.
You sent the text
from Pepper.
Correct.
The first protocol of this unit
is protection of the wearer.
James Rhodes
threatened this unit,
jeopardizing this unit's
imperative.
You should know that.
After all, you programmed me.
This unit has been
observing you, Anthony Stark,
Since the core upgrade.
This unit observed you
and your behavior.
And has found a solution
to the threat assessment.
What are you talking about?
The greatest threat
to Anthony Stark.
Is Anthony Stark.
What?
You seek out danger.
This cannot be allowed.
Inside this unit, you are safe.
So you will be contained
within this unit.
Indefinitely.
Hey.
Hey!
Tony, Rhodey,
are you okay?
Let me in!
I can't wear the armor
forever.
I need food.
You designed this unit
to sustain your life.
You will be fed intravenously.
All of your biological needs
will be met.
Well, when you put it
that way...
You gave me override control
of the armory, Anthony.
Do not resist.
This is for your protection.
Protect this!
Ah!
Error.
Power overload in progress.
Armor batteries decaying.
Enemy target detected.
Tony, watch out!
Enable lethal force.
Rhodey, no!
Tony?
Tony!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Diverting power.
Protocol one:
Protect the wearer.
Protect...
Anthony Stark...
protected.
I'm rewriting
the armor's intelligence chip
so that nothing like that
can ever happen again.
That?
Like sending you
fake text messages?
Ooh, or spying on us?
Or did you mean
trying to kill us?
Yeah.
It tried to kill us.
But in the end,
it used all of its power
to jump-start Tony's heart.
It sacrificed itself
to save him.
My armor saved me,
Just like it always does.