Thanks for download drama & subtitle here
::  www.airens357.net  ::
No.
I have too much work today.
Come see me when I ask nicely.
It's rude to disobey your boss.
Come see me now.
I'm hanging up.
You've just been promoted.
as my woman.
Hey, Park Dong Pal!
You stop right there!
Hey!
Are you okay?
Damn it. Hey Park Dong Pal!
You bastard.
Because of you
I went through hell, you bastard.
Tell me the truth.
I said I didn't do it.
Why are you asking the same question?
You know Jong Sik, don't you?
He told me everything.
You bragged to him while
drinking with him.
And then you bought your girlfriend
a fancy bag, didn't you?
You stabbed President Cho and...
you bought it with the money
you got in return, right?
About that bag, I
didn't buy it for her.
Where do you think you are
to lie like that, huh?
Where do you think you
are to act like a cop?
Why are you pretending to be a cop?
You be quiet.
Was it you who stabbed President Cho?
No.
The day before the accident, you
asked Byung Goo for a fillet knife.
How are you going to explain that, huh?
Can't you keep it down?
I'm the cop here.
He's the cop.
Be quiet.
Hey.
Explain.
Explain what?
Explain why you asked Byung
Goo for a fillet knife.
Sir, it was just...
you bragged to Jong Sik while drinking.
Shall I go and interrogate him?
How did you afford to buy your
girlfriend that luxury bag?
Tell the truth.
The truth will come out
during the investigation.
Anything else?
[Wanted, murder suspect]
Hey.
It's too early for that.
I brought you the real culprit.
If I had done it
would I be crazy enough to do that?
We will know for sure after
further investigation.
Gosh, it is not me.
It's been years since I stopped
associating with those people.
That's what you claim.
But what I believe is that...
once a trash, always a trash.
You answer my calls.
You are still under surveillance.
Don't take it down.
What is keeping Dong Suk so busy
that he can't attend the meeting?
He might have his personal matters.
Rude bastard.
Hello?
Hospital?
Code Blue.
Dr. Lee Chung Won from cardiology
Please report to the
emergency room immediately.
Redirecting your call...
He's had a heart transplant.
I know that.
What's his status?
His heartbeat is slowing down and...
his blood pressure is low.
His pulse is lower than 20% and...
he will be going in to an arrest.
His heart...
We will give up on his heart.
Dong Suk.
How did it go?
With this heart, it may be difficult.
What?
For now, the machine
is keeping him alive.
What should we do now?
He will need a new heart.
Then find it now.
It's just that...
Right now...
We will contact centers
for organ donation first.
Why do we need to go
through all those steps?
You know who he is, don't you?
He is Kang Dong Suk.
He's Kang Dong Suk of Hyun Sung Group.
I know that, ma'am.
But this is about a life.
Money or power can't
influence this procedure.
We don't need such things.
No matter what, just do it now.
Get out!
Get out, you bastard.
When are you going to start
acting like a human being?
When, when?
if you're going to live like that...
Why are you doing this?
It was all misunderstanding.
I didn't do anything wrong.
If you didn't do anything wrong
why are the police looking for you?
You must have done
something crazy again.
Isn't that why?
They found the real culprit.
The police won't come
looking for me again.
I'm serious.
- Are you sure?
- Yes!
Why didn't you tell me sooner then?
You didn't contact me
for a month now and...
you show up now?
I was chasing after that culprit.
Why were you chasing
after that culprit?
What are you, a cop?
Damn it.
Who else is going to take care of me?
The only way was to find him myself
and deliver him to the police.
So there won't be any
other problems, right?
That's right.
I gave him the evidence
and the witness too.
They won't be saying anything else.
Man!
While trying to catch that guy
I couldn't even drink for a month.
Wait.
Wow.
Mom, you are the only
one who cares about me.
I'm not giving it to you
because I care about you.
I worry that you'll make a scene
if you drink on empty stomach.
What customers are you talking about?
I will have Dae Suk over
and drink with him.
He's at the hospital now.
Hospital?
Why?
So?
There is nothing we can do right now
except wait.
Yes.
Dr. Lee.
Isn't there anything else we can do?
Only if by chance
there is a donor from your family.
Got it.
There are 57 people
on the waiting list.
57?
Is there any way to cut in?
Who in their right mind
would give up their turn?
Their lives depend on it too.
Shall I look into lists overseas?
Find it within the country first.
Someone in my family.
Someone in your family?
If a family member becomes the donor
the transplant can
be done immediately.
But still...
If there is no donor in my family
I can make someone
become my family member.
Isn't there a chance that someone like
Dong Suk could exist somewhere?
Bring him to me, no
matter what it takes.
Even if you have to kill him.
Dae Suk.
Ji Hyuk.
How did you know?
Man.
When your father passed away
you should've called me first.
You were nowhere to be found.
That's right.
I'm sorry I've been busy.
- Is he your father?
- Yes.
How come there aren't many
people at the funeral?
I'm a bit hungry, so...
can I have Yukgaejang or something?
Excuse me.
How much?
About the records at all the
hospitals in the country
I've already sent them to you.
Even all the DNA records at
the prosecution's office
I will send them as soon as I get them.
We have to find a match
as soon as possible.
Please find a match.
Definitely.
Gosh.
I feel lousy.
- Why?
- Isn't that obvious?
My father passed away.
He didn't do much for you.
You said it was better
not having him around.
I was just saying that.
Even if he was a lousy father
between parents and kids
there is something you
don't know about.
What do you mean I don't know?
Parents should do their
job to be called parents.
When they don't do anything for you
is it okay for them to
give birth and be done?
Parents become parents
when they provide and raise the child.
But if your father shows up
you would feel differently, too.
No way.
I would totally ignore him.
Wait and see.
How shameless does he have to be
to show up after all these years?
But still...
it's better to have him around.
Father.
I'm sorry.
Like other people
you should have waited for your son to
send you on a trip abroad, before you died.
Hey, Dae Suk!
Wait a second!
Your father...
Ji Hyuk.
Will that be able to go overseas?
America?
Why would President Kang
all of a sudden?
Do you have to know
the reason, So Mi Ra?
Even his short local trips
I've been handling them.
I've even packed his suitcases.
But without even telling me
the reason why he's left
for America suddenly...
You know how they work.
They do whatever they want
and do it whenever.
When we work for people like them
we can just do what they want us to do.
If he wants to swim across the
Pacific to get to America
we get him the best swimsuit
and the best life vest.
We don't think about the
reason nor need to.
Then do you know how I can contact him?
- Do you really want to know?
- Yes.
I have to know.
Then do a search on the Internet.
If you search a female actress who
left for America around the same time
then you will find the answer
that you're looking for.
Sir.
The hospital just sent you the records.
Okay.
You may go.
Bingo.
Ji Hyuk.
From a whole cow
this is such precious meat that
we can get only this much.
Why would you bring this
precious meat to me?
You should go sell it instead.
You sent my father on a trip overseas.
Did I do that for free food?
About the beef shank
in the refrigerator
Man, I was saving it
for something else.
You stop right there.
Hey.
I was paying for the beef.
I was going to give him
the money for the beef.
How much is it?
Really?
How much can this beef possibly be?
30,000 won.
I will give you the
money after I finish.
You have to pay me, okay?
I was surprised he'd do that.
Hello?
No, I have to start work soon.
What about tonight...
What?
Is it a long distance?
Yes, I will be right there.
Kim Ji Hyuk.
Long time.
When did you get  out?
A while ago.
I've been busy settling, so...
I haven't been in touch.
By the way
I heard that you took
Dong Pal to the station.
That...
Is he one of your guys?
It's so strange.
We always get tangled like this, huh?
We must have been enemies
in our previous lives.
So what is it that you want to say?
Say it now, so I can go.
As his boss
I can't let this go, you know.
We all know that it was you who did it.
Bastard.
Are you threatening me now?
Do you want to die?
It's okay.
In front of my guys
you can't talk to me that way.
Give me a break.
Hey, if you want to keep them around
learn how to treat your
ex-boss with respect.
What's with the eyes?
Plus.
I'm not in that business
any more, so...
don't act like you know
me from now on, okay?
It's embarrassing.
You left this life?
Gosh, it's too bad.
He was once the best in this business.
Yes, sir.
Kim Ji Hyuk?
Taxi!
I know him very well.
Kim Ji Hyuk.
Here.
The buses in this area run late, right?
There are no buses here.
Ah, really?
Then how long does it take
to walk to the bus stop?
I don't know.
I've never been on a bus.
Taxis come out here though, right?
Why do I have to care about
how you're going to get back?
If you're going to be whiny about it,
I can call somebody else.
It's irritating.
What bad manners.
What did you say?
Ah...
I wasn't talking to you.
I was reminded of my
sister who left home.
She looks very much like you.
When she talks, she
also had bad manners.
That's a coincidence.
Pardon?
You look like my brother
who left home too.
He didn't know his place and...
he was sarcastic.
You guys are very similar.
I wonder what he's up to.
At his best, he would
be a substitute driver.
What are you doing?
Sorry but I can't be caught
by the police right now.
Stop the nonsense and stop the car.
Hey!
Stop the car!
You've been drinking, haven't you?
You did that because you were
driving under the influence, right?
Like I told you earlier
I'll be in trouble if I get
arrested by the police now.
What do I do?
I don't give a damn.
A charge for an attempted
murder will be added.
Hey.
Lady, no ma'am!
Damn it!
Are you okay?
I'm okay, so just go.
Don't make a scene.
- Just go.
- Okay.
Over there.
What garbage.
Think before you act.
You and the garbage are here alone now.
Wash it off.
So you won't smell like garbage.
Call the hospital.
to get the trash out.
The surgery would be possible.
I understand.
Get rid of him.
Doctor, we have an emergency.
Page him quickly.
Last night
there was a 31 years old
male with a head trauma.
There is no sign of other injuries.
Due to the head injury
We suspect encephalitis at this time.
Currently, he's not able
to breathe on his own.
There is a chance of brain death.
Good work. You may leave.
Yes, it's been confirmed.
Thank you.
Oh my, good to have you.
I know how busy you are.
Good to have you here.
Thank you.
Okay. Good work.
Is everything okay?
Everything is going to be okay.
So please smile a little.
Is it easy as that?
I will go first.
Jin Ah.
What is it?
Are you leaving already?
I'm sorry, but something
urgent came up.
I'm sorry.
Myung Ho, what are you doing?
You should take Jin Ah home.
Sure.
Hey.
I know it's forced, but...
can you at least pretend?
You weren't even trying.
You knew I was pretending?
President Kang and Mrs. Kang.
you guys look younger
every time I see you.
Do we?
Don't get too much younger.
I will have a lot of
catching up to do.
When Myung Ho and Jin Ah get married
I will be the only one who
will look old at the wedding.
Oh my, you're too funny.
President Kang, it's been a long time.
Ah.
What brings you here, Prosecutor Chang?
It's just that...
I was working in the other province.
I managed to come back
to Seoul some time ago.
So now I get invitations
here and there.
I see.
Anyway, thanks to you...
I rested well in the other province.
I see.
I will pay you a visit soon.
When someone does something nice to me
it's my nature to carve it in
to my skull and never forget.
Then...
So Mi Ra.
Sir.
I told you not to do this at work.
Sorry.
Your view from behind was beautiful.
Finish your work and...
go wait at the place we usually go.
I will meet you there.
Can we just go together?
Well, not yet, Mi Ra.
Are you that scared to reveal
that you're seeing me?
Yes, I'm scared.
especially my mom.
If she finds out that we're dating
she will take away my title and...
take me out of our family tree.
If that happens
the wife of the president
that you longed to become...
will disappear instantly.
You're saying that I've wanted
to get that title, huh?
Then the reason why
I'm dating you is...
you're saying I purposely
tried to hit on you, huh?
Wait.
That wasn't it?
Gosh, I'm crazy.
When I knew that there would
be such a misunderstanding...
Then I will set you free.
I don't need to be the
wife of the president.
Are you sure?
Can I really go?
Did you really mean that?
You really meant that, huh?
Where is that man?
Bring that man here right now!
I'm sorry.
We've called him so many times, but...
he's not answering.
Get in touch with that man somehow.
There are so many things
he's responsible for.
If not, you'll have to
take full responsibility.
I will be here until he shows up.
Get him over here now.
What in the world did he do?
How could you send him as my driver
when he was drunk?
I had never been so close
to death in my life.
Does he think he's Tom Cruise
or something?
He was engaged in a car
chase with the police.
He knew that I was
going to look for him.
That's why he went into hiding.
I will definitely find him.
Should I call the police
and press charges?
Are you crazy?
I wouldn't want to go to the police
station because of some loser.
Jin Ah.
What's your real reason
for trying to find him?
Are you really trying
to get his apology?
Gosh, I'm tired after all
that screaming in that dump.
Wake me up when we get home.
Go in.
Thank you.
My brother left without saying
anything to you, either?
Yes.
So are you disappointed?
No, it's not that.
Because he disappeared suddenly
I just have a lot of
things to take care of.
I hope you understand.
He's never focused as you know.
Good night.
Hey.
Do you want to fly that from there?
I want to see if it can come up here.
Try.
Dong Suk, your tutor is here.
Okay, mom. Wait a second.
Is it broken?
Sorry. What can I do?
It's okay.
I asked you to do that.
You can throw it away.
If we fix it, it might fly again.
Then can you fix it and fly it again?
Dong Suk.
Okay, I'm coming.
Bye. Better luck next time.
Soon he'll be pronounced
brain dead and...
when we get his heart out,
we will perform the transplant.
- Get ready.
- Yes, sir.
If we make any mistakes
we all won't be able to
work at this hospital.
- You all know that, right?
- Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Why are you thanking me?
He's not just your son, but mine too.
Dong Suk will come back to
the way he used to be, right?
Just thinking about it makes me happy.
Thinking about seeing
my son smile again...
Even if you love it, try
not to show it too much.
The man who will be
pronounced brain dead...
he's your son on paper too.
Ah, that's right.
This is the same test
done six hours ago.
There is no pupillary
reflex or brain activity.
He's maintaining the flat
electroencephalogram.
He's been checked out for hemophilia.
There is no chance of
spontaneous respiration.
Kim Il Tae and two
others at cardiothoracic
surgery at Hyun Sung hospital
we pronounce him brain dead.
If any of your family members
object this decision
you can ask for a reexamination.
Do you object?
At 15:30 on April 15th, 2014
we pronounce Kang Ji Hyuk brain dead.
Even though I walk through
the valley of darkness
I will fear no evil,
for you are with me;
your rod and your
staff, they comfort me.
You prepare a table before me
in the presence of my enemies.
Even though your body stops breathing
the body God gave you
will be shared with other
unfortunate souls.
We will now perform the
transplant on Kang Ji Hyuk.
Scalpel.
Sir, hold on.
- I notice his oculo movement.
- What?
Confirm it.
Does he show light reflex?
No.
What was that?
I'm serious. I saw something earlier...
He's already been
pronounced brain dead.
Medically, he's same as dead.
Start the surgery now.
Suction.
Are you not going to do anything?
Aren't you going to
start gauze packing?
Sir.
This can be considered as
a sign of nearing death.
So we will start the operation.
Sir.
This is not right.
The surgery is over already?
I agree.
How could you finish this fast?
The patient, Kang Ji Hyuk
has come back to life.
Who came back to life?
Kang Ji Hyuk.
What are you talking about?
He was already pronounced brain dead.
During surgery
his brainwave resumed.
There was a problem in
pronouncing him brain dead.
Then...
What's going to happen to Dong Suk?
Dong Suk won't be able
to have the surgery?
He can't.
Dr. Lee.
Something must be wrong.
It was all over.
It was already confirmed.
You can just go perform surgery.
There is some misunderstanding.
It was the machine error.
Please.
Please go back and try.
Please go back and perform surgery now.
Ma'am.
In a situation like this
if I put a scalpel on his chest
I will be a murderer.
Dong Suk.
- Dong Suk.
- Ma'am.
- Honey.
How is my wife doing?
She is doing okay.
She just needs to rest.
How about that guy?
He's in the recovery room.
How did you let this happen?
I'm sorry.
This was a case of 1 in 10,000.
It was a miracle...
A miracle?
I'm sorry.
Is there a chance he might
become brain dead again?
It's not entirely impossible, but...
no one knows for sure at this point.
There is nothing we can do
now that things are complicated.
Look into the lists overseas.
We'll always consider him as an option.
Yes, I understand.
And don't let this get out.
Act like nothing happened.
Yes.
Ji Hyuk hasn't been here either?
No.
What happened to him?
His cell phone is switched off too.
Why do you worry about him?
Is this his first time doing this?
No, something is not right this time.
When he went in hiding in the past
he just wouldn't answer the phone.
He never switched off his cell phone.
He must have broken it
during a fight somewhere.
When he comes home
please let me know.
Don't bother.
I will sever my ties
with him this time.
If he calls you, tell him.
Tell him not to even think about
setting his foot in this place again.
Are you not worried? For real?
Why would I worry about him?
Are we related by blood or what?
We have no relationship, whatsoever.
Gosh, where can he be,
and doing what?
On 15th of this month
at the party for our new family members
For the appetizer, foie gras.
For the main course
Japanese Wagyu and truffles.
For wine, Monte Verde
it should be served at the table
for the president's family only.
For the rest, have
something cheaper ready.
About the foie gras
only refrigerated foie gras
for the president's family.
For the rest, we'll go
with frozen foie gras.
For all the other parties,
use this as a standard.
Wait.
At the president's house
there is a problem with the air
freshener in the bathrooms.
The French company of the
product went bankrupt.
We don't have any in stock.
What should I do?
Why are you bringing it up now?
Don't you know how sensitive
Mrs. Kang is about the scent?
I'm sorry.
Right now, send the French headquarter
samples of fragrances she likes.
Tell them to send air fresheners
that are close to that scent.
I will.
And...
Go over to the hotel
where we are having
our founding
ceremony next month.
Check their cleanliness
and reservation lists.
Can I help you?
Ah, it's...
I heard someone was looking
for a machine in China.
Hold on.
And on the whole fifteenth
floor at the hotel
make sure no one is allowed
except the president's family members.
Yes, sir.
Next, we have an issue about the
president's house cleaning.
I was going to bring
it up to Manager So.
Mrs. Kang...
We have to find the matching part.
Something that matches ours here.
Sure.
Anything you forgot to mention?
I think we've covered it all.
Then let's wrap it up.
Good work.
Due to President Kang
Dong Suk's car damage
the car service contacted us, so...
can you go over to check?
It might be better to scrap it.
Sure.
Hold on.
What did you say happened
to President Kang Dong Suk's car?
It might have been in an accident.
- We will take care of it...
- No.
I will go take care of it myself.
Tell me where the service center is.
What do you want me
to do with that car?
Do you want it to be fixed?
When the accident happened
Were you there yourself?
Yes, I was.
Do you know what
happened to the driver?
Well, I only saw him
carried to the ambulance.
Nothing happened to him, did it?
I'm sorry, but...
about the accident
I was asked not to say anything, so...
I can't tell you anything further.
Was he still alive at least?
Pardon?
Just tell me that only.
whether he was alive or not.
He was alive.
when I was there at least.
Thank you.
What do you want to do with the car?
It's okay.
He will be okay.
He should be okay.
Hi, Manager Do.
Where are you now, So Ra?
I'm out at the moment.
Go to Hyun Sung hospital now.
What is it?
In the VIP room
find a man named Kang Ji Hyuk
who is not conscious.
Report to me everything
that's happening to him.
Kang Ji Hyuk?
Who is he?
Don't second guess the
work you're given.
Don't you know the creed?
Yes, understood.
Manager Do.
About President Kang Dong Suk
is it true that he's gone to America?
He got on a plane.
That's all I know.
Don't get sidetracked
with some nonsense.
Do as you're told.
Are you his guardian?
Yes.
You must be thrilled.
Pardon?
After being pronounced brain dead
it was very rare that
he came back to life.
Besides, his recovery is very fast too.
Ah, his hand moved earlier too.
I can only explain this as a miracle.
Is that right?
Among the patients in the VIP rooms
by any chance, can you check
if there is Kang Dong Suk?
I'm sorry, but we are not
allowed to give you that information.
I'm an employee at
Hyun Sung headquarter.
You can tell me if he's here or not.
I'm sorry, but I can't.
Hello, this is the information
desk at Hyun Sung hospital.
Manager Lee.
Uh, what are you doing here?
There is something I
was asked to do here.
What brings you here?
Well, Madam Choi asked us to
move something here, so...
This is...
Hello, you're from Hyun Sung, right?
Yes.
Give it to us. We will move it.
We can carry it.
No.
Except for the hospital staff
no one else is allowed in, so...
Give it to us.
We will move it for you.
Alright then. Thank you.
Ah, thank you.
- Sir.
- What is it?
I might have exclusive news.
- Exclusive news?
- Yes.
Reporter Park called me and...
At Financial Supervisory Service
according to Prosecutor Chang Won Tae
you know that they are trying
to target Hyun Sung, right?
I do.
Why is that exclusive news?
When they were investigating
taxes on inheritance
they found another son of President
Kang Sung Wook at Hyun Sung.
- A son?
- Yes.
Other than President Kang Dong
Suk at Hyun Sung Distribution
there is another son on
their family registry.
It was recent too.
Is that right?
Find out about him.
We will break that news first, okay?
Sure.
Get on it.
I was told that he's recovering fast.
What should we do?
We are looking into China for now.
About that man
when he regains his consciousness
we will move him to a
different hospital.
It's not easy to keep it under
tight control in a big hospital.
If the situation becomes a dead end
get rid of him.
Without a trace.
You can hear this, right?
This is the Mozart that you like.
Yes, I'm at the hospital.
I wanted to get some air.
Where did you say you were?
Dong Suk.
Why are you in there?
Please open your eyes and tell me.
Will you?
Tell me that you're okay.
Tell me that you're just fine, huh?
Dong Suk.
How is he doing?
Not bad.
So far.
So far?
There is blood circulation, but...
he hasn't regained his
consciousness yet.
I worry about the after effects.
How long does he have?
He will be okay up to a month.
A month...
What about beyond that?
It will be difficult to expect
to see him the same way.
- You came.
- Yes.
How long do we have to wait?
I've been contacting the centers, so...
Not an answer like that...
I'm saying take some
immediate action, now.
Whether you use that guy
to take his heart out or...
Honey.
I'm just going crazy. That's why...
Nothing is getting done
here at the hospital.
I'm sorry.
Go home. Dong Suk will hear you.
I will do everything I can
to give him that operation.
So don't say things without thinking.
Go to Hyun Sung Hospital now.
In a VIP room
find a man named Kang Ji
Hyuk who is unconscious.
After being pronounced brain dead
this was very rare to come
back to life like this.
Whether you use that man again
to pull out his heart or...
Dong Suk.
Dong Suk, excuse me!
- Excuse me!
- I'm okay.
I'm okay.
Dong Suk, are you okay?
What is it? What happened?
This might happen often.
What I have in here...
it's not mine.
Dong Suk.
So don't stress me out with anything.
I might explode into pieces.
Good night.
What is it?
What? Why the reporters?
Tell the hospital to move his room.
Now.
- To that side.
- Yes.
Over there!
No, I have to live.
I want to live.
Can somebody grab me?
Grab me.
Grab me!
Thanks for download drama & subtitle here
::  www.airens357.net  ::
There is nothing to
think about this time.
Kill him.
Don't judge the work you're given.
I will follow that rule exactly.
- You.
- Are you Jin Ah?
You were that garbage, right?
There is something wrong with my eyes.
Mom!
Did you get into trouble again?
I got into mega trouble.
Before you do more
Don't worry about him.
There is a reason why I
gave him that title.
It might be something that
was in the bag that you had.
What was your motive?
You can just be my lover.
President Kang Sung Wook!
My father was a bastard.