玛瑟拉
Messala.
玛瑟拉！
Messala!
玛瑟拉
Messala.
玛瑟拉？
Messala?
我赢了吗
Did l win?
没有  你差点没害死自己
来吧
No, but you nearly killed yourself trying to.
Come on.
-还有别的方法可以分出伯仲吗
-去问母亲大人吧
-ls there any other way to race?
-Tell that to my mother.
一  二  三
One, two, three!
真应该在身后拉一群奴隶
l should have a line of slaves behind me.
最该有个奴隶来提醒你
你本凡人  而非天神
And one beside you, whispering in your ear
that you're a man, not a god.
这才是罗马精神  对吧  奥克塔维斯・玛瑟拉
ls that not the Roman way,
Octavius Messala?
-另一辆马车怎么啦？
-有一段路颠簸不平  所以翻了
-What happened to the other cart?
-We went over some rough ground.
-它们可不是比赛用的战车
-我警告过他了
-They're not racing chariots, you know?
-l told him that.
我们会修好的  母亲大人  我保证
We'll repair it, Mother. l promise.
你们两个今天去哪里了
为何没带我一起去
Where have you two been all day?
Why didn't you take me with you?
因为你乳臭未干  不适合与年轻壮士为伍
Because you are child
and not proper company for young men.
使劲搔她的痒  玛瑟拉
Tickle her severely, Messala.
尤达
Judah.
有个从卫戍部队来的信使  送来了这个
是给玛瑟拉的
A messenger from the Garrison
delivered this. It's for Messala.
我们都知道它迟早会来
We always knew this would come.
可自他母亲过世算起  已经五年多了
But it's been five years, more,
since his mother died.
难道你希望他父亲当时就把他带走吗
Would you prefer his father
had sent for him immediately?
-蒂莎会伤心欲绝的
-谁都高兴不起来  尤达
-Tirzah will be most unhappy.
-None of us will be happy, Judah.
另外  西蒙尼特斯已经到了
And Simonides has arrived.
见他之前  你必须换件衣服
You must change your clothes
before you greet him.
遵命  我都忘了他要来
Yes, l forgot he was coming.
很抱歉  他来时应由我接待的
l'm sorry.
l should have been here to meet him.
没错
Yes.
你的确该担负起应有的责任了
lt's time for you
to take up your responsibilities,
玛瑟拉也一样
and for Messala to face his.
无忧无虑的童年到此为止了
Childhood only lasts so long.
这么说  我们的童年要在同一天终结了
So our childhoods end on the same day,
his and mine.
而后我们就会分道扬镳
And our lives go in different directions.
虽然分道扬镳  却是殊途同归  成为真正的男儿
Different directions,
but the same journey to manhood
and all its rewards and responsibilities.
And l know that you will meet
whatever lies ahead
with a good heart and a brave spirit,
for you are your father's son.
And my mother's.
No mother was ever more blessed in a child.
去吧  尤达  告诉他  游戏时间结束了
Go now, Judah,
and tell your friend playtime's over.
看来只能如此了
So it would seem.
-究竟有何诀窍
-只需事先准备好即可
-What's the secret?
-You just have to be ready.
谁写来的
Who is it from?
我那位显赫的父亲 元老院议员马赛勒斯・阿葛瑞帕
From my illustrious father,
Senator Marcellus Agrippa.
你读吧
You read it.
这是私人信件  玛瑟拉
lt's a private letter, Messala.
我们关系这么好  没有什么不妥
l don't think you'll be embarrassed
by too many intimacies.
记住  诀窍就在于随时估计它的走向
Remember, the secret is to expect it to fall
every single moment.
"致奥克塔维斯・玛瑟拉
''To Octavius Messala.
将有一支军队护送你离开耶路撒冷  前往凯撒利亚
''You will leave Jerusalem
with the next military convoy to Caesarea
那里已安排好你回罗马所需的交通工具"
''where transportation has been arranged
for your journey to Rome.''
-就这些吗
-他是个少言寡语的人  马赛勒斯・阿葛瑞帕
-ls that all?
-He's a man of few words, Marcellus Agrippa.
我有时真嫉妒你父亲已不在人世
l sometimes envy you having a dead father.
-尤达  见到你真是太好了
-很抱歉当时没有亲自接待您
-Judah, how good to see you.
-Forgive me for not being here to meet you.
-没关系  身体可还安康
-当然  劳您关心
-lt is of no matter. You are well?
-Yes, yes, thank you.
您呢  一路车马劳顿  是否疲累
And you? Your iourney was not too tiring?
从安提俄克到这里的路程依旧遥远
The distance from Antioch
does not grow shorter,
而我也依旧苍老
and l do not grow younger.
尤达  你应该知道  你已故的父亲
Judah, l think that you know
that your father, of blessed memory,
希望我们两个家族的关系可以不仅局限于商业伙伴
hoped that one day we would unite
our families in more than mercantile matters.
The painter does my daughter no iustice.
Esther is not simply a face,
but a mind and a spirit of rare quality.
l hope your father's and my aspirations
will be fulfilled.
Yes, yes.
lt has to be your wish also.
-And Esther's?
-Of course. Of course.
Thank you.
No, no.
It is for you until you meet in person.
-Come with me.
-Would if l could.
Where you are going
is the centre of the world, Messala.
Things that would never be possible here
will come your way.
Will you write to us?
l doubt it. l am no hand with a pen.
But l'll think of you, all of you.
And l'll miss you.
-And l will come back.
-Promise?
You be safe, Octavius Messala.
-We will race again.
-God willing.
Forward march!
Left, right. Left, right. Left, right, left.
Judah! Judah!
-This came for you.
-Messala is here.
-Open it.
-What does it say?
''Judah Ben Hur
is ordered to present himself
''to the Garrison Commander
upon receipt of this notice.''
Well, it's to the point.
-Probably written by a scribe.
-lt certainly wasn't written by a friend.
Well, you better not keep
the Garrison Commander waiting.
Halt.
l see you forgot nothing l taught you.
You know what the emperor Octavius
said of Rome?
He said, ''l found this city built of bricks,
and l left it made of marble.''
That is what l intend to say of Jerusalem.
That is a remarkable aspiration
for a garrison commander.
l won't always be a garrison commander
any more than Pontius Pilate
will always be the Governor of Judaea.
We could do great things here
together, you and l.
Marcellus Agrippa's got plans for me.
He spent a great deal of money
and influence advancing my career.
-Only shows his regard for you as his son.
-No.
No, it's his regard for his own future.
He wants a strong man on his side,
someone with military renown to his name.
Yes. And he's chosen you, Messala.
No, not quite.
l mean, he still hasn't given me his name.
l am still his unacknowledged bastard.
Begotten of a mistress he abandoned
when he found someone younger.
No. My father, the senator,
is a cruel, cunning, capricious man,
and those are some of his better qualities.
He's given me this chance,
which l am determined to take.
The trouble is it's earned me the enmity
of Pontius Pilate.
So l must tread carefully.
You can be of help to me, Judah.
Of course, in whatever way l can.
This festival of the Passover.
Now should you know of any elements
that plan to disrupt Pilate's arrival,
l'd want to know of them.
lt would reflect badly on me,
you understand?
Are you asking me
to become an informer, Messala?
l'm asking you to help preserve the order
of a Roman province.
This is my career, Judah.
l can't afford mistakes.
Not now, not at the start.
Pilate, he'd have me removed or demoted,
given a chance.
All l'm asking, between friends,
is if you know, or hear, or suspect anything,
just let me know.
Believe me, it saves much worse
if such things can be nipped in the bud.
Speaking of nipping in the bud,
which of these do you prefer?
l give you first choice.
l'm nothing if not a generous friend.
lf you will excuse me.
Shouldn't have thought you suffer
from the Greek affliction.
Judah, when may l pay my respects
to your mother?
-She's well l hope?
-She is.
She's looking forward to seeing you.
And Tirzah, she must be married by now
at her ripe age?
No. Tirzah has set her standards so high
that none of her suitors can meet them.
So there is hope for me yet.
Come and eat with us.
lt's good to see you, Judah.
We'll do great things here, you and l.
A great thing has already come to pass.
You are here with us again.
Hey! Let's hurry up. Get a move on.
He's a surly bugger,
that foreman of yours, Judah.
-Saves me from having to be one.
-Yes.
Well, that's what l'll be doing
under the new Garrison Commander.
What do you mean?
l'm being forced to step down a rank
for some child.
Well, he must the qualifications,
or he wouldn't have been given the post.
lt's not what you know. It's who you know.
The Governor's none too pleased.
He wanted to make me permanent.
Mind you,
l wouldn't trust Pilate's judgement either.
lt's all politics with these buggers.
-That's it then, David.
-All done.
-You intend to enter the chariot race, Gaius?
-ls there any other reason to live, Judah?
You'll be safe laying a talent on me.
lt wouldn't do for a Jew to wager
against his own team, now would it?
Suit yourself,
but you'll be throwing your money away.
Shalom!
You see? Didn't even count them.
We've already done that, haven't we?
Never hurts to rob those bastards
when you get a chance.
When you have a business
of your own, David,
you'll find out how well it pays
to cheat your customers.
Romans are not customers.
They're bloody conquerors.
Sometimes l think you forget that.
You know, l appreciate your animosity,
David. Your brother suffered at their hands.
Suffered?
Nailed up on a stick is how he suffered.
-Three days it took.
-He killed a Roman soldier, did he not?
Whose side are you on, Judah Ben Hur?
lt is not a question of sides.
We are under Roman occupation.
-Now that may be unfortunate, but it's a fact.
-Well, we'll see about that.
You know, a time is coming when
you'll be asked to say where you stand.
-Are you threatening me?
-No.
l'm iust telling you how it is.
You'll see what happens
when the Governor shows up at Passover.
Don't involve me in your conspiracies,
David. You know my position.
Pay your taxes and collaborate.
You know, you have a way with an argument
that turns into a quarrel.
l wondered when you'd be back.
You know, we have Simonides arriving,
bringing you your bride.
That is not funny.
You know there has been no understanding
between Esther and myself.
That's not what Simonides thinks.
Anyway, it's about time you were married.
Give us an heir apparent.
David Ben Levi was at me again today.
Why don't you get rid of that man?
He's a zealot.
No, Tirzah, he's an excellent overseer,
and he knows the business
as well or better than l.
l will not dismiss him for convictions
he holds as genuinely as l do my own.
Do you never get tired of being
so reasonable and even-handed, Judah?
People like David Ben Levi are dangerous.
They make life impossible for people like us.
You know, he as much as told me
there would be a demonstration
against the Governor at Passover.
-Well, then denounce him.
-You forget yourself, Sister.
We do not denounce our fellow countrymen.
There'll be solders everywhere.
You start something,
and there will be a massacre.
We should take note
of those who welcome him.
Put them on the list.
We must be prepared
to take advantage of any situation.
All of us should be armed
so we may strike a blow.
Leave us.
-So, you came.
-To warn you.
Judah, we are already warned.
Every day we see our enemy.
We know who they are.
The new Garrison Commander is determined
that nothing interfere
with the arrival of Pontius Pilate.
He will be on the alert,
and he will take action,
drastic action,
in the event of any disturbance.
You think this is news to us?
l know this Garrison Commander,
and he will not risk his reputation
on such an occasion.
-You know him?
-Octavius Messala is my friend.
That friend, you don't want anything
to spoil his big day.
l don't want to see any more men crucified
or sent to the galleys.
Very well, you've done your part.
You've warned us.
Now can l have your word
you will not betray us?
Were that in my mind, it would have been
a Roman who knocked at your door.
He must have changed to speak
in such a way to you, his best friend.
Of course he has changed, Tirzah.
He is a man, a soldier. He has been to war.
But he never forgot us. That much l know.
And he is glad to be back.
-What of his father? Did he speak of him?
-Not with any great affection, l'm afraid.
He referred to him always
as Marcellus Agrippa or the senator.
Poor boy.
And when can we expect an audience
with the poor boy?
He will dine with us in a few days.
And l hope you will manage
a more welcoming manner, Sister.
l have not invited him under our roof
to have him mocked.
You will see for yourself
how much he has changed
and how much he is still the same Messala
we knew and loved.
For we did love him, did we not?
-Yes. Yes, we did.
-Yes.
And we shall again.
-Judah!
-Here they are at last.
Greetings and welcome.
Let me present my daughter.
Esther.
Welcome, Esther, daughter of Simonides.
lt is my honour and my family's.
Welcome.
l saw her face, Judah.
-Saw what?
-That she was not disappointed.
l do not like to see birds kept captive,
but my father says they are never free
of the chains of the sky.
lndeed.
You need not approve
my father's nonsense, Judah.
Do you really think these creatures
would not wish to fly away at this moment
-if l opened their cage?
-Perhaps.
Although they might not survive for long.
lf l were they,
l should wish to have the choice.
How happy l am to see Jerusalem at last.
To you it is a familiar sight, l know.
But l, too, often stand here
and admire this view.
lt is the city of our faith,
and while we have it,
we have our centre, our heart.
Forgive me. l have a tendency to pontificate.
l do not mean to...
No, no, go on. Please, continue.
Esther, l realise your father has
certain expectations
as did my father,
and you should know that
l am not opposed to their wishes.
But you think we should make
our own choice in a matter so important?
As you say.
Be you betrothed to me with this, my wealth.
For the first couple of years l was in Rome,
l didn't even see Marcellus Agrippa.
lt was all military training.
Poor Messala, learning how to be a soldier.
lt has its compensations.
The ladies of Rome are very patriotic.
Did you teach them to catch the stick?
Your father must be so proud of you.
No. l wouldn't go so far as to say that.
He's expectant, maybe, but...
l'm not ungrateful.
He has given me so much advice,
advice which has stood the test of reality.
''He over whom you have no power
has power over you.'' That's his motto.
Power, he says,
is the only currency worth hoarding.
lt never loses its value.
But there are powers other
than those Marcellus Agrippa speaks of.
Of faith, of family, of friends, fair dealing.
ln Rome, no such powers prevail.
Even Tiberius, our emperor, gave up
his beloved wife and his three children
to make a dynastic marriage
with his brother's widow.
Everyone applauded his wisdom.
l think that not wisdom
but an affront against God.
Whose god? Yours?
Rome and its values are not for you, Esther,
nor my friend, your husband-to-be.
But they're for those whose ambitions
remain unchecked by conscience,
whose loyalty can be purchased
by advancement and coin.
And have you become such a one, Messala?
l have.
l mean, l think l have.
But such is my fate.
We are all in the hands of the gods,
are we not?
Such is our belief.
So have you given any thought
to what l said earlier?
Regarding provocations, disturbances
and so forth?
lt is as l have told you.
l will have no hand in any demonstration
against Rome.
l know.
l talk of hearsay, rumour.
Nothing?
-Why do you question your friend's word?
-He hasn't given me his word. Have you?
ls it so much to ask assurance of a friend?
Come, you need only ask Gaius Antonius
to know that the Hur family
have always cooperated with Rome.
l'm asking Judah.
lt does Rome no credit to impugn a friend
under his own roof
while in receipt of hospitality.
l impugn no one. l do as my duty requires.
ls it so much to ask for Judah's word?
-l give you my word.
-Thank you.
Shame on you, Octavius Messala,
to speak so to those who love you.
Daughter, Messala is a guest and our friend.
-Apologise to him.
-No.
l should apologise. l spoke out of turn.
Thank you, Judah.
It's of great comfort to me.
To all our futures. May they be happy
and prosperous, however brief.
She's got a mind of her own, Esther.
You should have a care, Judah.
When she takes the reins,
she'll ride you hard.
And your sister.
You should know l've contrived
to have Pilate's procession pass here
in front of the house
so you'll have the chance to see me
in all my pomp.
l'll be the handsome one on the white horse.
Forgive me.
You know, half my performance
is to convince myself.
Messala, no need of forgiveness.
Go with God and be yourself tomorrow.
All will be well.
Forward!
March. Left, right. Left, right.
Left. Left. Left.
Have a care, Judah.
He could be a dangerous enemy.
And a more dangerous friend.
At the first sign of any trouble,
any demonstration from the crowd, quell it.
Use the butt end to begin with,
but if that proves unavailing,
give them the blade. Is that understood?
-Yeah!
We should be bringing Pilate
to the Garrison direct.
Keep him on the main streets.
We'll have clear space on either side.
The lower city is too narrow.
You make it seem as if l were
sneaking Pilate through the back door.
l don't think he'd appreciate
the caution, Gaius.
l think he might find it
an affront to his vanity.
Your iob is to protect, not to flatter.
There speaks a voice
with no concern for politics.
And who thanks the gods for it.
Go home, Romans.
-Keep on riding.
-Go back where you came from.
Have respect, Romans.
You have no respect.
A sullen lot, these Jews.
Better to be obeyed
than beloved, Excellency.
Drop back a length.
Go home, Romans.
Have some shame, Romans.
Go on.
There's Pilate at the front,
gleaming like a brass pot.
Messala does look splendid, l must say.
Look out!
Do something.
Seize him!
Arrest Judah.
Move!
lt was an accident. A tile fell from...
lt was an accident. Please!
It was an accident!
-Judah.
-Tirzah.
lt was an accident! Judah!
ln broad daylight,
an attack on Rome's emissary.
Tiberius will hear of this and of
your incompetence, you place-bought fool!
l will have you removed, you hear?
Sent to the furthest reaches of the Empire!
Am l not iniured enough?
l could have been killed.
Those responsible are under arrest,
Excellency.
Crucify them!
The weapon could have pierced my skull.
Well, what are you waiting for?
l said crucify them.
-Excellency, it is the feast of the Passover.
-l know that!
That's why l am here
to make Rome's presence felt.
Who are these rebels?
One of the foremost
of the Jewish families in Jerusalem.
Judah Ben Hur and his mother and sister.
Well, make an example of them.
Crucify the man and garrotte the women.
Do you hear me?
Thank God. Are my mother and Tirzah safe?
You have more to concern you
than their welfare.
You attempted to kill his Excellency,
Pontius Pilate.
Messala, it was an accident.
A tile fell from the roof.
When the governor of a Roman province
is attacked in the street,
it is not an accident.
It is a rebellion against Rome.
Have you gone mad?
-You gave a signal for the riot to begin.
-You cannot believe that.
-My family and l are your friends.
-You and your family have destroyed me!
Do you understand that?
Messala, l knew nothing.
Liar! You lied last night.
l saw it in your eyes.
Admit it.
Give me the names of the other plotters,
the ones you signalled, you and your family!
Don't threaten my family.
They are even more blameless than l.
Let me go before Pilate and explain.
He wants you crucified,
and your mother and sister
to be executed by strangulation.
-No! No!
-Hear me, Judah.
You have destroyed the house of Hur
and me with it.
-Messala, listen to me.
-No, you listen to me.
Where there is a war, someone must go to it,
and it will not be me.
Messala! Messala! Messala!
These two are going to get the wire.
Be assured my report will make clear
that it was your incompetence
that led to this insult to the Emperor.
-Excellency...
-Silence!
l'm dismissing you as Garrison Commander
and reinstating Gaius Antonius.
And trust me, your patron, Senator Agrippa,
will not intervene this time
to keep you in a post
for which you are manifestly unfit.
Get up! Up, come on. l said get up!
All right, get out of here, you.
Forgive them,
for they know not what they do.
forgve them.
Simonides! Simonides! Simonides!
Am l not to be crucified?
No such luck.
Your sentence has been changed.
You're for the galleys.
A year from now, you'll be wishing
they'd put you up on a stick.
You are now under the command
of Quintus Arrius,
commander of the Southern Fleet
and victor
of the Battle of the Corinth Straits.
You have been chosen
to carry His Excellency
to receive reward for his service
from the hand
of the Emperor Tiberius himself.
You may consider yourselves honoured
and will acquit your duty accordingly,
or by the gods, you will answer to me.
Honoured, do you hear?
Silence! Silence at the oars.
Let every man know that any infraction
will be severely dealt with.
Severely dealt with iust for a change.
Prepare to increase.
And stroke. And stroke. And stroke.
Quintus Arrius.
He is the one who cleaned out the pirates,
and honoured we are
to be rowing him to Rome.
You feeling honoured, Number 40?
They killed my wife,
and my daughter, and my son.
They create a wilderness and call it peace.
Every night l dream, my friend.
Then l wake up, but l'm still Number 41.
Do you ever think maybe it's all a bad dream,
and death is when you wake from it?
Go to sleep, Antegua.
Dream of killing Romans and kill one for me,
Number 40.
They have two anklets. Is one not enough?
l switch the rowers from port to starboard
on a regular basis, Excellency.
lt keeps them better balanced.
It requires being able to chain them
to battle stations
whichever side they are rowing.
And does the result outweigh the cost
for the extra anklets?
Yes, sir, they are better oarsmen for it.
Well, commendations, Hortator.
Thank you, Excellency.
He did not tell you it was Number 40's idea.
Silence at the oars!
-Whose idea was it, Number 41?
-Number 40's.
ls this true, Number 40?
Would Number 41 lie to Quintus Arrius?
He mentioned it to me, Excellency.
And you took the advice of a galley slave?
Congratulations on having an open mind.
The thing of it is,
l am not afraid of death.
Either it will be better than this,
or it will be nothing,
which will be better than this.
What are you afraid of?
Nothing.
l am afraid of going down in the chains.
On your feet.
We're only iust off the oars.
You're wanted up top.
You're going to see His Excellency.
You mind your mouth in there.
l don't want any of your smart opinions
about how to run a galley.
ls that clear?
Come on.
-Pull them out.
-Pull out! Pull it.
Watch the side.
Right ship, turn!
Come.
Number 40, Excellency.
l don't suppose you know much
about naval strategy, do you, Number 40?
Mine is not the best place to learn.
Then why would you suggest the hortator
switch the rowers from side to side?
l believe he explained the reason.
The rowers would be better balanced.
Yes, he did.
But why would you care?
Efficiency is better than it's opposite,
even for a galley slave.
How long have you been at the oars?
Almost three years.
Well, you are certainly thriving on it.
How long did you get?
There was no limit put on my sentence.
And what did you do to deserve that?
l was betrayed by a friend.
Well, that usually carries
a maximum penalty.
Are you going to tell me now
that you are entirely innocent?
Well, if we lived in Rome
it wouldn't be worth comment,
so commonplace it would be.
That is little consolation
when you have been wrongfully accused
and convicted without a hearing,
your family destroyed, and all on the word
of one who was your friend.
Well, l'm surprised
that a man with your education
and intelligence has lasted so long.
This work is for unthinking brutes.
l've had encouragement in that direction.
Come. Come.
Sir. Three ships sighted.
Just put out from the headland.
They are pirates for sure.
They have the land breeze,
but they're no match for our rowers.
We can outrun them.
Outrun? No, no, no, no.
Outmanoeuvre, outthink, outfight,
but not outrun.
ln case the news gets back to Rome,
and it's converted to running away.
Quintus Arrius does not run away.
Off you go, Number 40, and take the grapes.
lt will sweeten your stroke.
What is that?
Trumpet calling us to battle stations.
l was dreaming
l was in a garden drinking sherbet.
l can taste it.
Battle stations.
Three pirates came out to greet us.
May they capture us and kill all the Romans.
May we kill those they leave behind.
We're going to port.
lt's your lucky day, isn't it, Number 40?
Battle stations!
Oars out!
And stroke.
And stroke. And stroke.
Port! Hold!
Port, oars in! Hold!
Coming about.
-Secure port.
-Hold steady!
Port, withdraw!
And stroke.
And stroke. And stroke.
Give me speed!
Stroke. And stroke. And stroke.
Archers at the ready!
-Ready arrows.
-Hold formation.
Hold your position.
Starboard in.
Release!
Oars out!
And stroke.
And stroke. And stroke.
Port, in!
Hold!
How many?
Two more.
Port, withdraw!
And stroke, and stroke.
And stroke.
Ramming speed!
And stroke. And stroke.
And stroke.
Back oars. Back oars! Back oars!
Judah, unlock the chains!
The chains!
Quickly, Judah.
Judah.
lt's no use.
Go, Number 40, and kill a Roman for me.
Don't let me drown in these chains.
You?
Number 40.
Who else?
Are there other survivors?
There's been no sign.
This needs to come out.
Not if it's barbed.
Try.
One good pull. It's an order, Number 40!
lt's very clever.
Detach blade so it stays in the body.
The Great Quintus Arrius
adrift with a slave in his hour of triumph.
You are still alive.
You mean l am not dead.
There's a difference.
l know the difference.
Well, the gods
have their own sense of humour.
l trust you still believe in your god.
How can l say other
when l am delivered from my chains?
Not by a god.
Before each battle,
l unchain one rower.
Why?
Call it a reminder of humility,
an antidote to hubris,
or simply habit.
Why me?
Maybe l like the way you eat grapes.
What?
What is it?
A sail.
l will not be taken by pirates.
lf this is a pirate ship,
you must not let them take me.
So having saved your life, l should take it
to save you from the oars.
lf this is a Roman ship,
l will not let them take you back.
You will come to Rome as my slave.
This is a better form of servitude.
You have my word on it, Number 40.
My name is Judah Ben Hur.
You have my word, Judah Ben Hur.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Their chieftain is here as you ordered.
His family?
The women killed themselves.
He was only taken alive with great difficulty.
It cost us three men.
Will we crucify him, sir?
No. Keep him alive.
l have a better idea.
My son will receive his reward
at the hands of Tiberius himself
when he returns to Rome.
Such are his triumphs against the Thracians.
Well, l am glad that your son
has finally made you proud.
You've waited a long time
for a return on your investment.
Bastards got on mistresses
need time to prove themselves.
And at least l will have a son
to carry on my name.
So, Marcellus,
you've seen fit to bestow it on him.
l need Tiberius' approval.
Well, you know how he likes
a man to die without heirs,
so that all his estates
are subject to his decree.
Well, let's pray he survives you
to carry on your illustrious name.
Quite so.
l hope to prevail on Tiberius
to grant Octavius Messala
the governorship of Judaea.
Replace that wretch who did so much
to obstruct his advancement.
And Tiberius will grant this favour?
There are ways to influence an emperor.
My Thracian will take his fancy,
and of course,
Athene can be most persuasive.
Gods.
l feel the need of a little intestinal relief.
Excuse me.
l can give you something to dull the pain.
And how do you feel about
being on loan to our Emperor?
l am a whore. How should l feel?
So which is your
galley-slave-turned-gladiator?
The blond one.
But he's no gladiator. He's my body servant.
Skilled in arms.
What, does the victor
of the Corinth Straits fear assassination
that he must go guarded in the streets?
He's beautiful, your body servant.
lndeed.
You pick well, Quintus.
We chose each other.
Chose each other, did we?
Enough! Enough!
You improve day by day.
A fine looking specimen.
What say you match him
against my Thracian before the Emperor?
There is no likelihood of that.
l value him too much
to see him butchered for your amusement.
l'll give you odds.
He's learning well, and he's learning fast.
-Could you have killed him?
-Today?
Only about a half dozen times.
l am Athene.
Judah.
So you are a Jew, and l am a Greek.
Both of us conquered peoples
subject to the will of Rome and Romans.
We should make a common cause
while we have the chance.
lf you'll excuse me.
Did you...
The Greek, did she take you to her bed?
She's not to my taste.
Judah, no...
Don't make me laugh. It hurts too much.
Go to her.
Are you asking me
to sleep with this woman?
No. l'm ordering you to.
lt will not be such a hardship.
Why would you wish it?
Because Marcellus Agrippa wants it.
Marcellus Agrippa?
He uses her for his ends,
few of which are carnal.
She will inquire of things he wants to know.
Such as, what you are to me,
how long you think l will last,
and who are my heirs.
Why does he want to know these things?
Because in Rome, knowledge is power.
And he over whom you do not have power
has power over you.
l see you've learned the ways
of the Imperium.
l had a good teacher.
Have your physicians no remedy
for your pain?
No, l have had my fill with them.
When my time comes,
l will take the pink bath.
-The Roman way.
-Yes.
Come, rest now. All will be well.
Judah, l will have you as my heir
to have at your disposal my estates,
my name.
And to go with them, Roman citizenship
and a full pardon
for all charges held against you.
What of your kin?
l have none, saving you now, Sextus Arrius.
Sextus was my son. He died many years ago
in a plague with his mother.
You do me honour to give me his name.
Then all l ask is you do not disgrace it.
No more than l would my own father's.
Then we are both well pleased, my son.
Come.
You know, l cannot rest
until l've had my revenge
upon he who killed my mother and sister.
Octavius Messala.
Emperor, my sources report
that Pontius Pilate is inept,
incompetent, and corrupt, and that Judaea,
were it administered properly,
would contribute five times the sum
you presently receive from its taxes.
Octavius Messala
would assure these revenues.
lndeed, l will guarantee them in advance,
such is my confidence in his abilities.
l was never handsome.
My mother said
l was her least favourite child.
Do me iustice but no favours,
do you understand?
Tell me, Marcellus,
is this not the same Octavius Messala
who not four years ago was sent abroad
in disgrace by Pontius Pilate
for conspicuous neglect of his duties?
A contrivance against him
so that Pilate could re-install
his own favourite.
Messala knows these Jews.
He's lived amongst them.
He speaks their language,
knows their customs. He has assured me...
l will consider it.
l could ask no more.
What's this l hear
about some gladiator you own?
Yes. My Thracian.
Sent to me by Messala.
Already he has three kills to his credit.
l shall like to see him in action.
By your decree, Emperor.
But l am having difficulty
in finding him opponents
or perhaps l should say victims.
l challenged Quintus Arrius to put
his young protg?up against him,
but he prizes him too much.
l think perhaps there is more to that matter
than meets the eye.
There usually is.
But l doubt Quintus Arrius
uses bum boys as gladiators.
Well, we must find some way
of having your prodigy
entertain us at my next gathering.
At the Emperor's command, it shall be done.
l didn't expect virginity along with virility.
But l am honoured to receive it.
You must allow me the privilege
of advancing your education.
And why would you do that?
l might teach you to pleasure me
as well as yourself.
And some day you might have a wife
who would appreciate such skills.
And it would give you the time to find out
whatever Marcellus Agrippa bid you learn.
You may tell me what you please or not.
But did not Quintus Arrius
bid you do the same?
We will not quarrel over this.
Marcellus Agrippa.
He has a son.
Octavius Messala. Do you know him?
A great hero by all accounts.
No doubt
l will have the chance to j'udge for myself.
l see l have your attention again.
This time, keep in mind
that it is not a sprint.
Look at this.
l would exchange it all
to be once more on the battlefield.
Did you not find it so, Quintus Arrius,
that war is so much simpler than life?
But one cannot make war forever.
There comes a time
when you have to put the sword down.
Especially when you can't hold it.
My dear Quintus, you look worse than l do.
Shall l send for my physician?
He has not killed me yet.
No, l have made my own arrangements.
But l thank the Emperor.
-Then what can l do?
-For me, nothing.
But l would have your approval
of my intention
to leave all l possess, including my name,
to someone of whom l have become fond.
To whom, indeed, l owe my life,
what is left of it.
This is your galley slave?
The one that Marcellus speaks of
as your catamite?
He is my companion, nothing more.
My dear Quintus,
you are at liberty to bequeath
your name, and its fame,
and all you possess to whom you choose.
Your service to Rome and its laws
grant you that.
But in Rome, the supreme law is yours.
So how is it a galley slave
saves the life of an admiral?
By the will of the gods.
lndeed, we do amuse ourselves
in the most peculiar fashion sometimes.
Very well. If that is what you wish.
But l must meet this fortunate young fellow.
Bring him to my next masque.
l am in your debt.
l may require you to acknowledge that
before you slip anchor.
l wouldn't delay your request long.
l wouldn't want to disappoint my Emperor.
-May l...
-You may.
Emperor.
l have the honour
of presenting to you my son,
Sextus Arrius.
Well, let me have a look at the paragon.
Take off your mask, Sextus.
l hear you are no mean man at arms.
l am but an apprentice at the trade, Emperor.
Well, l hope to have some evidence
of your prowess.
l would have your new-found heir
display his skills for us, Quintus Arrius.
ln what manner?
Why, by combat.
l hadn't thought
that such a display would be necessary.
Did l not say that you were in my debt,
and did you not tell me
l must make haste to have it repaid?
l am the Emperor's to command.
What of the Thracian of yours?
At the Emperor's pleasure.
Emperor, this was not my understanding.
There is no understanding but mine,
Quintus Arrius!
Replace your mask.
You do not have my permission
to show your face!
Sword against spear,
the best of all the pairings.
ls it to your satisfaction?
lf they know how to use them.
l can assure you my Thracian does.
And what about your Sextus?
Emperor, Emperor, l beg you.
Kill him.
Emperor!
lt seems you were right.
The gods amuse themselves
in a peculiar way.
Emperor. The man was mad. Emperor?
Your god, he sets his hand
against self-slaughter, does he not?
lt is hard to tell with gods
whether they care about our ways,
or whether, indeed,
they are anything but our fancies
writ large.
Well, l shall know soon enough. Or not.
For waiting for me is
maybe a sudden darkness.
Do not grieve unduly.
l have had about as much life
as one can live.
You have a long way to go, my son.
Do not spend it all in vengeance.
Do not sour it with hatred.
Maybe there are no gods.
Maybe one lives on in others.
So when you eat a grape, you think of me.
Your grief does you credit.
Who would not grieve
such a man as Quintus Arrius?
There are many dry eyes, l assure you.
Yes. Well...
Marcellus has other concerns, does he not?
Has he managed to placate the Emperor?
We are doing our best.
He's persistent, my master.
We are headed to Jerusalem
to meet his son at the games.
He means to have him installed there
as his new governor.
My condolences on your loss.
But you'll soon feel better, Sextus Arrius,
now that you have your late father's estates.
Perhaps we will meet again
in more cheerful circumstances.
At your son's investiture in Jerusalem?
What would take you
to that godforsaken place?
Jerusalem is not forsaken by God, Senator.
You're a Jew.
Well, certainly if you come
for the chariot racing,
you will meet Octavius Messala.
l will live in hope.
l will miss you, Judah.
Farewell, Quintus Arrius.
l promise you
l will not disgrace the name you gave me.
But l will have my revenge.
No matter the cost.
...and yet forgive them. Once? Seven times?
No. Not once.
Not seven times,
but 70 times seven.
We've heard it said,
''An eye for eye, a tooth for tooth.''
l say to you,
do not fight those that wish to harm you.
lf someone hits your left cheek,
offer them the right.
lf they ask for your tunic,
give them your cloak as well.
Forgive them,
for they know not what they do.
forgve them.
lf they say, ''Walk this mile with me,''
walk two miles.
As you've heard it said,
''You should love your neighbour,
and hate your enemy.''
But l say to you, love your enemies
and bless those who curse you.
Please, can you help a leper?
Step back!
You are under arrest!
Stay!
Stay there.
And what brings you
to this armpit of a country?
l've come for the games.
Come. Empty your mind
of what troubles you.
David.
-Esther.
-Leave me alone.
What's happened to you?
My sentence was life at the oars!
When does Octavus Messala arrve?
Octavius Messala will be here?
l told you your replacement was on his way.
My son has many good qualities,
but patience is not one of them.
Have some care there.
So that is your son?
Yes, of course. You have not met.
l will meet him tonight.
What was it,
the name of the family you lived with?
Who cares?
Welcome, Marcellus.
Most especially Octavius Messala.
What's this game, Judah?
This game is one that you will lose.
l should have had him crucified
as Pilate ordered!
What stopped you?
l'll challenge him to race me in the games.
Judah Ben Hur!
l mean to see the light go out in your eyes.
The race can be to the death
as easily as to the line.
These damn games were not trouble enough.
lt wll only rouse the populace,
lke ths zealot n town.
Wait until after the race and hand him over.
-Forgive him.
-l have no forgiveness in me.
And Judah Ben Hur.
That is a bitter finish line indeed.
The knot is tied and cannot be undone
but with a cut.