(SPEAKING YIDDISH)
Dora!
(DORA SPEAKING YIDDISH)
(LAUGHING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(SCREAMS)
(LAUGHING)
(ALL CONTINUE
SPEAKING YIDDISH)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
ON HEADPHONES)
(MALE TEACHER
SPEAKING HEBREW)
(TEACHER CONTINUES
(WHISPERING)
Fagle!
Huh?
(TEACHER CONTINUES
SPEAKING HEBREW)
All right.
Hold still now.
(SPEAKING HEBREW)
(ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES
PLAYING ON HEADPHONES)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING LOUDLY
ON SPEAKER)
(SHOUTING IN HEBREW)
(STUDENTS CLAMORING)
Mmm-hmm. Yes.
Well...
Oh, sorry.
No, thanks.
Well, you're
in good health.
So how's Judith
and the kids?
Good. Everyone's good,
you know.
Danny must be, what?
About to be bar mitzvahed?
Two weeks.
Well, mazel tov!
They grow up fast,
don't they?
Hmm...
(EXCLAIMING)
Yeah, you put the...
(SPEAKING HEBREW)
(SIGHING)
That's right, you put the...
(SPEAKING HEBREW)
(SIGHS)
(DOOR OPENING)
(CUP RATTLING)
(COUGHS)
LARRY: You following this?
Okay?
So...
This part is exciting.
So, am I right?
So, okay. So...
So, if that's that,
then we can do this.
And that's
Schrodinger's Paradox,
right?
Is the cat dead?
Or is the cat
not dead?
Messages,
Professor Gopnik.
Thank you, Natalie.
Oh, Clive, come in.
So, what can I do for you?
CLIVE: (HEAVILY ACCENTED)
Dr. Gopnik, I believe
the results
of the physics midterm
were unjust.
Uh-huh? How so?
I received
unsatisfactory grade.
In fact, F,
the failing grade.
Yes. You failed the midterm.
That's accurate.
Yes, but that is not just.
I was unaware
to be examined
on the mathematics.
Well, you can't do
physics without mathematics,
really, can you?
If I receive
the failing grade,
I lose my scholarship,
and I feel shame.
I understand the physics.
I understand the dead cat.
But you can't really
understand the physics
without understanding
the math.
The math tells
how it really works.
That's the real thing.
The stories
I give you in class
are just illustrative.
They're like fables, say,
to help give you a picture.
I mean...
Even I don't understand
the dead cat.
The math is how
it really works.
Very difficult.
Well, I'm sorry, but I...
What do you propose?
Passing grade.
No, no.
Or perhaps I can
take the midterm again.
I know now it cover
the mathematics.
Well, the other students
wouldn't like that,
would they?
If one student gets to
retake the test until
he gets a grade he likes?
Secret test.
No...
Hush-hush.
No.
That's just not workable.
I'm afraid we'll just
have to bite the bullet
on this thing, Clive...
Very troubling.
ON PHONE:
Sy Ableman:
Hello, Sy.
Larry Gopnik.
Larry: How are you,
my friend?
Good. How you been, Sy?
Fine: Can
we talk, Larry?
What? You...
Uh...
Hello? Larry?
Call back!
Clive!
(PHONE RINGING)
That was Sy Ableman.
He said he
got disconnected.
ARTHUR: Out in a minute.
I gotta wash my hair.
I'm going out tonight.
ARTHUR:
I'll be out in a minute.
Jesus Christ!
Why is Uncle Arthur
always in the bathroom?
He has to drain
his sebaceous cyst.
You know that.
Will you set the table?
Why can't he do it
in the basement
or out in the garage?
I had 20 bucks in it,
too. Inside the case.
Twenty bucks?
How come?
Bought a lid
from Mike Fagle
a couple of weeks ago.
Still owed him 20.
He already
gave you the pot?
Yeah. But a couple
of weeks ago,
my funding got cut off.
Fagle said he'd pound
the crap out of me
if I didn't pay up.
What funding got
cut off? Where do
you get your money?
What happened?
Rabbi Turchik
took his radio.
Had money in it.
That fucker!
Yeah. I think he said
he was confiscating it.
He's a fucker.
Where do you
get your money?
Mike Fagle's
gonna kick his ass.
Last week
he pounded the crap
out of Seth Seddlemeyer.
He's a fucker!
Fagle or Seth Seddlemeyer?
They're both fuckers!
ARTHUR: Out in a minute!
Are you still in there?
ARTHUR: Yeah,
I'll be out in a minute!
Arthur!
ARTHUR: Yeah?
Dinner!
ARTHUR: Okay,
out in a minute!
We should wait.
Are you kidding?
Mr. Brandt keeps mowing
part of our lawn.
Does that matter?
What?
JUDITH: Is it important?
It's just odd.
Mom, how long
is Uncle Arthur
staying with us?
JUDITH: Ask your father.
Honey.
Did you talk to Sy?
Sy?
Sy Ableman.
That's right, he called.
But I...
You didn't talk to him?
No.
You know the problems
that you and I
have been having?
Mmm-hmm.
Well, Sy and I
have become very close.
In short, I think
it's time that we start
talking about a divorce.
Sy Ableman?
This is not about Sy.
You mentioned Sy!
Don't twist my words,
Larry.
A divorce?
What have I done?
I haven't done anything.
Larry, don't be a child.
You haven't done anything.
I haven't done anything.
Yes! Yes, we haven't
done anything.
And I'm probably
about to get tenure.
Nevertheless, there
have been problems,
as you know...
Well...
...and things
have changed.
And then, Sy Ableman.
Sy has come into
my life, and I...
Come into your...
What does that mean?
You barely know him.
Oh, please. We've
known the Ablemans
for 15 years, Larry!
Yes, but you said
we hadn't done anything.
I haven't done anything.
This is not some
flashy fling, Larry.
This is not about
woopsy-doopsy.
Sy Ableman?
ARTHUR:
I'll be out in a minute!
SARAH: Oh, Jesus Christ!
Look, I didn't know
any other way of
breaking it to you
except to just
tell you and treat you
like an adult.
Is that so wrong?
Where do I sleep?
What?
Arthur's on the couch.
Look, Sy feels
that we should...
Esther is barely cold!
Esther died
three years ago,
and it was
a loveless marriage.
Sy wants a gett:
A what?
A ritual divorce.
He says it's very important.
Without a gett,
I'm an aguna:
A what?
What are you
talking about?
You always act
so surprised.
I have begged you
to see the Rabbi.
(DOOR OPENING)
(PANTING)
Messages,
Professor Gopnik.
Yes, thanks for
coming, Clive.
Have a seat.
We had, I think,
a good talk
the other day,
but you left something...
I didn't leave it.
Well, you don't even know
what I was going to say.
I didn't leave anything.
I'm not missing anything.
I know where everything is.
Well then, Clive...
Where did this come from?
This is here, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
That is there.
This is not nothing.
This is something.
Yes. That is something.
What is it?
You know what it is,
I believe.
And you know
I can't keep it, Clive.
Yes, sir.
I'll have to pass it on
to Professor Finkle,
along with my suspicions
about where it came from.
Actions have consequences.
Yes. Often.
No, always!
Actions always
have consequences!
In this office,
actions have
consequences.
Yes, sir.
Not just physics,
morally.
Yes.
And we both know
about your actions.
No, sir.
I know about my actions.
I can interpret, Clive.
I know what you
meant me to understand.
Meer sir my sir.
"Meer sir my sir"?
Mere surmise, sir.
Very uncertain.
(MAN CHANTING IN HEBREW)
(RECORD STOPS)
(REPEATING IN HEBREW)
(CHANTING RESUMES)
(RECORD STOPS)
(REPEATING IN HEBREW)
You little brat fucker!
You snuck 20 bucks
out of my drawer!
Studying Torah,
asshole.
You little brat!
I'm telling Dad!
You gonna tell him
you've been sneaking it
out of his wallet?
You know what I'm gonna do,
you little brat,
if you don't give it back?
Dad?
DANNY: Dad, you've
gotta fix the aerial.
Hello, Larry.
Have you thought
about a lawyer?
DANNY: Dad!
Honey, please!
We're not getting
channel four at all.
Can we
discuss it later?
I can't get F Troop:
Larry, the
children know.
Do you think
this is some secret?
Do you think this is
something we're going
to keep quiet?
Dad, Uncle Arthur is
in the bathroom again,
and I'm going
to the Hole at 8:00.
ARTHUR: Out in a minute!
Ow! Stop!
She keeps doing that!
What's going on?
(MAN SINGING IN YIDDISH
ON RADIO)
Arthur?
ARTHUR: Yes?
What are you doing?
Working on the Mentaculus.
Any luck, um,
looking for an apartment?
No.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Sy.
Good to see you, Larry.
I'll get Judith.
No, listen, actually,
I'm here to see you,
if I might.
Such a thing.
Shall we go
in the kitchen?
You know, Larry, the way
we handle ourselves
in this situation,
so important.
Uh-huh?
Absolutely.
Judith told me
that she broke
the news to you,
and she said that
you were very adult.
Did she?
Absolutely.
The respect she has
for you...
Yes?
Do you drink wine?
Because this is
an incredible bottle.
This is not
Mogen David, Larry.
(CHUCKLING)
This is a wine.
A Bordeaux.
You know, Sy...
Open it.
Let it breathe.
Ten minutes.
Letting it breathe,
so important.
Thanks, Sy,
but I'm not...
Listen, I insist, Larry.
There's no cause
for discomfort.
I'd be uncomfortable
if you didn't take it.
Larry, listen.
These are signs.
Tokens, Larry.
I'm just...
I'm not ungrateful.
I just don't know
a lot about wine,
and given our...
It's okay.
...respective...
Larry, we're
going to be fine.
(BUS DEPARTING)
Want some of this,
fucker?
(DRAWER OPENS)
(EXCLAIMS)
Fuck.
(FAGLE PANTING)
(CHATTER ON RADIO)
(MAN SINGING IN YIDDISH)
Would you read this?
Tell me what you think?
Okay.
Boy! You should have
worn a hat.
(SNORING)
MR. BRANDT: Let's see
some hustle, Mitch.
ARLEN: Larry?
Hi, Arlen.
Larry, I feel that as
head of the tenure committee,
I should tell you this.
Though it should be
no cause for concern, and you
should not at all be worried.
Okay.
But I feel
I should mention it,
even though
it will carry no weight
in our decision
on whether or not
to grant you tenure.
So again,
no cause for concern.
Okay, Arlen.
Give what any weight?
Well...
We've received
a number of letters
denigrating you
and urging us not to...
Not to grant you tenure.
From who?
Well, they're anonymous,
so we dismiss them completely.
Well, what do they say?
Well, they
make allegations...
Well, allegations...
Assertions.
And though we
give them no credence
at all, Larry.
Well, I'm not really
at liberty
to discuss the specifics of
the committee's deliberations.
But I think you're saying
these won't play any part
in your deliberations?
None whatsoever.
So what are they?
Moral turpitude,
you could say.
Uh-huh.
Can I ask?
Are they...
Are they idiomatic?
Hmm?
The reason I ask,
I have a Korean student.
South Korean.
A disgruntled South Korean,
and I meant to talk to you
about this...
Oh, no, no.
They're competently,
even eloquently written.
A native English speaker.
There's no question
about that.
Uh-huh.
Let me reiterate.
别放在心上
我只是觉得不该瞒着你
对 没错
向Judith问声好
我得拿回我的收音机
也许那混蛋把它寄存在了屁眼里
我得拿回来
否则Mike Fagle会揍扁我的
一路往上
下午好
去洗手 Mitch
去打猎了?
那是要...
要做成一个船棚
是吗
好极了
- Brandt先生...
- 我说去洗手 Mitch!
今天不上学吗?
我去学校接他出来跟我去打猎的
呃 Brandt先生
那里差不多是地界线
我觉得我们不该--
- 在超过10英尺...
- 地界线是那棵杨树
那棵...杨树
- 即使那里 你也超过了
- 你去量
- 我不必量 你可以看出来...
- 分界线是杨树
怎么回事?
没什么
Larry?
什么事?
你去找Sieglestein Schlutz了吗?
没有 我...还没去
Larry
约的是星期一
你去哪里?
我要去Hole
什么? 现在才5点?
我们要在Laurie Kipperstein家停一下
我可以洗个头
你好 Gopnik先生
- 你不能在这里洗?
- Arthur叔叔在浴室里
我马上出来!
- 你准备好了吗?
- 嗯?
- 我们要去Embers见Sy
- 我也去?
我们一起去 我告诉过你 Larry
Larry
你好吗?
Sy
你好 Judith
你好 Sy
Larry 我要感谢你过来
我们能讨论这些事非常重要
我很高兴来Embers Sy
但我想 也许最好把讨论留给律师
当然 法律问题就让律师去解决吧
橘子苹果不能混为一谈
我求你去见律师
我说我星期一去
星期一来得及 这不是...
Embers不是法律事务论坛 你说得没错
Judith和我只是想讨论 呃
实际事务 住房安排
毕竟大家对此都没有异议
住房安排?
我想我们都同意孩子们
不该受紧张关系的毒害
这一点至关重要
我们不该让孩子受影响 Larry
孩子没有...
我说的是"我们" 不是指代谁
没有人要指责谁 Larry
我没这么说
也不要影射其他人
- 我没有! 我...
- 好吧 听我说
我们退后一步讲 化解这个情况
你知道 Larry 有时候我觉得
如果我数到10...
4...
或者默念
说真的 为了把事情安排妥当
迎接Danny的成人礼
孩子的成人礼 Larry
我和Sy认为 你最好搬走
搬走?
- 这显然很有道理
- 生活可以继续...
搬走? 搬去哪里?
比如说 "海盗旗"就很合适
价钱也不贵
房间非常适宜居住
也方便你来探访孩子
那里提供便利设备 还有个泳池
你搬去跟Sy住不是更合理吗?
Larry
Larry 你...你在开玩笑
我真的认为搬去"海盗旗"
是最适当的做法
听着
你个小混蛋 把钱还我!
别打了! 我会拿到的!
还给我!
你欠我20美元 屎球!
- 放心!
- 给我 讨厌鬼!
- 我会拿到的!我会拿到的!
- 讨!厌!鬼!
- 怎么回事?
- 没什么
- 什么情况?
"律法"的进度如何?
你能用音响放吗?
什么? 我能借一下这个吗?
我要带些东西去"海盗旗"
- 爸!
- 没问题 爸
爸! 有个中国人!
文化碰撞
恕我直言 Park先生
我觉得不是这个问题
- 是
- 不是
如果在你们国家 买学分是惯例
那才叫文化碰撞
是
你是说那是惯例?
不 这是中伤 我要告你
我说白一点
你威胁要告我中伤你儿子?
是
- 但是...
- 这人找你茬吗?
他找我茬? 没有
我 呃...
你看...
如果是中伤 必须有个人
听我说中伤他的话 否则我...
好吧 简单讲
我可以假装没有钱这回事
那就没有中伤任何人
对 然后给他及格
- 给他及格?
- 是
否则你要告我?
告你收受贿款
所以他是留了钱?
这是中伤!
这没道理 他要么留了钱 要么没留
请接受这个谜案
给我 混蛋
他很擅长数字
我想是他的社交技能阻碍了他
不过他真是个好人
Arthur有一颗善心
他从不抱怨 不像我
有时候我没有给他足够的赞赏
他想告诉我他在忙的东西 叫...
Mentaculus
他说那可能是宇宙的地图
他出去社交吗?
他在努力
打算去希勒尔旅馆的单身聚会
其实我也没好到哪里去
Judith怎么样?
很好 她很好
有时候这些事不该发生的
你需要时间感受真相
反正我从来没有感受到!
简直是晴天霹雳
什么意思?
一切都不是我原本想的那样
这就是你认识真相的机会
我不想信口说教
解读上帝的旨意并不容易
但你不必自己一个人扛着
我们是犹太人
我们利用优良传统帮我们理解
当我们有疑问时
有过相同问题的前人
早把亲身经验传给了后人
你跟Nachtner拉比谈过吗?
怎么不见见他?
拉比能告诉我什么?
如果我知道 我也去当拉比了
这里的空气真清新
我说 如果有人把这空气装瓶
他们能赚上一百万
第一个拉比
你好 Larry 见到你真好
哦 Scott拉比
我以为我约的是Nachtner拉比
他被人叫去主持etz monim了
Ruth Brynn的母亲住院了
情况不太好
Nachtner拉比叫我来代班 进来吧
她想要一个gett
一个什么?
- 她想要...
- 哦 gett
嗯 当然
我感觉像地毯从我身下抽走
我不知道那端朝上
我甚至不知道怎么回应
脑子里一团乱麻
她要离婚的理由是什么?
她没有理由 只是说--
事情不是很顺利
是这样吗?
我想 我不知道
她在这些事上比较在行
我本希望Nachtner拉比能...
他...他能...什么?
以他丰富的人生经验
无意冒犯
当然不会 我是初级拉比
没错 长辈也许有过相同经历
他们的意见会更有帮助
你该去见见资深拉比
甚至Marshak
如果能约到的话
他很忙 但也许...
我能跟你说个事吗?
因为我也有过失去Hashem的感觉
你的问题就在此
我也忘了如何见到他
发生这种事时 你会想
"如果我见不到他 那他就不存在
他消失了"
但不是这样的
你只要记得如何见到他
我说得对吗? 我是说...
这里的停车场
虽然不大
但你若想象自己是个游客
并不熟悉这些汽车之类的东西
还保留着感到惊奇的能力
拥有一个全新的视角
就是它 Larry
因为有了正确的视角
你就能见到Hashem向人们伸出援手
他就在我们中间 而不仅仅在教堂里
听起来你看世界 看你妻子的视角
已经疲倦了
好像她变成了一样东西...
一个问题
一样东西
她跟Sy Ableman好了
- 哦
- 他们计划...
所以他们才要gett
哦 对不起
这是他的主意
他们确实需要gett才能再婚
但是...这就是生活
你得把这些事看成是上帝的旨意
当然你不必喜欢它
老大不总是对的 但他终归是老大
没错!
情况还不算太糟
瞧瞧这停车场 Larry
只要看看停车场
现在就开始吃了?
Sarah要出门
哦! 少来!
怎么回事?
爸不吃吗?
他在"海盗船"
哦 对了
你怎么样 Larry?
上帝 真遗憾
- 你遇上这档子事
- 还好...
我一直以为你和Judy会白头到老
这事太糟了 Larry 叫人震惊
你知道 我的看法是
这是让我静下来思考的好机会
我能重新认识世界 你知道
而不是循规蹈矩 以旧眼光看问题
是吗?
我不知道 也许不是
法律上我要警告你
作为丈夫向来要吃亏的
除非 妻子存在违背婚约的问题?
哦 没有 不是这样的
不过她打算嫁给Sy Ableman 但他们...
Sy Ableman!
- 对 但他们...
- Esther尸骨未寒!
她死了三年了
但这还是改变了局面 Larry
Sy Ableman
并不是...他们没有奸情
据我所知
- 哦
- 对 我敢肯定没有这回事
事实上Judith想要一个gett
一个什么?
离婚仪式
这样他们才能自由再婚
啊 没错 当然 呃...
不算什么法律问题
好吧 呃...
行 行
那么...
另外一件事 邻居的地界线
我叫Solomon Schlutz去看了
房产方面的事交给他就放心吧
好的 你们怎么...
我想我有点担心
你们怎么...我手头比较紧张
我们的收费情况? 按小时计算
Dave Sieglestein和Solomon Schlutz
每小时110
律师助理 比如我 收费是...
Gopnik先生的电话 Danny从家里打来的
你可以在这里接
Danny?
- 喂 爸爸
- 你没事吧?
你没...一切都还...
"F战队"看不清
什么?
"F战队"还是看不清
爸? 你还好吧?
Clive?
Clive!
你个小混蛋! 下次要叫你妈来吗?
小混蛋! 我要找你!
稍等
Gopnik教授 又是Dick Dutton
Dick Dutton
你好?
你好 Gopnik先生?
我是哥伦比亚唱片俱乐部的Dick Dutton
我打来是因为已经过去四个月
我们还在等你支付第一笔款
你们搞错了
我不是哥伦比亚唱片俱乐部的会员
先生 你是Fern Hill路8419号的
Lawrence Gopnik吗?
不 我住在"海盗船"
你说什么?
不是 我...
好吧 是的
- 你是Lawrence Gopnik?
- 好吧
"好吧"的意思是
好吧 我是Lawrence Gopnik 是的
你收到了12张介绍性专辑
四个月来一直在接收每月主选集
每月主选集? 那是唱片吗?
我没有索要唱片
每月主选集是免费的 你...
That's right.
I haven't done anything.
Yes, that's why
you received the
monthly main selection:
(STAMMERING) But...
The last one was
Santana Abraxas. You: : :
I didn't ask
for Santana Abraxas:
You request
the main selection
at the retail price
by doing nothing:
It's automatically
mailed to you,
plus shipping
and handling:
You're about to receive: : :
I can't afford
a new record every month!
I haven't asked...
You're about to get
Cosmo's Factory, sir:
The June
main selection:
Look, look,
something is very wrong!
I don't want
Santana Abraxas:
I've just been
in a terrible auto accident.
I'm sorry, sir:
Well, thank you.
But I...
Are you okay?
Yes, yes.
No one was hurt.
Okay: Good:
Well, you had
14 days to listen
to Santana Abraxas.
Sir?
Look...
(STAMMERING) I didn't ask
for Santana Abraxas,
I didn't listen
to Santana Abraxas,
I didn't do anything!
Sir! Your son.
Mr: Gopnik: : :
He says it's urgent.
We can't make you
listen to the record: : :
Okay, okay, okay...
We provide: : :
Okay, I have to
call you back.
This is... I'm sorry.
No, no,
Mr: Gopnik, please: : :
Danny?
DANNY: Yeah: Listen, Dad: : :
Did you join
the Columbia Record Club?
Danny?
Um: : :
Danny, this is
completely unacceptable.
I can't afford to...
Okay, Dad, but you
gotta come home:
Is it F Troop?
No, Mom's real upset:
(JUDITH SOBBING)
SARAH: Dad?
Yes?
Does this mean
I can't go
to the Hole tonight?
Does what mean?
What happened?
Oh, Sy Ableman,
he died in a car crash.
DANNY: Hey, Dad.
What?
So you're coming back home?
Can you fix
the aerial?
What?
It's still,
you know...
(JUDITH WAILING)
(JUDITH SCREAMING)
She seems to be
asking an awful lot.
But then...
I don't know.
Somebody has to pay
for Sy's funeral.
Uh-huh.
His own estate
is in probate,
but why does it
have to be me?
Or is it wrong
to complain?
Judy says it is.
But I'm so strapped
for cash right now,
carrying the mortgage,
and paying
for the Jolly Roger,
and I wrecked the car,
and Danny's bar mitzvah
coming up, I...
Something like this,
there's never a good time.
I don't know
where it all leaves me.
Sy's death.
Obviously, it's not
going to go back
like it was.
Mmm.
Would you even
want that, Larry?
No, I...
Well, yeah.
Sometimes.
Or...
I don't know.
I guess
the honest answer is,
I don't know.
What was my life before?
Not what I thought it was.
So what does it all mean?
What is Hashem
trying to tell me,
making me pay for
Sy Ableman's funeral?
Mmm.
And did I tell you
I had a car accident
the same time Sy had his?
The same instant,
for all I know.
Mmm.
Is Hashem trying
to tell me that
Sy Ableman is me?
Or that we are all one
or something?
How does God speak to us?
It's a good question.
You know Lee Sussman.
Dr. Sussman?
I think I... Yeah.
Did he ever tell you
about the goy's teeth?
No. Uh, what goy?
So, Lee is at work one day.
You know, he has
the orthodontic practice
there at Great Bear:
He's making a plaster mold:
It's for corrective
bridgework in the mouth
of one of his patients,
Russell Krauss.
The mold dries, and Lee
is examining it one day
before fabricating
an appliance:
He notices
something unusual:
There appears to be
something engraved
on the inside
of the patient's
lower incisors:
Hey vav shin yud ayin nun yud.
Ho-she-ay-ni.
"Help me: Save me:"
This, in a goy's mouth, Larry.
He calls the goy back
on the pretense of needing
additional measurements
for the appliance:
"How are you?
"Noticed any other
problems with your teeth?"
"No:"
There it is:
Ho-she-ay-ni.
"Help me:"
Son of a gun:
Sussman goes home:
Can Sussman eat?
Sussman can't eat:
Can Sussman sleep?
Sussman can't sleep:
Sussman looks at the molds
of his other patients,
goy and Jew alike,
seeking other messages:
He finds none:
He looks in his own mouth:
Nothing:
He looks
in his wife's mouth:
Nothing:
But Sussman
is an educated man.
Not the world's
greatest sage, maybe.
No Rabbi Marshak.
But he knows
a thing or two about
the Zohar and the Kabbalah:
He knows that
every Hebrew letter
has its numeric equivalent:
8-4-5-4-4-7-3:
Seven digits:
A phone number, maybe?
"Hello? Do you know
a goy named Krauss,
Russell Krauss?"
"Who?"
"Where have I called?
"The Red Owl in Bloomington?
Thanks so much:"
He goes:
It's a Red Owl:
Groceries, what have you:
Sussman goes home:
What does it mean?
He has to find out
if he is ever
to sleep again:
He goes to see
the Rabbi Nachtner.
He comes in, he sits
right where you're
sitting, right now:
"What does it mean, Rabbi?
(INAUDIBLE)
"Is it a sign
from Hashem? 'Help me: '
"I, Sussman, should be
doing something
to help this goy.
"Doing what?
The teeth don't say:
"Or maybe I'm supposed to
help people generally
lead a more righteous life?
"Is the answer
in Kabbalah? In Torah?
"Or is there even a question?
"Tell me, Rabbi,
what can such a sign
"mean?"
So? What did
you tell him?
Sussman?
Yes.
Is it relevant?
Well, isn't that why
you're telling me?
Okay.
Nachtner says, "Look.
"The teeth, we don't know.
"A sign from Hashem?
Don't know.
"Helping others?
"Couldn't hurt."
No, no,
but who put it there?
Was it for him, Sussman?
Or for whoever found it?
Or for just... For, for...
We can't know everything.
It sounds like
you don't know
anything!
Why even tell me the story?
(CHUCKLING)
First I should tell you,
then I shouldn't.
What happened to Sussman?
What would happen?
Not much.
He went back to work:
For a while, he checked
every patient's teeth
for new messages:
He didn't find any:
In time, he found
he stopped checking:
He returned to life:
These questions that are
bothering you, Larry,
maybe they're
like a toothache.
Feel them for a while,
then they go away.
I don't want it
to just go away!
I want an answer!
Sure. We all
want the answer.
Hashem doesn't owe us
the answer, Larry.
Hashem doesn't
owe us anything.
The obligation
runs the other way.
Why does he make us
feel the questions
if he's not going to
give us any answers?
He hasn't told me.
And what happened
to the goy?
The goy?
Who cares?
NACHTNER: Sy Ableman
was a serious man.
Sy Ableman was a man
devoted to his community.
To Torah study.
To his beloved wife,
Esther,
until three years ago
she passed,
and to his duty,
as he saw it.
Where does such a man go?
A tzadik: Who knows,
maybe even a lamed vavnik:
A man beloved by all.
A man who despised
the frivolous.
Could such
a serious man simply
disappear?
We speak of olam ha-ba,
the world to come.
(SOBBING)
Not heaven.
Not what the gentiles
think of as afterlife.
"Olam ha-ba:"
What is olam ha-ba?
Where is olam ha-ba?
Well, it is not
a geographic place,
certainly.
Like Canada.
Nor is it the
Eretz zavat chalav udvash,
the land flowing
with milk and honey.
For we are not promised
a personal reward.
A gold star.
A first-class VIP lounge
where we get milk
and cookies to eternity.
(MOURNERS LAUGHING)
Olam ha-ba is
in the bosom of Abraham.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Arthur Gopnik?
Are you
I'm Lawrence Gopnik.
Do you go by the name
Arthur Gopnik?
No.
Is that Arthur Gopnik?
Can you tell me
what's going on?
We're sitting shiva here.
You're what?
A religious observance.
We're bereaved.
Who died?
My wife's, uh...
(WOMAN SOBBING)
It's a long story.
Look, you tell Gopnik,
Arthur Gopnik,
he's breaking the law.
We're not arresting
him now, but
next time we will.
Gambling's against
the law in this state.
That's just the way it is.
All right.
Go back to your thing.
Sorry, sir.
Dad, we get
channel four now,
but not channel seven.
Arthur, how could you
do that to this family?
On Sy's...
It's hardly a crime.
I mean, nobody got hurt.
That doesn't
make it right!
He won
a lot of money, Dad.
The Mentaculus
really works!
You knew about it?
Well...
They must have
finked me out.
They knew I could
just go on winning,
so they blackballed me
and now...
What did you do
with the money
you won?
What's going on?
Well, I didn't want it,
and Danny said
that he could use it...
That is so unfair!
LARRY: What are you...
I'll tell you what's unfair.
What's unfair is them
not letting me play
in their card game.
Why give him the
money? You know what
he spends it on?
I know about
the records.
Records? Do you
think he buys records
from Mike Fagle?
At least
I'm not saving up
for a nose job.
What a brat!
LARRY: What?
Nobody in this house
is getting a nose job!
You got that?
(FANFARE PLAYING ON TV)
(EXCLAIMING)
Danny! You're
not excused!
We're still talking!
What was this
card game, Arthur?
Some goys put together
a private game.
I think that
they're Italian.
Danny!
What's going on?
Danny? We're
sitting shiva here.
(MEN CHATTERING ON TV)
Well, she has retained
Barney Silver
at Tuchman, Marsh.
This is a...
This is an
aggressive firm, Larry.
Mmm-hmm.
These are not
pleasant people.
Judith is free to
retain whoever she...
I take it
you don't talk?
It's hard. I think she
emptied our bank account.
Mmm.
I tried to ask her about it,
very civilly. She...
Yeah.
Yeah, you need to
open a new account
in your name only.
Put your paychecks
in there from
here on out.
Can I?
Oh, absolutely.
It's not dishonest?
You...
I hate to say this,
but I think she's also
been sneaking cash
out of my wallet.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy.
Yeah, well, this is
definitely adversarial.
(CRYING)
Larry? Are you
all right? Larry!
Hey, come on now!
Larry! There's
no need for that.
Larry, Larry, we...
We're going to
get through this.
Have you talked
to the Rabbi?
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
I talked to Nachtner.
Was he helpful
at all?
What, did he tell you
about the goy's teeth?
You should try to
talk to Marshak.
They told me
he doesn't do
pastoral work anymore.
He just...
(INHALING)
...congratulates the
bar mitzvah boy every week.
Well, that's too bad.
He's a very wise man,
Marshak.
Getting old.
Very old.
No, me.
Uh, Dick Dutton.
Columbia Record Club.
Not now.
Does he ever
come to the phone?
If I came in, could...
Well, how about
at Rabbi Marshak's
convenience?
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Well, could I give you
my number at the Jolly Roger?
LARRY: X squared,
so that delta X equals
the square root of
.077 A squared minus zero,
from which we derive
the square root of
.077 A squared.
And also, the uncertainty
in P is equal to
the square root
of bracket P squared
minus bracket P squared,
which also equals
the square root
of H over A squared.
Which lets us
delta X, delta P
equals the square root
of.077 A squared,
H over A squared,
and 1.74 H bar.
Okay?
The Uncertainty Principle.
It proves we can't
ever really know
what's going on.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
But even though you can't
figure anything out,
you will be responsible
for it on the mid-term.
Did you follow that?
Of course.
Except that I know
what's going on.
How do you explain?
Well, it might be that in,
you know, in olam ha-ba: : :
Excuse me, not the point.
In this world, Larry.
Now I'll concede that
it's subtle, it's clever.
But at the end of the day,
is it convincing?
Well, yes,
it's convincing.
It's a proof.
It's mathematics.
No, excuse me.
Mathematics is the art
of the possible.
I don't think so.
The art of the
possible, that's...
I can't remember.
Something else.
I'm a serious man, Larry.
I know that. So, if I've
got it wrong, what do I...
So simple.
See Marshak.
I know!
I want to see Marshak!
I fucked your wife, Larry!
I seriously fucked her!
That's what's going on!
(SHOUTING)
See Marshak!
(GASPS)
(WHIRRING)
Mr. Gopnik.
Hello, Mrs. Samsky.
I was going to knock,
and then I thought
you weren't here.
I thought
I heard something.
Can I help you?
Do you want to come in?
No, I...
It's cooler.
Oh. Okay.
I've noticed that
Mr. Samsky isn't around,
and I, uh...
He travels.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
So I thought I should
let you know, since you're
somewhat new here,
if you ever have,
whatever, chores
that you'd, um...
Or just help with something.
I've decided to help others,
in a neighborly way.
How thoughtful.
Oh, it's nothing.
It's just good to
know your neighbors,
and to help.
Help others.
Although I don't care much
for my neighbors on the
other side, I must say.
Goys, aren't they?
Mmm. Very much so.
Although maybe it's
not fair to judge.
I have to admit...
Won't you sit down?
Oh, um...
Okay. Thank you.
Iced tea?
I have some.
Okay.
I don't see you
much around either.
Yes, actually
I haven't been home
a lot recently. I, uh...
My wife and I are...
Well, she's got me
staying at the Jolly Roger,
the little motel there on...
You're in the
doghouse, huh?
Yes. That's an
understatement,
I guess. Thank you.
I guess I...
Do you take advantage
of the new freedoms?
What do you mean?
It's something I do.
For recreation.
That's
marijuana?
Mmm-hmm.
You'll find you'll
need the iced tea.
Is it...
Well, okay.
(RECORD SKIPPING)
Maybe Rabbi Scott was right.
Who's Rabbi Scott?
The junior rabbi.
What did he say?
LARRY: He spoke of
perception.
All my problems
are just...
Just a...
A mere...
Is that a siren?
No.
Sometimes people
get paranoid...
(SIREN BLARING)
Holy cow, that is a siren.
Hey!
POLICEMAN:
Does this man live here?
Sort of. He sleeps
on the couch.
This is crazy!
I didn't know what to
tell them. They asked
me for my address.
It's just mathematics.
You can't arrest a man
for mathematics.
I didn't know whether
to tell them here,
or at the Jolly Roger.
Do you know this man?
I just figured that
this would sound better.
I don't know.
Dad, why is Uncle Arthur
in handcuffs?
It's all a mistake.
I mean, not a mistake,
a miscarriage...
Hello, Mrs. Samsky.
Hello, Arthur.
Does this man
live here?
He sleeps on the couch.
Look. What did he do?
Nothing! I didn't
do anything!
DANNY: Dad sleeps on a cot.
Sir, we picked
this man up
at the North Dakota.
But I didn't do anything!
I didn't...
The North Dakota?
Solicitation.
Sodomy.
Very serious.
But I didn't
do anything.
"Sodomy"?
What's sodomy,
Dad?
What does Arthur say?
He says he didn't
do anything.
Uh-huh.
He says he just
went in for a drink.
Uh-huh.
Does Arthur drink?
No.
Uh-huh.
The North Dakota.
Well...
You'll need
a criminal attorney.
Okay. Who's...
Ron Meshbesher.
Is he good?
Ron is very good.
I don't understand.
He goes to mixers
at the Hillel House.
Mmm.
I would call
Ron Meshbesher.
Is he expensive?
Ron is not cheap.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Yeah.
Oh, Sol, come in,
we could use
some good news.
DON: Sol's been going over
the property line issue
and he wouldn't
go into details,
but he seems to think
there's a nifty way
out of this.
Says it was pure luck
that he caught something.
I guess that's why
you're full partner,
eh, Sol?
(DON CHUCKLES)
Danny's bar mitzvah is...
This week.
DON: This Shabbas?
Great, great.
(GROANING)
Professor Gopnik,
Dick Dutton.
Heart attack.
Call back.
(UNLOCKS DRAWER)
Larry?
As you know,
the tenure committee
meets on... What?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry. I know
you've hit a rough patch.
Someone just...
But I'm fine.
Well, as you know,
the tenure committee
meets on Wednesday
to make its final
determinations, so if...
Arlen,
I am not an evil man.
No, no, Larry, no,
of course not.
I am not!
No, we don't make
moral judgments.
I went to the
Aster Art once.
I saw Swedish Reverie:
No, it's okay.
We don't need to know.
It wasn't even erotic.
Although it was,
in a way.
It's all right, really,
Larry. Believe me.
Yeah, okay.
Okay. Okay.
So, we decide
on Wednesday.
So, if there's anything
that you want to
submit in support of
your tenure application,
we would need it
by Wednesday.
Submit? What do you...
Well, anything.
Any published work.
Anything you've done
outside the institution.
Anything at all that
we should be aware of.
I haven't done anything.
Uh-huh.
I haven't published.
You're still
getting those...
Uh-huh.
Those anonymous...
No, no, I know.
Yeah. Uh-huh. Yeah.
Okay. Okay. Wednesday?
Uh-huh.
Um. Okay. Uh...
Don't worry.
Doing nothing is
not bad. Ipso facto:
Just relax.
Try to relax.
Oh, my God,
Mrs. Samsky!
So good.
(LARRY PANTING)
(EXCLAIMS)
Nailing it down.
So important.
(LARRY SCREAMS)
LARRY: Please. I need help.
I've already talked to
the other rabbis. Please.
It's not about
Danny's bar mitzvah:
My boy, Danny.
This coming Shabbas:
Very joyous event.
That's all fine.
It's more about myself.
I've had quite a bit
of tsuris lately.
Marital problems,
professional,
you name it.
This is not
a frivolous request.
This is a...
I'm a...
I've tried to be
a serious man,
you know?
Tried to do right,
be a member of the
community, raise the...
Danny, Sarah, they both
go to school, Hebrew school.
A good breakfast...
Well, Danny goes
to Hebrew school,
Sarah doesn't have time.
She mostly
washes her hair.
Apparently there are
several steps involved,
but you don't have
to tell Marshak that,
just tell him I need help.
Please. I need help.
(SIGHS)
The Rabbi is busy.
He didn't look busy.
He's thinking.
(ARTHUR SOBBING)
Arthur?
What's wrong?
It'll be okay.
Arthur, we'II...
Don't worry, we'll
get Ron Meshbesher.
It'll be okay...
(WAILING LOUDLY)
Arthur!
(WAILING)
Arthur! You've got
to pull yourself
together!
It's all shit, Larry!
It's all shit!
Arthur,
don't use that word.
It's just fucking shit!
Arthur.
Look at all that
Hashem has given you!
What has he given me?
He hasn't given me shit!
Arthur. What do I have?
I live at the Jolly Roger.
You have a family!
You have a job!
Hashem hasn't given me shit.
He hasn't given me bupkes!
It's not fair to blame
Hashem, Arthur. Please.
Sometimes...
Please calm down.
Sometimes you
have to help yourself.
Hashem hasn't given me shit.
Now I can't even
play cards.
It's okay,
it's okay.
(SOBBING LOUDLY)
It's okay,
it's okay.
Is this it?
ARTHUR: Yeah, I think.
Yeah, there.
Look, this should
help you get back
on your feet.
Oh, my God.
Where did you get this?
It doesn't matter.
This is a lot of money.
It should get you started.
I know, but this
is a lot of money.
You sure you
don't need it?
Arthur, I'm fine.
Come on, get in.
When you're settled,
let me know how
to get in touch.
You're sure?
It's fine.
Larry. I'm sorry.
What I said last night.
I know.
It's okay.
Goodbye!
(GUN FIRING)
There's another Jew, son!
(SCREAMS)
Were we out at
the pool last night?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
It's Shabbas:
(MARIJUANA CIGARETTE SIZZLING)
Give me that fucker.
(INHALING SHARPLY)
(PRAYING IN HEBREW)
(VOICE DISTORTING)
(PRAYING SOFTLY
IN HEBREW)
(PRAYING IN HEBREW)
I'm sorry that...
That things have
been so hard for us.
It's okay.
Sy had so much
respect for you,
Larry.
He wrote letters to
the tenure committee.
(RABBI PRAYING IN HEBREW)
(CONGREGATION PRAYING
IN HEBREW)
Jesus Christ.
...taking your place
as a member of our tribe.
Now, you will go
and see Rabbi Marshak.
Afterwards, you will
celebrate in a reception
downstairs in Schanfield Hall.
And then, you will be
a member of B'Nai Avraham
and the Nation of Israel.
Danny Gopnik,
the Sisterhood makes a gift
to you of this Kiddush cup,
so that you will remember
this blessed day on the
next Shabbas and the next,
and on every Shabbas
of a long and fruitful life.
And until that wonderful day
when you stand under
the chuppah, we say amen.
(CONGREGATION SINGING
IN HEBREW)
When the truth
is found
to be lies...
(SNORTS)
...and all the hope
within you dies...
Then what?
Grace Slick.
Marty Balin.
Paul Kantner.
Jorma...
Kaukonen.
...something.
These are the members
of the Airplane.
Mmm-hmm.
Uh-huh.
Be a good boy.
ARLEN: Danny was magnificent.
Oh.
Thank you, Arlen.
Mazel tov:
It was wonderful.
Yes, it was. Thank you.
Such a time of nachas:
He's your youngest,
you have to savor it.
I do.
I will.
Well, see you
at the staff caf.
Yes.
I, uh...
Just, um...
I shouldn't tell you this,
I'm not telling you
officially.
The tenure candidates
aren't notified
till Thursday.
Yes?
You'll be very pleased.
Thank you, Arlen.
I didn't say anything.
Mazel tov:
(TEACHER SPEAKING HEBREW)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
ON HEADPHONES)
(GIRL SPEAKING HEBREW)
(BOY SPEAKING HEBREW)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(TEACHER SPEAKING HEBREW)
(WHISPERING)
Fagle.
There's a tornado warning
from the weather service.
Mr. Turchik has decided
to move us into the
basement of the synagogue.
(SPEAKING HEBREW)
We will form two lines.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(RINGING)
(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
That fucking flag's
gonna rip right off
the flagpole!
(RINGING CONTINUES)
Hello?
MAN: Larry?
Yes?
Hi, Len Shapiro:
(CHUCKLES) Oh.
Hello, Dr. Shapiro.
Listen,
mazel tov on Danny:
Yes, thank you.
Listen, could you
come by to discuss
these x-ray results?
Hello?
Yes?
Larry, could you
come in to discuss
these x-ray results?
You remember the
x-rays we took?
We can't discuss them
over the phone?
I think we'd be more
comfortable in person:
Can you come in?
When?
Now:
Now is good:
I've cleared
some time now:
Hey, Fagle!
Fagle, I got your...
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
ON HEADPHONES)