lawyer speed race air
Oh bit young to be evident midlife
crisis and I'll gosh and all this stuff
i don't have this kind of money
this is just getting ideas for a man may
your year went so my girlfriend has been
cracking the whip lately for me to get
my life in order is work getting more
serious
so how to do things like bring pop3
candy or go to you know the bar with my
friends to watch the game but I am NOT a
pushover
no I didn't matter that I get one day
long that I can do what ever I want haha
so what exactly are you planning for
your big day
well no I want to do is be a home and
snuggle my girlfriend and catch up on
glamour girls so pathetically it's worse
than I thought hmm
activate you put a man gay what's today
gentlemen we need light bulbs here got a
helpful might figure out what he's gonna
do on his mandate it is vital to his
self-respect
ok guys I do appreciate what you're
doing here I really do but you know
maybe I just need to accept this is
gonna be my life from here on out and
that some crazy talk man you gotta drink
that you coke and green coconut even
know how long often thinks it's bad for
me
you better get up there quick someone
get me a coaster glass Lanson at the
most dirt and don't need a coach to go
ahead drink it straight for the bottle
footballs that's cool let's do this
thing alright then do it
ok let's take care of the morning any
idea wake up a new person asking for
breakfast a bitch watch SportsCenter on
ESPN my gosh stuff is genius whole time
you're working on my friend independent
at the head is that right on a scrap of
paper
alright what's next log onto a xbox live
in play halo for five hours straight
it's been so long since I've played halo
I don't even know if I remember where I
put my fingers anymore so like riding a
bike
just don't take care of itself alright
uh afternoon any other ideas on the
sports bar and watch the game eat as
many spicy chicken with yes you can
I got to be nothing but she chose
cookies and drink nothing but red bull
or chicken wings
it's done it is
yeah
hello
I babe no I'm doing great are you
your mother's where no no i'm not i'm
not saying that i would love to meet you
know that's fine I can just do it
another weekend be that means i don't
get to have one for like a home-made no
no I knew they'd get her up
shrewd he played the mom card no man can
stand against the mom card
the worst part is everything we just
came up with is going to go to waste all
of it
yep is there something we can do to help
you know why what if you guys when did
everything on this list and then I just
live vicariously through you
okay I gotta go watches chick flick
movie with a girlfriend yeah man I gotta
pay my girlfriend's house and wash your
car this saturday
yeah my dad duty with the kids wife is
taking his body with her friend or foe
so you always whipped as I am
want another shot of coke bring it
man cave now you end up good condition
let's go downstairs to my man cave we
can drink beer and play video games all
we want is your dress with a teapot
increase the cookie don't see
like calls any pictures and pop
education way into to eat
let's brainstorm and get some light
bulbs for the new show demonizes whole
from obligations and watch out watch out
chick i binge-watched the second season
of house of cards last weekend and more
about you home with the ID people
notching Carla it was dangerous
done with you don't sit inning is it
should be impact she jumped to the
shenanigans and she's looking for july
for the hot seat back in $YEAR jon is
totally whipped his wife wrapped around
her little finger
John should go to onion one tracks watch
SportsCenter feel like crap right glass
coaster
ok i will note on the card
pashmina hi usual play the moms in town
card about my life on jump I play the
sympathy card documenting pipe don't
play the cute little girl card it's not
going to work on me you know what wrong
class on your show
push it