Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
http://hdmovie.vn & vnbits.org
Hey, quit looking at that.
Stop reading.
I'm searching for other fun places to sight see.
For our next trip.
This guide is not meant for you.
It's written for people who's clueless
about traveling.
Where do you fancy going? I'll take you.
I have no clue precisely.
That's why I'm brushing up.
Up to you.
You're better looking photographed.
Really? No kidding.
It's a great photo. Who took it for you?
Someone.
Of course, someone.
I'm asking who.
What does it matter who?
So many trips I took. How can I remember?
Couldn't even remember the person you were with?
I've taken trips with so many people.
I'll have memory overload if I remember everyone.
This isn't exactly...
your first trip going with someone.
It's actually my first time.
I quit my job to accompany you.
Nobody asked you to quit your job.
You were unhappy with it.
- I did it on purpose
- Playing the Stewardess of course not
I was sexually harassed by the editor.
Andrew? He seems gay.
Some drinks
Forget it. No need to dwell on aggravations.
Whole point of holidays is pleasure seeking.
You like to order?
Coffee. Thanks.
A glass of water please.
Thank you.
Right, trips are suppose to be fun.
Look at you. So happy.
How can you not remember?
Is it not allowed?
Even if you can remember, don't let me know.
You don't have to know if you don't ask.
I wouldn't have to ask if you didn't do it.
What have I done?
You know very well what you did.
That's a joke.
What did I do that...
you know about and I don't?
Why not ask yourself
what you don't want me to know.
Don't want you to know?
Why not just come out and say what you know?
Country code for Australia is 614, right?
I guess so...
You guess so?
So it was she who called.
You're snooping around my phone?
Can't help if the screen's so gigantic.
No need to peek if it's visible for miles around.
Don't you know about privacy rights?
- I have the feeling...
- Big screens don't give you license to snoop.
...the man's hiding something.
Don't be such a busybody.
Curious to see if his screen is really that big.
If it's you, how will you answer?
I won't say anything.
So you're still in touch.
Breaking up doesn't mean the end of friendship.
What's wrong about friends caring for each other?
How can you still be friends after splitting up?
Is it possible to be friends after a break-up?
Depends on who.
If it's you, very unlikely.
Why?
Am I that terrible?
I mean I don't intent to break up with you.
It's you who can't be friends.
Doesn't mean the same for others.
You and your attitude.
How can any of your ex be friends with you?
It's not a matter of being close,
it's how close you intend to be.
She's very straightforward.
Outspoken as always.
You know her?
Oh, she's Zhou Yi.
So, did she or didn't she?
If it's you, will you admit to it?
What does it matter if she did or not?
I'm sorry. We were plastered...
Saying sorry doesn't make you right.
- Stop it. There's people around.
- Leave me alone.
Listen to me.
Sit down first.
Let's split.
I already apologized. What do you want?
Go our separate ways.
You want to split, split.
Why do you need to throw things?
Sorry, I thought he was going to hit you.
Lucky she didn't hit anyone first.
Just drop me where I can catch a cab.
Anywhere convenient to get off.
It's good to know when to get off.
Know the meaning of troublesome?
It's OK. No trouble giving you a lift.
Right. it's not you who's driving.
So? Haven't got your driver's license?
He failed twice.
It's OK. I don't mind driving.
Twice? That makes it five failures total.
You're something else.
Right, didn't get your name...you're...
I'm Cee.
Funny, I'm B.
Just kidding. I'm Zhou Yi.
I know. Ping has mentioned you before.
Bet it's nothing complimentary.
Who has time to talk about you?
Not this apartment?
People are asleep. Quiet.
Miss Lin...Miss Lin...
Get up, Miss Lin.
What?
Miss Lin.
You again?
Miss Zhou, what time is it?
What do you want?
Sorry. A mishap.
I like to continue renting.
Wasn't it your idea to break the lease?
I've already returned all your deposit.
What the hell do you want now?
I beg you, another year.
My purse...
Normally, you call me Fat Arse right?
Not true.
Now it's Miss Lin this and Miss Lin that.
First you say go, then you say rent.
And if you impulsively take flight again?
What should I do? Return the rent?
No way.
- it's not that, Miss Lin...
- Mind your hands.
Miss Lin, you have similar units available?
- You can rent me?
- What happened to Mr. Mustache?
Switch to Mr. Spectacles?
Now a threesome.
Have you considered love motels instead?
Wake up, check out.
No need to clean up after yourselves.
Meaning what?
Good suggestion.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Hey...
So, now what?
How do I know?
What now?
Can't find my passport and my purse.
Maybe your boyfriend has them?
Babe, I'm in San Diego.
I just checked in.
Aren't you going to England?
Last minute change of plans.
What's your next stop? Are you coming back?
Next stop Japan. Looking up friends.
Don't go. Come back first.
I'm penniless. Someone took my passport.
I've given up my apartment.
Don't have any place to go.
Even then, it will take me
over 30 hours to get back.
Where are you? You're in a dive?
What dive? I'm on the street.
A friend gave me a lift from the airport.
What friend?
The one who kept failing the driver's test.
How many times did he take the test?
Five times.
Shame! I have to go.
Call you when I get back.
Alright, bye.
Mum says she can't make it back.
It'll take 30 hours. We heard.
You overheard that?
Your phone was on really loud.
That so?
Something wrong with your ears?
It's itchy. Maybe an infection.
Don't worry about it.
Jolin, can I crash your place for a few days?
Never mind. You take care.
What?
Battery low.
Sorry.
So...now what?
Off, shoes off...
Wow, how big is this?
800 square feet.
You're sharing?
He's renting. I'm just bunking.
I know I'm a nuisance but I'll clear out soon.
It's his flat. I don't mind.
Once my Mom returns, I'll leave.
Not thinking of a long stay, are you?
Didn't I say I'll leave right away.
Do you really need such a big lamp?
It's antique. Landlord says can't take it down.
It's pretty. Why hide it behind a lampshade?
Doesn't match.
It agrees with you.
- You're so materialistic. - Don't touch.
You have no say. This is my flat.
Your flat? You're just a tenant.
I'm tired. I'll bunk here.
Don't worry about me.
You really making yourself at home!
Sleep in the study.
Study? You're kidding me.
Chen Jun Ping, you must be kidding.
Don't tear it apart.
It's late. She's a lone girl by herself.
Can't expect her to go to a love motel.
Did I say anything? It's fine.
Zhou Yi. I'll get you a change of clothes.
Thanks.
Top...pants.
- Rest well. - Thanks.
Wash first. You're dirtying the sheets.
I'm too tired.
You're spreading fleas.
Spread fleas?
Hurry up!
There's fleas? Is this where they're hiding?
Stop it.
Let me scratch. Is it here?
Excuse me. I was hungry.
Do you want eggs?
Sure. You want some?
No. I'm on diet.
You don't look like you need to.
Thanks.
What?
For frying.
No need.
Just do this.
- Let me. - Thanks.
You've known each other long?
Chen Jun Ping?
A few years. Almost six.
There's nothing between us now.
You sure you don't want some?
No thanks, we don't have the habit
of midnight snacking.
What?
Nothing.
I'll turn in now. Take your time.
- Good night. - Night.
Do I have to keep repeating?
Keep the shower curtain inside the tub.
- Spilling water all over. - I'm late.
Can't drop you off work.
Why are you in here?
Nothing you haven't seen before.
Your hand's filthy. Don't touch my lips. Out!
Use to put it in your mouth. Was it hygienic then?
I need to shower and hurry to work.
Wash your stuff later, OK?
It's killing me!
Are you alright?
It hurts. Get me some pain-killers
and sanitary napkins.
Me? How?
Buying sanitary napkins! I'll be a laughing stock.
I'll do you a favor.
Stuff this in first as a stop gap.
Stuff your ass! Hurry up.
Is it really painful?
Let me kick you in the groins.
See if it hurts.
Will I still have to go...
if I let you kick me?
Just kidding.
Fine. I'm on my way.
Also "Bang" killers.
"Bang"killers'?
Pain-killers!
Back in a jiffy.
Here. Stem the flow.
What the heck?
What's wrong?
A grown man...
and can't tell a sanitary napkin from a pad?
What good does it do a man
to know things like that?
Isn't it almost the same?
Are you alright?
Need to get to the hospital
for a shot of tranquilizer.
That bad?
I'll call an ambulance.
You're letting the whole village know?
An ambulance due to menstruation. How shameful!
What a nuisance.
Easy does it.
Can we afford to Calla cab here?
Doesn't cost us. Sol is a buddy.
Hi!
His family runs a fleet of taxis.
Howdy!
This taxi is for private use.
You're the only one uses it like a private car.
What happened?
Her period.
Get in.
Forgot my I.D.
Hold her a sec.
- OK. - OK. OK.
I'm ticklish.
I'm sorry.
Get in first. Mind your head.
I'm off to work.
Keys on the cabinet. Help yourself.
Can I use your computer?
My laptop's batteries ran out.
Charger's with my luggage.
Sure. Always never bother to ask first.
What's the password?
Still using the same old one.
What's it to you?
Look at this.
Your Mom's really traveled all over.
What kind of obsession is that?
Taking pictures of bedrooms solely.
Can I give Woody your address?
So that he can forward my stuff?
Sure.
You're sure he'll send it all back to you .
Think so.
What's your address?
After me, was it just Woody?
No, there's Ben, Oscar...
Then Woody.
After me was it just Cee?
No.
There's Kitty, Pat, Rachel.
Then Cee.
Not the Rachel with the body odor?
No, that's Rachel Ma.
Mine was Rachel Chan.
I know this girl.
Charlie?
Yeah.
A co-worker at the publishing house.
Don't tell me you went with her.
Think I'm as promiscuous as you?
Can you believe she use to go with Sol?
What? They're still an item.
How do you know?
I took her to see Sol's band perform.
She's now an adoring fan.
Bastard! Does musicians have it easier with girls?
He invites you to his performances?
He often leaves me tickets.
How come I never run into you?
I know when to avoid you.
Thanks.
What?
Thank you.
Come again.
I said thanks.
Aren't you in a hurry?
There's stains.
- What? - Didn't wash off.
What?
Look for yourself.
No. Come here.
Quick. Over here.
Look.
Like a heart?
Looks alike.
Aren't you ashamed?
It's a copy.
Next time is it possible for you...
...to add a star here?
Sure.
Hey, Andrew.
What are you doing back here?
You're formidable. Snaring a writer.
Aren't you on a trip with Woody?
Unexpected change of plans.
Change of plans or companion?
Can you check with Accounting for me?
See about collecting last month's pay.
It's the accountant's day off.
You and Woody have the same habit.
Forsaking your wages to go on a trip.
What song is that?
What?
Just want to know which song.
It's really familiar.
Forgot the name though.
Do you know?
No.
What are you doing here so late?
I'm waiting for my cheque.
Why are you stuck here this hour?
Overtime.
Take your time.
You're punctual with assignments...
...but only collect paychecks every 6 months.
You must have money to spare.
I can save it with you.
Scared you'll abscond with it? Thanks.
Weren't you searching for references?
Why is it taking you a lifetime?
Print them out.
Make 6 copies of the agenda from my thumb drive.
Put it on my desk.
What?
Thumb drive? Six copies?
Want me to give you one?
Fine.
Press.
Gift from fiance?
Yes.
We've split.
Next time...
Hitch on to a bestseller.
What's up?
Just re-packing my stuff.
I notified the airline of my whereabouts.
They got my luggage off the plane.
That's good.
I'll wash first.
What's your plan?
What?
Have you've found a place to stay yet?
Need to lend you some money?
No need.
Don't worry. I'll be gone soon.
I won't be a nuisance.
I don't mean that.
Gecko!
Where?
Here!
They're beneficial. They feed on mosquitoes.
Hey!
What?
A moth!
Living in the boondocks.
You have to learn to live with vermins.
Get rid of it quick!
It takes one kind to deal with another.
Find us a gecko.
Gecko feeds on bugs and moths.
It's voracious.
It's you who's scared of moths.
How are we going to find a gecko?
We've been raising one...
behind the closet.
It only comes out to feed at night.
Don't you believe me?
It makes noises.
How can gecko make noise?
Come with me.
What?
It's really there. Go in!
- You're mad! - Trust me. Hurry.
Do I look like a sucker?
You think I'm so easily fooled?
Nuts! Gecko are beneficial.
Can you hear them?
Is that rig ht?
Quiet! Hear that?
Didn't I tell you.
It's true. I hear it.
I hear it too.
It's your slippers.
Slipper! Slipper! Slipper!
Here! Kill it.
Didn't you tell me gecko's beneficial?
There's no mosquitoes here.
I thought you don't snack late.
You're hungry?
No.
She's asleep. Lower the sound.
Told you I'm not hungry.
I'm watching.
This one?
This?
News.
What are you doing?
Not so loud. People's asleep.
Stop! I give up.
What's this?
Look and see.
Why is there only one?
You're too much.
Perfect.
What?
Make way.
Move. I'm in a hurry.
What? Did you drop something?
Look for it later.
How can you drop things down the drain?
Barging in without knocking.
I wouldn't have dropped it otherwise.
I live here. Why do I need to knock?
Why didn't you look the door?
You're ruining my flat.
You're not happy till you tear everything apart.
None of your business.
It's my flat. What you destroy here is my concern.
Why are you forcing the drain open?
Did you drop something in? Let me help.
Mind your own business.
Why are you bossing me around?
Can't I show a little concern for friends?
Who said," can't be friends after breaking up"?
Say you're forgetful yet
you remember things like that.
How can you forget what you said before?
Why should I remember?
What do you want?
And you?
Nothing.
You weren't like this before.
Before? Why talk about before?
Before when we were together...
your only concern was the past.
You haven't improved one bit.
- Come here! Look carefully. - What now?
I'm leasing this spacious flat
with kitchen and study.
Let go!
Do you know what I'm doing at work?
I'm a producer, not a designer.
You wanted to be a designer.
You switched jobs
because you weren't earning enough.
And you?
You impulsively quit your job
to travel with a guy.
I haven't improve? And you?
What are you? You're nothing!
Let go!
Bugger off!
I don't appreciate your books.
I don't know how to shop for you.
Everything I buy is a mistake.
It's all wrong.
Those colors don't really suit me.
Just try it on for me.
Do you wear clothes for her sake?
What are you saying?
Talking about her.
You're crazy!
If you don't miss her...
why keep her things around?
Throw it out. Throw everything out!
Did I ask you to throw your things out?
So unreasonable.
Do you still carry a torch for her?
Think what you like.
I'm exhausted.
I'm tired too.
Let's call it quits.
No more games.
What now?
Just kidding. Don't leave.
Can't you at least pick the right things to throw?
- I'm sorry. - Always like this.
Go...
Go!
Do you have an upset stomach?
Any drugs you're averse to?
You have asthma?
Menstrual cramps?
Why keep shaking your head?
No or don't know?
Don't know
If you have cramps it's probably menstrual.
At menstruation,
it's possible that blood clots...
will cause cervical contractions.
When it constricts, it's agonizing.
Juveniles often have to deal with this symptom.
After puberty, experiencing sexual activities...
it's not a serious problem as you mature.
Some don't experience this in their youth.
When they're adults, the pain starts. Strange!
How old are you?
Twenty-five.
I'm Forty.
If it continues after 25, it's unusual.
Probably caused by emotional disorders, Stress...
...inducing hormonal disorders.
Chinese medical diagnosis:
liver & 'qi' asphyxiation.
Maybe your emotional life is irregular.
Lovesick?
Doctor, what are trying to tell me?
There's a cause...
for everything in this world.
Let's see if I can be of any assistance to you.
Doctor...
Can we discuss my insurance policy first?
That...
Actually I don't believe in insurance.
That's why I need to learn more about it.
What are you doing?
The drugs you buy over the counter
have a lot of impurities
that stays in your body for over 5 years.
But they're effective pain-killers.
As the saying goes: eat reservedly,
speak with caution.
Look at the carcass you're devouring.
See how the blood gushes out.
See it?
It's full of bacteria like Salmonella.
What's up, brother?
How should I know?
Your name's Du?
That's me.
No mistake then.
There has to be a reason.
Job's done, boss.
But the target wants to know why he's hit.
Boss says to keep your fucking mouth shut.
Why are you so good to me?
But you're with Cee already.
Doesn't mean I can't be good to you too.
It's not that you can't...
...but WHY be good to me?
Does everything need to be spelled out?
Fine...
I'll take care of it tomorrow.
Don't worry.
If you're disfigured...
I'll marry you.
Water? Let me get you a glass.
I get you a glass.
After that, you became a couple?
Some things are better left unsaid.
Can I ask you now? Can I?
Then why are you still asking?
Where were you?
Nowhere.
I've changed jobs.
Better quit if you're unhappy.
What will you be doing next month?
I don't even know about tomorrow.
Why?
It's my Dad's birthday next month.
We'll take him to dinner.
He's not here.
Where is he?
In the cemetery.
Let's visit.
OK?
Did he spoil you?
He's a man of few words.
Mom does all the talking.
Mom use to say
The one you like best
is never the one by your side.
But I think...
Great if someone's at my side listening.
That's great!
Aren't I listening to you now?
Actually, when do you intend to go?
What? Go?
Go where?
Thailand
You were planning a trip anyway.
Why are you always like this?
Never explain where or what you're up to.
Suddenly making me leave.
Going for how long? Coming back when?
Don't know yet.
Have to leave now.
I'm not going!
Why's everyone like that?
Never keep your word.
I'm good for my word.
Trust me?
Why is our timing always off?
Every time after breaking up...
I try to look you up.
It's you who never see me.
We can still be friends after break up.
Actually, I've tried calling you.
I lost my mobile.
Babe, tell Mommy
Babe, I'm not getting any signal.
Hello...Hello...
Hello
Ping's in the shower,
who's asking for him?
Hello, hello
I didn't know you called.
My number's still the same.
Just waiting for you to call.
Do you remember...
where I finally found you?
At Franster's.
I remember.
The first thing you said:
You can discuss this at my graveside.
Mom use to visit every year.
But lately, she stopped coming.
Though she didn't like him best...
...there's still no reason to forget him.
Don't worry. If you die...
I'll visit every year.
I actually prefer being first to die.
Better to be missed than to miss someone.
Let's travel. Where do you want to go?
England.
I just started work. Can't take time off.
How's Taiwan? Just for a few days.
I'm broke.
I'll pay first.
It's just that I bought something.
What a waste of money.
Hey! Stop it...it's ticklish!
So puny.
Never realize your fingers so big.
"F"you
Really?
Do it now.
Can't. Leg cramps!
- Which one? - Both.
Can't wait.
You always play your own music.
The customers never complain?
The music's good.
But you got complains before?
I'm not really a taxi driver.
It's your boyfriend who treats me like one.
What do you actually do?
I'm a musician.
Really? How impressive!
What now?
I forgot my passport.
Can't leave now.
Sol, can you take me home?
From here?
Don't have time. It's 5 already.
Sol!
I'll try to rush.
Why rush? If you forgot your passport...
...how do you expect to travel?
I really want to go.
Sol, can you make a u-turn here?
Stop teasing, you bastard.
She's tearing up.
What?
I have your passport.
You left it on the coffee table.
I took it for you.
Stop the car. I'm not going.
We end up failing to go on a trip.
Don't. Don't.
It's just a prank.
Don't get mad.
What prank? You don't intend to go to Taiwan.
You like England, isn't it?
I never said that. Come on!
You want to go, go yourself.
Take her there. I'll find my own way.
I don't have my passport. I shouldn't go.
Let me. Let me.
Excuse me but this car isn't mine.
It's my Dad's, OK?
If you have any needs, call me.
If you need to use the car, call me.
You're not really leaving are you?
Don't be mad.
Sorry.
Hey.
Larry, I really admire you.
But without compensation,
one can't survive on talent only.
Opportunity wasted. it's a shame!
Without compensation,
one can't survive on talent only.
Opportunity wasted. it's a shame!
Yes. I'm sorry, Mr. Ho.
Ping,you shouldn't be short-sighted.
If your work's exceptional,
someone's bound to notice.
Don't dwell on fame and fortune.
If you're famous, you will be in demand.
But Mr Ho, I can't accept it.
It's my design.
How can someone else claim credit?
Ping, I really respect you.
Hello...Ping
Yes...
I honestly can't accept it.
You motherfucker. Why are you so stubborn?
You think you're really an artist?
You're a disgrace to your profession.
Motherfucker!
You make his family frantic,
mentioning them so much.
He's quitting. Save your breathe.
Who's that?
Sorry, Mr. Ho.
Chen Jun Ping
The girls you pick are either crazy or stupid.
It'll be disastrous
if I hand you bastards the job.
Mr. Ho, why don't you...
...go stuff yourself.
So what now?
Unemployed. No big deal.
I want to move to Kowloon.
Don't want to live here.
Mr. Chen, I understand you just lost your job.
I have some savings. Will last me a few months.
You can move in with me first.
You have a point.
How are we going to leave?
Are you nuts, Chen Jun Ping?
$8000 for a sofa. Are you loaded?
What?
It's OK. Don't worry.
It'll be done soon.
Careful. Hands off first.
Look up.
How's that?
It's CK.
You're terrific!
Next time don't buy if there's no delivery.
It's nine flights!
Mind your hands!
This has been on my wish list.
But my former flat was too cramp.
Now it's discounted.
Yeah, it's cheap but have you considered...
...in my 300 square feet apartment...
...how congested with this in it.
When we move to a bigger place, it will fit.
- Let's go! - OK...
I'm really pooped out.
Just a short haul. It won't kill you.
You die now and I'll burn it as offering to you.
Then no need to haul it.
"F"you
Forget it.
I can't. It hurts.
My jaw was dislocated today.
How was it dislocated?
At my interview.
The guy was really hilarious.
Nuts! Who ever dislocate their jaws laughing?
You think I'm a fool?
- No. - Let's go.
It was hysterical. He ran into a glass panel.
What was the interview for?
Publishing house.
Publishing?
Right.
- How capable! - Right.
- Talented girl. - Right.
Can you read?
"F"you
Now? Make it quick!
While no one's around.
I'll ignore that.
Where you going?
Toilet. Wait.
I'll wait. I'll be here.
There's people.
Actually after splitting with you...
...I only went with Cee.
Same here. For me it was just Woody.
Why did you lie?
Heard of the statistics?
Every person averages 6 lies per day.
So few? Like..."I don't want to see you again!"
"You better leave soon."
"I've forgotten you."
Seems too conservative an estimate.
Yeah, so idiotic.
Also...
"I don't fancy you."
What?
Menstruation.
Hi.
I'm...on my way to office.
Traffic jam.
You forgot something?
I can't return in time to give you the key.
Where are you?
Is she on her way?
So early? No work today?
I forgot something.
Zhou Yi.
It's best you leave.
Let me return your clothes.
Can we start speaking?
Yeah.
Is it recording?
Yes, is still recording
Say you're not in Hong Kong. Leave a message.
You're not in Hong Kong. Leave a message.
Hi, where are you?
When can you get back?
Hi.
- Hi. - Why did you come?
I called and you said you're here.
I'll put this in the car first.
No, I mean why are you here?
Ping text me. Asked me to call you.
Watch out.
Actually, Ping asked me to watch out for you.
What's there to watch?
You do everything he tells you to?
What a chump!
Sorry!
Why apologize?
He who should be apologizing doesn't bother.
What are you sorry about?
It's just that I kicked your bag.
I'm sorry. Every time we meet I lose my temper.
You weren't angry...
the first time we met.
When was that?
Careful. Watch it.
Hey, watch out.
What song is this?
Don't know. What is it?
Don't know either.
I thought as a musician you'd know everything.
What musician? I'm just a hack.
I like your music.
It's passable.
Of course not. If I sing as well as you...
I'll sing without stop.
Normally those who can't sing...
...loves to sing to others.
Don't misunderstand me. I'm talking about Ping.
Are you pretending? No fooling.
Why did you come back?
Didn't realize I have your passport
till I was on the plane.
The minute I landed I changed my flight home.
I called you.
Called me?
Right. I answered.
Hey, eat.
By your looks, you must have skipped breakfast.
My hands are clean.
I tell you, breakfast is the most important meal.
Can you not talk with your mouth full?
You're talking as you're eating.
Why are you eating with your swim cap on?
Don't you wear it only when swimming?
Eating, you only use mouth.
The head is idle, isn't it?
Life's short. Use your time wisely.
My Cantonese has deteriorated but you understand.
You're just like your mother.
I'm prettier.
That's for sure.
You have taste.
Auntie, I'm Woody.
Yes, Uncle. It's Woody, isn't it?
'Woody' as in 'Wood'. Right?
Yes.
So did you pass your driver's test?
How many times did you have to repeat?
I passed on the first try.
Not him.
How many are there?
So, who's the one who kept failing?
Can you not ask?
You question me and I can't question you?
Babe, you're wrong.
If two people are together...
...there's nothing
that can't be asked and answered.
We've broken up.
Then you're improper.
Didn't you tell me over the phone...
...that you're going with my daughter.
Well, we ARE together now.
Don't know what the devil you're up to.
Don't waste it. I'm going.
Where are you going?
You'll get cramps if you swim after eating.
Not swim. Rinsing.
Time's up.
Your Mom's marvellous.
Court her. She likes travelling too.
You'll make a fine couple.
What are you saying?
You're enough for me. You have her genes.
Passport. Purse.
Could have mailed them. Why come back on purpose?
Postage is expensive.
Plane ticket isn't'?
Well, isn't it better to send me back also?
Sorry.
Come back. Sit.
I'm sorry.
What?
Can't hear.
I said I'm sorry. OK?
A lot happened the last few days.
Were you listening?
Here's the ferris wheel.
This is IFC Building. With the lightning rod.
What?
I thought you'd check in another room next door.
What are you saying?
Move over.
Such a big bed. You're hogging it.
Don't step on me.
When I was small you'd forbid me
jumping on beds and sofas.
Now you're stomping away.
That's right.
Remember?
You were always bouncing up and down on my bed.
Ruined all the springs.
Your Dad complained bitterly...
when he went to bed.
Stomp then, but watch my body.
Here I go.
I'll not stomp, I'll jump.
Come on, move!
I have menstrual pains.
Better menstrual pains than no menstrual.
Come on. Get up.
Move a little.
Move and no fear of menstrual pains.
Jump.
What now?
What?
What are you thinking?
He wants to be with me.
Which one? Taxi driver or Uncle?
He has a name.
Babe, how many boyfriends do you have?
Who's the one who failed
his driver's test 5 times?
Even if I tell you,
you'd still don't know who he is.
Then thanks but I don't really want to know.
More important is that you're clear about it.
I don't want to be like you.
Discover too late...
the one beside you isn't one you like best.
Wrong!
I never said the one beside me
isn't one I like best.
I said the one I like most...
...is no longer beside me.
Mom, can you take me travelling?
You can go on your own.
You're mature enough.
How did you get water all over?
Don't wipe it.
Give me that.
Get up. I'll do it.
Let go.
Let go!
- Morning. - Morning.
Why don't I take another test?
Again?
You've taken it 5 times.
You have to chauffeur me all the time.
it's not very well.
Doesn't matter. I'll take you wherever.
It's not convenient.
You had a late snack?
Yes.
Why didn't you clean up?
You're seeing someone else?
What?
Are you're going with someone else?
We talked about this. Why are you throwing things?
Are you or aren't you?
Stuff are meant for you to throw?
At least pick something expensive.
Yes or no?
No. What do you want?
No or not yet?
What are you saying?
I'm asking you, yes or no?
No.
Toss.
Toss them! Keep it up!
Throw it!
You like throwing things, chuck it all!
What do you want?
Let's split.
We'll get plastic ones tomorrow, OK?
Sorry.
No need to apologize. Just wipe it up.
I'm not talking about that.
It doesn't matter.
Forget it.
Is there something not good about me?
I can change.
Drop it, OK?
I don't want to drop it.
I can't do without you.
There's no one on Earth
who can't do without another.
Where do you plan to go?
No plans.
So?
So what? I'm getting out.
Bye.
Thanks.Bye.
When are you returning?
I'm going on a trip, not emigrating.
Look me up.
Can't you look me up?
I don't know when you're coming back.
I mean... fly over and look me up.
OK.
Good. Let's go.
- Now? - Yeah.
I don't have anything on me.
Buy what you need.
Don't even have my passport.
Later then.
Think about it later.
Be careful.
You too.
- Bye. - Bye.
Take care
OK.
http://hdmovie.vn & vnbits.org
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org