###
Shortly after accidentally clicking "like" on nearly 400 of his ex-girlfriend's facebook's photos earlier today,
panicked area man Adam Neutzling spoke to Onion reporters about his mistake.
I was just looking at... one of her photos that showed on my news feed,
and the next thing I know, I just...
liked every single photo she post in the last four years.
I didn't mean to.
It... just kind of happened.
The 28 year old told reporters
that he had browsed through fourteen of his ex-girlfriend's albums while inadvertently clicking "like" each and every picture,
including dozens from her office picnic last fall,
her trip to New York in 2010
and a photo of her and her first boyfriend from 2006.
I thought if I went back and click "unlike" on all those pictures then she shouldn't be getting notifications.
but then I saw some other albums,
and I ended up liking any more photos on my wall...
Shit...
God damn it...
I look like just shared last four she said somethings too.
Shit...
For more on this story, check this week's Onion review.