Ooh, sorry Mr. Frost.
I didn't mean to startle you.
We're running a wee
bit late this morning.
We overslept and Donald's
got a terrible migraine.
Nice sport this, isn't it?
I was thinking of
taking it up myself.
Slow and gentle.
Must get a lot of
thinking done, do you?
If it's thinking you want,
try Open University.
Competition this is.
All right.
I saw a bloke catch
a body in here once.
About a year ago, it was.
I don't know what it weighed,
but it wasn't half a big one.
Look, haven't you got
anything useful to do?
You're frightening
the flaming fish.
Sorry.
Oi!
Hi, Debs, just off?
What's that, the
new (unintelligible)?
You'd smell it if it was.
Just a little something
to brighten my living room.
How's the physio-therapy?
I don't do physio.
It's aroma therapy.
And you know that very well.
It's fine, thank you, Les.
See you sometime.
Hello, Shangri.
Anything else you
care to say to us?
No sir, you've been
most considerate.
What about you,
Chief Constable?
Nothing, chairman.
I think the file tells us
everything we need to know.
Well, then thank you,
Superintendent Mullett.
I have to say
you've answered all our
questions very lucidly.
If we should decide to recall
you for the final round,
you'll be hearing from us
within the next seven days.
Thank you.
Glad to hear it, sir.
Competition's weak too.
One word in the ear though.
Denton's time sheets.
I'm informed they were
late again last month.
It is very important
to keep a tight ship
in the circumstances.
Remember, performance
is the big buzzword now.
Yes, I do know that, sir.
How's Jack Frost, by the way?
Awful, that young
Barnard's death.
Must have been a
real blow for Jack.
A lesser man would have
resigned from the force.
Colonel,
a word in your ear.
(Knock on door)
Come.
DS Wallace, sir.
Ah, DS Wallace.
Welcome back.
Thank you, sir.
How was the college?
The course went
very well, sir.
Ambition.
It's a very fine thing.
I like your new office.
Yes, things have
changed a good deal
since you were here last.
For the better, I think.
There's a modern
professional attitude
right through the station.
And you heard
about D.I. Frost?
Yes, sir.
Although I'm
surprised he resigned.
Resigned?
Who told you that?
No, no.
The fact is I granted him
extended compassionate leave.
The death of DS Barnard
hit him particularly hard.
He always was an
emotional officer.
Me too sir.
I was very close to him once.
What, Frost?
I meant DS Barnard.
Really?
The man at the top
is always last to
know about these things.
Does that mean Inspector
Frost is coming back, sir?
Well, better assume not.
When I...
The fact is, sergeant,
his leave has put me
in an awkward position.
Well, you knew him,
you know what
I'm talking about.
Frankly he left the
place a perfect tip.
Always was his way.
Well, it's no longer
our way, sergeant.
First job, I want you
to take over his office,
working to me.
Sort it all out.
Just go through everything.
Unfinished cases,
untranscribed
interviews, notebooks.
Staff recharges,
time sheets.
The lot.
No witch-hunt mind,
but I need a very tight ship
over the next
couple of weeks.
Inspection, sir?
As I said, ambition,
it's a very fine thing.
(Phone rings)
Hello.
Oh, it's you, how did I guess.
No, not this one.
Not this time.
Yes, I know that's what
we've done in the past.
Up yours too.
See you tomorrow,
thank you.
Hi, anybody home?
Course not, why ask?
Hazel.
Hello, George.
It's good to see you again.
Well, Mullett's given you
Jack's old office I see.
It could do with
a perfume spray.
He's asked me to go
through his paperwork.
Rather you than me.
Did you hear about Jack?
Yeh?
Mullett said he's on
compassionate leave.
Crafty old devil.
No, Jack resigned.
But Mullett
doesn't want to upset
the Chief Constable.
Jack always was his
favorite copper.
Yeah, I remember.
What's he doing now?
Wandering round Denton
dreaming he's free at last.
Mr. Frost.
Nice day?
Is it?
I meant yours.
No, not really, Brian.
No, not really.
Donald's doing
eggs Benedict tonight.
One of his specialties.
He should really
be in a restaurant.
Yeah.
Yes all right, Brian.
All right, thanks.
Shangri?
Puss, puss.
Puss.
Shangri.
Hello.
Good girl.
Do you want some dinner?
Ah, good evening, Norman.
Good evening.
Quite a coup for Denton.
The Lydian Quartet.
Yes, yes, absolutely.
Well, well.
The Bill goes classical?
I'm sorry?
I take it we are
off duty for once?
You failed to recognize me
without my mortuary gown.
Derek Simpkins,
your friendly
neighborhood pathologist.
Yes, of course.
You know, Superintendent,
I never had you down
for a lover of serious music.
Ah, well I'm not really.
It's my wife Elsbeth.
She belongs to a small
music club you know.
Ah, there you are Diana.
Remember
Superintendent Mullett?
Yes, of course, good
evening Superintendent.
Are you?
Waiting for my wife, yes.
You'll have a long
wait, I'm afraid.
In that case let's get seated.
I can't bear to
have music interrupted.
You're not still at it?
This will take ages.
I don't think Jack ever filed
a single thing in his life.
No, he thought
the filing cabinet
was the same as the fridge.
Have you checked his computer?
His computer!
Have you found anything
on the Black Farm Murder?
Black Farm?
Yeah, take a look at that.
It happened about
eight years ago.
A rich farmer, Jonathan Dale
was murdered
just outside Denton.
A tealeaf called
Branson went down for it,
died in prison last year.
Now this new bloke says
he pulled the trigger.
One of Jack's?
Oh, yeah.
Who fancies a nice night out?
Who wouldn't?
Suspicious death,
Riverside Apartments.
Jordan's already down there.
Yeah.
Well, off you go.
It's time for your first solo.
It's this room here.
Hello, Chris. what is it then?
One dead male,
probable suicide.
The girl from next
door Leonie Viner,
found him when she
looked in to feed the cat.
That's her, through there.
You did put someone with her?
Yeah, a WPC.
Yes, of course, right.
Better show me then.
Right.
Through here.
Leonie called a
doctor, lives upstairs.
He said he'd been
dead an hour maybe two.
Got an ident yet?
Yeah, she says
he's the tenant,
Lester Bryce-Jones.
He lived alone,
except for a
large bunch of keys,
some nice pictures,
and his cat.
Leonie feeds it sometimes.
She's very distressed,
her mother's not home yet.
You said suicide?
He'd been drinking,
taking pills.
Couldn't it have been sexual?
No idea, darling.
I'm a married man.
What's this?
A doctor?
(Beeper)
Duty calls.
Yours probably!
You could have a four
letter word ending in UCK.
There you are.
Right, go on.
How many's that then?
You've got a
triple letter there,
so that makes twenty.
Some people have all the uck.
Let's have another glass.
Ah, we're dry.
I'll go and ask Donald
for another bottle.
He makes a nice
selection, don't you think?
Uhu.
Or would you prefer
a cup of Horlicks?
No no, I'll stick with this.
DS Wallace,
thank you for coming.
You are aware I was
at a chamber concert?
Sorry.
Not seen you before.
New, are you?
You have,
but you won't remember.
I used to be in uniform.
Didn't they tell you?
I'm a pathologist,
not a police doctor.
I don't attend crime scenes,
I conduct autopsies
and forensic research.
I thought a pathologist
ought to be on scene.
Did you really?
I'm not sure it's suicide.
There are drugs around,
possibly some
hospital connection.
Oh well, get out
your notebook, Diana.
I don't generally take
it to concerts, Doctor.
Will this do?
Wouldn't have a stethoscope
in there as well, would you?
In here I suppose?
Interesting.
Aah.
Over here, sir.
What's this then?
Our art collector?
And you left him
hanging just for me.
Mr. Lester Bryce-Jones.
I presume a doctor
looked at him already?
Yes, sir, said he was dead.
Brilliant, can't
be faulted, can he?
What of, though?
He thought hanging, sir.
We'll decide that
at the post-mortem.
But I see why you
need a pathologist.
Anything else here
that might be lethal?
He seems to have taken drugs.
There are more
in the bathroom.
These aren't drugs,
these are medicines.
Come here, Diana, will you?
What's all this
on his eyelids?
That's mascara, doctor.
What's going on?
Darling are you all right?
You should have called me.
You don't like me to.
Mrs. Viner?
Let me tell you, your
daughter's been brilliant.
She called the doctor.
And the police.
I know she's
brilliant, thank you.
Why did you go in there?
To feed Shangri,
I thought he was out.
Anyway, what happened?
I saw him in the hall earlier.
He seemed fine.
Why did he do it?
Kill himself?
We don't know that
he did, Mrs. Viner.
What else then?
I mean, surely nobody
would want to murder Les.
You knew him quite well then?
We need a formal
identification.
Oh no, no, no.
I didn't know him.
Not really.
He must have
relatives somewhere.
Do you know where?
No, I don't know where.
I don't know
anything about him.
He'd only lived there a year.
Now go away, please,
I want to look
after my daughter.
Leonie, I'm sorry,
we're going to have to
talk to you again tomorrow,
as a witness.
Will you be all right tonight?
Of course she will,
now please go.
Ssh, it's all right,
it's all right.
There we go, Mr. Frost.
Donald says enjoy.
In that case I will
Brian, thank you.
You should really
try muesli sometimes.
It's a lot better
for the bowels.
Oh, I nearly forgot.
Letter for you.
Oh, right.
Well, blow me.
Good news, is it?
Granny died and left
you a massive fortune?
Well, very nearly.
About a year ago
I burnt my house down
because I wasn't paying due
care and attention, was I?
So half a lifetime,
you know, went up in smoke.
Doesn't sound like
very good news to me.
Ah, but I was insured.
God knows how because
I could never remember
sensible things like that.
"...Iike to advise you the
process of refurbishment
is complete and your property
will shortly be available
for reoccupation... "
Oh, Mr. Frost.
I'd say that calls
for a celebration.
So do I.
Let's have some fried bread?
I really wouldn't like to
be your stomach, Mr. Frost.
Donald, Mr. Frost
wants some fried bread!
Why?
Why was the
Black Farm murder file
removed from the records?
No idea, sir.
It must have been
for fresh inquiries.
Well, who took it?
Why wasn't it signed for?
I can't imagine, sir.
This is a disciplinary matter.
I've called a press conference
on the Black Farm Murder
in an hour's time.
Somehow I assumed
I'd have the file with me.
Find DS Wallace.
She's on a case, sir.
Dead male, Riverside
Apartments, possible murder.
Isn't it all on the computer?
This was eight
years ago, Toolan.
Before we had computers,
if you remember.
Yes, I do remember, sir.
Sergeant, come here.
I need that file at once.
Now do I have to start
an official investigation?
Very well, sir.
You'd better come and see.
And what's that?
Well, that must be one of
Jack's little jokes, sir.
It's here.
Ah, at least it hasn't
left the building.
Well, you'd better
look inside, sir.
I see.
Is that another
of Jack's little jokes?
Well, he must have taken
the stuff home with him.
Well it's totally irregular.
Yes it is sir.
But I expect he
meant to bring it back
when he returned from his
compassionate leave, sir.
It's not the only one, is it?
Jack liked to keep
things in his head.
Right that does it.
I want his head
and I want it on the block.
Find him, bring him to me.
And that file.
I'm not quite sure
where he's living, sir.
Then start a search for him.
Arrest him if necessary.
Arrest him?
Yes.
He's broken procedural rules.
He's impeding
an urgent inquiry.
He's bringing the
force into disrepute.
You heard me.
Arrest him!
Mr. Frost.
Hello there.
Hi.
Here we are.
All ready for inspection.
Yes, It's nice.
Very very nice.
You'll be pleased
to have it back.
After all,
home is always home.
Full of memories.
Family.
You never forget, do you?
No, I know what you mean.
We've restored most
fixtures and fittings
and we're willing to
pay a reasonable sum
for furniture replacement.
That's very good.
Shall we look around?
I wonder, if you'd mind.
I like to look
around on my own.
Yeah, sure.
It's all yours.
Oh, thank you.
My pleasure.
Bye now.
Goodbye.
Looks like one of ours.
Certainly has
our laundry mark.
But you can't tell
who it belongs to?
One of the doctors perhaps?
Doctor?
No.
More likely
one of the porters.
A porter?
How much would he earn?
Working all hours?
Say a thousand a month.
Not a lot is it?
If you want a lot of anything,
you don't work for the NHS.
Anyway these days it's
nothing to do with us.
It's a privatized service.
All to do with
the internal market.
You'd best talk
to the contractors.
They might be
able to help you.
They're in the High Street.
Thank you.
It's very comfortable
isn't it, sir.
Ideal for the study.
Yes, yes.
Very pricey though, I bet.
It is genuine cowhide though.
Ah, is it?
all right, well,
I don't think so.
Well, I don't think
my insurance company
will stretch to it.
They're a bit
worried about BSE.
Well, if there's a problem,
we can arrange a
year before payment,
or no percent finance...
No joy, sorry.
We never employed
a Lester Bryce-Jones.
Do you recognize him?
Don't think so.
Nice boy though.
He isn't now.
When you employ people,
do you check
their drugs record?
If they'd been busted
we wouldn't have hired them.
How would you know?
If they put it on a form?
Can I see a form?
(Car horn)
Mr. Frost?
Yes?
Can you come with us, please?
Do what?
Mr. Mulletts orders sir.
You are joking?
Look, all right!
You're going to
be in big trouble!
I'll tell ya,
(unintelligible).
All right I can
manage, thank you!
Right.
Good morning.
Thank you for coming.
Now I've called
this conference
in view of the
recent press story
about the Black Farm Murder.
It may seem that there's
been a new development
and that we...
Jailed the wrong man.
There's no evidence
of that Mr. Longford.
A man was tried and convicted
after a thorough investigation
by a senior officer.
Jack Frost?
Yes.
So this confession in
Spain by Mr. Ferdie Giggs,
you don't recognize
it as genuine?
That is an
uncorroborated interview
given by a foreign journalist
with someone we don't know.
You don't know him?
But he was interviewed
as a suspect at
the time, wasn't he?
By Detective
Inspector Frost.
As far as we are aware,
he was never seriously
considered as a suspect.
He claims he was at
the scene of the crime.
Does he?
He'd have to be, if he did it.
What do police records show?
Mr. Giggs' statement
will be looked into
and any necessary
action taken.
Even reopening
the whole enquiry?
Yes, if the
evidence warrants it.
So, if you'll bear with me
until the full
facts are available,
I'll call another
conference then.
Thank you very much.
Still no Frost?
No, sir.
Well, who's looking for him?
Mr. Toolan.
Well,
several things to make
the day an interesting one.
First, apart from being dead,
he was very healthy.
Suntanned.
Could have
used a health club.
Two, he was gay.
There are certain well,
clear indications.
This could explain
why he used mascara
and faint face make-up.
Might have been
an actor of course.
Three, dental work
wasn't done here.
Maybe America.
It's a long way
to go to the dentist.
Four, he had a severe
fracture of the tibia,
maybe ten years old.
So he took painkillers.
He wasn't a druggie, though.
I'll fill this in and
Diana will give you a copy.
A. Disease or condition
leading directly to death,
Massive constriction
of the throat.
Otherwise
asphyxiation by hanging.
That's definite now, sir?
Yes.
B. Other disease or
condition leading to
A. Drugs overdose,
specifically painkillers
dextroproproxyphene,
which may have produced
unconsciousness.
I see.
C. Have I reported
the case to the coroner
for further action?
Yes, I have.
Which will presumably result
in a verdict of
death by misadventure.
Could it have been murder?
If he was unconscious,
he could hardly
have hanged himself.
Unless he was experimenting.
We'll leave those subtleties
to the coroner, shall we?
Evidence of
identification, your problem.
Diana will give you dental
records and fingerprints
so you can check them with
your usual due diligence.
Found out anything
about him, sergeant?
Not much.
But if it's foul play
it passes to
a senior officer.
Oh, Jack.
Well, how are you?
Well, it's very
nice of you to ask,
since I gather you issued
a warrant for my arrest.
Nonsense, Jack,
I just needed you
back here in a hurry.
Why don't you sit down.
All right, thank you.
Now, things are in a real...
You do realize you're still
on the strength don't you?
Didn't you get my
letter of resignation?
Of course.
You handed it to me yourself.
I've kept it here
under lock and key.
Now I realize it was written
in emotional circumstances.
Yes, it was.
I just wanted to give
you time to reconsider.
Well, both of us
time to reconsider.
That's very nice.
And there's me imagining
that you were over the moon.
Jack, I won't deny that
Iife has been quieter
over the last month.
Until lately, anyhow.
But you're missed, Jack.
Sorely missed.
You do realize....
I heard about your
application for promotion.
Really?
Funny how news
gets round, isn't it?
Mind you it
must be a bad time
having a senior
officer retire.
Especially the
Chief Constable's darling.
That has got
nothing to do with it.
Private ambition doesn't
come into this at all.
The point is
that since you left
we've had two major
problems at this station,
both of them
connected with you.
First it was
the time sheets...
You haven't called
me back here
to talk about time
sheets, have you?
These days we need to
keep a very tight ship.
Now it's the
Black Farm Murder.
But you've seen
the press reports.
It seems we can't
settle it without you.
It seems to be a
very poor reflection
on the other
officers, doesn't it?
Because when we looked
for the file it wasn't there.
And even if it had been
I don't suppose there'd
have been anything
in it, would there?
Now I want you to
get back to that case,
and this time I want
you to do things properly.
Everything in the notebook,
everything on
the record sheet.
Expenses properly kept,
files stored on the computer.
Every problem I have in
this station at the moment
is down to you and
your slipshod ways.
Just remember,
nobody's indispensable.
Well, all right then you
probably are indispensable!
Jack.
I'm going to
tear this letter up.
No, I think I'd better
hold onto it, sir.
You never know.
One of us might
want to reconsider.
Anyway, good luck sir.
What?
With your promotion.
You know,
onward and upward.
Good morning.
Nice to see you, guv.
Thank you.
Jack?
Yes?
Oh come on tell
me, how was it?
Oh, you know, as well
as can be expected.
He said I could
either be a DI again,
or go to prison.
Oh, difficult choice, eh?
Yeah, you could...
Well, what the
hell is going on here?
You turn your
back for five minutes
and look what happens.
You're lucky your
stuff's here at all.
Mullett said put
it in the corridor.
Yeah, but who did this?
Look they've completely
ruined my filing system.
Sorry, guv, it was me.
Well, well.
WPC Hazel Wallace!
What are you doing here
without your clothes on?
I've been made up.
Detective Sergeant.
Really, good, well done.
If I'd known that I'd
have been back weeks ago.
Well, you were one reason
I asked for some time here.
Oh, really.
George, the
Riverside Apartments case.
Looks like it
might not be suicide.
Well, shouldn't I be
told about it then?
(Phone ringing)
Frost.
Yes, yes, yes it is.
Yes, all right.
Yes, she is.
All right, thank you Ernie.
That was Ernie Trigg.
He's got something
for you downstairs,
and he says...
You're never
going to believe this.
I've never seen anything...
All right, Ernie,
just try us will you?
All right.
Now, this death at
Riverside Apartments.
It's just been confirmed
as a possible suspicious.
Oh, right.
Well, these are
the fingerprints
taken at the crime
scene by the SOCOS.
Most are the victim's.
A man we think is
called Lester Bryce-Jones.
Yeah, all right,
get the lights, will you?
But this one, FP1 7,
that's an unident.
Except, see,
we've got a match.
Prints from our own files.
Identical, right?
Yes, well, that's what
it looks like Ernie.
Whose are these?
Well, that's what you're
not going to believe.
Those prints are from an
old case of yours, Jack.
The Appendix Man?
Remember?
Oh, don't be daft.
The Appendix Man
died a year ago.
He was fished
out of the river.
He was drowned,
I know 'cos I was there.
So was I Guv,
Yeah.
And then because we
couldn't identify him
he was stuffed into the
morgue for ten months.
They don't do that
without good reason.
I know that, Jack.
Come on, this is ridiculous.
Are you trying to tell me
that a bloke who
died a year ago
hops out of his coffin,
hitches a lift down to
Riverside Apartments,
commits a murder,
then nips back
to the graveyard
probably stopping off at
the Red Lion for a pint?
Well, there it is Jack.
Scientific fact.
He's called
Lester Bryce-Jones,
we think.
But we've
still not established
evidence of identity.
Check banks,
social security,
especially hospitals.
Another thing, check
gay clubs and gyms,
he was into exercise.
In more ways
than one, apparently.
(Applause)
Yes, all right, thank you.
Yes, I'm back,
but it's not all good news.
Hornrim Harry is still here.
All right, come on,
let's pay attention.
It appears that
we've got two unidents.
One old one and one new one.
Now, can anyone tell
me do they remember him?
We all do, guv.
Yes, but you
didn't though, did you?
That's The
Appendix Man, right?
Yes, well done, Jordan.
The Appendix Man.
So called because one
Saturday last summer,
when Denton Football club
was playing it's
big match at home,
he walked out of Denton
General in a hospital gown
even though his appendix
was about to burst.
A few hours later
he was fished out
of the river DED.
We thought he
might be a head case.
Yeah, well, we
checked out everything.
Hospital records,
dentistry, fingerprints.
They all came back zero.
Now, is that his
stuff down there?
Yes.
So, we had a
man without a past,
without a present
and without a future.
Everything that
we know about him
is here on this table.
Right, so, come and
take a look everybody.
Especially the newcomers.
Right.
What have we got.
Hospital gown.
Hospital bracelet
with a number on it,
and his clothes.
All good quality but worn.
Might have been
down on his luck.
Yeah, well, could be.
There was the
driving licence, guv.
Oh yes, and the
driving licence.
Now this driving licence was
found in his jacket pocket
and it's in the name
of Colin Drysdale.
But Colin Drysdale
is a local headmaster
who somehow allowed it
to be nicked by a tom.
All right.
So, there you have it.
The Appendix Man.
Sorry, sir.
Yes.
I'm new.
Was he the criminal
or the victim?
Neither.
There wasn't a crime,
only a mystery.
He died from drowning.
And if he hadn't his appendix
would have killed him.
He could have jumped,
or he could have been pushed.
There wasn't a crime then.
But there is now.
Because his prints were found
at the Riverside
Apartments crime scene.
Sorry again, sir.
Yes.
But I understood you to
say he died a year ago.
Yes, he did.
But the prints at
the scene were fresh?
Yes they were.
Stand up, what's your name?
PC Martins, sir.
Martins, well done.
Because that's your
problem for today, children.
We've got two unidents.
One died a year ago.
And the other one died
a couple of nights ago.
So how did the phantom
hand of dead male one
turn up near the
corpse of dead male two?
Answers on a postcard please.
So, come on let's
get back to work,
chop chop, off we go.
Hello, Darren.
What do you want, Mr. Frost?
I'm not doing nothing.
Well, I'm doing this.
Yeah, so I see.
I wanted you to
remember the last time
you were doing nothing.
When was that then?
It was about a year ago.
When you were living
in the amusement arcade.
You bought a stolen
driving licence for a tenner
from a tom
called Nikki Bulmer.
I think you
were just doing
one of your good
turns at the time.
You must think
I've got a memory
like a hippopotamus.
Look, I'm an
uptight citizen now.
Mr. Blair's looking after me.
I'm on the new
employment scheme
for young people.
Raising my consciousness.
That's very good, Darren.
How high is it now?
Pretty high.
I told you
everything at the time.
I definitely recall that.
You blagged like a villain.
Mr. Frost, that's a cliche.
You remember what I said.
There was a drugs bust,
I dropped the
licence on the floor.
That's what I said
last time, isn't it?
Tell me something Darren,
if there hadn't
been a drugs bust,
how would you have got rid
of that driver's licence?
I mean you must have
known someone who'd take it,
someone who'd move it on.
Come on, you can
tell me, can't you?
Come on, you want
Mr. Blair to be proud of you.
All right, all right, look.
There's that arty club
up on Felix Street.
The Cave Club.
The barman there
sells stuff like that
right over the counter.
Glasgow today is such
a fashionable subject,
is it not?
And in contemporary painting
it helps to be Scottish,
don't you think?
That's two thousand
five hundred,
and the big oil is four.
Excuse me a moment.
Can I help you at all?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
You can tell me
about these paintings.
Well,
the first thing I can tell you
is they're not paintings.
Prints.
Etchings in fact.
Are they valuable?
It depends on your standards.
Possibly the lower hundreds.
Is there any way
of tracing their, um...
Provenance?
Yeah.
Not easy to say.
Paintings by leading artists
are generally catalogued.
Lesser work like this
usually ends up with
the smaller collector.
Then they could
have been nicked?
In that case wouldn't
they be known to the police?
If you do come across
anything about them,
would you mind
giving us a call?
That's my provenance.
Denton CID.
Goodbye.
Thanks.
Here.
Someone told me
something about you.
Said if I needed
to change my life,
you could help me out.
How can I help you out?
This person said
you might be able to
fit me up with new papers,
driving licence.
That sort of thing.
I think you're fitting me up.
Who said that?
Well, I don't know who it was,
because I talk to a
lot of people, you see.
Cause I'm a policeman,
from Denton CID.
Got all the papers you
want then, haven't you?
I've got some more here.
I'd like you to
have a look at.
Have you ever seen
this bloke before.
Has he ever been in here.
A while ago.
Never seen him in my life.
All right, hey, just a minute.
I haven't finished yet.
Come here.
So you wouldn't have sold
him this driving licence?
About a year ago,
Iook at the name,
Colin Drysdale.
No, I didn't.
Now don't you tell me porkies,
because I know you
bought this driving licence
off a young tearaway
called Darren Matthews.
Don't tell me that you
didn't try to sell it on.
Not to him I didn't.
Right
Mr. Frost!
So you're a free man then?
What?
I'd no idea you came here.
Donald's joining me later.
Care for a cocktail?
Oh, yeah.
I see what you're saying.
Not now, thanks very much.
I've got to dash.
Perhaps another time.
Excuse me?
We're making
enquiries about a murder.
Wondered if you
knew who he is?
He could have
worked here once.
Yeah, course he did.
Casualty porter.
Well, who is he, then?
That's, Les.
Les for Lester?
Lester Bryce-Jones?
Les for Leslie.
Leslie Jackson.
Leslie, Leslie...
You could be in luck.
Listen, I've had a thought.
Maybe the
Appendix Man was gay.
Leslie Jackson was.
Who?
Lester Bryce-Jones
was also Leslie Jackson.
Let's see.
Leslie Peter Jackson,
born 1960 Perth.
Check him out
with Scottish police.
Not a lot of use, George.
This is Perth,
Western Australia.
Australian police then.
There's an address here,
Infirmary Road.
Before he moved to
Riverside Apartments.
But I'm going to get
PC Martins to check it out.
Good.
He went to the Captain
Cook High School, Perth.
And then medical orderly
at the Les Patterson
General Hospital.
Don't tell me.
He then went on
to the Edna Everage
State University?
No he didn't.
What?
Come on,
Les Patterson's a
character invented by an
actor, Barry Humphreys...
Oh... sod.
He's made all this stuff up?
I'm afraid so, love, yes.
He's probably not
even Leslie Jackson.
No, I wouldn't
have thought so.
Hazel, come on,
don't worry about it.
Happens to us all.
I tell you what,
I'd like you to show me
these Riverside Apartments.
Come on, let's go.
Thanks George.
All right.
Body was over here, guv.
Oh yes?
The Appendix
Man's fingerprints
were on a whiskey
glass on this table.
Ah, I tell you what.
You could make us
both a cup of coffee.
Guv, I thought you'd
come to see a crime scene.
Yes, but the golden
rule at a crime scene
is always check the things
that other people
haven't bothered with.
Everything was
checked thoroughly.
Was it.
Good.
That means that
someone's check
the Saint Martin's
School of Art?
They should have done
because this book was
borrowed four years ago
Mr. Mullet's going to
have one hell of a fine
if someone doesn't
return it soon.
And while you're at it,
see if you can find out
the name of the borrower.
See if he did an art
course there in '94,
also see if his name
could possibly have
been Lionel Jacques.
All right.
Now then, tell me something?
These paintings,
any good are they.
I'm a Stag at Bay man myself.
It seems it's
collector's stuff.
It's worth a few thousand.
Really?
Well, not bad for a
hospital porter then, is it?
I suppose you've checked
with the Art Squad, have you?
Haven't come up with anything.
Oh, yeah.
Now is anything missing?
Because if it is murder
it helps to have a motive.
Could be something missing.
How would we know?
Ah, yes well there's the rub.
I tell you what,
if it is murder how
did the killer get in,
because you said that the
front door was locked?
Yes, but the veranda
doors were open.
Oh, were they?
Oh, look it's a cat flap.
Come on puss, come in.
There you go.
Hey I thought you were making
us two a cup of coffee?
Forget what you take, guv.
One lump or two.
Two.
(Talking)
What do you think about all
these other keys then, pussy?
What do you think
about all of them?
They've been checked too.
The Yales fit the apartment.
Yeah.
But these don't, do they?
No, guv.
No.
Do you know what I think?
I think if you can't find
any of his paperwork,
or his passport,
anything like that,
that may mean
that he's got a place
somewhere else, you know.
It's all right,
dear, it's all right.
It's all been cleared up.
Okay.
Now then, you
came in with the key.
So what did you see?
Just take me through it.
You were looking
for the cat, yes?
Yes.
Actually I liked
it when he's away.
Feeding the cat gave
me something to do.
Just tell me,
what did you see
before you found poor
Mr. Bryce-Jones?
I saw pills on the table.
Some on the floor.
Then the cat was
yowling and then I saw...
Yes, yes, of course.
Just think back Leonie.
When you first came in.
Was anything missing?
The picture, you mean.
Yes, most probably.
So, go on.
When I came home from
school the door was open.
There was a painting
on the easel there.
Then when I came for
Shangri it had gone.
(Phone ringing)
Do you know much
about painting, Leonie?
Not a lot.
But I think it was a Hockney.
A Hockney?
Are you sure?
Well, it had to be, didn't it?
It had a swimming pool in it.
Right, thanks.
Just stay where you are,
we'll be right over.
Guv.
That address
in Infirmary Road.
Someone's been using it.
A man in a hospital coat.
Really?
Thank you.
Thank you very much, Leonie.
The neighbors say
he comes quite often.
You know, picks
up mail and stuff.
All right.
Aha.
Look at this, guv.
What?
Addressed to
Mr. Leslie Jackson.
Right.
Call for backup.
I want this whole
place searched.
Alpha bravo 16 to Control?
Hazel!
Oh, thank you.
Mr. Frost,
you might have said.
You're not one, are you?
Not one what?
Not a policeman.
The barman at the
Cave Club told me...
Yes, only in the afternoons.
And you shouldn't listen
to gossip, should you.
And you always seemed so nice.
Yeah, well.
Yeah, talking
about that Cave Club.
Is it a good place
to meet people, is it?
I should hope so,
that's what it's for.
Did you ever see him there?
No.
I've never seen
him before in my life.
Is he a friend of yours?
No not really.
I never knew him
when he was alive.
Now no-one seems to know
him now that he's dead.
Oh dear, is he?
Found drowned in a
river about a year ago.
What about this one?
Have you ever seen him there?
His name's Leslie Jackson.
Now him I'm not sure.
I think I just might have.
I'll go and ask
Donald, all right?
Yes, please do, Brian.
Yes?
Sorry, Mr. Frost.
Donald says nice
man but definitely no.
Oh, right.
Thank you for trying Brian.
Could I have
another pot of tea?
Of course you can, Inspector.
Morning, Jack.
Morning Harry.
I've had ten quid's worth
on pump number three.
There you go.
Do you want a
receipt for that?
Yes please.
And I want one of these,
a Chicken Duchesse
with a light curry
sauce on wholemeal.
That's expired, I see.
Here, you couldn't
let me have twenty or so
of those blank
receipts could you?
You'd be helping me out
with a very important case.
Yeah, course I can Jack.
You're a good man.
And the sarnie's on the house.
Oh, cheers.
I've seen his Bank Manager.
Guess how much in his account?
Twenty five thousand.
Maybe I should be
a hospital porter.
Maybe.
Anything from
St. Martin's School of Art?
Yes.
He was known as
Lionel Jacobs there.
Enrolled autumn 1993,
and then quit after Christmas.
He took a course in...
Basket-weaving?
Not at all.
Figure drawing.
Did quite well.
He said he came from
Brisbane in Australia.
So that's Perth, now Brisbane.
I bet he came from Sydney.
Unless it was Melbourne.
What about Adelaide?
Anyone seen Jack Frost?
No.
Only Mr. Mullett's
getting a bit rattled.
He wants things
tidying up quick.
What's the news?
Well, he's got another
interview on Wednesday.
So, fingers crossed.
Ok, thanks very much.
Art squad.
They need a
detailed description
on those paintings.
But they do say
there was a Hockney
among the pictures
stolen from Black Farm.
Pity Jack's lost
the file, isn't it?
Yeah, that's nice.
I feel better already.
That's because I'm
giving you deep healing
along with the massage.
Got many clients, have you?
A lot of corporate ones, yes.
I've heard it
changes people's lives.
We've helped a lot of
people discover themselves.
Trouble with me is
I'm always so busy.
There.
Well, if you
can't find a window,
I can always give you
a twenty minute massage
at your desk.
Assuming you've
got a quiet desk.
Would you like me to
take your business number?
Yes.
Yeah, I would.
That's a very good idea.
There it is.
Oh no.
Not here too.
Morning, Gaynor.
Just go through and undress,
I'll be with you in a minute.
I am busy, as you can see.
Yes, nice work
if you can get it.
I assume this is about
the man across the hall?
Lester Bryce-Jones.
Yes, if that
was his real name.
He seems to be using
quite a lot of names recently.
Did he?
I wouldn't know.
I knew very little about him.
That'll be fifteen
pounds please.
Yes.
All right.
Your daughter, Leonie
has been very helpful.
Yes I know.
She's also very upset.
Isn't it time
you left her alone?
She's a very clever girl.
Does she know a
lot about modern art?
About art?
Not much, she's only fifteen.
So you would say
that she wouldn't know
the difference between
a hockeystick and a Hockney?
A Hockney?
She reckons that she
saw a Hockney painting
in Lester Bryce's
flat that afternoon.
Did she?
Only it isn't there now.
Yes, well, I'd say
that's about as likely
as seeing the
Royal Yacht Britannia
in the Denton River,
wouldn't you?
Leonie is smart,
but I wouldn't trust
her with your investments.
Now, can you see
your own way out?
Ah, Frost.
Ah, sir.
Very glad to hear you've
got another interview.
I want you in my
office immediately.
I'm just on my way...
Whatever it is, it can wait.
The Black Farm murder can't.
I've got the
press all over me.
Now, have you found that file?
I'm still looking for it.
And I want your time sheets.
And your petrol expenses.
And your report on
the Riverside Murder.
And what's all this
about The Appendix Man?
Good morning, sir.
Good morning.
Just bringing your coffee.
Yes, sir.
Shall I take it upstairs?
Yes, please do yes,
thank you Sergeant Brady.
Well?
I tell you Jack,
no way those prints are wrong.
Crossed checked
in the old faithful.
Yes, but, hang on.
Not all of those prints
are ours, are they?
The Appendix Man's came
from the Pathology lab.
Because that's
where they took him
when he came out of the river.
You know Jack,
it would help a lot
if you didn't
lose all your files.
Yeah.
I don't know though.
Here, have a sandwich.
Thanks for the tea.
Morning, doc.
Remember me?
All too well.
I thought you'd
retired from the force.
Suddenly life seemed
far more pleasant.
Oh, just for once
this isn't one of yours.
Really?
Who are you doing
it for, a friend?
Knife?
What is it, Inspector?
Ah, do you remember
the Appendix Man?
How could I ever forget him?
Never identified him, did you?
Which is why he slept
in the morgue for so long.
Well, he's not
there now, is he?
No, he's not there now.
He went to an unmarked grave.
You signed the
request to the coroner.
Yes, I know.
And now I've got
to dig him up.
I beg your pardon?
We're reopening the case.
There never was a case.
The man had every
right to leave hospital
if he wanted to,
however foolish
he might have been.
As for his death,
he drowned
himself, didn't he?
I would if I was
in that kind of pain.
The truth is doc,
it's all rather embarrassing.
But they've gone
and lost your original
pathology report.
So I thought
I'd just pop in here
and see if you've got
a copy in your files.
Diana.
Will you see what you can
do for this impossible man?
Thank you.
DC Jordan?
Joanna Kenwothy
at Ansty Galleries.
I thought you might
be interested.
Someone's just
offered us a painting
we feel very doubtful about.
No a woman.
We're awfully
busy at the moment,
but if you wanted
to stop by sometime.
There.
Everything you need?
All right.
Thank you.
There is just one thing.
Could you explain to
me exactly what you do
when you perform
a post mortem.
I'm sure Dr. Simpkins would
be delighted to show you.
Do come through.
No no, sorry
I didn't mean that.
I meant how do you actually
make out the report?
It's perfectly simple.
The doctor does
the examination.
I make a detailed record.
I do a dental report.
Take fingerprints.
Report on vital organs,
cause of death.
Ah, you take fingerprints.
I wonder, would you
mind taking mine?
What?
No, you see I'm trying to
understand the process.
Trying to see if
anything could go wrong.
Nothing could go wrong.
Well?
Very well.
Thank you.
You have very warm hands.
Do you live alone?
No.
Only child?
I have a brother.
Brother.
I always wanted a brother.
Except my dad took
one look at me
and thought my mother
had suffered enough.
Yes.
Nearly finished.
All right.
I see, thank you.
Now then, so what you do
is you fill out this report,
put it in a file like that,
Thank you.
And you send it over to us.
Is that how it works?
Yes, one here, one to you.
I'm not sure I understand you.
You're saying you lost
the file we sent you?
Isn't it kept
in police records?
Well, if it
arrived at my office
it could have
ended up anywhere.
Well, then I don't think
you should take ours.
Oh, all right.
Well, just make a
copy of that will you
and send it over to my office.
Really, Mr. Frost.
Thank you.
What do I do with these?
Oh, I'd put them on file.
You never know,
save you a job,
in case I end up
on one of your slabs.
Jack!
Been looking for
you everywhere.
I want a talk about
the Black Farm Murder.
Come on Sandy,
you're talking
about eight years ago.
I'm talking now.
I warn you, Jack,
you've got a real
scandal on your hands.
Our feisty local MP's
off to see the
Home Secretary.
Sandy.
Ferdie Giggs is a small time
crook with a big time mouth
who can say anything
because he's living in Spain.
Ferdie would admit to the
Slaughter of the Innocents
if it meant he could
get a big fat check
out of one of you lot.
He says Mrs. Dale hired him
to kill her husband
for the insurance.
The Black Farm murder was
an art theft that went wrong.
Ferdie Giggs wasn't
even there the night
that Jonathan Dale
was murdered.
He was there for the
funeral though, wasn't he?
Newspaper files, Jack.
That's Ferdie Giggs, isn't it?
And that's Mrs Dale?
Yes, yes, yes, all right.
You kept this
file on the case?
Course.
That's how
newspapers function.
You couldn't let me have a
copy of that file could you.
Over at my office,
as soon as possible?
Paper co-operates
with re-investigation?
Or have you just
lost your records?
My office as soon as possible.
Thank you, Sandy.
Possibly in her early forties.
Quite intelligent
and educated.
Sunglasses, wearing
a big overcoat.
And what was the painting?
I recognized it at once.
It was a Hockney.
One of the California
swimming pool series.
No doubt you asked
about its provenance.
Yes.
That was when she said
she didn't want to sell it
and walked out.
Hockney?
Wouldn't that
be really valuable?
Yes, of course,
a small fortune.
Mrs. Dale?
Detective Inspector Frost,
Denton CID.
We met about eight years ago.
Yes, I remember.
When Jonathan was murdered.
I have been expecting you.
Ever since I read that
story about Ferdie Giggs.
Yeah, that's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
I'm sorry, but I do
have to ask you this.
Ferdie Giggs maintains
that you asked him
to do the killings so
that you could collect
the insurance money
on the paintings.
There wasn't any insurance
Jonathan never bothered.
Take a look.
It's not worth a
killing for, is it?
No.
Ferdie was a dealer.
He sold Jonathan
a few paintings.
And so Ferdie
tipped off his friends
that there was something
worth taking at the house.
but he wasn't
there that night?
No.
We'd been away
for the weekend.
The weather turned bad
an Jonathan was
worried about his beasts.
We came home on
the Saturday night
and there in the house...
Were two men, right?
One was Branson.
Who was the other?
Well, we never
found out, did we?
No, because he was wearing
a balaclava over his face.
But it couldn't have
been Ferdie Giggs,
he was too tall.
Exactly.
So what about your
husband's paintings?
One of them was
quite valuable, was it?
You mean the David Hockney.
Yes.
Yes, his brother
gave it to him.
He said he'd been given
it by Hockney himself.
Jonathan never
insured that either.
It went in the robbery,
and that was that.
Did you know it was
offered for sale yesterday.
At the Ansty Gallery.
You've found it then?
No.
It was offered for
sale by a woman.
Oh, and you thought it was me.
It wasn't.
No, well I did wonder,
but I don't
believe it was you.
Did you know a man called
Leslie Jackson, an Australian?
No, I didn't.
Should I have done?
No, it was just a thought.
Well, thank you
very much Mrs. Dale.
Does this mean I might
get the paintings back?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I honestly don't know.
Something for me?
Yeah.
Miss Grey brought this
over from the path lab,
said you've to be more
careful with it this time.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, and this stuff
just came over
from the Denton Evening Echo,
and Jack?
Yes?
Mullett wants to see you.
And he won't take
no for an answer.
Good, cos I can't
wait to see him.
I will.
Yes, I will dear.
Yes, dear.
Well?
I thought you wanted
to see me, sir.
You know I do, yes.
Now I'm being interviewed
for the post of Assistant
Chief Constable on Wednesday.
And very good
luck to you, sir.
No doubt some
people in this station
would be pleased to
see the back of me.
Oh, no.
In which case I'd appreciate
a good deal more co-operation.
Everything in
this station's fine
except for three
outstanding problems
every one to do with you.
You're not referring
to my petrol expenses,
are you, sir?
Thank you very much,
but that's not
what I meant, no.
What about the
Black Farm Murder?
Yes, here's the file.
Sorry it took so long.
They're just
newspaper cuttings.
Yes.
But we've nearly
settled the case.
Ferdie Giggs was lying.
He was only after a
Fleet Street handout.
He never was at the
scene of the crime.
We've also managed to trace
a number of the
Black Farm paintings.
Trouble is, they were in the
hands of Lester Bryce-Jones.
The victim at the
Riverside Apartments.
But, he does seem to be
linked with the Appendix Man,
so, one investigation
leads to another.
We should have this
all cleared up in,
well you know,
no time at all.
By Wednesday?
Wednesday?
Yes, probably Wednesday, yes.
Well, that's excellent.
Good.
Thank you, sir.
Oh, there is one small thing
that you could help me with.
I need an exhumation order.
Who for?
Well, I don't know his name.
He's the Appendix Man.
If you don't know his name,
how do you know you
need an exhumation?
Well, I will
know his name
when I've taken
his fingerprints.
I thought he'd
been dead a year.
Yes he has, but he's been
in the freezer in the morgue
until a couple of weeks ago,
so that should
present no problem.
You do realize
you're putting me under
the most absurd pressure?
Yes, I know sir.
If you could do
it before Wednesday.
It means that we could
close all three cases at once.
You know, just before
your interview.
You know, this job
would mean a great deal
to Elsbeth, my wife.
It means a great
deal to everyone, sir.
I just hope you get
a result, that's all.
I really had to
twist Coroner's arm.
Yes, I'm very grateful, sir.
Did you pass on
those petrol receipts?
Yes, I did.
Why?
No reason.
I just wondered if County
was pleased, that's all.
Will this take long?
No.
Not long, sir.
Yes, all right, Ernie,
come on get on with it.
Oh, right.
Now listen carefully.
This is the fingerprint
of the Appendix Man
taken from our records.
And this is the fingerprint
taken from the glass
from Riverside Apartments.
They are the same.
And this is the fingerprint
taken off the Appendix Man's
dead body this morning.
Different.
So whose are
these others then?
Well it's not so much as who,
as to why and how.
How did a stray set of
prints get into our system?
Someone wanted
to disappear?
Maybe someone
wanted him to disappear.
Someone didn't want us
to find out who he was.
Maybe he's got form.
Could you check him out?
Yeah, yeah, sure
give me an hour or so.
It still won't tell
us who did the switch.
Could someone
hack into our system?
Only someone on the inside.
It's not a very
nice thought, is it?
No, it isn't.
By the way.
Could you get a set of
prints off that file for me?
Yeah.
What is the matter with you?
Oh, I don't know.
My stomach's giving
me gip this morning.
Must have been
something I ate.
Really?
All right?
Did the dead man speak then?
Yes he did.
He said tell that
idle sod Jordan
to get down to
the art gallery
and find out who
really did offer
that Hockney for sale.
Yes, guv.
Thank you.
Guv, we've a proper ident
on Lester Bryce Jones,
alias Leslie Jackson.
What?
He was Leonard Jefford
from Adelaide, Aus..
How many more names
is he going to have?
South Australian
police had him on file.
Oh, well, he'd got form then?
Minor stuff.
He was part of the gay scene.
He was known around as a
bit of an actor and painter.
Worked as a
waiter and a deckhand,
and then in 1993,
he decided to
come to the Big Smoke
and seek his
fame and fortune.
And the poor sod ended up
as a porter in
Denton General.
Don't knock it, George.
He had twenty five
grand in the bank
and a Hockney in the cupboard.
Problem is, how did he get
it there from Black Farm?
Well, come on keep thinking.
Thank you.
All right, there you go.
Get those Black Farm
files I sent you?
Yes thank you, Sandy.
Hornrimmed Harry
was very grateful.
Cheers.
What about you?
Change your mind
about Ferdie Giggs?
I will never change my
mind about Ferdie Giggs.
He tells porkies.
He always did
and he always will.
He said he did it
so that Mrs. Dale could
claim the insurance money.
Only problem is, the
pictures were never insured.
Mrs. Dale got nothing.
Are you sure?
Course I am.
So who did kill Jonathan Dale?
Branson.
The man I put away.
There were two men, Jack.
You never found the other.
The one that got the pictures.
Well it wasn't Ferdie.
We've got the pictures back,
well most of them anyway.
Oh, great.
Who then, if it wasn't Ferdie?
If you're very good, Sandy,
you'll be the first to know.
Good afternoon.
Ah, Jack!
Yes, that's me.
The Appendix Man.
Oh, yeah, what about him?
No ident on file.
But I got another
match for you though.
You'll never guess where from.
Black Farm murder.
How could you know that?
Because I asked myself
a question, Ernie.
How could a painting that
went missing eight years ago
end up in the apartment
of a hospital porter.
The only answer
I could come up with
was the Appendix Man.
Just a minute.
You know those other
prints, the stray ones.
I got a match on them too.
Off the cover of
that pathology file.
The one marked Dead Male One.
Aah.
Inspector Frost!
Sorry if I startled
you, Miss Grey.
Just thought I'd drop by
and thank you for
letting me have that file.
Well, don't
lose it this time.
No I won't.
Unfortunately I seem to
have made another mistake.
Really?
Yes.
You see one of our rules is
that anyone who is at
the scene of a crime
must have their
fingerprints on file.
It's for elimination
purposes, you understand,
but unfortunately we
don't seem to have yours.
Mine?
Yes.
So I was wondering
if you wouldn't mind
just popping down
to the station.
You know, you've seen mine,
I'd like to see yours.
Is that really necessary?
Well, yes, I'm afraid it is.
You see we've found a set
of unidentified fingerprints
on a drinking glass
at Riverside Apartments.
And I was just wondering
if they could be yours.
Oh, yes,
I did pick up a glass.
Ah, well, that would be
it then, wouldn't it?
But unfortunately those
prints are exactly the same
as the Appendix Man's.
I don't see how
that's possible.
A mix-up in your lab?
If there was a mix up,
I apologize, of course.
But isn't it more likely
the mix-up was in your office?
Oh, yes.
It's very possible.
But you did know him
didn't you Miss Gray?
Who did I know?
The Appendix Man.
What was his name?
Ian Pri...
Ian Priest.
Thank you.
I know you felt
sorry for him once.
You shouldn't have.
He wasn't a nice man.
He was a thief
and a blackmailer.
I'm surprised that you
knew him then, Miss Grey.
He knew my brother.
David's a solicitor.
And a homosexual.
As was Ian Priest.
He made a habit of
stealing from his boyfriends.
Not just small things,
paintings, antiques.
If they complained,
he threatened
them with blackmail.
In the end he'd taken
everything from David.
And then Priest,
the Appendix
Man ended up here?
I substituted my
fingerprints for his.
I knew if you
identified Ian Priest,
the whole story
would come out
and David would be ruined.
I didn't know what to do.
I didn't think
it would matter.
He was dead anyway.
I wasn't hurting anyone.
And then you left
your fingerprints
at Riverside Apartments.
I must ask you this,
were you
involved in any way
in Ian Priest's death?
Of course not.
His death was
accidental drowning.
Yeah, well, I'm not
so sure about that.
Well, I don't know.
But I had no part in it.
And Lester Bryce-Jones,
did you recognize him?
No, I didn't.
Thank you, Miss Grey.
What's going to happen now?
Are you going to charge me?
Oh yes.
Go on get your coat.
Well, well.
Bit of a mess, isn't it?
Yes it's all the stuff
from his hideaway
in Infirmary Road.
There's his passport,
He arrived in 1993.
He wasn't even in the country
at the time of the
Black Farm Murder.
You surprise me.
And a photograph.
Isn't that the Appendix Man?
Yes.
Yes it is.
And did you know his
name was Ian Priest.
So, so he knew Leslie Jackson
before he went into hospital.
Of course.
It all fits.
What does?
Ian Priest knows
that he's very ill
and he's got to
go into hospital.
And he's worried in case
the authorities
find out who he is
and links him with
the Black Farm murder.
So, what does he do?
Empties his
pockets and goes in
with a stolen
drivers' licence.
So there he is,
Iying on the hospital bed,
with a burst appendix
when who comes
rattling down the ward
with his bedpans
but Leslie Jackson.
He killed him?
No, no, no.
No, no, I reckon
he tries to help him.
Says he'll get him
out of the hospital.
Find him a private doctor.
But of course,
once Priest
leaves the hospital,
he's finished.
He's too far gone.
Leslie Jackson
finds out about that,
and there's only one
way to keep it quiet.
Come on, man!
Don't die on me now!
Jesus!
But you don't know that?
I know that
I don't know that.
I can guess it though.
And then a year later someone
kills Lester Bryce-Jones
and one thing
leads to another?
Yes, I hope so.
Who then?
That's what we've
got to find out.
Debbie?
I'll just be a moment.
I'm sorry, I can't...
Not you again?
Mmm, I was just having a
look at my astral chart.
Trouble is I can't remember
what my star sign is.
Look, I've got a client.
That's all right, go
ahead, don't mind me.
I only came in
looking for a painting.
Pamela, would you?
What painting?
A painting of a swimming
pool by David Hockney.
And what makes you
think it's here?
Because you tried to
sell it two days ago,
at the Ansty Galleries.
The attendant identified you.
Do you want to know how?
By your tattoo.
Well Mrs. Viner.
Do you want me to
get a search warrant?
Or will you just
show me where it is?
That painting we found in
your shop, Mrs. Viner,
it was stolen.
In a robbery
about eight years ago.
That's nothing to do with me.
I didn't know.
That's a pity.
You should always
ask about provenance.
Did you know that Leslie
dealt in stolen paintings.
No.
Look, that day he came
home with the Hockney.
He wanted someone
to help him sell it.
Oh, really?
And what time was this?
It was in the morning.
I saw him in the hall.
He asked you to help
him sell the painting?
What sort of help?
Oh, did I know any galleries?
Collectors who might
come to my studio?
And he gave it
to you, did he?
He just gave it you,
just like that?
Yes, he did.
No, he didn't!
Because your
daughter Leonie said
that she saw the
painting in his apartment
at 4:30 when she
came home from school.
You left and came back
again, didn't you?
Why would I?
Because you realized
Leslie had something
worth a small fortune
and you wanted
your share.
Only what you
didn't know was
that he couldn't get
rid of that painting
because it
was hot stuff.
It came from a murder scene.
I didn't go back.
You had a key to the door.
You had the opportunity,
the motive and the will.
Do you know what I think?
I think that you and
Lester Bryce-Jones
were running a
nice little racket.
Clients at your studio
could buy paintings
with no questions asked.
And then you and
Leslie or Lester
or whatever his
ruddy name was
could split the proceeds.
Sorry, no way.
Oh yes.
But this time he wasn't
playing ball, was he?
So I think that you went
to have it out with him.
When you knocked at the
door and go no answer,
you used your key
to let yourself in.
And when you went in
you found Leslie up
to some deviant trick,
probably high
on painkillers
but certainly not in
a position to argue.
I don't believe this.
And then you tightened
the belt around his neck,
just to make sure.
Then you opened
the doors to the patio
so it looked as though
someone came in that way.
You returned the
key to your apartment
then you took the
painting to your studio.
Mrs. Viner, I believe
that you are responsible
for the murder
of Leslie Jackson,
alias Lester Bryce-Jones.
No, it wasn't like that.
He was unconscious.
(Knock on door)
Yes?
DC Jordan has
entered the room
with a note for DI Frost.
So he was dying
and you offered
him no assistance?
I took the painting.
I was strapped for money.
The studio earns nothing.
There are
Leonie's school fees.
I'd helped him before.
Not that I liked him.
Fact is he made
my skin crawl,
but the money was useful.
Except this time he
was cutting me out.
And as soon as
I saw that picture
I knew what it was.
But it wasn't.
What do you mean?
It was a forgery.
The painting wasn't genuine.
Morning Mullett.
Morning, sir.
A word in your ear.
I'm really sorry, sir.
Yes.
I think everyone
will be really sorry.
Yes.
Especially Mrs. Mullett.
Did they give you a reason?
Yes, they gave me a reason.
There was another candidate
that some of the
board preferred.
A woman Super
from Northumberland,
very strong on management.
Oh, well, you can't
blame yourself then.
No, I can't.
I can blame...
Who?
I don't know how you
could do it to me, Jack.
You can't blame me, I did
everything that you asked.
I cleared up my three cases.
I did my expenses.
Yes, that was what did it.
What?
It seems I foolishly failed
to check your paperwork.
You signed those petrol
receipts yourself didn't you?
Forged the signatures.
As someone on the board
was very quick to point out.
Yeah, well, I mean,
I didn't think that...
No, you didn't, did you?
My resignation.
Just get out of
my office, Jack.
Go on, get out!
Brian, are you there?
Mr. Frost.
Ah.
On your way?
Yes, yes, I am.
I'm moving into
my new house.
Well, it's my
old house actually.
Got to start learning
how to be a domestic
animal once again.
You should get
yourself a cat.
Well, me, no.
Can't stand them.
Anyway, we shall
miss you, Mr. Frost.
Well, I'll miss
you too, Brian.
You've been a great support.
And Donald.
Is he here?
I never did get to...
I'll tell you a
little secret, Mr. Frost.
There is no Donald.
It's all just me.
Donald left three months ago.
Goodbye, Brian.
Jack.