Brought to you by Ramensoupsubs
Translators: suebee, mell, mJ1991, mandu00, one_lone_star
Timers: warunee123, elle_SJ, rayne86, RamenSoupFan, metalguy, tern3
Editors/QC: swtsrwlove, melijay, suebee
Typesetters: sasa7320, beauty0fparting, samsters, rayne86, binchaeln
Encoder: melijay
Uploader: melijay, tiff80, kinubic, azngrl1198
Raw Provider: K-Aigo Media
[Before filming]
[Kookjong returning back to his singing]
[Reverting back to his sweet image...]
Hello?
Hello Family! This is Yoo Jaesuk!
This will be our last time filming the show.
[Reporting the Family's last destination]
We will be returning to Kangol village.
Please don't be late and meet in front of the village hall by 10AM on Monday.
This really is over, and out. Goodbye~
[The Grasshopper's final report]
[At the same time...]
[The last New Family members gets a call...]
-Hello?
-Yes, it's been awhile.
[Who are they?]
Okay, see you then.
[Quirky Shiyeon]
Oh, we've been there before.
[Clumsy Chunhee]
I better pack a lot then. I'm going to pack this much!
[Sweet and Savage Lady Yejin]
[A final memorable trip with the precious former members]
[Day of filming]
[Returning to Kangol village!]
[Summer of 2008...]
[At the beautiful bamboo forest in Kangol village]
[The Family created beautiful memories]
[The Family will make their last memories while recalling the past]
[In front of the village hall]
[The first Family member to arrive?]
[The diligent Game Devil]
[Followed by the Elder's arrival...]
[And so the Family arrives one by one]
Lee Hyo! Why don't you pick up when I call you?!
She usually never picks up her phone.
-Hi!
-Hey...
[And Daesung finishes up the arrivals!]
-Hyori...
-What?
[A noblewoman's attire?]
-You must be doing well nowadays...
-It's fake!
-Buy me a mink coat, oppa.
-Alright.
-Haejin, it's your first time here isn't it?
-No, I came on as a guest here.
-Remember, the bamboo forest?
-That's right, that's right.
Who's that?
[Just then]
[The first former Family member to arrive...]
[Eager since they haven't seen each other in so long]
[4th dimensional] [Quirky beauty Park Shiyeon]
[Shiyeon returning for the Family's final filming]
I haven't seen Shiyeon's walk in so long.
It really has been awhile seeing her walk.
Have you been well?
Oh! Is that a couple ring? What is that? Are you wearing a couple ring?
[A ring?]
-I just felt like wearing a ring.
-Oh really?
Buy me a ring!
A diamond one!
[The flustered oppas...]
You want a ring, a fur coat...
Lee Chunhee is here!
[The second car slowly approaching]
[The second Family that has got Stepmother Kim so delighted?]
[The return of Chunderella, Lee Chunhee]
Hey, it's the shoes Chunhee bought for us last time.
I thought you guys would all be wearing them, but I guess not...
Why is his hair all done?
[Getting mistreated right when he arrives...]
Do you think you're filming a drama right now?
Shiyeon doesn't know my image yet...
What are you talking about?
[All of Korea knows your image...]
Here she comes!
[Finally, the last Family member arrives]
[An elegant force(?) already emitting from the car...]
[Interested]
[Who is that?]
[All the local chickens won't dare to meet her eye...]
[Sweet and savage] [Lady Yejin, Park Yejin]
[Happily greeting everyone...]
They all are changing to an urban image!
[The furry hat people are not pleased...]
It's because we've lived in the city for awhile now.
[The well off city siblings]
You should have come wearing your Queen Seondeok outfit!
Why?! She's not on it anymore!
Then come back as the dead...
[Just saying whatever since it's the final show...]
We have all returned...
For the third time, to Kangol village.
With Miss Shiyeon, Mr. Chunhee, and Miss Yejin...
Why are you being so respectful?
It's the last show...
Remember, he talked to us formally when we started the show.
That's right! Back then, you guys were all Miss or Mister.
Alright, our last show...
Let's just get on with it.
Alright! Let's start our last show!
Let's go!
[The place where the Family will make their final memories...]
[Their memories in Kangol village engraved in their memories]
[Goodbye]
[Family Outing]
I heard Jongkook and Yejin talk to each other casually now?
I just dropped the Kim from Kim Jongkook oppa.
[Growing closer after shooting a music video together]
Ah... Why, why, why, why?
Just to be more comfortable, why else?
But he said not to tell Hyori unnie about it...
That we don't speak formally anymore.
[Kick]
[Kook & Hyo, the fighting couple to the very end]
You want some of this?!
Let's end it right here!
This is where Yejin caught her first chicken!
Right there by the net!
[Old memories rushing back~]
It's like a historical site.
Yeah, they closed it all off.
[Right in front of the Grandmother's house...]
Wow, I remember this.
Hello!
[Jun Youngnam] [Jo Myungyub] [41st Family] [Kim Gongsoon] [Hwang Jungim]
[Happy to be able to meet again...]
Last time Father was here.
But it's just you and your friends this time?
Yes, the Grandfather went to the dentist.
So we're going to meet him on the way.
We'll finish all the chores you left for us. Have fun on your trip.
[Trusting the Family with their home]
[The grandmothers head off on a trip]
[Please return... with wonderful memories]
Our last list of chores.
Hyori! Harvest the citrons!
Alright, let's go!
[1. Harvest the citrons]
[Part 1. The Return of the Family]
Ok, let's head over to the citron field.
[The sticks used to harvest]
I started poking you in the butt here too...
How about one for old time's sake?
This isn't a good memory for me...
Alright, shall we go?
[A duel with the boom mic?!]
Let's go!
[Carrying the long poles to harvest citrons]
Be careful here!
[Huh?]
[The only one getting stuck is Chunhee]
[Oh... my... Chunhee...]
[Welcome to Clumsy Chunhee]
[The impatient Jongkook trying to help...]
Haejin! This is how you walk through...
[Unchanged(?) despite the time that has passed, Clumsy Chunhee]
It's like we're in the Amazon!
Here's the bamboo trees we climbed up last time.
Oh yeah, I remember coming here.
And Sooro oppa was giving us acting lessons.
[The Family still walking down memory lane]
Variety is hard.
[Still strong] [Sooro's comical charisma!]
That's right. That was when Sooro hyung said variety shows are hard.
We dug the bamboo shoot out here!
That's right.
And Chunhee pulled it out so clumsily...
[Chunhee getting stuck on a tree!]
[Whether it's the past or present...]
-Sooro hyung!
-Yeah?
We played the game over here!
-Haejin, do you remember?
-Yes.
[Seeing who could hang on to the bamboo tree the longest]
Back then we weren't completely certain of Chunhee's clumsy ways.
If Sooro hyung got picked for a team, Chunhee would get picked for the rival team.
His face would turn red and he'd ask for a rematch...
Just one more try!
[Hard to imagine Chunderella's competiveness?]
Wow, the citrons look really ripe.
[Arriving at the citron field]
So this is the citrons to make citron tea?
[The deliciously ripe citron]
You can smell the fragrance.
Yeah, you can.
So we just hit it?
Oh, like that!
Chunhee, what are you doing?!
[Only sending down a shower of leaves~]
The two clumsy people are next to each other.
[Stepmother Kim comes for 1:1 instructions]
There you go.
[Of course Stepmother Kim is the best at nagging Chunderella]
There, and one behind you.
Whoa! It's in my hood.
It smells so good~
I know, it does. Can we just eat it?
[The Elder, peeling one to try the taste...]
[What does it taste like?]
Is it good? Is it good?
[Jaesuk also tries...]
[The citron seeds automatically spilling out??]
[Like someone knocked out his teeth...]
[Encore?]
[The Nation's MC even making citron seeds funny!]
Hyori, you do it too!
-Why are you asking a girl to do that?!
-Just do it!
-I'll hit you!
-Just once!
Let's have all three girls do it!
Come on, get over here!
Lead actress in a drama!
[Confused] [Shiyeon starts it off]
Like you walked into the bamboo tree!
And do your walk when you walk into the tree!
-Is it okay for us to do this to our actressess?
-Of course!
Noona!
Yeah?
[Smack]
[Showing a proper(?) demonstration...]
Shiyeon, did you really hurt yourself?
Yejin, it's your turn!
[Giving it her all in the performance(!)]
Don't be good to me!
[Lady Yejin's turn]
You used to not care about these things~
[Nasaly]
[Mm~Mmm~]
[It's been awhile] [Lady Yejin's cute nasal sounds]
Pretend you're Princess Cheonmyeong getting smacked...
Hey!
Do it right!
[As expected... Lady Yejin...]
[The Sweet and Savage girl has returned!]
You can't hit me for real!
[How will Hyori's acting be?]
[A real facial act!]
Nice!
[As expected from the Family's Main Madam Hyori!]
So fun!
This is... This is... This is the taste of variety!
(11;52): [Back to harvesting the citron...]
Yejin, do well!
Oppa, why isn't it falling down?
How do I hit it?
You used to be a monster back in the days!
I just got so accustomed to city life...
You just try to hit it over here...
[Huh?] [Jongkook kindly explaining how to do it for Yejin]
Are you trying to help Yejin?
When Yejin wasn't here, you'd follow me around everywhere~
Oh really, he did?
Yeah, it was no joke.
When I was around he'd try to flirt with me!
[Fake scandal...]
Ah~ I'm scared~
Yejin, be careful!
Yejin, you said you're scared?
Don't lie!
You're being so tricky!
[The chicken catching Yejin... is saying she's scared of citron...]
If it falls on your head...
-You're so tricky!
-Yeah you are!
[Tricky and sly? Savage Yejin?]
Jeez hyung, she probably has her reasons~
-Oh, what the heck?!
-What's with you?!
[Jongkook constantly sticking up for Yejin]
The only one on my side...
The only one by your side lately is Jongkook, isn't it?
They filmed a music video together...
[Jongkook's new song
<Don't be Good to Me> M/V]
[Lady Yejin as the leading lady!]
[The soft scent of love(?)~]
Was there a highlight point in the music video?
Oh with me?
I started whining and took his music so he'd chase me.
[This scene!]
[Stealing what he was looking at]
[Whine]
[Awkward]
[Embarrassed]
Show us! Come on you two!
Why do we have to?!
Don't be good to me~
Did you write that thinking of Hyori?
No!
Don't be good to me, because it makes me like you...
Don' be good to me, if you're not even going to be mine...
-Oh, that's pretty much it!
-Really?!
[Oh... Pretty similar to my lyrics]
Isn't this like a Gag Concert skit?
Alright!
Wait, you want me to sing?
Yeah, act while you sing.
[Please don't be good to me anymore...]
[One Man pleading her not to be good...]
[and the One Girl clueless to how he feels...]
[Cute] [Cute]
Oh, did oppa pick this?
Uh... why!
[Awkward]
[Jongkook awkward no matter how you see it!]
What the heck was that?! "Uh... why!"
We had to film this part 5 times because of me...
[Jaesuk suddenly standing in the center]
Why are you standing there, move away!
Let's just part ways here!
Just give each of us a camera...
[Plop]
[Excellent timing...]
[As well as Hyori's butt poke...]
[And so the Family's final chore ends...]
[Part 2. The Family's Last Battle!]
Alright, let's play a game!
It's been awhile...
[The Family's Last Game in the empty rice field]
We'll just play a last game with everyone. A simple game, just for fun.
[The two teams will try to make each other fall off the monkey bars to win]
Our first game was on an empty field too.
We jumped over the haystacks.
Yeah, and I saved you all that day.
[Falling Hyori actively playing]
Oh, that's right.
Lee Hyori gave it her all that day.
I'll play modestly for the last game.
Park Yejin, get out here!
You must have been itching for this!
[The Live and Die Together Sisters reunite on Family]
[The last battle to end it all today]
Alright everyone, so this is our team!
[Team Chunhee] [Team Yejin]
[Jongshin, Jongkook, Hyori, Haejin] [vs] [Sooro, Jaesuk, Shiyeon, Daesung]
[Round 1. Fight]
Everyone ready?!
-Set...
-Hold on!
Go!
Come out! Come out!
You come out!
-Are you coming?!
-If you go, I'll go!
[The Elder] [The Family's Weaklings] [The Grasshopper]
[The Elder jumping on to the bars...]
Hold on, grab my feet!
[Finally, they meet!]
[Just then]
[Jongkook's surprise attack]
[He had fearlessly entered enemy lines...]
[But now he's caught by Kookjong]
[The Game Devil goes to save the Grasshopper]
[But...]
[The Grasshopper's back splits in a whale fight]
[TN: "A shrimp's back splits in a whale fight" meaning "An innocent bystander gets hurt"]
[In the end, Jaesuk falls]
[Chunderella climbing the top of the bars]
[Now it's
Chunderella vs Stepmother Kim]
Ah! Sooro hyung! Ah!!
[And now Daesung climbs up too]
[The Elder suddenly coming forward...]
Jongshin oppa, get out of the way!
[Gasp gasp...]
[The tired old man needs to look after his body...]
[He's even an nuisance for his own team...]
[What made him want to come out...]
[The Elder falls]
[Pathetic even in the final game...]
Now! Now!
[The Game Devil hanging alone]
[Kookjong from below!]
[Chunderella from above!]
[Sooro falls]
[And now Daesung is surrounded...]
Yejin, go!
[And now, she has come...]
[Savage Yejin has appeared!]
Oppa, sorry.
[Apologizing... but her feet... so savage...]
Daesung, what the heck are you doing?! GET UP!
Why did you climb up here?!
[Seriously, why did you...]
[The impatient Kookjong comes forward]
He's coming! Chunhee, kick him!
Chunhee, kick him!
[Huh...??
They're on the same team...]
Oh, sorry!
[Always clumsy...]
-KICK HIM!
-Chunhee, he's on our team!
[His butt slips through]
[Caught]
[Push]
[Endure!]
Yejin, just step on him! Step on him!
[Or fall down!]
[There's no mercy in games!]
Haejin, push Yejin!
[Pow] [Pow] [Pow]
[Being attacked on his arms and legs]
[Just then]
[The final blow]
[Chunhee... must be wondering why he came back to Family...]
[Endure...]
[Resisting to the very end...]
[But then reality...]
[Such a clumsy manner...]
[Clum...sy...Chun...Hee...]
[Chunhee is out]
[Team Chunhee] [Remaining players] [Team Yejin]
[Jongkook, Hyori, Haejin] [Shiyeon, Yejin, Daesung]
[A foreboding force...]
[Coming closer to Yejin...]
Yejin! Yejin! Behind you!
[Hyori is coming]
[Flustered]
Hurry up and get up here!
Oh no!
[The siege slowly coming closer]
[The closing horror...]
(Oh no Yejin...)
[Lady Yejin... Will she be able to escape this?]
Ah... This is scary, hold on...
[Hyori, was climbing with such force earlier...]
Ah, I'm scared!
[Tremble...] [Tremble...]
What the heck are you doing?!
Yejin, just fall down!
Just slip through!
[Two people are trying to attack Yejin]
[Daesung isn't really much help...]
Nuna, just slip your butt through the bars.
She's like an octopus!
[Yejin, resisting them by herself pretty well...]
Yejin is seriously so good at this.
[It's been awhile since we've seen the Fight Til Death Sisters]
[Tickle] [Tickle]
Good job Yejin! Good job!
[Yejin's counterattack has begun!]
Take off her socks!
[Hot pack?]
[Gathering the feet adorned with hot packs]
[Following to the hay~]
Unnie, sorry~
[Hyori is out]
Yejin nuna, take care of Haejin hyung.
Why do I have to?!
[Pushing Yejin from behind...]
[Haejin, you're dead meat]
[She's no longer Sweet Yejin!]
Yejin is amazing.
[Savage Yejin's powerful kick]
[At his wit's end]
[That's what you get for your surprise attack...]
[Yejin attacking rapidly and indiscriminately]
[In the end...
Haejin is out]
That's it! That's it!
We have 3 people on our team!
[Team Chunhee] [Remaining players] [Team Yejin]
[Jongkook] [Shiyeon, Yejin, Daesung]
It's 1 against 3!
I'll take care of this.
[Nimble Daesung!]
[As soon as he arrives!]
[His confidence was futile...]
What the heck?!
[Bewildered]
Why the heck did you go all the way there?!
[Daesung is out]
[Now the remaining players are Jongkook vs Shiyeon and Yejin]
It's ok. You girls can win this!
[The two ladies just as strong as the men!]
[10 years of fitness... Radient Kookjong!]
[Kookjong, politely moving to the enemy side]
[Savage Yejin kicks him on arrival]
[Enduring the relentless high kick attacks]
[Flustered]
[Kim Kookjong trying to endure it!]
[Shiyeon, moving on from her high kick attack]
[Now moving on to phase 2!]
[Useless attack... Shiyeon is out]
It's these two again!
[Somehow it's these two left again...]
[In front of the watching Hyori]
[Of all things, these two...]
Don't be good to me!
Do your music video, you two!
[For some reason, a peculiar atmosphere...]
Why are you so shy all of a sudden?
I don't know, since I acted with him I turned out this way...
[So bashful...]
Like I want to be nicer to him.
JUST DO SOMETHING! FALL IN LOVE OR PLAY THE GAME!
[However...]
[Like this...]
[Or that...]
We promised to be nicer to each other.
[And One Woman just observing everything]
[Holding on to her arm]
[Thank you, oppa~]
[You're welcome...]
(Take a look at them...)
Oh, they're going all out.
Did anyone see Hyori's eyes light up?
She's been cooking him breakfast and dinner all this time...
I helped increase your muscles...
[Hyori, don't be good to me...]
Are you going to date her or not?
[Their hearts... beating for one another]
It's a little weird between the two of them.
[Does the One Man's heart belong...]
[To Yejin...]
[Or Hyori...]
Yejin, you can attack me.
[To make it easier for Yejin]
[Kookjong's consideration...?]
[What will she do now...]
[Of course! It's Savage Yejin]
[There's no romance in games!]
Oppa, sorry!
[The final blow!]
[As expected, Savage Yejin!]
[She shouldn't have even bothered apologizing...]
(I shouldn't have trusted her...)
-Oppa, that's how it goes.
-Did you see how Yejin just kicked you?
[Just toying with Jongkook's heart]
[The Sweet and Savage Lady Yejin]
For the next round, let's just have the men play.
[Team Chunhee] [Team Yejin]
Sounds good.
Let's make it lively!
(Jaesuk, come out!)
Let's just do 1 on 1, and quit trying to trick me.
[The Elder focused on beating Jaesuk]
[But the Game Devil steps up...]
[Gasp...]
[Retreat to stay alive!]
[Shaking the monkey bars]
[His legs too short once again...]
[Slip~]
[The pathetic short-legged Elder...]
You ran away?
I was telling you to come out!
[Being cocky for nothing...]
He looks so scared!
[So pathetic... so pathetic...]
[Chunderella vs
The Game Devil]
[Chunderella's uprising!]
[Or the reigning Stepmother Kim!]
[Everything will be settled with their match]
[Chunderella charging forward with force]
[While Stepmother Kim calmly looks for his chance]
[Head-to-head
Fight]
[Stepmother Kim, dominating in one try]
[Obtaining an advantageous position!]
[Now someone just has to drop!]
[The Game Devil shows no mercy!]
He hasn't seen Chunhee in so long... And he's so determined to win...
[Just then]
[I won't go down alone!]
[Like a water demon latching on]
[The Game Devil and Chunhee both fall]
[Chunhee feeling like he won because he dragged him down]
It's now 2 against 2. Start!
[Jongshin, Jongkook
Daesung, Jaesuk]
Start shaking!
[Maybe he should just sit this out...]
[He's nothing but a burden to them...]
[Scared to death]
Daesung. This is up to us.
Hyung, let's just go and end this.
[2:2 battle]
[Close game]
[The men's pride on the line]
[I cannot be the first to fall]
[You will fall first!]
[Just then]
[Slip~]
[No one pushed him down...]
[What the heck...]
[Followed by the Grasshopper...]
[What exactly did the two do...]
[Jongshin and Jaesuk are out]
[Jongkook vs Daesung]
[The only two left for each team!]
[Plop]
[Calm]
[Maknae Daesung, won't just lose that easily!]
[Using his feet like hands...]
[Tickling attack]
[The tables have turned]
Good job, Daesung!
[The fatal tickling...]
[How much longer can Kookjong endure?]
[Kookjong recovers, and escapes!]
[Utilizing the muscles he formed from 10 years of working out]
[Daesung falls]
[10 years of working out, finally paying off]
How come you two are so weak?!
[Team Chunhee] [Team Yejin]
-We should have a final play-off
-Yeah, we will.
-Yeah, well we can...
-Like both teams maybe...
Park Yejin, come out!
[The summer before last...]
[Live and Die Together Sisters' big match on the bars]
[Hyori properly defeated]
[Prepared to redeem herself for that day!]
Park Yejin, come out!
Ok, this will be our final match!
That's fine, but know that I felt bad for that...
[I'm not the Lee Hyori you remember!]
[Hopeless]
You've been itching for this moment!
[Ready for a sweet victory!]
-You guys think Yejin is going to win?!
-Hyori! Show them all a singer's strength!
[Big sister]
[Revenge incarnate, Lee Hyori!]
You're capable of a win!
[Little sister]
[Invincible legend Park Yejin]
We'll determine which team wins from this match.
[The Live and Die Together Sisters,
Their fated battle will now begin!]
[Tsk tsk...]
I won!
-No, you didn't!
-Why not?!
She wasn't able to get up, that's why!
[Because Dumb and Dumber couldn't lift Yejin...]
Why is she going backwards if you're lifting her?
[In the end, stepping on them to get up...]
-Are you ready?
-Yeah! 1, 2, 3!
[Quitely moving over]
-Wait, what?!
-Alright, you guys move out!
[The Sisters' battle has finally begun!]
[A fight with no regrets!]
[Who will be the first to fall]
[This important victory]
[Caught]
[Victory right in front of her!]
[Will Yejin lose like this!]
[Ah!]
[What just happened?]
[Pow]
[Knee kick?]
[Hyori caught by the knee kick]
[A new method spurning from the emergency moment]
[Was revenge just a hopeless dream!]
Sorry~
[Sweet] [Savage]
[Apologizing during the final blow]
[She... lost... again...]
Park Yejin! Park Yejin! Park Yejin!
[Invincible legend, Savage Yejin]
Wow, her knee kicks...
I suddenly thought of your butt pokes...
And because her knees are so bony...
I'm lucky she didn't use that move on me then...
That means Team Yejin wins!
[The Family's final battle
Team Yejin wins]
[Part 3. The Neverending Gag]
So today. Yejin and Chunhee...
Actually, Chunhee is a bit awkward today.
Since he cried so hard on his last show here...
[The two crying as if they'd never see each other again...]
Aren't you guys embarrassed for crying that hard and coming back again?
See! I was right to not cry back then!
[The Elder was the only one that didn't cry that day]
You guys were just sniveling and crying!!
I heard Yejin caught a chicken when she was here.
Since we cooked you guys breakfast when you left, why don't you take care of dinner tonight?
When we were on the show we suffered so much, and nowadays you guys just order from restaurants?!
That was just one time!
Whatever! You guys go to salons and get your hair done!!
Chunhee. Do you have anything you want to say?
[Compared to the animated Lady Yejin]
[Remarkably quiet Chunhee]
Do have any ideas?
Well since Yejin is here we should catch a chicken.
And cook the chicken...
And Hyori said she wanted to eat octopus.
Should we buy it or catch it?
We should catch it!
Who's going to go catch the chicken?
[Today's menu
Barbeque chicken, oyster rice, octopus and fishcake soup]
Me, Jaesuk oppa, and Hyori unnie.
[Lady Yejin with the Nation's Siblings~]
Oh, good choice.
Chunhee, who do you want to take?
[They have to go on a boat to catch octopus...]
I'll take my litte brothers then!
[Unexpected]
You want to take them so you can act like the older brother, don't you?
No...
Haejin always has to do the hard stuff.
I think the first time we were here was when I started adding ramen soup in.
How many times are you going to mention that?
That's not very important.
My history is important too!
I find it very important!
No one else is going to talk about my achievements!
-That's his achievement.
-That's right, ramen soup!
He always needs to talk about himself.
That was a sensational moment!
Alright, we'll be off then.
We should go too then.
I get to go with my beloved little sisters. Let's go.
There's three women leaving!
You talk the most out of all of them!
[The elated Elder]
[as well as Sooro and Jongkook are left at home...]
We need to soak the citrons. And we have to make oyster rice.
So we need to wash them, cut them, then soak it.
So then hyung, you can wash them.
Someone else will cut them. And someone will soak them.
-You wash them.
-In cold water.
I'll cut it...
I'll soak it in sugar!
-No, you wash them!
-No!
No you wash them. Then I will cut them.
[His muscular little brothers bullying him...]
Give me a signed copy of your CD!
[Supressed right away]
Fine! I said I'd wash them!
-You're not listening to me!
-Ok hyung, you wash them.
I said I would.
Hyung, I'll do a good job~
Fine. But don't try to take the washing task from me!
Wow, you're so lucky hyung!
[The Elder is 41 years old...
with a pathetic Annoying Old Man's life...]
-They're all gathered over there.
T-here they are.
Yejin, just end it before the sun sets.
The sun is going to set pretty soon.
-So catch one really fast.
-I think the chickens are bigger than before!
[Bigger]
[and stronger]
If they're bigger, they're easier to catch!
[Yejin is scary~]
It's better if they're bigger. They're easy to catch.
Our way of thinking is so different.
[Sweet] [Hi~]
Little ones!
[Yejin is here~]
They're already panicking.
That one looks sturdy!
Some of them are just sitting.
[On alert]
Hi~
[Why me?]
Come here~
[Trying to make itself smaller...]
[Hyori goes closer...]
[More scared than the chicken...]
They're not that easy to catch.
[Just then]
Ah! I stepped in poo!
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Hyori!
[Scared]
There's so much poo here...
[While they were distracted, the chickens escaped]
We were going to catch them, but they ran off...
They're right over there.
Someone needs to herd them over here.
Oppa, go bring them over!
Just herd them over so I can catch one.
[Going because he's a man, but...]
Go behind them.
Oppa, don't let them run up the hill.
[Immediately... Losing trust in him...]
Ok, ok.
Make sure the big one comes back.
[The Grasshopper sets off]
[Over what...]
Oppa!
It's totally a chicken world over here. I can't do it!
Oppa herd them here!
If it's a chicken world, then it should be easy!
I was completely surrounded. This won't work.
Surrounded by what?
Those chickens think I'm easy since I'm alone, so they surrounded me.
[Tsk...] [The pursuer ends up being pursued...]
Call Jongkook!
The chickens are going away now. Just look at that.
This won't work. I can't do this myself!
[The chickens going further away]
Jongkook!
Kim Kookjong!
[Calling for Trainer Kook in the end...]
Jongkook oppa!
Kim Kookjong!
[Jongkook has gone to the kitchen]
What?!
Hey, they're calling for Jongkook.
Kookjong, put that down. They want you to go there!
Why do they need me there?!
Jeez...
[Jongkook~~~]
What?!
[Come quickly!]
[teasing] Hurry and go. So you can help Yejin.
[immediate] Yeah, I have to help Yejin!
Don't help anyone else.
[The Elder feels at ease because Jongkook is leaving]
One of them is half the size of my torso!
Quit lying!
[What kind of a lie(?)...]
Look! Even from far away it's like half of my torso!
[Am I that big?]
Oppa, bring it here then! How can there be chickens like that?!
If I could, would I come back empty-handed?
[He wouldn't be like this if he could catch it...]
I'm not kidding.
It's bright here, but it's really dark over there and...
It's Gyu Hwan's dad?
[Play on words. 'Gyu Hwan's dad' sounds like 'total chaos' in Korean.]
[Gyu Hwan's dad = (chaos)]
You can't hear it from here but they're like...
It's so scary! Try and listen!
[The Grasshopper exaggerates...]
[Finally, she's going!]
It's scary. No no no...
What's scary? Yejin isn't scared.
If it comes over here, you have to catch it!
Oppa don't try to avoid it!
Ok, I got it.
Even if you have to throw yourself on one.
[Yejin has to get involved]
Ok, ok. Don't worry.
Hyori, don't move backwards.
I think they're going to go that way.
Exactly.
Stand over there.
-Over there?
-Behind that tree.
-Why'd you need me?
-Oh there you are! Hurry and help us!
[Reinforcement troop Kim Jongkook is here!]
Those chickens are no joke.
Why, why?
They're flying everywhere.
[The real chicken-catching starts now!]
Catch it! Catch it!
[Lady Yejin going for the kill]
[Nation's Siblings scared to death]
[So are the chickens]
[The pursuer and]
[the pursued]
Catch it, catch it!
Over there, over there!
[In the midst of this breathtaking chase]
[Ratting (?) on them from afar]
Over there, Yejin.
That one there.
[Just then]
Are we going to catch all of them?
No, just catch that one there.
[Narrowing in on target!]
Surround it, surround it.
[Left: Yejin] [Right: Jongkook]
[The savage shadow gradually approaching]
[He is more afraid...]
Catch it, catch it!
[In a flash, running towards the mountain!]
[Incredible speed!]
Hey Jongkook, don't be afraid and go get it.
I'm not afraid!
If it runs, catch it.
[Lady Yejin immediately climbing over in pursuit]
[Swish~]
[But the chicken's tough too!]
[Extreme tension]
[Swish~]
[Almost caught it, but didn't!]
[Korean chicken that can fly as far as 10 meters]
Yejin, Yejin!
[And the legendary Savage Lady Yejin]
[What is the fate of the two?]
[Caught it!!]
[For the sake of their survival...]
[The return of the Queen]
[I caught it~]
You're really the best (?), Yejin!
We should apologise.
Huh?
[sweet] I'm sorry~
[But, you're really delicious!]
Give it to Kookjong.
Wow, thank you.
[Accepting the sincere chicken gift]
We're sorry.
[Aww~ You did so well.]
[Finished everything in 5 minutes]
Sorry, sorry.
Let's go.
It just took her one try!
Everything gets done when Yejin and Jongkook do it!
Yejin has to be around, or we won't get to eat meat.
It would have been difficult if Jongkook oppa didn't help.
I'll help you anytime...
No matter what our Yejin needs...
My Yejin?!
[Strange vibe between the two after filming the music video]
What's this.
I said 'our Yejin'!
Jongshin hyung must be sitting around and warming himself by the fire, no?
We have arrived!
[flustered] You caught it already?
Jongshin hyung was praising Yejin.
She was so successful in Queen Seondeok after doing a variety show.
Hyung, but you know right?
You're a variety star and now a drama star too!
[Sooro too, enjoying success through God of Study...]
That's right.
Who?
Sooro hyung.
Right!
Yejin!
Yeah?
Is Go Hyun Jung pretty?
-Why?
-Of course.
Because I've never seen her before.
-Is she prettier than me?
You guys have different charms~
I'm curious because I've never seen her.
As expected, there's laughter everywhere because Yejin is here.
Exactly.
Laughter is blooming indeed!
What?
Laughter is blooming.
Saying that out of her own mouth! She said laughter is blooming because she came!
It was blooming all along, you know?!
It's thanks to me too!
It's the last time.
Hyori, take care of the chicken!
The chicken? Let Yejin or Jongkook do it.
Hyung, you do it!
I've never done this before.
Exactly, so give it a shot. You've only done the marinade and never anything like this.
That's right. Since it's the last time, just give it a shot.
[The chicken the village chief prepared for them]
Jaesuk, look at him working.
[Somehow it's rather clumsy...]
You'll be shocked at how he's doing it.
[harsh] How did you wash this? It's full of water inside?
It wasn't me!
[It's always the Elder's fault somehow!]
Everything is Jongshin's fault!
Princess Chun Myeong, please give him a hand.
Yeah, I'll help him.
You guys will be reproached on Parent's Day for doing this!
Hold it open.
[Still have not managed to cut it in half...]
Be careful of Yejin's hands.
Oh my, this is frustrating...
Chop it open in one cut!
Oppa, press down on it.
Let go
(Sounds similar to watch me)
[Watch me?]
Look at you? For what?
Look at me!
Look only at me~
Oh my, I don't want to look!
What's wrong with him?
[Because it's the last episode, keeps throwing out gags~]
It's the last episode.
I'm just going to try any joke I think of!
Only look at me!
Oh~ I hate the sight of him!
[Meanwhile, can't cut it no matter what]
[Impatient Yejin grabs the knife from him...]
[Something so simple...]
It's because I cut it just now!
No doubt, Princess Chun Myeong.
Oppa, hold this!
Goodness... Really!
Chop off the legs.
As expected, because Yejin is here, dinner goes without a hitch.
[Demoted to assistant!]
[Cutting off the pieces savagely]
[Even cutting into the meat...]
[embarrassed] Isn't it better for seasoning if we cut it this way?
Asked her to clean the chicken up, but she's almost mincing it!
We have to cut more if we want to make barbeque chicken.
Hey, do you remember this..?
What?
I don't!
[Loss for words]
Oh, I got woken up (from my reminiscing)!
He said he doesn't remember.
[Since he said he doesn't remember, can't elaborate further]
What were you going to say anyways?
I can't remember!
[Yejin, struggling by herself!]
Oppa, it takes too long to do this alone. We should help.
Say, "please help me"!
What's wrong with him?
Why are you being such a brat?
[Silently picks up the knife...]
[Somehow... a weird vibe between... the two]
I'm just the closest to her.
Right, right.
Cook the rice, quickly! The oyster rice!
We have to look for some oysters.
-We already have them
-Where?
Over there.
You've cut up all the big portions already.
Make cuts here!
Oh my, oh my, oh my!
Oh my~ I'm dying!
He's really noisy!
[Whining explosion]
What's wrong with him?
Oh my goodness, come here for a second!
It's not joke!
Come over here and touch some charcoal!
How can you say that?!
[Going to touch some charcoal...]
Ah, my hands are cold!
Oppa, wear gloves and do it.
Hyori never seems to leave Jong Kook's side.
[But looking at them...]
But Jong Kook has no feelings for you.
[Hyori sitting by Jongkook's side...
But Jongkook sticking close to Yejin...]
This looks like an image from the Chosun Dynasty.
It wasn't a one husband, one wife era.
The ingredients for making the chicken?
Who's doing it? Oppa you do it.
[Jongshin bringing over the chicken marinade]
This is intestines!
[The very kind-hearted Jaesuk comes over...]
Put it over by the fire.
Where are you going?!
So I can make you do it twice, hyung!
[Disbelief]
Hyung, take these things.
Ok, hold on.
[Quickly running back...]
[Again]
(What is going on...)
Hyung! Take this please!
[What is happening...]
Stop it now!
[The sickly Elder can't bear it any longer]
It's been my dream to do that joke.
[The Grasshopper tired to death...]
Doing it over and over, it's as funny as the Mabbagi skit in Gag Concert!
Are you not making the rice?!
[Jaesuk bringing over the pot]
Wait, hyung, wait!
[Quickly escaping~]
You have to be faster than that!
(I shouldn't have taught them this)
[Doing exactly what Jaesuk did...]
Hyung, bring the pot! Why aren't you bringing it?!
[Throwing Jong Kook's shoes far away]
[Calmly bringing it over...]
Here, I'll take that!
[Why did he start this kind of gag...]
Hyung, bring the pot over!
- Hyori, I'm so tired.
- Then why'd you start it?!
Bring the pot!
[Wary]
How long are you going to drag this on?
[This time it's Hyori]
[Betrayed by a trusted person!]
-Hurry up and wash the pot.
-Go wash it!
Wash the pot!
Why are you not listening?
- When are you going to start the rice!?
- Your acting skills are good...acting skills are very good.
[Going off again...]
Jaesuk, don't joke around now.
-Jong Shin hyung!
-What?!
- Move around!
- I can't just sit here now?
[Jong Shin sitting quietely to stay out of the mess]
[Jaesuk finally pouring the rice in after difficulty...]
Jong Shin hyung, can you get the frying pan?
Not going.
[Uneasy]
- Hurry and go.
- I can cut up the things left over.
We can just cook it on the grill.
Hurry up, hyung.
- Get what?
- A frying pan.
[Glance~]
I'm not going to do it. We've done it too much now.
[Really...
not doing it...?]
-Frying pan?
-Yeah.
[Bringing his shoes in as well...]
Oppa! Bring the leeks too. The leeks!
Okay!
He's going to come out that way!
Like a con man.
[Correctly imagined]
How did you, how did you know?
[And so, the Neverending gag starts again]
Hyung, bring the frying pan and the leeks.
Oh, the frying pan isn't out yet?
[The secret enemy lurking around to ambush...]
[The Elder has come out]
[How come he's empty-handed...]
[Has used his brain...]
[Lady Yejin takes it]
Here's the frying pan. Are you sure you need this?
[Tricked]
[Still hasn't noticed anything...]
Hyung, hurry up and get the things.
- Why are you not doing anything?
- What a little brat!
He just called Yejin... a little brat.
- You're going to stop, right?
- Yeah, we'll stop.
[Now, walking closer...]
Hyung, we'll stop now.
Give me the leek, the leeks!
[Running away instantly~]
I won't do it anymore.
I'll cut the leeks.
Yoon Jongshin! Yoon Jongshin! Yoon Jongshin!
[Age 40 and yet still like this...]
It's funny when it's repeated, hyung!
Give it to me, quickly!
PASS!
[But taking a look...]
Hurry up and bring the leek over.
Why am I the only one doing the work?
[Only the Grasshopper is suffering]
Enough now!
[At this time, Chunhee who is off to catch squid...]
I think you've lost your touch in variety.
[Getting comedy instructions from Daesung]
Hyung, show us how an octopus moves.
Remember, you used to be really good at this.
Of course I can perform an octopus!
You guys would just copy me, so you guys go first.
The key point is the wave and how they move entwined.
You must perform the ocotpus's characteristics well.
[This is...an octopus...?]
That's a sexy octopus...
Yeah, this isn't working.
[Not even working for Gag Prodigy Daesung...]
Think about how octopus are.
They stick to everything!
When you drop them, they just stick to the ground.
[Flat]
[Even pointing his feet]
Make sure you stick!
That looked like it hurt.
- Did it look like an octopus?
- Of course. You're the best at this.
[Unrivaled when it comes to body gags...]
Alright, let's go now!
[Moving over to the small boat to fish!]
I'm uneasy just by looking at him.
[Tip: Using multiple hooks to catch octopus]
So you pull the octopus up like this?
Yes, they will come up with the fishing lines.
Use these strainers to catch the octopus.
Use Hyori?
No, strainers.
[Waiting for the octopus to be caught...]
[Nothing is coming up just yet...]
It's night time now, it's when the octopus are active.
But, will we catch anything tonight?
It's here, it's here!
[Here?]
[Huh?]
No~ That's not it~
[Disappointed]
I thought that was an octopus...
[This time, it really is an octopus!]
[Gasp... they lost it!]
[Stuck on the line...]
It's so big! So big!
[Extremely big]
Another one! Another one!
[An abundance of octopus]
Hyung, put it here.
[Fresh octopus that has been eagerly awaited for]
They're so big! They're like giant octopus!
[Gradually getting excited...]
[The octopus keep coming up]
It's two, there's two of them, hyung!
[Even two coming up at once!]
Don't lose it! Don't lose it!
Haejin over here! It's sinking! Hurry!
[Catching the escaping octopus...]
[Complete chaos]
This is spectacular...
Such wonders being filmed~
We didn't plan it like this.
We're just doing this and then we lose one and catch it again~
Octopus! Octopus! Octopus!
[Really determined]
[But, he still loses it]
It's right over there~
[Still, they end up with a lot of octopus...]
You should have a taste...
-Just eat it now?
-We can it it raw?
-Yup.
-Just like this?
Eat it, Daesung.
[Everyone hesitating to try]
I'll just cut off a tentacle...
Egh, Daesung!
You should eat the whole thing!
To test if you're a real man!
A real man would just eat the whole thing.
[Gasp... it's stuck]
It hurts, it hurts!
Let him go!
Hyung it's good~ it's good~
Eat the whole thing!
You know you can do it.
Of course I can. I'm a man.
[The older brother eating the whole thing~]
Take a few home with you to eat for dinner!
Mmph, thank you!
Hyung, what are you doing?
[In a desperate struggle with the ocotopus...]
[While Haejin...]
[Mmm~]
It's really good.
I'm so tired...
It sucks that the other members will never realize how hard we worked.
Right, they won't know until they see the episode. But we won't see them after that.
[They're too proud of themselves...]
Yeah, so how will they make up for it?
[Although it was hard work, they spend their final moment on the ocean...]
[The mouth-watering barbeque chicken marinade]
Oppa, lower the flame for the rice.
[The almost ready oyster rice]
-Really?
-Yeah, or the bottom will burn.
Oppa, this is the last time you get to eat our cooking!
That's right...
Do you remember...?
What?
Jongshin hyung is walking by me.
[Suddenly just saying something random...]
Remember what?
You're just saying "do you remember...?" for the heck of it, huh?
Yeah, I don't remember anything!
It's a memory test?
Memory~ test!
Do you remember?
Nope, I don't!
Should we start cooking the meat?
[Grilling the barbeque chicken!]
-This looks good.
-Yeah, it does.
Hyori should buy some land here.
[Mouth-watering]
And she can open up a restaurant here!
And on the weekends she can have perform Ten Minutes for the customers.
The restaurant owner personally performing to her customers.
And we can make our way down here once in awhile!
Watch. Kim Kookjong is going to be one of my employees!
Here's the grill~ Watch out!
-Oppa...
-Yeah?
It's our final show...
Don't lie, you just got smoke in your eye!
I know you were just joking, but now that I think it's our final show...
It really is our final show...
If I don't think about that, it feels like it won't really end.
Since you left FO, have you ever felt like you wanted to come back?
Answer honestly.
When I was eating!
[After eating with them for a year...]
When I asked if you guys were eating well?
Yeah, that too. But it was more like I missed the taste of the food here...
There really is an FO flavor.
Then we should just...
Meet up and cook food?
Yeah, meet up and cook food then leave!
It's fun and it tastes good making food while on a trip.
I found myself missing the games too...
Because you don't really play games like that elsewhere.
Yeah, she really looked like she missed it when we were playing the game earlier.
Hyori didn't have a rival in the games after you left.
I won everything after you left.
She became so arrogant and rude!
Arrogant and rude?!
You're just trying to break it off since you're leaving, aren't you?
[The distance...]
Trying to break up with me, aren't you?
Your heart must be breaking doing this.
[Don't be enticing to me~]
Hyori's a dangerous girl!
She said that when we all went out to dinner once.
What happened?
She kept telling me to give up on her
So I said "Fine, I will"
Hyori didn't hear that part.
I just say what I have to say and then stop listening.
That's true. She always does that.
Oppa, I saw you get teary-eyed when I won the daesang?
You were able to see that?! With my eyes?!
That's quite a feat...
It's because Jongkook wanted the award for himself!
[Now all they need is the octopus for the soup...]
The kids that went out haven't come back yet...
The marinade is so good!
What took you so long?
That was totally a morning chore!
What happened?
To get out there was 1 hour, and it took 1 hour to come back!
We brought three back.
Put it in!
[Finally, the octopus are added!]
Open it.
[Just looking at it makes our mouths water...]
I'm so happy~
Poor Shiyeon...
[Shiyeon went to the hospital...]
She hurt herself while playing the game...
[Feeling bad for not being able to do anything for her...]
Alright, let's eat.
[Are they thinking that it's their last dinner together...]
[Is that why they seem so depressed...]
Our last dinner together.
[The final dinner together with the Family]
[Their last dinner consisting of barbeque chicken...]
So good!
Is it?
Yejin, eat this.
No, I got a lot of fishcakes. Give it to someone else.
[Each person looking out for one another]
Sooro oppa, eat this.
[Of course Little Boy Kim eats it!]
This is so good~
Chunhee, Yejin. How do you guys feel eating with us after so long?
This is so delicious~
-Chunhee?
-Yeah, it's so good.
[Chunhee eating with them after so long]
[Even the Elder is amazed]
I want to eat Hyori's fried vegetables too!
She's going to make it tomorrow.
Hyori said she's going to do a frying festival tomorrow.
She's going to fry anything that's fryable.
Who's making breakfast tomorrow?
You are!
[The Family that was together for 1 year and 8 months...
Their sincere story will continue on]
[Part 4. The Last Night... The Last Story]
After we light the campfire~
It's our last night. Our last night.
So it is...
Let's spend it laughing.
We keep mentioning it, but it really is our last night...
Last. Last.
Did you guys write your letters?
[Write everything in their hearts in a letter]
Let's read them now!
Start with Hyori!
Hyori, did you write yours to me?
Yeah, I did.
[What Hyori wanted to say to Jaesuk]
You're going to read it standing?
It's kind of embarrassing listening to it right next to her...
To Jaesuk oppa.
Hi mom~
It's really awkward writing a letter to you like this.
It's even more awkward having to listen to it!
To be honest, there were a lot of moments I hoped I wouldn't get picked for morning chores or breakfast.
And whenever you got picked, I thought "A good amount will get done"
I think I was being too selfish.
I feel like I've been riding on your coat tails.
Because of that, I've been able to get such a big award.
I think I made a really good choice.
Oppa, you worked so hard. And I'm really grateful.
If I'm able to continue to work as a MC, I want to be a MC just like you.
[Touched]
Until then, it's okay if I continue to ride your coat tails, right?
[Long live the Nation's Siblings...]
Bye oppa. P.S.
You better call me a lot. If I have time, I'll answer the phone.
[Hyori...]
[We will always be the Nation's Siblings]
Did you like it?
-Yeah, thanks
-Keep it...
I wrote mine to Daesung.
[What Jaesuk wanted Daesung to hear]
Daesung!
My Dumb and Dumber little brother.
There's not much of a difference between our IQ.
You and I understand each other so well, my little brother Daesung.
You were like our endorphine during our filming.
[Their actions even Dumb and Dumber]
Although you were the youngest, you were a reliable wittle brother.
[In case you forgot he was Dumb...]
-Wow, you're a MC...
-He speaks well, but he can't read!
He can speak well, but he can't read.
-Daesung, I... lo...
-Just say it!
I love you.
[I love you!]
[Shy]
Daesung! You're the best!
[Loving it...]
[Whatever they lacked in]
[They made up with laughter, Dumb and Dumber]
To my hyung, Jongkook.
I was able to realize what a warm person you are with the times we spent together.
Deep in your bulging(?) muscles, like a steamed white bun...
Was your warm heart...
I'm grateful for how much you looked after me.
[Heeheeheehee]
Truthfully, before I met you. Whenever I heard I looked like you...
I didn't like to hear that!
But after I got to know you, I realized that it was a compliment...
I came to realize what a good person you are.
I love you. Hyung, fighting!
Jongkook hyung, fighting!
[Small Eyes Brothers fighting!]
-I didn't write a long one.
-That's fine.
Sit up straight when you listen!
I am!
[Tense]
Even though he's younger, he's so aggressive.
15 years have passed since I first met you when I was 20 years old...
At first you were a veteran singer, but now you're like a neighborhood hyung... like we're family.
[A serious atmosphere unlike we've ever seen...]
Since those 15 years, I was able to see Yoon Jongshin sunbae provide so much laughter.
I admire the delightful image you have created for yourself.
I'm grateful for the times we've spent together.
[Sharing his sincere feelings in this moment...]
You guys really seem like a sunbae and hoobae now.
[The loving veteran and junior, Jongshin & Jongkook]
Check to see if he spelled everything right!
I wrote it well!
[Of course, the serious atmosphere won't last long in Family]
-I wrote it well, didn't I!?
-Everything seems good.
This is for Yejin.
You're even more beautiful than when I see you on TV!
When I first met you, I thought you'd be frail.
But on the contrary, you were always fearless!
When we began filming, we couldn't look out for you that well!
They're like lyrics.
[Somehow sounding like lyrics...]
I loved getting to know the person that you are!
Instead of just experiencing that during filming, let's become so that I can experience your delightful personality in reality...
I treasure you more than you'll ever know. Love, Jongshin oppa.
[Their friendship surpassing their age difference
The Elder & Lady Yejin]
Hug! Hug!
I like skinship~
(Oh God...)
I like skinship!
Are you crazy?
Very much! Very much!
[The unbelievable Elder...]
Mine is to Chunhee oppa.
Dear Clumsy Chunhee oppa.
When I first met you in the drama sets...
I never realized what a warm person you were.
After we began FO, I began to realize what a good and kind person you are.
[Pleased]
Even though we're not tied by blood, you will always be my family. Bye.
P.S.
I'm sorry for calling you stupid all that time.
Love, Sweet and Savage Yejin.
[Touched]
She's really good at reading.
Of course you think she does everything well.
Mine is to Sooro hyung.
Sooro hyung is really anticipating his.
[Anticipating]
Dear Sooro hyung.
You want to burn him?
(Dear and burn sound similar in Korean)
Burn him in the fire!
Dear Sooro hyung.
Sooro hyung!
First of all, I wish you good fortune in the new year.
[Little Boy Kim displeased with the belated New Year's greeting]
Time has flown and I've realized we've known each other for 14 years...
Yet you're still a magnicent hyung in my eyes. And someone I aspire to be.
I feel like this past 1 year and 8 months, we've gotten to be a lot closer to one another.
I'm sorry that you had to look out for me so much.
[Their memories popping in his head]
I will commit my mind and body to become a better hoobae. No, a better little brother to you.
[Mind and body?]
[Like pledging his allegiance to Sooro...]
Once again, I want to express my gratitude.
It was a great pleasure to spend 1 year and 8 months with you.
Love, Your little brother Chunhee.
[Chunderella's letter delighting the usually bratty Little Boy Kim]
So this is what makes him happy.
I love my Chunhee.
I wrote mine to Haejin.
It's two pages?
[He sure wrote alot...]
Haejin.
We've made a lot of great memories filming FO together.
As your sunbae, I wasn't able to look out for you that well.
But spending all this time together...
It's like a gust of wind!
[Gust of wind]
[Cracking up over Sooro's charisma]
It's probably because your words were so empty~
I look forward to seeing you as an actor. Your sunbae, Ro Kim.
P.S. You're such a cool guy!
Yet you seem to forget to greet me during the holidays.
[Of course, Little Boy Kim to the end...]
I'll look forward to this coming Lunar New Year~
[Unfamilar in variety, Sooro and Haejin bonded over their awkwardness]
[A video message to the Family from Haejin...]
I had such a great time on the show.
At first I was uncomfortable, but going out overnight felt more like I was going on a trip with close friends.
They were happy times.
I wouldn't consider this hard, but...
[Q: Your hardest moment?]
When I was watching the show with my mom, she asked "Why don't you ever talk?"
She kept asking why I hardly appeared on the show.
Truthfully, that was hard for me.
I always brought food and drinks whenever I came to film.
[Q: What was your best work?]
It never appeared on the show, but I always brought snacks for the family...
That's right, it never came up on the show. All his snacks.
Everytime I packed those snacks, I...
[Those days coming to his mind]
[Suddenly his throat tightens...]
I...
I felt proud.
[Although a minor contribution...]
That I could at least do that much for them.
[Providing even a small happiness...]
That I could do that much.
[The Family understanding his efforts more than anyone could...]
Even though it's not much, they still appreciated it.
I think of that.
It really wasn't much, but they still thanked me.
I wish I could have done more.
[No words, but only tears...]
I'm grateful to everyone there.
I always felt so sad at the end of filming because I didn't do well.
[Q: The person you're most thankful to?]
But the oppas would always come and pat my back.
And Hyori really looked out for me.
The show is such a precious memory, but it shouldn't just be that for me.
I feel bad for the viewers...
I regret making such a rash decision to join.
There's a lot of thoughts racing in my mind.
[Q: Your feelings towards the final filming?]
Family Outing was my first variety...
Sorry, I cry really easily. I'm trying not to, but it's not really working.
I don't think I'll ever forget my times on the show.
I don't want our bonds to break once the show ends. I hope we continue to meet in the future.
(Don't cry...)
I don't know what else to say, except that I'm grateful and I'm sorry.
[A precious moment for them to express their heart]
[The Family's last night is a deep night...]
[The Family's last breakfast!]
[Making breakfast for the 100 member staffs!]
[The Family demonstrating their improved skills]
[Handing out one dish after one dish]
[It was a pleasure working with you all]
[The final filming has ended...]
[The Family saying their regretable final farewell]
[Please spend one final moment with the Family]