(There's an unexpected guest.)
(There's someone at the door.)
(Someone pulls an awful prank.)
(Why is this happening to them?)
What's going on?
(The shadow of vengeance is near.)
(The Runjuring)
Please go inside and fill in the questionnaire.
Where?
- Do you mean this one? - Yes.
- Do I sit there and fill this in? - Yes.
"What kind of theme would you like to try on Running Man?"
(Are they answering a questionnaire even before the programme begins?)
"Where would you like to visit?"
"What kind of theme would you like to try on Running Man?"
I want a thriller special.
(The Second Running Man questionnaire)
(Seok Jin writes down his wishes.)
Every...
(Boom)
(Screaming)
(That really scared him.)
My goodness.
Gosh, you should've hung it properly.
Every...
cast member...
could be...
the suspect.
Just like the movie, "The Neighbour".
(Water drops on his head.)
What was that?
(Surprised)
What happened?
(Something just fell on my head.)
What was that? Water just fell from the ceiling.
It was water.
(What's going on in this room?)
"What kind of theme would you like to try on Running Man?"
Oh, my goodness!
(Oh, my goodness!)
(He's shocked.)
(It's giving him goosebumps.)
Why did it fall?
My goodness!
(Startled)
(He's sniffing.)
(What just touched my hand?)
(Ji Hyo enters the mysterious waiting room.)
Hi, Ji Hyo.
(She gargles her mouth to feel refreshed.)
- What's this? - Please fill out the questionnaire.
"What kind of theme would you like to try on Running Man?"
(She screams.)
My gosh.
What was that?
Something feels wrong about this room.
(Is this a haunted room?)
I'm scared.
I feel like something is going to crawl out from under the sofa.
(There's something weird about this room.)
(Ji Hyo moves aside and starts filling out the questionnaire.)
I'm done.
Please go to the next room.
You can go.
It's just a door.
(Why does everything feel so eerie today?)
(The members who've gone through this are waiting in the next room.)
(They've all become quiet after the incident.)
If I scream when the door opens, would Ji Hyo be startled?
If you scare her,
would she slap you in the face or not?
- I'll bet my entire fortune. - Really?
- She'll definitely hit me. - Do you think so?
She'll swear at him while hitting him.
I'll bet on that, too.
- She'll hit the back of his head... - Give it a try.
or slap him in the face.
- Grab her shoulders and scream. - Right.
(Kwang Soo is nervous.)
- Hi, Ji Hyo. - Something fell off, right?
- Yes. What was it? - What fell off?
(She screams and swears at him.)
(I'm sorry.)
- You were right. - Look at her facial expression.
- I was right. I kept my fortune. - You were right.
- I'll protect my own fortune. - Good job.
Come and sit down.
- You were right. - That's right.
- I knew it. - Your prediction was right.
What's with that room anyway?
- I don't know. - I don't know, either.
I've been waiting here without knowing what's going on.
(What is going on in that room?)
What was that? What are we going to do today?
(All the cast members enter through the mysterious room.)
- Hello, everyone. - Hi, Gary.
- What was that? - I think something is in there.
What's going on?
(I have a bad feeling.)
Everyone, before I tell you...
about today's race, I'll introduce you to a special guest.
- Okay. - I see.
Please come out. In 1, 2, 3!
- What's going on? - What's happening?
(Everyone is startled.)
(Oh...)
(my...)
(gosh.)
(They fall backwards.)
(They take a deep bow backwards.)
- My goodness. - What just happened?
(Why do they have to greet the guest like this?)
- Welcome! - Who is that?
(He looks familiar. Who is he?)
- It's nice to meet you all. - Isn't that Gyeong Gyu?
(Lee Gyeong Gyu, the king of variety show with a 36-year experience)
- I lost again. - Look!
(Gyeong Gyu challenged the cast members three months ago.)
(His challenge ended in a disastrous and humiliating defeat.)
He tried to protect his name tag, but he lost it.
I'll abandon all of my team members and challenge you again...
by myself.
(He's back for revenge.)
My goodness!
(The Runjuring was only a taste of Gyeong Gyu's revenge.)
You're joking, right?
(Everyone, look forward to my revenge.)
- Was it a hidden camera prank? - Hello.
- Hello, Gyeong Gyu. - Welcome, everyone.
I can't believe this.
(No wonder I had a bad feeling.)
(I never knew Gyeong Gyu would come back.)
(That means...)
- We'll go home early today! - Oh, yes!
(We'll go home early today thanks to Gyeong Gyu.)
I knew you would come back. I knew it.
- I'm here to celebrate Chuseok. - It's the Chuseok Special.
- It's the Chuseok Special. - That's right.
I'm here to redeem my defeat.
- You're rechallenging us? - That's right.
- Did you form a team again? - Again?
- Yes, I formed a new team. - I see.
- I formed a new team. - His last team was very strong.
- We caught even Kim Dong Hyun. - Exactly.
- My new team is very strong. - Is that so?
- I removed all the weak members. - Yes.
- You found faster people? - I found new members.
- I'm excited to meet them. - Right.
Today's theme is Running Man versus Avengers Part Two.
It's the second part.
(Running Man vs Avengers Part 2)
You'll have a match with Team Avengers who became stronger.
The winning team will be decided...
through Name Tag Elimination at the end.
- Name Tag Elimination? - Like last time.
Each team gets to choose the lucky and unlucky members...
who will be given special missions.
Before the final match, the team that wins the first round...
will be given a hint about the other team's lucky and unlucky members.
So it's very important to win the first round.
The winning team will receive the golden shield.
The leader of the losing team and the member the leader chooses...
will be hit on the forehead by the other team.
- That's the penalty. - Gyeong Gyu, will that be okay?
- Can we hit Gyeong Gyu, as well? - Do you expect us to hit him?
- Yes, you can. - I can't even imagine...
hitting Gyeong Gyu on his forehead.
- I'll try my best to win. - I can't hit him.
(You don't have to worry about that.)
(I brought the strongest team for my revenge.)
I'm nervous to meet his team.
His team was great last time.
- That's right. - They were very strong.
- They were strong, indeed. - But we won.
(Last time was like an appetiser.)
(This time will be like a full course meal.)
- All right! - What's that?
(The members of Team Avengers will be revealed.)
- What's that? - Who is that?
- Hi, Hye Jin. - My goodness.
- It's Hye Jin. - It's been a long time.
(Han Hye Jin, Team Avengers)
- Welcome. - Hello.
Congratulations on the birth of your baby.
- Thank you. - How have you been?
- How have you been? - It's been a really long time.
It's good to see Hye Jin again.
- Since the last time she was here, - Hello.
- "Healing Camp". - Hye Jin...
got married and everything. You two hosted "Healing Camp".
- That's right. - We hosted the show together.
- They hosted it with Kim Je Dong. - That's why it's "Killing Camp".
- It reads, "Killing Camp". - That's right.
The first round is "Killing Camp".
"Don't Say the First Place".
The team that guesses more answers...
that are ranked from the 2nd to the 6th in the poll wins.
As soon as the quiz ends, we'll begin "Running Rumble".
The team who wins the first three points can...
eliminate a member from the other team from "Running Rumble".
(The first team to win three points can remove the other team's member.)
(We'll have a chance of winning if we eliminate the ace.)
- I can't believe this. - Right after the quiz?
They get to eliminate one of us.
The team will have one less member in "Running Rumble".
What are these boxes?
- I think people are in there. - What are the boxes?
- They need more members. - Only one member of...
- Team Avengers has been revealed. - That's right.
The rest of the members are hidden in those boxes.
- Is that so? - They're moving in the boxes.
You can't lock people in boxes like this.
Why do you keep moving in there?
- I wonder who are in there. - The fifth box moved a lot.
The more the box is moving,
the stronger the person inside of the box is.
- The 3rd box is moving a lot. - I wonder who's in the 5th box.
The 3rd and 5th box.
Each time you get the right answer,
you can open 1 cell in 1 of the boxes.
- I understand. - You can guess who is in the boxes.
- That sounds fun. - I see.
That way, you can eliminate one of the members.
When Gyeong Gyu and Hye Jin get the right answer...
Do you see the roulette?
- They get to... - They choose a member with it?
put the name tag of the member they want to remove on the roulette.
They can choose the member they wish to eliminate...
- I see more Seok Jin and me. - by spinning the roulette.
It seems like it has more of my name tags on there.
They'll put a lot of Jong Kook's name tags on there.
- You lose if you say the top rank. - Okay.
- Let's begin. - Okay.
- Please show us the question. - We shouldn't say the first place.
- "The most common baby nickname". - "The most common baby nickname".
Hold on.
This poll was conducted in 2015.
- Did your baby have a nickname? - She knows the answer.
- Lucky. - That must be the first place.
- It might be the first place. - I hope it's not.
- I hope it's not. - Did you say "Lucky"?
- I hope it's the first place. - It's not on the list?
- It's not in the top six? - It's not on the list?
- Is it not on the list? - It's not on the list.
Sparky.
- Who would use that nickname? - I don't think it's on the list.
- Lovely must be the first place. - Jae Seok.
- Lovely. - That must be the first place.
- I'm sure it's the first place. - Is it the first place?
- What's the ranking? - Is it the first place?
(It sounds very friendly. It feels like the first place.)
- Lovely. - Lovely.
- It's not in the top 2? - It was ranked the 2nd in 2016.
- Really? Goodness. - This one was conducted in 2015.
- I think this name is on the list. - Go ahead.
- Joy. - Joy.
- Joy. - It must be on the list.
- Did he get it right? - What ranking is it?
- It's not the first place, right? - Isn't it the first place?
(What ranking could "Joy" be?)
- It's the first place. - Oh, yes! I told you so.
(One team is happy while the other is sad.)
- I can't believe him. - I knew it.
(He said the answer that he had to avoid.)
- How did you get that? - Gosh.
- I'm sorry. - See? I told you.
- I was about to call out Awesome. - I told you, Hye Jin.
- I told you. It's 2 versus 1. - I'm really sorry.
- I really didn't know. - I didn't pick Joy for a reason.
- It was so obvious. - Was it?
- I didn't have a baby nickname. - Didn't you?
- Did you have one, Hye Jin? - I had one.
- What was it? - What was it?
- It's quite embarrassing, though. - Please tell us.
It was Boxing.
- Boxing? - Really?
- I got pregnant on the Boxing Day. - Oh, the Boxing Day?
- On the Boxing Day? - I see.
- That's why you named her Boxing. - What's the Boxing Day?
- The day following Christmas Day. - I see.
- That Boxing Day? - Yes.
- I see. - I've never heard of such name.
(This is embarrassing.)
Seok Jin. Did you have a baby nickname?
I don't think I had one.
- Really? Seok Jin? - No baby name for you? Really?
- How about Joseon? - Joseon?
- How about Liberation? - Liberation? No way.
How about Dumbell for Jong Kook's future baby?
- Dumbbell? - Dumbbell sounds good.
For twins, how about Dumbbell and Barbell?
- It sounds great. - Barbell.
- We should remove a name. - Let's put Jong Kook's name on.
Where should we put it on?
Right here. Let's put this over Seok Jin's name.
(We are taking Seok Jin out.)
Why was his name placed right next to mine?
Hye Jin thinks Ji Hyo is a tougher opponent than Seok Jin.
Hye Jin seems quite tough. She even named her daughter Boxing.
She is really cautious.
- Let's move on to the next topic. - All right.
- Let's see. - We must avoid the top answer.
"What are the most popular kind of SNS profile pictures?"
- We must know better than them. - What is it? SNS profile pictures?
- Scenery pictures. - Yes. They are really popular.
- Scenery. - Photos of sky, for example.
- Scenery pictures... - Yes.
- are second most popular. - Yes.
- That was close. - Good one.
Don't pick the usual ones.
- It was really close. - So please don't.
Scenery pictures are the second popular profile pictures.
Since you got the right answer,
(Haha can remove a sticker.)
- please choose a sticker to remove. - I'll choose box five.
Sticker number three.
- I'll choose 3 of box 5. - You chose 3 of box 5.
- What is it? - Why?
- I can see feet. - That person must be a man.
- What is that? - He must be sitting.
- I can't see any. - He must be lying down.
- He's lying down. - You can only see his feet.
- Look at his feet. They are big. - You can see big feet?
He must be really uncomfortable to stay in the box like that.
Let's remove sticker six next time.
That posture looks so uncomfortable.
Don't guess the first place.
Baby photos.
- That must be the most popular. - Baby photos.
- It must be. - No way.
I think selfies are the top of the list.
- Yes, selfies could be the top. - First place.
- Yes. - It's okay if it's not the first.
- It can't be the first. - Let's see.
It's fourth on the list.
- Good job. - Nice.
- Pictures of family members. - I see.
Let's pick 5 of box 5.
- Sticker 5 of box 5? - It won't reveal his face.
Do you want to see the face?
I can almost see though.
- That shirt is out of style. - I have no idea.
Hey. Hide your hands.
I can tell makeup is very lovely.
- That person must be a woman. - A woman?
- No way. It's a man. - Hide your hands.
- No, I think it's a woman. - I can see makeup on the hands.
That must be a man.
- How about pictures of coffee? - Pictures of coffee?
- No way. - Pictures of Justin Bieber.
- They pressed first. - Pictures of Justin Beiber.
- Selfies. - Selifies, selfies.
- Haha. - Do you mean selfies?
(Wait, selfies are really popular profile pictures.)
- Wait... - It must be the first place.
- What are you doing? - It's the first.
- No, I didn't mean selfies. - It's the first?
- I meant pictures of me, Haha. - It ranks third.
(It ranks third.)
- Gosh, Haha. - Oh dear, I'm so relieved.
- Selfies? Really? Only the third? - That's right.
- No way. - I thought selfies are the first.
- Selfies are not the 1st? - What's ranked 1st then?
Let's try the third box. Shall we?
Okay. Sticker 6 of box 3, please.
- Sticker 6 of box 3? - Yes. That's it.
- Let's see the face. - We're removing sticker six.
But they're not all lying down, right?
I can see the hips.
- That must be a man. - I think all of them are men.
His thighs are something.
- One of them must be Sung Hoon. - The thighs look really thick.
(Thick thighs)
(Hang on, I've seen those thighs.)
I can't see properly.
- Is he tall? - All right.
Photos of delicious food.
- Food? - Yes. Food.
- Food? - Yes.
- It must be on the list. - Yes, it must be.
- It might be the first. - Is it on the list?
- I think it's the 5th. - It's ranked 6th.
- Yes. - Okay.
- Good job. - Seok Jin. Let's try 5 of box 3.
- Sticker 5 of box 3? Okay. - Sticker 5 of box 3?
Okay. We'll remove the 5th sticker on the 3rd box.
- Who is that? - He's hiding himself.
- It's Moon Hee Jun. - Yes, it's Hee Jun.
(Peekaboo! How did you guys figure out?)
You shouldn't do that.
(Team Avengers, Moon Hee Jun)
What a surprise.
- Hello, Hee Jun. - It's Hee Jun.
He should be in the team.
- Is he strong? - Aim for the fifth.
(There're only 2 left now. The 1st and 5th.)
Default pictures.
Default profile pictures given by the system.
Default profile pictures?
- Yes. - It's on the list.
- Yes. - That's good.
- That must be the first place. - The basic profile picture.
- It must be the 1st place. - It is ranked the 1st.
(Kwang Soo picks the first of all things.)
I told you, right?
We don't have to do anything to win.
- Come on. - I knew it was the first.
- Kwang Soo is really unlucky. - You're right.
We don't have to do anything to win.
- I told you, right? - It was so obvious.
We'll win without doing anything.
- Gosh. - I knew this.
- I see. - Yes.
- We don't need him there. - Him?
Are you removing Seok Jin's name again?
It's me?
Is it Seok Jin again?
- They're determined. - Gosh.
There's only one left for Seok Jin's name.
We must eliminate Jong Kook from "Running Rumble".
- He has profile pictures of us. - Profile pictures of all members?
It's embarrassing.
Gyeong Gyu is really showing off.
- Really? - Is that your profile picture?
Look.
It's like a music album cover. There's even a title.
My father's profile picture is very similar to his.
- How did you even get this? - I know.
Where's my privacy?
- Come on. - You uploaded it to show everyone.
Wait. Do they have to lie down like that all day?
They must be keep tossing and turning.
- It must be really hot inside. - My goodness.
Let's see who's next. Wow, this is great.
Who's that?
"My precious Si On and Sung Yeung".
That was ranked the fourth.
- That's the kind. - Yes. Family photos.
- Si On is Boxing, right? - Yes, she is.
- Let's see who's next. - Who is it?
- Is this the number one? - That's right.
Yes. The most popular one. Default picture.
I'm not interested in those kinds of profile photos.
- That's not cool. - Gary.
Don't you think your profile picture is too handsome for you?
- Did you do that on purpose? - That's way too handsome.
I think he went to the salon for that picture.
Look. It's really neat. He definitely had a haircut.
- Jae Seok, can we speed up? - Sure.
- They are suffering inside. - I see.
- Look, they can't breathe. - I'm sorry.
This is the profile picture of Kwang Soo.
- He's definitely showing off here. - Yes, I can tell.
- No, it's not that. - So, global prince?
No. Not at all.
- He wants to be popular worldwide. - I see.
- Let's look at Haha's. - Look at that.
Haha always shows his dream to everyone around him.
(Haha wants to be tall.)
- The impossible dream. - What is that?
This picture says Haha wants to be tall like this guy.
- A basketball player. - "Of course. I'm a genius."
- It's like a real bluff. - My goodness.
This is Seok Jin's.
That's a typical 50s' profile.
- Really. I mean it. - I agree.
- Really. - That even embarrasses me.
Men of his age always put pictures of them look young and active.
- That's so typical. - "I am still active!"
- That's right. - "I can do it."
- He wants to show people that... - Gyeong Gyu's picture is similar.
he's still healthy and active.
Why did you put a picture of AOA members?
- Look at their faces. - It's the picture with our faces.
- Yes. It's with our faces. - I see.
I thought it was a farewell message to your agency.
(Seok Jin cancelled his contract with his agency after seven months.)
It looks like a farewell message now.
(Did you see my profile picture? How are you doing my friends?)
"Things you never want to hear from your boss".
- Can I begin? - Yes.
"Get it done before you take off today."
Is it on the list? It must be the sixth on the list.
- It was ranked the sixth. - I see.
- Shall we open up the 5th box? - Let's go with 6 of box 5.
- Okay. - All right.
Who is that?
- I'm curious. - I'm so curious.
(With flowery shirt and makeup, who could it be?)
- It's you, Key. - It's Key?
(Team Avengers, Key)
With his face revealed, he looks really stylish with that shirt.
Yes, he really does.
My face is all swollen. I was afraid you wouldn't recognise me.
Everything suits for a handsome guy, right?
(His flowery shirt suits him really well.)
- "Do it again." - "Do it again?"
That sounds annoying, but do people really say...
- Really? - Is it on the list?
- In our daily lives. - Let's go with the second box.
- Box 2. - Box 2, sticker 6.
- Box 2, cell 6. - Box 2, cell 6 please.
Would this person be lying down as well?
- I don't think so. - Let's find out.
- This one is standing. - I know.
It's pink.
- The socks are in pink colour. - Then is it a woman?
Is it a man or woman?
- I don't have any idea. - This one is fashionable.
- I think that person is a man. - It must be. We have Hye Jin here.
"This is why you always fail."
- That's why. - It sounds really horrible.
- It's on the list? Really? - Isn't this...
- Take the sticker 1 off. - Box 2, sticker 1 please.
- Who is that? - Isn't it...
Gosh.
- Who is he? - Isn't he Roy Kim?
- I'm so lost now. - Isn't he...
- an actor? - Is he tall?
- Isn't he Roy Kim? - I saw him, but I have no idea.
- My goodness. - Isn't he Shin Sung Rok?
- Isn't he the actor Shin Sung Rok? - No way.
"I wasn't like that when I was your age."
Okay.
- Good. - Gosh. That sounds awful, too.
Please open up box 2, sticker 2.
Isn't he on our team?
I really don't have any idea.
Who is he?
- Wait. Isn't he Sung Hoon? - Really?
You can't change your posture. Are you okay with that?
Let's keep the stickers 3 and 4 untouched until the end.
- Yes. - Let him stand like that.
- We won't free you until the end. - No way.
(Please remove the stickers.)
"I need to talk to your parents."
- What? - What are you talking about?
- No way. - It's not about school kids.
Nobody will bring in their parents to their workplaces.
"Why are you so ugly?"
Hateful comments on looks?
(Wrong answer)
"Actually, I like you."
("Actually, I like you.")
No?
"I just don't like you."
("I just don't like you.")
That was really straightforward.
- How about "Go away"? - Gyeong Gyu says it every day.
(All of their answers are wrong.)
"Just do as I say."
"Do as I order."
- That sounds like an answer. - That must be the first place.
- That must be the 1st place. - Or the 2nd place.
(It must be ranked either the 1st or the 2nd place.)
That must be the first place.
- First place. - First place.
(He guessed the first place again.)
This makes me feel annoyed.
- It's so annoying. - Gosh, Kwang Soo.
He got the first place right.
I can't believe it.
How did you pull it off?
Your name is gone now, Seok Jin.
Am I gone?
Seok Jin must participate in the competition.
- I have to compete no matter what. - You do.
- I'm so curious. - Choose number four.
- Number four, please come out. - He looks like someone.
Who is number four?
(Who is the person kept in the box throughout the show?)
(It's Yoon Hyung Bin!)
It's Yoon Hyung Bin.
- It's Hyung Bin. - Hello.
- He does mixed martial arts. - You're right.
- Martial arts. - He'll be great.
(Team Avengers, Yoon Hyung Bin)
(He's a professional mixed martial artist in entertainment field.)
I waited for a long time.
Look how big his thighs are.
- He's never lost a game. - That's right.
- He's never lost. - Can we let out number two?
- It's Sung Hoon. - Sung Hoon?
(He finally sees light after being kept inside for an hour.)
- He's pretty big. - He's sweating a lot.
- I'm a fan of your drama. - He has a great body.
His acting was good.
(Team Avengers, Sung Hoon)
Tell me it's not true.
(Sung Hoon is a handsome actor with a hot body.)
- He has a great body. - I'm a fan of your drama.
I watched his drama every day, but why didn't I recognise him?
- Number 1. - Who's number 1?
- I'm curious about number one. - Who on earth is it?
Who is it? I can't see.
(Is that a gorilla?)
- It's Dong Hyun. - It's Dong Hyun.
(Team Avengers, Kim Dong Hyun)
Please give them a round of applause. Thank you.
- Aren't they too strong? - They're too strong.
- It'll be very difficult. - They make a good team.
As Team Avengers won, one of Running Man members...
will be taken off the team when their name is chosen.
It's okay as long as Jong Kook isn't chosen.
Someone else has to be picked other than Jong Kook.
It's a member that will be taken off the team.
I hope I'm chosen.
It should be either Haha or Ji Hyo.
- Gosh. - I hope it's me or Ji Hyo.
This usually doesn't work in our favour.
It's Jong Kook.
- It's Jong Kook. - We're in trouble.
- It's Jong Kook. - Oh, no.
(Kim Jong Kook)
(It's not Jong Kook.)
- What? - It's Ji Hyo.
(It passes Jong Kook and Jae Seok.)
- What? - It's Ji Hyo!
- It's Ji Hyo. - No way.
- We're safe. - Thank goodness.
(Ji Hyo is excluded from "Running Rumble".)
- We still have Jong Kook. - We're safe.
Thank goodness.
Jae Seok can't be taken off, either.
(Will Team Running Man be able to take revenge?)
(It's a one-to-one competition with one member from each team.)
(An additional member joins after every 30 seconds.)
(The team to knock out all the opponents wins.)
What if Dong Hyun uses his martial arts technique?
- That's possible. - No way.
Shouldn't we warm up?
- We must win this game. - Let's warm up.
(The players ready to run away stretch their legs.)
- Here we go. - You should stay focused.
Me?
- I work very hard. - Why are you being careless?
Gyeong Gyu, I'm going to work very hard.
Show me something then.
Don't be careless. You must do your best.
- I'll do my best. - You can do it.
(In what order will Team Avengers compete?)
Here's the countdown.
- It's starting. - We can do it.
- Jong Kook, please do well. - You can do it.
(Everything will depend on who wins the first round.)
- You can do it. - Please.
(Who's the first player from each team?)
(The first player from Team Running Man is Jong Kook.)
- It's Jong Kook. - Is it Jong Kook?
- He's definitely the first. - Right, it's the same.
They have the same strategy.
(First player from Team Avengers)
He startled me.
(It's UFC fighter, Kim Dong Hyun.)
- Is it Dong Hyun? - Gosh. It is.
- This will be hard. - All right.
(Jong Kook vs Dong Hyun)
- Is It Dong Hyun? - I knew you'd come.
(It's a competition between the strongest member of each team.)
I thought it'd be you.
(He trips and falls.)
(He trips while trying to look cool.)
(It's a chance for Jong Kook.)
(However, he stands up immediately.)
I need to get rid of you quickly.
I need to get rid of you.
(It's a match between best players in their own field.)
(Jong Kook grips him hard.)
(Jong Kook makes a preemptive strike.)
If Dong Hyun loses, we'll be at a disadvantage.
It won't be easy to defeat him.
Jong Kook grabbed him.
(Jong Kook holds down his collar and attacks with his right hand.)
(Amazing)
Jong Kook got closer to touching Dong Hyun's name tag.
(Dong Hyun is at risk.)
- This is so exciting. - What if he gets him?
He's hanging in there.
(Dong Hyun endures even though Jong Kook has him by the collar.)
Don't come near me.
(The countdown for the second player to join starts.)
What will you do if Hyung Bin joins?
(Which player will join Jong Kook and Dong Hyun?)
It's not safe.
- Who's going in second? - Who's next?
There you go.
Five, four, three, two, one, zero.
(The second players join.)
Two, one, zero.
(Which players will join to determine the winner?)
(It's Lee Kwang Soo from Team Running Man...)
(versus Yoon Hyung Bin of Team Avengers.)
Grab him, grab him.
Take off Hyung Bin's name tag.
(It's Jong Kook versus Dong Hyun and Kwang Soo versus Hyung Bin.)
Oh, goodness.
(Members who are watching get fired-up.)
No, no.
Kwang Soo, attack him.
(While two battles are taking place...)
You have long arms.
(Jong Kook attacks him.)
(Dong Hyun grabs the name tag.)
(Tearing)
(He tore Jong Kook's name tag.)
You have long arms.
(Dong Hyun takes off Jong Kook's name tag in an instant.)
- I got it. - Over here, over here.
Over here.
(Jong Kook is out.)
Okay!
(Well done, Dong Hyun!)
- He took off the name tag. - He did it.
- He did it. - We got this.
- He took off Jong Kook's name tag. - What happened?
It's over for us.
- Goodness. - Kwang Soo, hang in there.
We're in trouble.
(Now, it's Kwang Soo against Dong Hyun and Hyung Bin.)
Grab him now. Go to the back.
Grab it from the back. Take his name tag.
(He defends himself with all his might.)
No.
(He has to withstand no matter what.)
Three, two, one, zero.
(Third players join.)
(It's Gary versus Sung Hoon.)
Hurry up.
(Kwang Soo, wait. I'm coming for you.)
(Tearing)
He tore it.
(Kwang Soo is out.)
They took off his name tag.
(It's a match of 3 against 1.)
What do I do now?
Don't resist, Gary.
Kwang Soo, why weren't you quicker?
Don't even resist.
Goodness, what should I do?
(Defence is the only way to survive.)
(His defence against three players is deft.)
Four, three, two, one, zero.
(Fourth players enter.)
(It's Jae Seok versus Key.)
- We're in trouble. - Wait.
- We're in trouble. - Is your name tag torn off?
- It's not off yet. - Stop it.
(All Team Avengers members corner the other team.)
We're in trouble.
- Stop it. - Wait a minute.
Their defence is incredible.
I'm trying to grab him.
You can do it. We're already holding them down.
Just tear it off.
(Jae Seok and Gary attack suddenly.)
(But Sung Hoon and Hyung Bin react quickly.)
Attack them.
(They're cornered yet again.)
- Gosh, what's going on? - You want to play like this?
(We can't survive on our own.)
- Is this how you want to play? - New members are joining.
(Seok Jin joins.)
- New members are joining. - Gosh, we're in trouble.
(Hee Jun from Team Avengers joins.)
- What's going on? - Gosh.
Gosh.
- No. - Watch out.
- No. - Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin is out as soon as he joins.)
- Goodness. - Seok Jin.
Why did you even attack Seok Jin?
(Seok Jin is out immediately.)
(Oh, no.)
What on earth was that?
(They burst out laughing.)
Oh, my goodness.
(It's 2 Running Man versus 5 Avengers.)
(Tearing)
(Hyung Bin tears off Gary's name tag.)
Wait, what happened?
(Sung Hoon eliminates Jae Seok.)
(All Team Running Man members in the ring are eliminated.)
Wait.
(They've been playing "Name Tag Elimination" for six years.)
(It's time for my revenge. I can't lose twice.)
Come out.
Come here.
(Only Haha remains on Team Running Man.)
Is everyone else eliminated?
(Seventh Avenger, Han Hye Jin appears.)
- We predicted this would happen. - Don't do it.
(It's time to go, Haha.)
- Turn him over. - Turn him over.
- See you later, Haha. - Hold him.
(They deliver Haha to Hye Jin.)
(Poor Haha.)
(Hye Jin tears off his name tag elegantly.)
(Tearing)
That was humiliating.
- That was so embarrassing. - Goodness.
How could they do that?
He eliminated Jong Kook.
- I wish we could play once more. - It's so unfair.
Team Avengers wins.
(Team Avengers is the winner of "Running Rumble".)
- It's a complete defeat. - We got completely defeated.
- That's too harsh. - Gosh, seriously.
We were completely defeated today.
We weren't this bad before.
Hyung Bin did much better than I thought.
- He was very fast. - How did you think of me, then?
- Seriously. - I thought you'd be easy.
Hyung Bin worked out a lot.
He was really fast but also frivolous at the same time.
- He was too frivolous! - I know.
- They've become too strong. - That's right.
How could you eliminate the name tag that fast?
I focused too much on the game and kind of lost my mind.
I could see that when I saw your eyes flipping out.
- He was seriously half crazy. - Gosh.
- Sorry? - Why aren't you getting married?
People told me to get married as late as possible.
We didn't mean this late.
You should've been married already by now.
- Sorry? - Why don't you join "Mum's Diary"?
- Me? - Are you casting him?
I am a good son.
- I'm scanning him now. - He's bad at things like that.
I am very close with my mother.
- He doesn't live alone. - He lives with his parents.
Paparazzi gave up on him because he's so boring.
He's either always at home or at the gym.
You'll hear only three answers if you ask him what he's doing.
"I'm on my way to the gym", "I'm working out" and...
"I'm going home from the gym".
He'll give you 1 out of these 3 answers.
(They had a good time in the bus.)
(They arrive at the place for the second round.)
The mission in this round is "Sixth Sense Quiz".
- The Running Man team goes first. - Is it...
(I have a bad feeling.)
- I think it is... - No way.
Each member will take charge of each sense.
And one member should make a guess...
based on the information from the other members.
Each team will answer two questions at once.
If you end in a tie, the team that took less time to answer will win.
- This is... - No way.
(We've done this before, right?)
(My premonition was never wrong.)
I was hoping we wouldn't do this.
(They've done this scary mission seven months ago.)
What is this? It feels so strange!
(It's scarier because they can't see it.)
What is this?
Get out, Ji Hyo.
- You can't decide that. - I'll smell.
The other members aren't allowed to answer on behalf of anyone.
The team members can only describe what they felt.
- Jong Kook should touch it. - You're right.
Jong Kook, you can touch it.
- You can't decide that. - Who will smell, then?
- I want to smell it. - He's sensitive.
Team Running Man, please discuss it over there.
- Team Avengers, please sit down. - Why should I do that?
- Please sit down and... - Who will see it?
(What items will they be guessing today?)
(Please wait and see.)
I am sure you prepared scarier objects.
If the object hurts me, I'm going to kill it.
Please do not kill it.
I made it clear now.
- Please don't kill it. - My goodness.
I really mean it. I'll kill it.
Here's the first item!
- Okay. - In 1, 2, 3!
(What is the first item that will stimulate the members' senses?)
- Gosh. - What is it?
- This is unbelievable! - My goodness!
(They're seriously shocked.)
This is really something!
- Will they really be all right? - That's too much.
(Will they really be all right?)
(Are they acting, or are they really shocked?)
(They're about to lose their minds.)
(Ji Hyo has to guess the answer.)
- My goodness. - I can't believe this.
- This is truly shocking. - Kwang Soo.
(It's giving them goose bumps.)
I'm going to hear this.
- I want to smell it. - Gosh, I'm scared.
- My goodness. - Look at Dong Hyun. It's real!
Gosh, this is so scary.
- Let's do it. - Go for it.
- I don't think I can touch this. - Go on.
They're just trying to scare us.
- It won't kill us, will it? - Gosh, this is crazy.
My goodness, just do it already.
Why don't you try it yourself?
- This is really scary. - They're so scared.
- I'm serious. - Do it! No, don't!
(Why are you doing this to me?)
Please don't do that!
- My goodness. - I've never seen that before.
(What is inside the box?)
- I can't do this. - Gosh.
- Is it moving? - It is moving.
- This is my first time seeing that. - Gosh.
(Is it a hand?)
- I have to feel it. - Go down.
(They're acting to scare Team Running Man.)
What is it?
(He is really scared.)
(Gary's hand is close to the hand in the box.)
- No, not there! - It's moving.
- I can't do this. - Not there.
(Cringing)
You look so ugly. Just do it.
Be quiet. That's not important.
(Screaming)
(He touched the hand inside the box.)
(Gary finally lost his mind.)
Why? What was it?
It almost bit you. That was so close!
- You almost got bitten. - Goodness.
(He's dizzy.)
- It touched me. - What did you touch?
- Is it moving? - My gosh.
- Is it alive? - It licked me.
(I think it licked my hand.)
(The hand touched Gary just like a reptile's tongue.)
- This is really something. - Are you serious?
- Describe it. - Tell me what you felt.
- What did it feel like? - Tell us.
- Tell us. - Come on.
I felt its skin.
- What? - It was skin.
- My gosh, this is scary. - I'm not sure if it was a tongue...
- or skin. - Really?
- Gosh! - I don't think I can do this.
Let's switch our positions.
- I'm not exaggerating! - You should do it.
- You know I can't do this. - My goodness!
- Will you not start? - You know I can't do this.
- What are you doing? - I can't do this.
- Just do it! - I'm too scared now.
(It's Kwang Soo's turn to hear it now.)
Is this sound really coming from the box?
(Kwang Soo, come on.)
He looks like a fool again.
(I can hear you.)
- Kwang Soo, what do you hear? - It was dry.
What does it sound like?
I'm telling you, it moves.
- Gosh, you're lying. - I am not.
(What did Kwang Soo hear?)
(The noise is 100 percent made only by hand.)
The thing moves. It moves.
- It moves? - I fought with it.
(It sounds like this.)
This is how it sounds like.
- Then... - Is it a dinosaur?
Is it a tongue?
- Gosh, I can't do this. - I think it's a tongue.
Toads are poisonous.
It's warm.
Right. It's really something.
Why is it warm?
- It's really warm inside. - Just do it.
- Why is it warm? - Feel the skin.
- My goodness. - Just do it.
I almost hit you with my elbow.
- My goodness. - We have no time to waste.
(He's hesitating.)
Do it slowly.
(He screams.)
(Jae Seok slightly touches the hand.)
- You! - What's wrong with you?
- It's alive. - I told you! It's moving!
- Is it really moving? - Gosh.
I told you that it moves.
Jae Seok just swore.
- Is it alive? - It is.
- Really? - It's moving.
Why are you doing this to me? No, I don't want to do it.
- This is... - Is it really alive?
- It's so scary. - Hold on.
(Haha smells it.)
Wait. It smells like my grandmother.
- What? - I'm serious.
(It smells like Haha's grandmother.)
- What does it smell like? - Please tell us.
It smells like a house where five guys live in.
You must touch it to guess the item.
- I am pretty sure. - Still, I have no idea!
It's like a room where five guys live in.
- Gosh, what on earth is it? - I'm so curious.
- What is it? - It really smells like guys.
- What colour is it? - It moved really quickly.
- What is it? - It's soundless.
- It doesn't have any hair. - But it moves very fast.
It's really hard to guess.
- If it's quiet... - Do people live inside the box?
If it is soundless...
(That's not entirely wrong though.)
- It is a soundless... - Take a look at it.
What colour is it?
It was moving before, but it stopped moving.
- You said it's alive. - It's dead now.
It's sinking down inside the box.
I don't think it's a living creature.
- What? - It's not alive. I think...
it's something made of steel.
- It is... - Made of steel?
Then...
It smells like...
- It's really hot in here. - It is.
Is it because it's breathing?
It's steaming inside.
(He moves his hand around.)
(They almost shake hands.)
Why?
It's a bit wet.
- Is it wet? - Yes, it's wet.
- I think... - It's wet.
- Why is it wet? - It's wet.
I've seen it a lot before.
It's really dangerous.
(Seok Jin gets shocked.)
- What was that? - I think it's an abalone.
- What? - An abalone.
It was wet, and it felt like skin.
- Is it slippery? - Mine was dry.
- Mine was dry. - But mine was wet.
- It moved very fast. - You didn't touch it.
I did touch it.
- You didn't. - I brushed up against it.
- Really? - Ji Hyo, it's like skin.
- Try putting everything together. - Can it be a sponge?
It made slurping sounds.
You said it was slippery.
It sounded more like this.
It moved quickly and touched my hand.
Did it really sound like that?
(Will they be able to guess it correctly?)
Is it a bullfrog?
(Her guess is a bullfrog.)
You're wrong.
- It's hard. - You were close.
- My goodness! - Isn't that a hand?
(Surprise!)
- It's a human hand. - There's a hand inside the box.
- Is it a hand? - This is what I touched.
- Gosh. - Is it a hand?
- How did it make such a sound? - Whose smell was it?
- I told you. - You thought it was calamari.
- Haha. - It stinks.
You were right, then.
- It is... - It smells like factory bread.
It's Team Avengers' turn now.
They don't seem that scared.
Let's open the first item right away.
Am I in charge of looking at it?
You should touch it.
- I'll listen to it. - No way.
In one,
- I can hear very well. - two,
- What? Who? - three.
(You were so relaxed when you were watching it, right?)
(What will be in the boxes this time?)
This is so different from ours.
(What could it be?)
- What is that? - Oh, my.
- They can't see. - This is not a joke.
- This is too much. - This is so different from ours.
So this is what you got for them. Good job.
Well done.
- You didn't betray us. - This is crazy.
- This is too much. - I'm not kidding.
- We're not lying. - What is it?
- I'm telling you for real. - This is real.
- We're not joking. - It really moved.
- This one looks angry. - Look at this. Look.
I swear that it is alive.
- It really is. - This is surprising.
- Look at this. - This is insane.
Take a look at this!
- Look at this one. - It is so active.
Look how active it is now.
(Are they faking it, or is it real?)
- But... - Wait.
I can hear some loud thumping noise.
(The loud sound is coming out through the headphones already.)
- Put in your hand first. - It's the first time I see it.
- Just put it in. - It's not very dangerous but...
- No. - It can be dangerous.
To my knowledge, it has teeth for sure.
- I can feel the movement. - It's moving.
- You're right. - It's really alive.
- I've never touched one alive. - Me neither.
- I mean it. - It's true.
- Try to touch it. - You don't usually touch it alive.
- Even if I knew what it is, I... - I would not be able to touch it.
(Are they telling the truth or not?)
(What is the item that will stimulate their senses?)
Hyung Bin, what's wrong with your hand?
(Welcome. Please explore me.)
Touch it right.
(I can't get my wrist straight.)
- You're almost there. - Almost.
- Is there a plate? - A little further.
It's already standing so just spread your fingers.
I've never seen anyone touching it alive.
No way.
- Does it have feet? - I can only touch it if it's dead.
- Only if it's dead. - Of course.
(He is just 1cm above the abalone.)
I'm scared to see their faces.
Oh, I couldn't...
(Screaming)
(He wants to fight with the abalone.)
Hey.
I hate it.
- I can't touch it even if I see it. - I felt something mushy.
- Mushy? - There's something mushy.
It's not too mushy, but it is a little bit.
- Did it bite? - It felt like a monster.
- Is it alive? - I think so.
- Is it wet? - Then what's this sound?
What is this?
I don't know why they put listening to this.
- I've never heard the sound of it. - I hear a fizzing sound.
Could you mimic the sound?
It's the sound of chewing something.
Try to make that sound.
- I can hear it, too. - Make the sound.
- Sung Hoon. - That's because it has teeth.
- Mimic the sound. - It sounds like it's munching.
- Did they feed it? - What on earth is it?
(It's the sound you can hear when you take abalones off.)
(Respond, my hearing organs.)
There is a fizzing sound...
and it's chewing on something.
- What is it chewing? - That's right.
- What's the fizzing sound? - It has to eat something.
- It has teeth anyway. - It's slippery...
and mushy.
- Is it slippery? - Yes.
- It has teeth. - Next, it's Key's turn.
(Key tries to guess by looking at it.)
Can you see it?
It's not moving, but what colour is this?
It is moving now.
Is it moving?
Let me see.
- Are you done? - It's light green.
- Light green? - Great.
- It must be a reptile. - He's good.
How did you notice that?
Next, it's Gyeong Gyu.
- Is it a snake? - In fact,
- I'm not afraid of anything. - No way.
I mean it. What should I do?
(You have the most active one.)
You have the most active one.
(Suddenly, he's flustered.)
It is very energetic.
It's the only one that is still standing.
- Really. - Yes, it's still standing.
It's the only one standing.
It is as if an alligator is opening its mouth like this.
- It really is. - Right.
Yours is incredibly active.
- He looks scared. - It's still standing.
- You should know that. - It is true.
(Decide which hand is more important to you.)
Decide which hand is more important.
(He changes to his left hand.)
Which hand do you use to hold your microphone?
Put in the hand that is less important.
- He put in the left hand. - Yes.
He must be right-handed.
- It's moving. - It's not there.
It's not over there but in the centre.
- It's in the centre. - Centre.
Don't pretend you are touching it.
- He's pretending. - You said you're not afraid.
This one is really moving a lot.
- He's almost there. - Almost there.
Just a little further.
(Screaming)
(That was such a frightening touch.)
- It's moving. - It keeps moving.
- It touched my hand suddenly. - It moves a lot.
It was going to bite me.
- He's startled. - He's flustered.
You touched it with just the tip of your finger.
You're easily scared.
- You're timid. - You are a coward.
- He easily gets scared. - Gosh.
I still respect you.
I felt it just with the tip of the finger.
Is it alive?
He is a respectable senior...
- It is slightly mushy. - yet he is timid.
Next, let's go, Hee Jun.
Does it smell?
(Let's try to smell it.)
- Can you smell it? - Does it smell?
Smelling is important.
(Who are you?)
- It smells like a new house. - A new house?
- Yes, a new house. - A new house?
Maybe with four bedrooms?
It smells like the wall of a living room.
He has a keen sense.
There is a P apartment in there.
I think it's R apartment.
(Why not E apartment?)
- Stop joking and smell it. - Okay.
- It smells... - I think it doesn't have a head.
like an apartment in Busan.
It smells slightly fishy,
so it's like an apartment near the beach.
He is so sharp.
- Next, it's Dong Hyun. - Go ahead.
- He is so brave. - Let's see.
- Dong Hyun is so manly. - Dong Hyun's is so scary.
(Let's see if you are a real man.)
- That one is active, too. - It's the most active.
I've never seen it like that.
(He flies like a butterfly and dominates the ring.)
(He's like a stun gun that terrifies the opponents.)
(He is the professional fighter, Kim Dong Hyun.)
(Dominate the abalone for the honour of a fighter.)
- I don't think he'll get hurt. - Oh, goodness.
(Now, it's time to respond.)
(He's twitching.)
- He twitched. - It's moving.
(A guy whose nickname is a stun gun seems to be attacked by one.)
(They immerse themselves in acting and make a fuss.)
It's moving!
- It's standing. - Please stop.
- Really? - Please stop it.
(Goodness!)
Some parts are hard,
- but other parts are soft. - Really?
And is it alive?
I think this one is dead.
- It's alive. - It is.
(Now, try to guess what is in the box.)
(What is Hye Jin's conclusion?)
- It is both hard and soft. - It's a turtle.
(The answer of Team Avengers is a turtle.)
- A turtle? - Is it a turtle?
- A turtle? - I don't think it's a turtle.
It doesn't smell like a turtle.
- The correct answer is abalone. - So it was them.
- They are so active. - Oh, gosh.
Smelling like an apartment in Busan was correct.
- They are alive. - And they are active.
(The current score is zero to zero.)
They are really alive.
- I'd like to look at it. - I can do that.
We need two people to touch it.
- You try to touch it. - I can't even look at it.
That place if for touching and this is for looking.
- I want to look at it. - We'll reveal the third item.
- I can't do this. - In one,
- They are arguing. - two,
- Who is touching it? - three.
I'm startled.
- You need to taste it. - What?
- Taste it? - Yes.
(What could it be?)
(The Avengers start to overreact.)
- You should not taste it. - Don't touch that part.
You mean I should taste it? No way.
(Do you want to taste a piece of it?)
Kwang Soo, go ahead.
- I'm scared. - It smells awful.
It has a strong smell. We should figure it out.
I think it's a fermented skate ray.
- It smells like a fermented skate. - Gosh.
- I think it's a dried fish. - A little more backwards.
- Move backwards. - A little more.
- Be careful over there. - It's scary when you don't see it.
(This looks like a reaction competition.)
- So it's that. - That is...
You are able to touch it though.
I didn't touch it yet.
What do you think it is, Kwang Soo?
(He doesn't dare to touch it yet.)
- What is it, Kwang Soo? - Hold on.
Please explain it to me.
- Go on. - We don't have much time.
We don't have much time.
It's hard. It's hard. It's hard.
- Is it hard? - It's hard. It's hard.
- That means it's dry. - Then it's a dried fish.
Then Gary, what do you see?
I can't see it very well.
It looks like a tail or something.
- What? - Excuse me?
- Does it have a tail? - It looks like a brush.
- A brush? - Yes.
- Next, Haha. - What kind of dried fish is there?
It looks like the tip of a brush.
- You'll find out if you hear it. - It must be a tail.
Is it a dried fish?
I can hear it from here.
- It's alive. - Excuse me?
What sound is it?
(It's a crunching sound.)
(It's crunching sound you make when you tear something.)
What sound is it?
Hey, I have to stick my tongue in here.
(What is this scary sound?)
He really is a musician.
- He is a musician. - You make that sound to your baby.
- I'm serious. - His baby?
You make that sound when you play with your baby.
- He's making me scared. - It's Seok Jin's turn now.
What kind of a game is it to stick your tongue into it?
- Do not put in your tongue fast. - Really?
Why do you say so?
(They are enjoying Seok Jin's anxiety.)
It will be okay, right?
Your tone is funny.
(I'm in charge of tasting. May I kiss you?)
(What can be the romantic item to arouse Seok Jin's taste buds?)
Try to taste it.
I think it doesn't have teeth.
What's wrong?
- What's wrong? - What did it taste like?
Did it touch your tongue?
It felt like a hard piece of wood.
What about the taste?
It has no taste.
It has no taste?
- It has fishy taste, though. - Fishy taste?
Jong Kook, touch it and describe it to us.
He might hurt his hand if he grips it.
- Be careful. - What is it?
- Can you tell what it is? - What?
Can you tell what it is?
- It feels like wood, but... - Right.
it smells like fish.
And...
- Is it something dried? - It's something...
we can touch with ease.
All right.
You'll sense the strong smell.
It smells like fish.
- It's that. - It's...
- Did you smell it often in Pohang? - I smelled it often in Pohang.
- It's not something... - Stop.
- that's completely dried. - It wasn't that soft.
It doesn't smell like something that's completely dried.
How does something that's completely dried smell?
I thought it's completely dried.
I thought it was that and she's...
It smells like the salt water...
- rather than fish. - Let's decide that as the answer.
(What's Jae Seok's final answer after Ji Hyo's description?)
(It feels hard like a piece of wood.)
(It has a tail that looks like a brush.)
(It sounds crunchy as if something is being torn.)
(It has no taste, but smells fishy.)
(It smells like Pohang and something half dried.)
(Team Running Man gets a hint for the final mission if it's correct.)
Dried pollack.
(Jae Seok's answer is dried pollack.)
- Isn't it dried herring? - That's right.
I got confused when you said Pohang.
I thought you'd say dried herring.
- I almost said dried herring. - You didn't, though.
So this is dried pollack.
Wow, this is the dried pollack.
(The strange sound Haha heard was...)
- You make that sound when you play. - I'm being serious.
(that of tearing dried pollack by hand.)
Here's the second object.
In 1, 2 and 3.
Key is up next.
- What is that? - What is it?
- What's going on? - Here they go again.
What is this?
(Here come the people who are experts on bluffing.)
- Goodness. - What is it?
How did you even get this?
- How did you even find this? - Does it even exist today?
I can't believe they came up with this idea.
This is unbelievable.
- Wow, that's... - I would give up.
Let's start with Key.
What are the chopsticks for?
(Is it something we can't even touch?)
- Does he need them for tasting? - To taste it?
How can he taste it?
- It's impossible to taste it. - This is no joke.
Excuse me, but is it possible to make any sound with it?
How can they taste it?
- It's impossible to taste it. - This is no joke.
(The scary unknown object is pork skin.)
It's Key's turn.
- Is there a plate? - There's a plate.
(Startled)
(Haha exaggerates his reaction.)
He just touched it.
- You just touched it. - Did I?
You just touched it, you fool.
(He taps it slightly.)
(They exaggerate their reaction.)
- What is it? - How does it feel?
It feels like some kind of skin.
- Is it alive? - It feels like skin?
- Skin? - Is it alive?
(Fooling them is so fun.)
(Hee Jun listens to the sound.)
Someone is making jeon.
- Someone is making jeon. - Really?
- Gosh, what is it? - What happened?
- There's a fire. There's a fire. - What's going on?
Things are on fire.
There's a fire.
- There's a fire. There's a fire. - What's going on?
(It's the sound of pork skin sizzling on the pan.)
At first, it sounded like someone is making jeon.
(Hee Jun describes the sound sensitively.)
- Then the sound quietens down. - You're so good at explaining it.
- Your description is amazing. - I can even hear the sound now.
- Yes, that's what I heard. - His expression is amazing.
He's very good at describing it.
Everything got burnt.
(It's Hye Jin's turn to touch it.)
- Goodness. - Please.
- Don't do that. - I was really surprised.
(Hye Jin doesn't hesitate at all.)
- What is it? - Let's move onto the next person.
(Mothers are amazing as they fear nothing.)
Gosh, she's not scared at all.
(She gropes about.)
- Gosh, don't do that. - Don't do it.
(She isn't fooled by their reaction.)
- How can she do that? - She's not scared at all.
Why is she doing that?
- Come on. - That's not fun.
That's not fun.
(They try to distract her.)
She's becoming less attractive.
(His comment doesn't affect her.)
- Isn't she too bold? - That's not attractive at all.
She should be scared a little.
- What does it feel like? - It's...
very thin...
and is oily.
- It must be something slippery. - Aren't you scared?
(It's not a big deal.)
That's impressive.
Hye Jin is incredible, indeed.
(It's Dong Hyun's turn.)
Why is she not scared of that?
If it were Ji Hyo, she'd be crying already.
It looks like a thumb.
That's strange.
- It sounds a bit cruel. - Dong Hyun.
Dong Hyun, you're amazing.
(They're impressed by his sight.)
- He never disappoints us. - It's like...
- they put a thumb in here. - Are you talking about this?
- You're very impressive. - It looks like a thumb.
Does it look like this?
It does look like a thumb.
I've never smelled it before.
- I don't know what it smells like. - I wonder what it smells like.
It smells like my grandmother's pillow.
(It means his grandmother used pork skin as her pillow all her life.)
It's so familiar like my grandmother's pillow.
- I don't know why, but it does. - Really?
It's not an odour that gives you a bad feeling.
It's somewhat savoury.
- Right? - It's a little savoury.
Figuring it by taste is the problem.
Making them taste it is...
- It's cruel. - Sung Hoon.
- Will he be okay? - Poor Sung Hoon.
It's not something you can touch.
- Hey, you. - Wait.
You said you'd do everything.
- That's not what I meant. - You said that to me.
You said you didn't know what to do because...
you didn't fear anything.
(Is this what you meant by having no fear?)
He asked me, "What should I do?"
I asked why. He said he didn't fear anything...
and he was worried about the show getting boring.
- I mean this is too... - Just eat it then.
Would you push my head down?
- Here you go. - Gosh.
Put more of your tongue inside.
(He gives up.)
That's enough.
(He throws a fit after tasting pork skin.)
Look at him.
Do you give up?
His actions are too different from his words.
He tapped out.
- Did someone attack you? - I mean this is really...
Please say the answer.
It doesn't have any taste.
- I didn't taste anything at all. - That's right.
It was like skin of fruit. It was like this.
- He's getting close. - He's observant.
It's thin and slippery.
- It had no taste. - It smelled savoury.
Gosh, it's so difficult.
- This isn't it. - In 5, 4, 3...
Why are you counting down?
(It's a competition after all.)
(If Gyeong Gyu gets the answer right, they get tie again.)
- It had no taste. - We're doomed because of you.
Goodness.
(If Team Avengers answers more quickly, they get the hint.)
(What is Gyeong Gyu's answer?)
Fritters?
Is it squid fritters?
(It's incorrect.)
- Is it correct? - That wasn't even close.
They almost got to the answer, though.
- Hye Jin is so competitive. - This is fun.
(Team Running Man wins Round Two.)
Take a look at the second one.
Hye Jin, you know the second one, right?
- Is it pork skin? - Yes.
- How did you know? - It's pork skin.
(Sorry, was it too difficult?)
- If I had known... - The winner of this round is...
Team Running Man.
(Team Running Man receives a hint on the final mission.)
- It's still neck and neck. - It's a tie anyway.
We got one.
- We got one, too. - That's right.
The final mission is "Name Tag Elimination".
Each team decides a lucky and unlucky member from their team...
and put a sticker under their name tags.
If you take off a name tag of a lucky member,
you can not only eliminate the lucky member, but you can also...
eliminate an additional member of your choice within three minutes.
(Getting a lucky member will allow you to eliminate one more.)
If you take off the name tag of an unlucky member, your team loses.
Will the whole game be over?
Does the team lose if you take off an unlucky member's name tag?
- Yes. The game ends then. - We have to be careful.
What if we take off a tame tag of an unlucky member?
- Do we get to go home? - Your team loses.
- I'll be the unlucky member. - Being unlucky is good.
Let's look for the unlucky member.
You want it to be over quickly instead of winning?
I want to hit him.
(Which team will be the final winner?)
Did you decide on the lucky and unlucky member?
Let's look for the hint.
Let's look for the hint first.
Wait. We have to find the hint,
but this place is too big.
- I don't know where to start. - Can we go inside the store?
Don't you think the hint is in here?
I don't think many people looked through here.
Where is R?
(Find the hint on who's lucky and unlucky.)
(You must find the hint to prevent from losing.)
This place is huge.
It really is.
Even this store is big.
(Goodness)
We should leave.
- Gosh. - I'm sorry.
- I didn't know. - I'm sorry.
- I had no idea. - Come on, Jae Seok.
I really had no idea.
(Meanwhile, Team Avengers are also searching for hints.)
It will take forever to look through all these.
(Goodness!)
(Did Hee Jun finally find a hint?)
Can't I have ice cream?
(You said, you were on a diet.)
This is so hard.
(Where are the hints?)
How would it look like?
- Are you the unlucky member? - Yes.
Me, too.
You received a hint, right?
No, I didn't.
I thought you received one earlier.
I'm coming to eliminate you.
- Can I rip your name tag? - Yes, you can.
- Seriously? - Yes, I'm serious.
(You can rip it off if you want to.)
(Has Kwang Soo released an album before?)
Well,
- you can eliminate me now. - Really?
So only one of you are the unlucky member, right?
- But the hint said that Ji Hyo... - One of you aren't the unlucky.
and Kwang Soo can't be the unlucky.
We'll receive a hint soon.
- I'm pretty confident. - We can eliminate him.
- We can eliminate Kwang Soo. - Why?
He didn't release an album...
Oh, I see.
I see.
(Kwang Soo runs off as soon as Key slips out the hint.)
- What should we do? - Hurry.
(Who is this?)
(It's Jong Kook.)
I just heard their hint.
Jong Kook!
- I'm such a fool. - Jong Kook!
(They can't approach easily because of Jong Kook.)
Jae Seok, their hint is someone who released an album.
"Someone who released an album" must be their hint.
- What? - "Someone who released an album".
- Why did you let it slip? - We promised not to reveal that.
- Oh my. - Goodness.
I must be a fool!
(Gosh, I must be a food.)
Ji Hyo!
What? What's going on?
"Someone who released an album" must be their hint.
- You mean that's the hint? - Yes, for the unlucky member.
So it's about our unlucky member.
Ji Hyo, run away!
(We are their targets.)
What's happening?
(Team Avengers are on their way to find other hints.)
- This place is suspicious. - There's nothing in here.
- This place is suspicious. - I feel there must be something.
It's somewhat suspicious.
What?
- Oh, my. It's here. - Did you really find one?
- Where did you find it? - Good job.
It was in here. I spotted it when I was trying to sit on the swing.
You are amazing.
- Nice job. - What? What's this?
You'll get a hint if you choose the yogurt without vinegar.
- It's completely random. - I see.
Since you have the box, why don't you try to pick one?
Gyeong Gyu.
Look at the colour. I can't tell from the colour.
- I think number 7 is the yogurt. - Is this number 7?
- Isn't this number 1? - It's number 1.
How can you say this is seven?
My goodness. How could this be seven?
- I thought it was 7. - This is number 1.
- Please choose. - I choose number two.
(Gyeong Gyu chooses number 2.)
- Now, drink it. - Yes.
Does he need to drink it all at once? Oh, my.
- I think I know what it is. - What if it's the vinegar?
(What will it be?)
(He drinks it down.)
(It has to the yogurt to receive a hint.)
This is amazing. Is that the vinegar?
(Moving his mouth)
- Is it the yogurt? - It's the yogurt!
- Really? - Are you serious?
I noticed it when you said "number seven".
Let's see what number one is.
(Oh, dear.)
(Congratulations. Number one was the vinegar.)
- That was amazing. - Well, it's...
- Your face is turning red. - I think he is bloating.
- This is quite fun. - Yes, it is. This is exciting.
The hint will be sent to your mission phone.
- The mission phone. - Oh, it's here.
- This fast? - It was really fast.
- It's because we're standing close. - Such a nice world we live in.
He could've just said it rather than sending a message.
- I know. - It's a nice world.
What a nice world we live in today.
- The unlucky member is single? - Unmarried?
- Then it must be Ji Hyo or Gary. - Ji Hyo or Gary.
- Ji Hyo or Gary. - Kwang Soo is also single.
Or Jong Kook! There are four.
- There are so many. - Among them,
- Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo didn't... - They didn't released an album.
- It must be Jong Kook or Gary. - Jong Kook or Gary.
- Jong Kook or Gary. - So it's one of them.
- Jong Kook or Gary? - Yes. The unlucky is 1 of the 2.
There are four unmarried members.
We found out that Jong Kook or Gary must be the unlucky member.
- They are all over there, now. - Are they together?
- All of them are there. - Let's go.
- Where? Where? - Sung Hoon could be the unlucky.
- Right. - Key is very active.
- Dong Hyun might be the one. - I think I saw someone here.
- There she is. - What?
- It's Hye Jin. I feel sorry. - We need to eliminate her.
Where are the others?
(Is Hye Jin in trouble?)
(Here you go.)
(Is Hye Jin the unlucky member?)
(She tries to eliminate Kwang Soo.)
- Wait a minute, Hye Jin. - I'll do it.
- Hye Jin. - Can I eliminate you?
(How dare you?)
You rip mine, and I'll rip yours.
- Can I eliminate you? - Can we really do this?
- I have to go watch soccer. - She was trying to rip mine off.
I have to hurry home to watch the soccer game.
- You mean you need to go home? - Can I rip it off?
Sure.
Then we can all call it a day.
- Come on. - Why are you doing this?
- Eliminate her. - Leave it.
(I don't think Hye Jin is the unlucky member.)
(Ripping)
- Come on. - You ripped mine.
- Eliminate her. - Hold on for now.
(He ripped mine.)
(She's such a good actress.)
- Didn't he just rip mine? - You are such a good actress.
They're here.
(Team Avengers is here.)
- Why? Go ahead. - Don't come near.
(Finally, they are here.)
- Wait a minute. - Hey!
- What's going on? - No, it's fine. Eliminate me.
Hey, don't go there.
(Running Man members could be hiding...)
- Don't go near them. - Gyeong Gyu.
(like this.)
(Jong Kook was hiding when Team Avengers arrived.)
(He sneaks from the back.)
(Gary, who was also hiding, approaches.)
(Ripping)
(Sneaking)
(Jong Kook and Gary make a surprise attack.)
- He's eliminated. - They attacked from the back.
(Gyeong Gyu was not on the list from the beginning.)
- What happened? - Let's leave. Let's go.
- We can't be here. - What's going on?
We have to get Kwang Soo.
(Is Gary in trouble?)
(He escapes.)
Don't eliminate Gary or Jong Kook!
(If we eliminate them rashly, we may end up losing the game.)
Do not eliminate Gary or Jong Kook!
(They are running after them.)
It's okay to eliminate him.
(Ripping)
- He's out. - Seok Jin is eliminated.
(Seok Jin is eliminated.)
- He's eliminated. - Oh my.
(Jae Seok is cornered.)
Eliminate Jae Seok!
(Eliminate Jae Seok!)
- Hold on. - Eliminate him!
(They're vigorously attacking Jae Seok.)
- Wait a minute. - It's fine. Eliminate him.
(Gary attempts to rescue Jae Seok.)
Hey! Get back! Not him!
(Sung Hoon, you can't eliminate Gary!)
(If he's the unlucky member, then we are doomed.)
Leave Gary alone!
(They can attack other members as much as they like.)
- Jong Kook! - Hyung Bin, Hyung Bin.
(Screeching)
Eliminate Hyung Bin.
(Haha is cornered.)
We got him.
Haha is eliminated.
(Jong Kook sneaks in.)
Gary, eliminate him. Eliminate Hyung Bin.
(Will he rip off Hye Jin's name tag?)
(Earlier)
Isn't this the hint box?
(Ji Hyo found a hint box.)
(A hint will be given if you pick the normal chopsticks.)
(It's a success.)
(The unlucky member of Team Avengers uses a nickname.)
The unlucky member uses a nickname.
- A nickname? - Yes.
(If so...)
(Since Hye Jin uses her real name, she can't be the unlucky.)
(Ripping)
(Hye Jin is eliminated.)
Eliminate him.
(Kwang Soo is confronting Key and Sung Hoon.)
(Ripping)
(He succeeds.)
(Kwang Soo is eliminated.)
(Team Avengers repaid their debt.)
- Good job. - Guys!
Goodness.
- Are you all right? - Jae Seok.
(Gyeong Gyu is coaching his team even when he's eliminated.)
Who's that behind Jae Seok?
(Eliminating Jae Seok is only a matter of time.)
(Jong Kook appears.)
Hey. No way! Dong Hyun!
- Goodness. - No way! Dong Hyun!
(He rips off Dong Hyun's name tag.)
(Dong Hyun is the lucky member!)
Dong Hyun is the lucky member.
(Team Avengers' lucky member is Dong Hyun.)
We need to be prudent. Lucky member shouldn't get eliminated.
- Yes, he shouldn't get eliminated. - So he needs to be strong.
- I suggest Dong Hyun... - Right.
- or Sung Hoon. - Okay. Let's do that.
Gary or Jong Kook is the unlucky member.
We'll choose one to be eliminated.
- We should've eliminated Jae Seok. - Be careful!
- Please be cautious. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Hyung Bin. - Hyung Bin.
- Hyung Bin is out. - He's out.
- Me? - Yes.
- Why? - You mean this is the end?
We also had a hint.
- You're not the unlucky member. - The hint says so.
What do you take us for?
We already know you're not the unlucky member.
Any last words?
(He rips off his own name tag.)
- Nice. - Will you give me back my name tag?
It's okay to eliminate Jae Seok.
(Remaining team members)
There's a possibility that...
they may think I'm too passive to be the unlucky member.
I used guerrilla tactics and not attacked them actively.
But they might have perceived you as being active.
Since this is hit-or-miss, our option is Sung Hoon or Key.
We'll have to make a choice and eliminate one. There's no other way.
No, we have no idea what will happen when the situation gets tense.
- Maybe it's Key. - It's so uncertain.
I'm sure they are more confused than us.
- You're right. - Yes, I'm sure they are.
Even if we have the hints,
taking the bull by the horns is the only way.
- There's no way to eliminate them. - Right.
- I think Jong Kook is the lucky. - In order for us to win,
we need to eliminate everyone except the unlucky member.
I think we should eliminate Jong Kook and Jae Seok.
What about Ji Hyo? She's still alive.
- Right, she's still alive. - Yes.
Then...
- She must be the lucky member. - Yes.
Is she?
That's why they told her to hide and not to roam around.
- They must be over there. - Where? There?
I can hear them.
- There they are. - Yes. I can see them.
- Where are they? - Right over there.
They are approaching us. They must have found all the hints already.
Come on, Hee Jun. Let's just fight.
Let's finish this quickly.
- Yes. - It's hit-or-miss now.
Remember. Jong Kook isn't our first target.
Come on. Let's do it.
- Hee Jun. This way. - There's Jae Seok.
Go. Let's rip his name tag first.
(They are sure that Jae Seok isn't the unlucky member.)
- Rip it off. - There.
(Jae Seok is eliminated.)
- Be careful. - Go for Jong Kook's name tag.
(One of them is the unlucky member.)
(Who is the unlucky one?)
Come on, Jong Kook. Please.
(They are wrestling hand-to-hand.)
Come on.
Jong Kook. Do you call this a variety show?
This is a fighting show.
(Sung Hoon reaches out for a name tag.)
(Is he trying to rip Jong Kook's name tag...)
(or Gary's?)
(Whom is he going to attack?)
Maybe there isn't anything.
(Sung Hoon goes for Jong Kook's!)
- Gosh. - What?
(He rips off Jong Kook's name tag.)
(Team Avengers loses right away if Jong Kook is the unlucky member.)
(If Jong Kook is the lucky member, they can eliminate Ji Hyo and win.)
(How will this battle end?)
- Gosh. - What?
(Jong Kook is the lucky member.)
Where is it?
Where is his name tag?
(We did it.)
I couldn't rip his name tag off.
(Hee Jun found a hint box.)
- I found one. Isn't this the one? - Where is it?
- That's right. - Yes.
I'll get a hint if I eat the one without mustard in it.
Can we check?
I succeeded.
The unlucky member of Team Running Man uses a nickname.
(Gary, who uses his nickname, was the unlucky member.)
(Unlucky)
- Choose one to be eliminated. - We will eliminate Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo is eliminated.)
All right.
Jae Seok shouldn't have been eliminated.
Team Avengers has won.
(Team Avengers has won.)
The sequel is always better than the first.
Today, we had Running Man versus Avengers Part 2...
and Team Avengers won.
(Sung Hoon was the ace of Team Avengers today.)
We will give this golden shield to Team Avengers.
(The golden shield will be given to Team Avengers as the prize.)
Do you get it? Be modest.
Why do you live like that? Act your age.
- Can you just do it? - You shouldn't scold him.
- I'm not done yet. - Let's finish here.
(Waiting to be penalised is more tiring than penalty itself.)
That must be more tiring.
(Gyeong Gyu slaps his forehead.)
Did you hear that sound?
He fell with a thud.
The sound resonated in this place.
(Running Man vs Avengers Part 3 coming soon!)
(It's time for Running Man TV.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(The most popular videos with the most popular keywords)
(Haha's channel)
(Become popular with a three-minute video)
(Jong Kook's channel)
(Bring in anyone you want.)
(Show how charming you are.)
(Kwang Soo's channel)
(You can't guess what's coming next.)
(Seok Jin's channel)
(Meanwhile,)
(there is a man wandering around Running Man members.)
(The scene stealer)
(Running Man TV)