So, have a nice day!
That's ruined now anyway.
Why?
Because you're leaving.
You fool!
I really hate to interrupt you, but either I take care of our milk supply
and you take care of table 9 or the other way around,
or we tell everyone to leave and close.
Okay, I'll take care of table... - ...9 ! And I'm in the basement.
Well, and I'm off!
Yeah, you all just go and abandon me!
I'm so sorry!
Hey! - Oh, hi!
Err...are you together?
Well, are you...?
Happy for you! Bye! - Thank you!
There's a free table. - Hello! - Hi!
Oh, Miriam! We'd like to have two No Limits special breakfasts.
It includes everything you could wish for.
Frederic!
What are you doing here?
Err.. working!
And you?
You two know each other? That's funny, where from?
Well, funny?
Is something wrong?
Good question! Is something wrong?
Miriam, please, it's...
How's Yvette doing?
That's his wife.
I can explain everything to you. Please, calm down!
I don't want to calm down! And I don't want to hear any explanations!
I didn't mean to hurt you.
But rather just have some fun, I get it!
Well you've had your fun, now leave!
Rebecca, I ...
... I'm sorry!
Hey, the guy isn't worth it.
I really thought this could be something serious for a change.
Yeah, he knows how to give you that feeling.
Did he... with you?
Oh God, no!
I went to school with his wife.
And this is not the first time I've heard something like this about him.
Why do I have such bad luck with men?
You're not the only one.
I mean, ever since my boyfriend and I broke up...
Oh, forget about it!
But you know what? It's not our fault!
The state of the market is somewhat less than perfect.
But that'll change at some point.
Sure.
Well, I firmly believe in it.
And until then, we'll just look at the bright side.
I mean, you've surely had fun last night, right?
You see!
Who says that only men are allowed to enjoy these kind of nights?