Subtitles by DramaFever
[Entrance of the 11th Running Man!]
[The identity of the Running Man...
They were all wondering about...?]
[The last Running Man...]
[He is here...!]
[The eternal Captain]
[Park Ji Sung]
[Park Ji Sung and Running Man]
[The historical first meeting!]
-This is awesome!
-Park Ji Sung!  Park Ji Sung!
-This is seriously the best!
-You really came!
The world's soccer star!
Park Ji Sung!
[The honorable world soccer star!
Park Ji Sung!]
Are you seriously going to be doing
Running Man with us?
Yes, that's right.
-Have you ever watched our program?
-Yes.  I watch it often.
I know you must be really busy during season,
do you have the time to watch TV?
Yes.  We have lots of time to watch it.
He's so honest.  So honest...!
He was so honest about it,
that I got flustered!
By any chance, does Coach Ferguson...?
[Is the coach of Manchester United also a viewer?]
What are you talking about right now?
Maybe Coach Ferguson catches what
Park Ji Sung is watching..
-And he could ask..
-What is this?
This is Gary!
I don't know about the coach...
but Abram watches it.
He watches it!
Abram!  Abram watches it!
-Who knew that he'd be watching us?
This is truly an honor.
Abram... wow!
Is it fun?
[Scared? No, it's fun!]
What are you talking about?
Are you going to be okay if we tear off your
name tag and stuff while doing this with us?
Yes.  I'm confident that I won't get caught.
I'm begging you, but please tear it off
of Jong Kook's back once.
Jong Kook is just impossible for us!
If you win the race
playing against Park Ji Sung,
You'll win an invitation to
Asiana Dream Cup,
and you'll be able to run a lap with
Park Ji sung on the field.
-Think of it as an honor...
-We're going to get to play soccer too?
[The chance to participate in a charity game
with world stars!]
But Park JI Sung has to draft you in order
to get in the game...
[That first step!  Psychic soccer!]
[Just what does psychic soccer mean...?]
Do you by any chance know what it is?
-Using the psychic powers...
-Yes.  The man who controls the time...?
Do you know death note?
My death note?
Death note...
Wasn't it picked as the least popular?
[Out of all the member's powers,
Kwang Soo's voted the least desirable]
Oh my... Park Ji Sung knows all about it.
[A brand new psychic power makes its entry!]
[Dominate the ground!]
[And complete the Running Man mission
with Park Ji Sung!]
[Korea-Thailand bound Mission Impossible!]
[The ultimate winner win stands
on the Asiana stage!]
Now there is one more guest
that will be joining you today.
You're saying there's another guest?!
-Someone else is coming?  Who's coming?
-Come on out!!
Who is it?  Please come out!
[Wow!!  The nation's little sister, IU!!]
[Speechless...turns to embarrassment]
[The nation's little sister,
and the worldwide soccer star meet]
Is Ji Hyo that lacking?
Park Ji Sung all of a sudden
seems very embarrassed.
Why are you standing so far apart?
-Why are you being like that all of a sudden?
-Yeah.  Go stand next to her.
What's it like to see Park Ji Sung, IU?
It's so amazing!
It's like that for us too.
We're just pretending not to be like that.
[In truth, members of Running Man agree]
Now we're going to start the psychic soccer.
With the exception of Park Ji Sung,
everyone else will have 1 psychic power.
Why aren't you giving me one?
Park Ji Sung is asking
why you're not giving him one.
What is it that you want to have?
-A psychic power?
-Yes.
The power to dominate space.
That's my power.
Why don't you try shouting out
domination of balls?
Do you know how embarrassing it is?
[Even though it may be nice,
it's probably very embarrassing to shout out]
[It's actually very embarrassing to
shout it out in front of people]
-When I say mine...
-Show me.  Show me how you do it.
You have to do it with charisma...
Pull it up like this, and raise it...
That's right.
Dominate the space...
You have to finish it!
[Trying to do it seriously and
finds it embarrassing]
-You have to finish it!
-Oh, I'm so embarrassed!
Okay.  I'll give it another try.
[Demonstrating again with gritted teeth]
[The man who dominates space!]
[If done properly, the effect is visible]
-Why don't you give it a try, Park Ji Sung?
-Like this?
I just have to do it like this, right?
The man who dominates space!
That's not very cool!
You were very serious about it!
[The aftermath of embarrassment]
If you can get a psychic power,
what would you like to have?
-I'd want the death note.
-Why?
Who would you kill off?
-If we're playing soccer...
-Yes, you can kick them off.
Then Park Ji Sung...
[With the death note, Park Ji Sung...?]
You're saying you're going to kill me off?!
You can't do that!
I'm saying if he was on the opposing team.
Only if he's on the other team.
She's scary...
[Wait for it!]
[Scary Girl, IU's surprising action!]
First.  There will need to be 2 teams.
I'll announce the captain for each team.
-For 1 team, without a doubt...
-It's Park Ji Sung.
[One of the teams' captain is Park Ji Sung]
The captain for the other team is...
-Kim Jong Kook.
-I knew it!
Why are you doing that?!
Only one of the Running Man members
can go on Park Ji Sung's team.
-I'll go.
-Come on...
I can just go! Me!
I think we can make a go of it.
-You'll be okay, right, Park Ji Sung?
-No, that's not okay.
You're even giving them psychic powers...
[2-member Park Ji Sung's team vs.
7-member Running Man's team]
Park Ji Sung will start to tear off the name
tag from members he doesn't want on his team.
Is there anyone specific that you want?
No, not a single one of them.
I can just go behind them and tear it off?
I'm really looking forward to today.
[Yes, you can look forward to it]
[First off, Suk Jin is eliminated
from Ji Sung's team]
Now the game can start for the day!
He ripped it off without even hesitating!
He rips it off with such delight.
[First Suk Jin goes off to Jong Kook's team]
[Who's next to be eliminated?]
[Ji Sung's ripped off one person's tag,
Ji Suk Jin's...]
-Ji Suk Jin's...
[In the middle of his speech...!]
This time too, he tears it off
in such an entertaining way!]
That's awesome!
Park Ji Sung... Do you not have any intentions
of coming on the show often from now on?
[Even the nation's most famous MC lusts for
Park Ji Sung's appearance on his show]
-Isn't his timing the best?
-His timing is an art form.
That's awesome... Seriously...
[Then who's the 3rd to be eliminated?]
-I was expecting it...
-I'm sure you were expecting it.
It would've been fun.
I feel a little saddened by it.
-I'm seriously nervous!
-My heart is pounding!
-My heart is racing!
-I'm sorry...
-I'm sorry.
-Song Ji Hyo! Come over here.
You think you'd be picked
when IU is standing next to you?
[A sudden surprise
during a brief moment of reprieve]
Come here.
My heart really hurt...
I feel like I've just been dumped.
You feel like you've been dumped?
[Not being on the same team with Ji Sung
makes it feel like one's been broken up with]
I wonder who's it's going to be?
[Only ones that are left.
IU-Kwang Soo-Gary.  3 people!]
Don't expect anything, Kwang Soo.
I'm sorry!
[IU's whole body gets dragged!]
[Since she's so light,
she gets pulled along with the name tag]
[Ji Sung... Totally flustered]
[Captain Park in total shock]
No, I'm fine.  I'm okay.
It's because you're not strong.
[IU also eliminated from Ji Sung's team]
-It's just the 2 of them now.
-No way!
That seriously makes no sense!
Then... Why don't you each show us
your soccer skills?
Why don't you try what
you've just shown us with a real ball?
Please show us what you've got too, Gary.
-Only your back is showing.
-Look at the camera.
But he's standing here!
Because he was standing here...
[Captain Park is doing so well
even though it's his first day...]
He's doing whatever he can to
look good for Ji Sung.
You know this move, right?
[He is imitating something...]
I bet he's going to pick Gary.
[Just who will Captain Park pick?]
Park Ji Sung's pick...
1...
[Huh?  This mean...?!]
[Kwang Soo joins Ji Sung's team?!]
[It seems like Ji Sung's has uses
for the tall Kwang Soo]
[At last...]
[Psychic soccer kickoff!]
[Game time  5/20/2012; 10 a.m.]
[Park Ji Sung Soccer Center in Suwon]
[All the team members from both teams enter]
Kwang Soo, just come.
[Kwang Soo starts to loosen up his body
as soon as he enters the field]
You should do that after pictures.
That's what you're supposed to do.
We don't do that as we enter the field.
[At last, the entrance of
all the psychic soccer players are complete]
Ah... I wonder what my psychic power will be?
[Time to accept their new psychic powers]
In those bottles are the psychic powers
that all of you can use.
As you know from your previous experience,
once you drink from the bottle,
you can activate your psychic power.
First, you can each check your powers
starting with Gary.
[Starting with Gary, they each find out
what psychic powers that they have]
[Just what is his psychic power?]
Wow... You look sexy.
You look so manly!
[Just what is his psychic power?
Stay tuned...!]
Mine's a really good one too!
It's totally good.
[Just what is Ji Hyo's psychic power...?]
This is driving me nuts.
I think I'm going to go crazy!
[What is the meaning behind
IU's laughter?]
[With the exception of Park Ji Sung,
all the Running Man's powers are activated!]
The giraffe...
[Side effect?]
[Forget it]
-Where should we stand?
-Just stand right there.
-We just need to stand where we are?
-Yeah, just stay there.
Are you not going to tell us your powers?
I'll tell you mine now.
I'll tell you what my power is first.
Mine is...
I can give out a red card to someone
who gets in the way on my team.
-What kind of a power is that?
-So I'm telling you to do a good job!
[Other people's psychic power
that's still wrapped up in mystery!]
[15 minutes for the first half]
[Kick Off!]
[Just as Ji Sung is about to kick...]
Here it comes!
[Captain Park is the scariest even though
he doesn't have any psychic powers]
[Ji Sung moves up slowly for now]
How can I be the one to try and stop Ji Sung?
[Right away, the explosive drive!]
[In psychic soccer, offside is not foul]
[He passes... To Kwang Soo!]
[It's blocked!]
[Defending the post... Mr. Capable's block!]
[Counterattack of Running Man with
psychic powers!]
[However,
all of it is noise and it lacks teamwork]
[Park Ji Sung takes it again!]
[He sees something!]
[Seeing that the goal post is open,
he shoots!]
[No!!!]
[The mixed bag of a team that's
blaming everything on one another]
[The female players are ready to collapse
after that bit of running]
[Just what is Ha Ha's power that he's
walking around with strings attached?]
Hey!  Jae Suk!
[Even though we get an idea...]
You can only go around like that?
[Because of the strings, he can't go sideways
and only forward and backward]
[It's not like he's a subway train
with cables attached...]
Pass it to me!  Pass!!
I'll show you my powers!!
[A total miss]
[Could that be his power by any chance?]
Hey, you can't go sideways?!
[Out of bounds.  Running Man team's ball]
Me!  Me!!
-Jong Kook, hurry!
-Over here!
[Finally, Ha Ha gets the pass]
[The one who divides the air!!]
The one who divides the air!
[The one who divides the air]
[Can freely fly around]
[ However can only fly in a straight line]
[The one who divides space, Ha Ha!]
[But it's too scary!]
[Ultimately, he drops the ball!]
What's that all about?!
Scary!  That's so scary!
[Extremely afraid of his own powers]
What are you doing?!
[But if used correctly,
it seems it'll definitely be useful]
-So funny!
-You're driving me crazy!
[Easily outmaneuvers Gary, and pass!]
[Finally, the moment for Kwang Soo to shoot!]
[Out of the blue,
countless number of balls appear!]
[Fake balls falling  out of Gary's bag]
[The one who dominates the balls]
[The power to use the fake balls in the bag
to cause disturbance and protect the ball]
What was that all about?
-What was that?
-The bag wouldn't come off!
What was that?!
[The balls are tied to the bag,
so he has to carry the bag around]
Out, out.  Do that out there.
[The tedious aftermath of it too...]
[Ji Sung team's corner kick]
[Suk Jin intercepts the ball!]
[Ha Ha is right in front!]
[No matter how hard he runs...
He loses the ball because of the strings]
You must not be able to come this way.
[If he can't fly, Ha Ha is deemed useless]
[Ji Sung's team counterattacks]
Come this way!  Come down here!
[Wow... Cool footwork]
[The 2 girls getting flustered
in front of the goal post!]
[You and I... All we do is scream...]
[What's wrong with us?]
[Ji Sung, evades Gary]
[Shoots!]
Goal!!!!!!
[It bounces off of Kwang Soo's hips]
[Kwang Soo's score!]
[Ji Sung's team-2; Running Man team-0]
Let's go!  Let's do this!
-What the heck is this?!
-What are you doing?
[What a useless power...]
Just what the heck is this?
-Fly again.
-Do it right this time.
The man who divides the air!
[Ha Ha once again takes
to the air with the ball]
-What is this?
-That's so funny.
[Looks like he's used to it...!]
[However he once again fails to
pass it to his own team]
Do you know how many people are
having a hard time because of you right now?
[The wire team that enables Ha Ha to fly]
[During that time, Ji Sung counterattacks]
[The one who dominates the balls
interferes again!]
[Ji Sung doesn't even break a sweat,
and passes the real ball to Kwang Soo!]
[Kwang Soo calmly shoots the ball...]
I said, Woosa!
[Suk Jin did seem to shout something...]
I said Woosa!  What happened!
-What the heck is Woosa?
-It's the power to move the goal post!
[The man with the power to move the goal]
[Woosa means move the goal to the right]
[Jwasa's the power to move it to the left]
[Ji Sung's team-3; Running Man's team-0]
Come this way!
Do it when he's about to shoot the ball!
[Captain Park easily maneuvers the ball]
He's so quick!
You have to block Ji Sung!
Wow... He really is amazing!
Park Ji Sung really is good.
[Nice move... Ripping apart the pants]
[They're all seduced by Ji Sung's moves]
[Just one spot!
Eyes the empty space, and shoots!]
[Ji Sung's team-4; Running Man's team-0]
Just throw that bag away!
[Mr. Capable is slowly getting fired up]
[Can't lose this way!]
[Game resumed]
[Running Man team slowly starting to
build up their teamwork]
Woosa!  Woosa!  Woosa!
[The goal keepers are one step too late again]
[At last!]
[Jong Kook vs. Ji Sung!]
[Just what...?]
[That simply!]
[Now it's Captain Park's counterattack!]
[In front is useless Ha Ha]
[It's better than flying around]
[The giraffe gets revenge on the tiger
for all the pent up anger!]
[The ball is calmly
making its way to Suk Jin!]
[Running Man...
At last, an emotional first goal!]
[Ji Sung's team-4; Running Man's team-1]
Psychic power...!  Activate!
Jae Suk...
[Just what is that?]
My hand... My feet...
I can use my hands as feet!
You can use your hands as feet?
I can grab the ball!
[The one who's hands become feet]
[The ability to hold onto a ball
for 10 seconds]
Block the giraffe.  The giraffe!
[Gary starts to disrupt again with his balls]
That's not the ball.  It's this ball.
[So confusing]
[Suk Jin has the real ball]
[But Ji Sung intercepts that ball too]
Grab it!  Grab it!
[It went in!]
[Captain Park adds another point
with an awesome lobbying shot]
[What's the point of being able to
use the hands...?]
[This is hard on me too]
I didn't get to grab it.
[Ji Sung's team-5; Running Man's team-1]
[Passing it to Ji Hyo for now]
Ji Hyo, grab it and run!
[Ji Hyo gives the ball to Ha Ha!]
Man who can divide the air!
[Ha Ha delivers the ball to the
goal line by flying through the air]
[An inaccurate pass!]
[Ji Sung intercepts]
This is driving me crazy...!
Are you seriously just dividing up the air?
[Starting the counterattack by
showing off fancy skills]
[Uses his face for the head but...!]
[This is seriously a spectacle!]
Why did you hit it with your face?
I... Like you, oppa!
(Oppa=brother or term of endearment, honey]
I... Like you, oppa!!
[Just what kind of a power is this?]
-What's this?
-What is it?
[Ability to summon troop of uncles]
[If the song verse is chanted, an army of
uncles will escort IU to the goal line]
[But can only be used once per game halves]
What the heck is this?
[Gets up to the front of the goal by being
escorted by an army of protective uncles]
[Finally!]
[They score a goal by using IU's power!]
[Ji Sung's team-5; Running Man's team-2]
[Goal certified check!  IU's psychic power!]
Great job, guys!
This is the best... Even Ji Sung was flustered.
[No way to block that...]
[I'm jealous... Of her power]
There's only 3 minutes left to the first half.
Feel the wrath of my power!
The wind...!
What was that?
[He forgot his spell!]
What happens then?
[During that time,
Running Man's team starts getting attacked!]
[Running Man team is trying their best
to defend their goal!]
[The man who can call on the wind!]
[The one who can call on the wind]
[Interrupting the opposing team's attempt at
a goal by blowing 5 fans in front of the goal]
[However... Even still, Ji Sung scores]
[After the goal, they're working on the spell]
Just what the heck is this about?!
-What for?  Because you were hot?
-Um... I forgot the spell!
Did you do it because you were hot?
[You should've activated it earlier
for it to have any effect...]
[Ji Sung's team-6; Running Man's team-2]
Park Ji Sung, doesn't the fan feel cool?
[I seriously am about to go crazy]
[More engaging of a game than expected]
-The one who can stop time!
-What's that?
The one who can stop time!
[Huh?  Stop time?]
[Glad green people are suddenly on the field!]
[The one who can stop time]
[For 30 seconds, they can stop the other team
from moving.  One use per a game half]
What?  Wait!
[Captain Park in the meantime goes in leisure]
[The giraffe has a different goal]
That really hurts!  Hey!
[Finishes it as if
he's a prodigy for the showbiz]
[Ji Sung's team-7; Running Man's team-4]
You should've given me that power!
The one who can divide the air!
[First half's 15 minutes over]
What the heck?
[Ji Sung's team-7; Running Man's team-4]
Is it over?
You have 10 minutes rest time.
[Feeling like death warmed over
after running for 15 minutes]
[Comatose stare]
Ugh, this is so hard!
I don't think I can run anymore.
This is the first time in my life
that I've run so much.
[Coming up with a plan for the time
when they don't have enough manpower]
When we don't have enough manpower...
One person plays offense,
and the other plays defense.
And one person has to concentrate
on getting goals in.
Since you're tall,
you can be offense up front.
Then I'll send the ball over to you,
and you can head butt it in.
-Since you're the tallest.
-I'm confident I can do that.
When I saw you earlier,
you weren't very good at it.
IU is our guaranteed striker.
IU is the best.
Your power is the best.
Park Ji Sung was flustered for the first time.
-I'll take charge of the goal post.
-Okay.
And with my power,
I can constantly move it.
-You'd be best for that.
-Of course.
Use your power to move the goal
all the way out there.
How do you do the 'fighting'?
My team doesn't do that.
No one in Manchester does it.
It's not just me...
Do you not want to do it with me or something?
When told you I could do something,
you tell me I'm not good at it...
[Ultimately, he ends up doing it for him...]
When I say 1, 2, 3, just do it like this.
-You got it?  Then you'll work hard?
-Yes.  I'll work hard.
1, 2, 3. Ah!
So cool...
You're so cool!
-We'll start the second half!
-Here we go!
[Captain Park personally starting off
the camera slate]
-You have to scream out 1, 2, 3.
-I have to scream that out?
-Here we go with the slate.
[Nagging]
Here we go with the slate.  1, 2, 3.
Here we go!  1, 2, 3!
Running Man!
1, 2, 3.  Fighting!
We're all capable people...
You know that, right?
1, 2, 3. Ah!
Since it's just us two doing it,
it seems a little pathetic.
If he doesn't do it, the who would?
[Second half.  15 minutes kickoff!]
Get it!  Grab your bag and run.
You can't let him have it, Gary!
What are you doing?  What are you doing?!
Gary, what are you doing?
Use your skills!
[To confuse Ji Sung, he drops the fake balls]
[Gary has the real ball]
[Mr. Capable + Jae Suk.
A two-person attack!]
[Jae Suk's pass...
Mr. Capable finishes it off!]
[Ji Sung's team-7; Running Man's team-5]
Good job!
Awesome!  Awesome...!
At last, it's time for me to use it.
The one to call on the wind!
[Activating the strong wind]
What the heck is this?
Get me the ball.
[Captain Park, as soon as the whistle blows,
he shoots right away?]
[The shoot that goes up against the wind.
Could it be?]
[It hits the goal post and bounces out]
[Such a waste!]
[This is the power of the Wind!
The ball bounces out thanks to the wind!]
The one who calls on the wind!
-Why are you calling that right now?
-I meant for when he's attacking.
[A strong gale blows from behind]
-Jae Suk!  Over here!
-Get it!
[Riding on the wind, Jae Suk shoots!]
[The ball rides on the wind,
and strongly makes it in the net]
[Ji Sung's team-7; Running Man's team-6]
[As they learn about their powers,
Running Man team gets stronger]
[Current score]
[Ji Sung's team-10; Running Man's team-8]
The one who...!
The one who divides the air!
That hurts!
[The air or whatever...
The wire is hurting Ha Ha]
-Woosa!  Woosa!  Woosa!
-The one who calls on the wind!
[Running Man team moves the goal,
and even calls on the wind!]
[A total chaos in front of the goal]
The one who calls on the wind!
[Kwang Soo unable to shoot properly
due to the gale]
[Just then... Gary's lone chance!]
[Ji Sung picks up his speed!]
[Ji Sung flies in like lightning,
and succeeds at interception!]
[An astonishing focus and speed,
Captain Park!]
The one who divides the air!
Just slightly, slightly.  Okay, good.
Go forward.  Good.
I'm going to head butt it in.
[Ha Ha's plan to head butt it in]
-Keep your eye on it!
-Just kick it over!
[After Captain Park intercepts the ball]
[He misses!]
[No goal because Suk Jin moved the goal
with his psychic power]
[A total master
at the ability to move the goal]
What the heck?!
[Running Man team's counterattack]
[Finally learning to play together]
Gary.  Over here.  You can bring it here.
Gary!  Over here!
[Gary passes with his heel]
That's good!
[What the heck!]
[Unexpected incident!  Game paused!]
What are you doing?!
-Are you okay?
-IU, are you okay?
[Eliminator]
[With a red card, he can get rid of one of
his own members that gets in the way]
Hey!  I heard the sound of a drum
when it hit IU's stomach!
-Are you okay?  Why are you doing that?
-I'm fine.
I'm so sorry.
I was just trying to do it well.
[Running Man team gets back on the attack]
How are we doing this?
Good job, Ji Hyo!  That's right!
[Ji Hyo can use her hands for 10 seconds]
No!
[Kwang Soo is trying to block her]
Get away!
[Since 10 seconds are over,
she passes to Ha Ha]
[Makes a clean pass to Jong Kook]
Over here, Jong Kook!
[By another ball that Gary kicks]
[The ball ultimately goes to Jong Kook]
[Jong Kook fools Ji Sung...
Shoot!]
[Ji Sung's team-10; Running Man's team-9]
[Ah... So I wasn't hit
in the stomach for nothing...]
I... Like you, oppa!
[IU's power to call in her fans for backup]
Let's go!  Let's go!
-Let's go!  Let's go!
-There it goes again!
[With the protection of her fan uncles,
she approaches without hesitation]
[Captain Park sprawls out in hopes
of interfering]
[I don't think this is going to work]
-IU... That's the best!
-That's awesome!
[The psychic power that leaves even
her own teammates speechless]
Ji Sung just sprawled out on the ground
hoping to block her.
[Ji Sung's team-11; Running Man's team-10]
We have to score now.
Ji Sung has made up his mind
that he's going to score now.
[Ji Sung's glint in the eye has changed
with the scores coming close to a tie]
[Just how is Ji Sung going to go
about the game now?]
[Suk Jin, moving the goal with his power]
[How could that be?
How could he have scored?]
[Even with the goal moving,
he shoots it in accurately]
-Even when I screamed out Woosa...
-That's amazing... Amazing.
-Amazing!
-Seriously... That is unbelievable.
[From that distance,
even with the goal moving...]
[Ji Sung's team-12; Running Man's team-10]
Hey!  I'll be by the goal, okay?
[Running Man team on the chase!]
Give it to Ji Hyo.  To Ji Hyo!
[Have to make good use of Ji Hyo,
and her ability to use her hands]
Here, Ji Hyo!  Grab it!
[Huh?  Kwang Soo grabs Ji Hyo's back?]
That!  That's a foul!
[Kwang Soo sent to the penalty box.
Running Man team gets a penalty kick]
[Ji Hyo's kicking the penalty kick?!]
Ji Sung, fighting!
[Ji Hyo's power!
Penalty kick with her hands!]
[He blocks it!]
[Amazing.
After the block, he attacks immediately.]
This seriously makes no sense!
Jwasa!  Jwasa!
[Suk Jin moves the goal so Ji Sung can't score.
[Shoots from a really long distance!]
[This time again!
A goal that's hard to be believed!]
You should've pushed it more!
My powers are useless.
He scores anyways!
That seriously makes no sense!
[Game over]
[Ji Sung's team-13; Running Man's team-10]
[Even though it's only a 2 person team,
Ji Sung's team wins with their efforts]
Since Park Ji Sung's team has won...
Without even having to see...
It's not Park Ji Sung's team that won,
but it's Park Ji Sung that won.
-We're a team.  Aren't we as one?
-No.  He won on his own.
-Park!
-...Soo! (Meaning applause)
Since you're the MVP...
You can decide the teams.
Please choose the teams for us.
First... I'll pick Jae Suk.
[He picks Jae Suk right off the bat]
That's not right!
-Why is he like that?
-I have one more person to pick...
I didn't mean that... Sorry.
Ji Sung.  You and I are a family...
Since Kwang Soo was my teammate...
That's why I'm going to leave Kwang Soo out.
[I'm going to leave Kwang Soo out]
[Since you were on the same team once...]
-You have to pick one more.
-I'll pick Mr. Capable.
Really?!  Me?!
-Really?
-Us three?
[Ji Sung's team:
Mr. Capable, Ji Sung, and Jae Suk]
-You're serious?  Us three?
-Like this?
-Seriously?  Us 3 like this?
-Then it must mean the rest of us are together.
[Just what is the fate that awaits
Ji Sung's new team?]
[The next morning]
[Now getting ready for the race
with the newly formed teams]
Then I'm further away from him.
[Fighting for their spot even before it begins]
We need to put him in the middle!
Why are you trying to get in the middle?
-We should put Ji Sung in the center.
-Between us should be the center!
-You're driving me crazy.
-Why are we wearing green today?
Why are you dressing Jong Kook in green?
Get away from him.  Seriously...!
Why do you twist my words around?
We're all wearing green...
Let's all talk together!
[Suk Jin's explosive anger]
Seriously... Just amongst you 3?
Aren't you being too much?
Who cares about wearing green?
Let Ji Sung talk too!
It's because other people are talking too much!
You're the one who talked the most!
Are we starting right away?
[Today's mission is?]
The race that you'll be doing now...
Is the prize money race.
[Each mission has money attached to it]
There's money riding on each mission...
The sooner you pass,
the larger the prize will be.
Since the more prizes you earn,
the more it'll become later...
So you have to succeed your mission
so that you can win lots of prize money.
Soon, you'll be boarding a plane
headed to Thailand.
This is the currency
that you'll be using in Thailand.
Really?!
[Prize money race, start!]
Ji Sung, see you later!
[Fascinated by the cameras that are
attached to the car's interior]
-Jae Suk.
-Where is it?
[Find the Running Man landmark
at the fish market in Incheon]
Turn the air conditioning on for him.
The breeze outside is still cool!
Just look at the temperature in the car!
I'm doing it for his health.
So he doesn't get a cold...
You're doing it for your health!
Park Ji Sung and I are hot!
I turn it on when I'm in a car...
But because of the matches,
I don't turn it on in the hotels.
Jae Suk.  He and I have that in common.
Since I've been thinking about it last night,
he and I have a lot in common.
What? What do you have in common with him?
-Not feeling ticklish.
-You're not ticklish?
-No... But I'm ticklish on my feet.
-That's so weird.
Oh!  That's the same as me!
I'm ticklish on my feet too!
Most people are ticklish on their feet!
[Arguing in front of Captain Park]
We do have a lot in common...
The moment that I saw you...
Hey!  You stop talking!
Let me hear Park Ji Sung's voice!
Seriously... You're such a chatter box!
I didn't call you yesterday on purpose.
[Jae Suk didn't call Ji Sung
in case that he was exhausted]
I purposely didn't call you
because I thought you may be tired.
That's why I had the phone turned off.
[Great ad-lib that even took the
nation's MC by surprise]
I'm not just saying this because
Park Ji Sung's here,
but it's not easy what you're doing.
[Captain Park, who has been playing pro soccer
overseas for more than 10 years]
-There's the difference in language too.
That's what I'm saying.
It really isn't easy work.
Your English probably wasn't very good
in the beginning either, right?
That's right.
I couldn't speak English very well.
It must've been hard for you to communicate.
Especially during the games...?
Well when it comes to matches...
All the terms are pretty similar.
Since the terms are pretty much the same,
there's not a huge problem.
But when there were meetings before matches,
I didn't have any translators.
-How did you do it then?
-You really didn't have any?
Well you know... I did what I could
to get my point across with my gestures.
-They understood what they could.
-I'm sure that wasn't easy...
What about when the coach was explaining
his plans and everything...?
When the coach was explaining something
to the whole team...
Um... I just sat there
with a blank expression on my face.
With just a blank expression...
[Pretending to understand]
The coach and the staff must think that
he at least understood a little bit of it.
I understand it now...
but in the beginning... I was a blank.
Just pretending like I understood everything...
My coach asks me once in awhile
if I understood what he said.
-Then what do you say?
-That yes, I understood.
There are so many things
that I'm curious about...
-You can ask me anything.
-Seriously?  I can?
Um...
What's Rooney, the soccer player like?
He's lying about his age, isn't he?
There are people who make fun of that too.
-That they need to see his birth certificate.
-Seriously?
Yes.  That he's lying about it.
[Even people in his mainland suspects his age]
With how we lost the championship recently...
Did you see the picture where you were
seen behind your coach?
[The bewildered expression from
the dramatic loss of the game]
Then it wasn't taken by an accident,
but you really...
Yes, in reality...
I didn't know someone took a picture of that.
I had no idea that someone was
taking a picture...
-There's Running Man.  Out front there.
-Where?  Where?!
We came here too quickly today!
I was having too much fun talking...!
This is the beginning, Park Ji Sung!
[Towards the new game with Park Ji Sung]
How did we arrive here so quickly?
-Today is really...
-Hello.
[One of the three largest
fish markets in the country]
[Over 500 vendors and 2000 customers
who come in for the freshest seafood!]
-Hello, sir.
-Hello!
Because we came together with Park Ji Sung...
No one is able to get a full grasp
on what's going on because of that.
-Where is it?
-Hello, sir!
Hello!
-Park Ji Sung, yes.
-Do we just go up?
-We were talking to Park Ji Sung...
-Why are we doing this at such a nearby place?
We arrived here way too quickly!
-I purposely drove slower...
-We should've gone a few more blocks.
-Where?
-Where do we need to sit?
In the middle?
Before we start the first race...
No one's eaten yet, right?
-I did eat.
-I ate too before I came.
I told you we have a lot in common.
Park Ji Sung says he always makes sure
to eat his breakfast.
He says he always eats.
Anyways, we're going to eat first.
The reason being that the staff members
hasn't eaten yet...
So we'll all be eating together,
and pick off of the menu.
I'd like to have Kim Jong Kook, please.
I'm going to have Kim Jong Kook for breakfast.
-Would you like to have Kim Jong Kook?
-That sounds good.
Doesn't that sound good?
You want us to pick something?
For now, you can pick whatever you'd like
off of that menu first.
Since Park Ji Sung is here,
we'll order something nice...
Eat something nice.
What should we have?
The price on this is hidden.
Snow King crab.
Why are you eating king crab?
Who eats king crab in the morning?
We have to be hospitable!
Park Ji Sung's here!
If we're going to be ripping names off,
that's a little heavy.
-Then let's eat something lighter.
-Yes.
For athletes, sushi is very good for them.
-I'll have grilled mackerel.
-Grilled mackerel!
[Park Ji Sung's selection is grilled mackerel]
Park Ji Sung and I would like
the grilled mackerel.
And he'll take the rockfish.
-No!
-The domestic rockfish. $55.00
Have you ever seen food games being played?
Yes.  Memorizing the order and stuff...
[Respected as a viewer]
Here they come.
Here comes the other team.
Hey soccer player.
Was it loud on your way here?
-Did they get too loud?
-I couldn't even think straight.
It's because I feel bad for him.
[Worried about Ji Sung between the 2 gabbers]
-You even have the right to say that?
-Yeah, I do.
[IU team arrives]
Everyone orders something.
-IU, eat something delicious.
-Yes, eat whatever you want.
-IU likes mackerel sushi.
-Oh, really?
-Do you see the menu in front of you?
-Yes.
Since the staff hasn't eaten yet,
we're going to eat first before we begin.
-Yeah!
-Really?
-They haven't had breakfast...
-Awesome!  This all sounds so good!
We're going to have crab stew,
spicy octopus stir fry, and grilled fish.
And... Soju.
[But for some reason,
this breakfast is a little suspicious...]
Crab stew and stewed belt fish.
[Anyways, putting in the order
for what they want to eat...]
[The camera crews
are putting in their order too]
May 16th was IU's birthday.
IU, happy birthday!!
I'd like to have this be IU's birthday party.
Let's all pool our money together and
get a gift for IU.
-No, that's okay.
-What are you refusing for?!
We really need to do something for her.
You've suffered too much
from being on Running Man.
IU is trying to get her license and needs a car.
IU... What do you need for your birthday?
She's going to get her license...
Just eat comfortably.
Since it's our IU's birthday,
we can put our efforts together...
Car!  Car!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Yes!  Everyone fork out $10,000!
[Somehow it feels like he's really
going to get her a car for her birthday...]
I was going to just hold it, but...
Let's just buy her a car!
Everyone give $10,000 each!
[Starting a delicious breakfast...]
If by any chance we buy it for her,
Park Ji Sung, can you also...?
She's our little sister
in this industry.
Thank you, ma'am.
[Rockfish sushi that Jong Kook ordered...]
This is rockfish, right?
Thank you.
Are there people that order rockfish sushi
like this early in the morning?
-Yes, a lot of people do.
-Really?
[Her response takes the thunder out of plans]
I never even thought of that!
There really are a lot of people?
-Ma'am!  There really are a lot of people?
-Yes.  A lot of people come for that.
Everyone enjoy their meal!
Thank you for the meal!
[Breakfast together with Park Ji Sung, who's
returned to the country after a long absence]
Over here is father,
mother who has nothing to say...
Mother who doesn't have anything to say...
and the son who came home late last night.
What did you do last night, Kwang Soo?
He stayed up all night playing games...
And the mother forced him awake.
The mother doesn't like
her son or her husband...
[Mother Ji Hyo doesn't like either
her son or her husband]
Mother can't seem to believe that
this is her reality...
And the father is disillusioned
in thinking that this is a happy family.
This is... a very happy family.
[Park Ji Sung is enjoying Korea and
the food for the first time in a long while]
Oh my goodness!
[Kind IU who brings over some of their stew]
IU...
-Seriously... For your birthday gift...
-I'll enjoy driving it.
[Joking aside, it seems like
he really has to buy a car]
You've really changed.
IU, you've really changed.
She really told me...
'I'll enjoy driving it...'
Ji Sung... Why don't you have some more stew?
[Jae Suk goes off to get more stew
for Ji Sung]
Gary, you won't be on the camera for a moment.
-Jae Suk.  IU is worried.
-Why?
Whether she should get a black car,
or a white car.
I'd like a black one.
If Jae Suk buys you a car,
I'll get it tinted for you.
[IU's birthday gift incident
affects everyone like this]
I'll get it tinted for you...!
What are you going to get her, Ji Sung?
[Feeling pressured]
-You should say something.
-I'll... Get the seat covers.
-Seat covers aren't very popular...
-People don't use that much these days.
Jae Suk.  This is IU's mother.
[A phone call from IU's mother?]
She wants to thank you.
Hello?
Yes, mother!
Yes, you heard?
Yes.  Well, today is April Fool's Day.
Since I didn't get to see her on April Fools,
I did it today instead.
Yes, mother, yes...!
Goodbye.
-Park Ji Sung...
-She hung up?
Mother, you haven't hung up yet, right?
You're still there!
Hello, mother.
[Good at handling the situation]
Today is not April Fool's Day.
Today is not April Fool's Day...
He says he's going to buy her the car again.
I think she'll get the car by next month.
Please wait for it.
[Already used to the game plan]
Yes, I'll come to see you.
Is it really your mother?
[How... Gary-esque]
Because you were all on the phone...!
-Is everyone done eating?
-Yes, it was delicious!
I know there's no way that we
can just eat for free like this...
[A mission?]
[What's the mission?]
That's why they're telling us to eat
expensive stuff!
[First Mission -
Fish market part-time job]
[Sell enough fish to cover the expense of
the food that your teammates ate]
You just said that the rockfish was good?!
It was pretty good.
The plate is empty!
How much money have you spent
first thing in the morning?
I was feeling flustered when he
offered us breakfast!
There are 3 stores that we've
made arrangements with.
You just need to go to your designated store
and start your part-time jobs.
I'll announce your amounts.
IU's team...
Actors $78.00 + Staff $40.00.
A total of $118.00
Ji Hyo's team.
-Actors $98.00
-Why is it so much?
-It's this over here!
-This wasn't given for free?
We didn't order this!
Staff $49.00
-A total of $147.00
-Wow... Look at that.
This team ate the most expensive stuff.
-They're going to get more.
-I don't think it'll be that high.
-Team Park Ji Sung.  Actor $98.00
-That's not that bad.
-Staff $96.00
-What?!
[Park Ji Sung's camera crew
who has good appetites]
All the other crew members ate stews,
and they ate along that stuff!
Why did you eat sushi?!
Hey!
-Look at all the food!
-Who eats sushi this early in the morning?
The mackerel sushi, jellyfish salad,
and spicy seafood stew...
It's okay.  Just eat it.
We can eat all of that.
A total of $186.00
Isn't this fun?
Our dongsaeng (younger brothers)
ate more than us!
I just saw Gwan Hyul eating his rice
in a huge bowl like this.
[Good filming starts with good breakfast]
[Park Ji Sung Team-$186.00
IU Team-$118.00; Ji Hyo's Team-$147.00]
[Off to their part-time jobs]
[Let's quickly make money!]
-How could it have been that much?
-$186.00
It's Park Ji Sung, Jong Kook and I.
I've been a fan of yours since
you were in 'Turbo'.
Oh my... Thank you!
Yes, I understand!
[Already a fan of Jong Kook's]
[Even putting their boots on for them]
Thank you so much!
-My feet are just gliding in!
-It fits nicely!
We'll just put ours on ourselves then.
Thank you.
I'm sure you have a lot of people that
takes care of you, Jae Suk.
-I need to take care of Park Ji Sung.
-You're right.  You can do that.
-You have enough people.
-Yes, take care of Ji Sung.
-Kim Jong Kook!
-Hello!
If you're going to work,
you need to put gloves on.
This just came in this morning,
and it's extremely fresh!
-How much is this?
-You have to sell it for $30 each.
Okay!  That sounds good.
This octopus...
The octopus...
You can sell 5 for $10.00
-5 for $10!
-5 for $10...!
How do we sell this?
[Instead of a soccer uniform today...
Captain Park is at the market in an apron...]
Since I'm a worker... I'll do everything.
-We'll give it to you cheap!  Cheap!
-Excuse me!
Hold this and talk to some people.
[Appearance of their first customer!]
-Customer!  What would you like?
-Give me some octopus, please.
-Octopus!
-It's normally 3 for $10.00...
-But we'll give you 5 for $10.00
-5 of them.
Then give me $20.00 worth.
-Ji Sung...
[Captain Park grabs 10 octopus]
10 please, Ji Sung.
-Give me bigger ones, please.
-Sure.  There's 2, 3...
-She wants bigger ones.
-Larger ones?  Okay.  Here's 4.
[It's not easy with the octopus
getting stuck on everything]
-Is this 5?
-No.  This is now 4.
-Is that one in now?
-Yes.  Now that makes it 5.
-Why are you putting in the littlest one?
-No!  I put a big one in there.  I swear!
Come on.  I'm spending $20.00 here.
You have to do a good job!
Part-time job is still a job!
[Ji Sung gets scolded from the shopkeeper]
[Seems he may have succeeded with the rest]
-It's all in there now.
-Kim Jong Kook, tie up the bag now.
-Tie it.
-Do I just need to tie it like this?
-That's good.  Take her $20.00
-$20.00 please.
-Yes, thank you so much.
-Have a great time.
-Thank you.
I think you scold him more than
Ferguson probably does!
-No kidding!
-He needs to be scolded!
Isn't she tougher than Ferguson?
I think I can do it now.
I think I can manage it.
You have to tie it tightly,
otherwise it'll leak!  Get the money too!
-We have to get this to the customer first!
-That's right.
-Suk Jin, flounder.  Flounder, flounder.
-You'd like flounder?
Flounder is nice,
and the mackerel is nice too.
-Oysters are good, and sea squirts are nice.
-They're all very nice.
-Octopus is really nice too.
-You also get a picture with Song Ji Hyo!
-He already took it.
-He did?
Are you on our team or what?
[Not adjusting to the job very well...]
-5 octopus for $10.00
-That's cheap!
Please buy something!
Really?
-IU!  IU!
[Customer who came to see IU]
-IU!
-Song Ji Hyo!  Song Ji Hyo!
Come on now,
you know there's no contest.
It's hands down IU, right?
Tell him that you like him.
I... like you, oppa...
[Entranced]
-Just give me whatever.
-Whatever?  Then... The flounder is very nice.
-This one?
-Come out here and just buy $10.00. Come!
We've got another one here!
[Another customer who's been watching IU]
-Tell him that you like him too.
[Smitten by IU's sweetness]
-Flounder!  IU!  Another uncle is here!
-Hello, uncle.
Can we take a picture with my wife too?
-Sure, come here.
-Wow... IU's pull is no joke.
-1 flounder!
-He's taking 1 flounder.
Pick a nice one.
-Octopus!  We've got an order for octopus!
-It's 5 for $10.00
[All thanks to IU, no time for rest]
2 kg worth?
-Okay.
-2 kg worth.
[IU's team has no worries]
[Guaranteed fan service]
-I think we've hit our goal here.
-Really?
[Already...?]
I think this is it!
-$118.00!!!
-We've sold it all!
-$118.00!!
-Thank you!
-They won.
-Already?!
IU... Seriously.
That was nothing with her!
[IU's team wins first place,
thus gets the largest prize]
-Do we have to pick?  No?  Really?
-Oh, really?
No.  You can take the bag that has
$10,000 baht (Thailand Currency)
-That sounds good!
-Thank you.
-Give it to me.
-You can take this, Ha Ha.
[Find the Running Man landmark
at Songdoe University campus]
There it is.  It's all done!
-This is right.
-Tie it tightly.
I'm getting some of the water out!
You have to make sure it doesn't leak!
-He's such a great worker!
You have to tie it like this.
[The owner is Jong Kook's fan unconditionally]
-I swear you're spilling!
-He didn't spill.  He didn't.
This is a total Turbo shop.
A Turbo shop!
There.  Here it is.  Open up the bag!
This is a total Turbo shop.
-Enjoy it.
-Thank you, mother.
-Mother...!
-Jong Kook.  Switch spots.
Park Ji Sung is way too quiet.
That won't do!
-Stand here and try selling.
-From here?
I know why you wanted to switch spots!
So you could be closer to Turbo!
-Oh my...
-Thank you so much!
Thank you!
[Generously bringing over carrot juice]
-This is really good!
-This looks good.
-How much for the crab?
-Come buy something here!
She's here to buy crabs.
Hurry up and tell her.
Crabs are $30.00 each.
$30.00 per 1 kg.
[Hurriedly takes his juice away]
You took Ji Sung's juice away
even though he's not even done with it.
He's done. See?  He drank it all.
-Come on!  Look at you!
-Drink it slowly.  Take your time.
-You can drink it slowly.
-This is a total Turbo shop.
[Both the National MC and the National Hero
gets nothing from her in front of Jong Kook]
-Give me one please.
-What are you doing, Jae Suk?  Black bag!
-You can't even do that right!
-The constant trauma.
You can't even do that right!
-Come on, do it right!
-Oh, yes.  Yes.
-Thank you so much.
-Thank you!
This is a total Turbo shop.
-I'll put it to good use. Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
Thank you.  We'll be leaving now.
[Park Ji Sung's team, mission complete]
The money for you to use is in there.
[2nd place prize]
You know... Park Ji Sung got
scolded a lot today.
He got scolded more than he
would've from Ferguson.
She was such a fan of Jong Kook...
She was so forward about it!
She was playing major favoritism!
-My fans are very much like this.
-She was so forward about it!  And brazen.
[Find the Running Man landmark
at Songdoe University campus]
Oppa.... I like you soooo much...!
I do...
[Attempting IU's 3rd octave?]
He's going to go up to 27th octave.
[An octave that knows no end]
[This is... Ha Ha's 12th octave]
Are you jealous, IU?
When you go up that high...
You don't get vocal nodules?
No, I do get it.
Even though this may be hard early in
the morning, isn't it still fun?
Yes, it is fun.
[Even though tiring, Captain Park has fun]
Actually, Ji Sung needs to get fooled
or something for it to be really fun.
-That's when it gets exciting.
-I need to get some water guns.
-Once you get a water gun in hand...
-That's right.
-That's when it gets really exciting.
-He needs a water gun...
He needs a water gun and fool someone,
and play a psychological game to be fun.
That's when he'll think,
'Wow... This is fun'...
When Ferguson sees you next time,
he's going to think we corrupted you...
You know there are teams that hang
a towel on them and rip it off each other.
That's the fun stuff to do.
Since he did ours, then maybe we...
Since he did this on Running Man,
when he returns to his home,
he can maybe do something like that
with his friends.
I think that would be fun.
I bet it'll be really fun if we ripped
off the name tag with Abram and Rooney.
I think Rooney would get really mad
if we were to fool him.
-Since he gets mad easily...
-Come to find out, Ferguson was the spy.
-That water gun was nice.
-Yes, that water gun... That's a lot of fun.
It really is...
I was shocked when you
escaped twice from the jail too.
That time... I was also...
Why did you have to escape again?
I didn't know it was just me doing that,
I thought everyone else was like that too.
-We're here!
-This is the place!
-We're first. Let's keep that up, okay?
-Yes.
Let's go!!
Oh!  You were the umpire yesterday!
[Find 3 people that are wearing the same
colored coat as your team color]
-Okay!
-That's easy.
After finding 3 students in the same color,
go to the Running Man's landmark.
-We can get started right now.
-I understand.
-We find the students first?
-Yes.
[Similar color is seen everywhere...]
There!  No... It's a coat, right?
-Look at the skirt!
-No, it has to be a coat.
-It has to be a coat?
-Yeah, a coat.
-There are so many similar colors...
-I know...
[Find 3 people that are wearing the same
colored coat as your team color]
-3 people?
-There's someone in a green shirt.
Out of the people that are in here?
-Really?
-Will you help us out a little?
-But I can't!
-Why?
-You're fine.
-I just had surgery not too long ago...
What's our mission?
[Find 3 people that are wearing the same
colored coat as your team color]
Isn't it the easiest since
we're wearing white?
Once you find the 3 people,
find the Running Man landmark inside.
-White!  There's white!
-White!
Wear this.  Here... Wear this.
You have to come with us.
[Disguising it into a blue coat]
That's fine.
Tell them you normally go around like this.
There are tons of green here!
[Park Ji Sung's team now has
2 members completed]
There's green!
Green.  He's wearing green.
[Another person wearing green]
We're all set!
[Reacting like a girl when he sees Jae Suk]
We've found all of them.  That way?
[Completed team to go to the landmark]
-Do you have the time?  Let's go.
-Yes.
[While Kwang Soo's been gone,
Ji Hyo's team completes the mission]
-Let's go.  Let's go.
-There it is!  Let's go!
Here.  Give me your bag.
IU's here.  Awesome.
IU's here!
-Where did Gary go?
-Where did he go?
Gary!  What are you doing there?
No one is paying any attention to me!
-You don't think it's too blue?
-Come out here.
[Found the last member in blue]
-Isn't there a female student?
-Let's go!
I'll give it to the team that got here first.
Yes.  We were the first to arrive.
[Second mission]
[With the members that you found,
play a game of tug of war]
The team that were the first to arrive,
gets one free win.
[Extremely confident in Tug of War]
It's a Tug of War?
It'll be Park Ji Sung's team vs.
IU's team first.
And the winner plays the other team.
-We're playing 3 rounds, right?
-So we get 2nd no matter what?
Our goal is to get 2nd place.
Pil-Chok-Song-Cross!
So embarrassing!
Here they finally are.
-We're all set now.
-They're here.
You're going to feel different once
you see the mission.
[With the members that you found,
play a game of tug of war]
The team that gets 1 free win is already here.
-So you'll be going up against us.
-No way!!
[You're going to go up against Captain Park
and the Tiger...?]
You know that makes no sense!
IU, fighting!
IU, fighting!!
[All the male students rooting for IU]
-Everyone ready?
-Yes!!
2 out of 3.
-Here we go!
-What do we do?  Fighting!
Just look at his arms!
Don't use any force!
Do it with just one arm!
He has to use just one arm!
Look at his arm compared to mine!
One arm, one arm, one arm...
[Ultimately, as the crowd demands,
using just one arm]
[Just to make sure,
I'll hold one of his hand!]
Ready!
[Unilaterally superior, Park Ji Sung's team]
[Park Ji Sung's team wins]
[Too simple of a win?]
In this round, you can trade off
one person to be substituted.
As long as they're in the same color,
you can substitute someone.
-It doesn't matter the color of clothes?
-No, it has to be the same color.
Ah, it has to be the same color?
This is far too advantageous for us, isn't it?
[Did he find an exchange player?]
-He needs something blue...
-He got it!  He got it.
Okay, fine.  That's fine.
I think you'd be best up front.
[If Park Ji Sung's team wins this,
then this round is over]
I'm a little nervous about this one.
Set...
[The rope has gotten tighter
than the last game]
[Huh?  Jong Kook's arm?]
[This is it!]
[IU team wins!]
He bent my arm!
That's awesome!
[Park Ji Sung Team-1 vs. IU Team-1]
Fighting!!
Kim Jong Kook, one arm!  One arm!  One arm...!
[As danger approaches, he blocks with IU]
Kim Jong Kook, one arm!
[Tiger's throne is being challenged]
[The last round!]
Everyone grab the rope!
-Ready... Set...
-Park Ji Sung, fighting!
[The winner is unknown...]
[With every ounce of strength...]
[As if this was a championship league...]
[Just... Who will the winner be?]
[IU's team is getting pulled!]
[Park Ji Sung's team wins!]
[Close call to the end...]
-You worked out.
-That was a close call!
That was seriously very close!
[In the moment that they lost balance,
the game is over]
-IU...
-It almost went the other way.
The other team totally could've won!
-Is Kim Jong Kook using one arm?
-He has to!
This is just the first round!  Why me?
[Another request for Jong Kook's one arm?]
One arm, one arm, one arm...!
-Kim Jong Kook, one arm!
-Fine, I'll just use one.
Pull the rope back to match the line.
Hey. We can't be getting pulled already!
[But this team has 2 girls...]
[The tiger uses only one arm]
[An overwhelming superiority of
Park Ji Sung's team]
[Giraffe's riot]
[Park Ji Sung's team wins!]
Lee Kwang Soo!  Lee Kwang Soo!
[The giraffe being applauded for rioting?!
1 to 0!
[Ji Hyo's team to get a new team member!]
-We can get someone else, right?
-Then we'll use the chance now!
[Huh?  A gathering of ROTC students!]
Which one of you is the strongest?
Just one!
You can take a little rest.
[Trading in 1 female for a bulky ROTC student]
Just look at them!
[Even the oxygen tank Park Si Jung
looks overwhelmed]
I'm getting nervous.
[Ji Hyo's team that's been
tremendously upgraded]
He looks really strong... Tall too.
-He looks really strong.
-Tall people are usually strong.
Except for Kwang Soo.
Even though I'm tired after the last few,
I'm learning some tricks.
I can feel it whenever we're being pulled.
Park Ji Sung, fighting!
[The final round]
[Huh?  Park Ji Sung's team being pulled?]
[Song Ji Hyo's team wins!]
It's okay.  We were just out of sync.
-Let's win this.  Let's win!
-This is no joke!
[Now the final round]
We're just going to go with
the members we have to the end.
That's cool.
She's struggling so much at the end
with her high heels.
[The female student struggling
in her high heels]
-We're all having a hard time right now.
-Your face is full of sweat right now!
Let's all cheer on Park Ji Sung!
When Park Ji Sung started huffing with them
pulling so hard, I was flustered!
[An unbelievable scene seeing
Park Ji Sung being winded]
-Park Ji Sung, fighting!
-Fighting!
[Fighting!  Park Ji Sung!]
Everyone!  Now is the final round!
Let's all give a round of applause
for the both teams!!
[The round that determines the winner!]
Pil-Chok-Cross!
We can do this..!
Start pulling right away.
Heave, heave.  Heave...!
-It's going too far to that side!
-It's not on our side.
[Who will the winning go to?]
[Captain Park pulling with gritted teeth]
[Power of Ji Hyo's upgraded team]
[Park Ji Sung's team in danger!]
[Is this how Ji Hyo's team will win?]
[The awakening of Jae Suk-Mr. Capable...
And Captain Park!]
[How will this game end?]
Park Ji Sung, Park Ji Sung...
[The students' last cheer!]
[And the game that still won't end!]
[Slowly pulling the rope back!]
[But then... A reversal?]
[Park Ji Sung's team... Wins!]
[A historical show
right in front of their eyes!]
[Ji Hyo's team that did their best to the end]
Did you exert yourself too much?
Our Captain Park is exhausted!
[More exhausting than a soccer game]
How was the tug of war?
I'm reminded of the most difficult time
during my soccer career!
Because it was the most difficult...
[Park Ji Sung's team takes the
first prize winnings]
I'm sure now it's time to put this case down,
and start the race... Right?
It doesn't matter what place we have
at this point...
That's right.
Ultimately, it's all about the end.
-It's like a bag of sand right now.
-That's right.
I want to be cautious when I ask this...
But... You're not...
A spy or something, right?
You're not a spy, right?
[All of a sudden, suspecting him as a spy?]
Well... It's just that...
There's money riding on it and everything...
It's not like that, right?
Do you think that I can be a spy?
[I'm sure he's not...
But they've been too lax about their guard]
-Because we're always fooling each other...
-Yes, there's a lot of that.
I didn't say that to cause any harm.
I just said it to make sure.
[If... Park Ji Sung... Is a spy?]
If I'm the spy, I'm sure I'll be caught quick.
[Will he really be caught right away
like he says?]
Since you have such a poker face,
it may be advantageous to be a spy.
Getting scolded by the shop keeper...
And even when you got
scolded by all the ladies...
But you still... Didn't seem fazed.
I really couldn't believe that!
[Could he... Really be a spy?]
[Before the races began early this morning...]
-Hello.
[He is already at a location]
Do you know why you're here?
Yes... I get the feeling there's something
that I have to do.
I'm sure you know since you've watched
our show, but there's a reason why...
That's why we've called you here.
-Can I look at it now?
-Yes, go ahead and read it.
[On the mission card...]
Spy mission.
You're a spy.
Oust the members of Running Man!
However, you can scout one member as partner.
There are rules that we have for you
as our spy today.
This is... Scout.
You're familiar with scouting, right?
-Yes... In soccer, players get scouted.
-That's right.
You can pick one other spy.
-Me?  Anyone?
-Yes.
-However I want?
-No, not like that.
If you're by any chance allowed to pick
whomever you want...?
That would of course be Mr. Capable.
[This is?]
This is a spy scout menu.
There will be 2 races today.
You have to take the prize winnings
before the races are over.
-Both missions?
-Both missions.  And...
And you scored 7 goals when you
played the psychic soccer.
By myself?  Ah, I see.
You will be given 500 Baht for
each of those goals.
If that was the case,
I would've made all the goals myself.
I guess that's all I can do about that.
You will start off with 3500 baht.
Just for now.
Who else would you pick
other than Kim Jong Kook?
I don't know...
I feel like Gary's going to
get caught quickly.
If... I had the money...
I would take Song Ji Hyo.
But that would be hard since the big timers
usually don't get transferred easily.
If they don't want it themselves,
it usually doesn't work.
Ah... I don't know who it may be,
I will work hard with my fellow spy...
Since we didn't win any this season...
On Running Man, I'll make sure...
To show the winning side of me.
Fighting!
Kim Jong Kook and Park Ji Sung
need to go up against one another.
Where did Park Ji Sung go?
[The hottest face-off
in Running Man's history]
Come on!
[Strength vs. speed!]
[Stamina vs. Stamina]
[A face-off that's on a different dimension]
[And Jae Suk's secret mission...?]
You're not playing a joke, right?
[Park Ji Sung to carry out
Yoo Jae Suk's mission!]
Who's that?
[Jung Dae Sae]
[Rio Ferdinand]
[The surprising mission with world stars!]
[2012 Asiana Dream Cup in Thailand!]
[Running Man touching ground on a dream]
[Moment of honor they'll remember forever!]
[Jung Dae Sae and Gae Dae Sae will strike!]
Running Man!  Fighting!
[Subtitles by DramaFever]