Ladies and gentlemen,
you are cordially invited
to Scotland's
most spectacular weddings...
..where guest lists of 500
are ten-a-penny...
Very nervous, very nervous.
..and money is no object.
It doesn't matter about the money.
He doesn't know who'll pay.
Diamond encrusted Rolls-Royce.
In this series,
we have a VIP pass...
Let's do this!
..into a glittering world,
as a new generation say "I do."
Us Scottish Asians
are proud to be Scottish.
# Donald, where's your troosers? #
If someone was to play a good
beat on like a dustbin,
you'd see us just like kind of
shrugging our shoulders
and screwing in a light bulb
somewhere.
Courtesy of Saffron Events...
..who create these
magical occasions.
No, no, no, no.
Don't tell me to let go because
it's going to fall on your face.
You better stop phoning me.
From the anticipation
and excitement...
Mashallah, it's very nice.
..to the frayed nerves of making
everything just perfect.
I don't want to outstage the
bride. Mum thinks you are.
THEY LAUGH
You cannot be on the trampoline
in your wedding clothes.
We'll be there on the most emotional
day of their lives.
I love you.
I love you too.
If you don't turn out to be
a psycho, we'll get married.
It's August, which means it's peak
wedding season at Saffron Events.
Yeah, I can do cash. That's fine.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, save time.
With owner Hassan at the helm,
a top team of 60 employees will be
working their magic
on not just the 20 weddings
they have scheduled
but also 60 more
events and functions.
Saffron plays a big part
in the local community
because when their clients throw
a party, they do it in style,
often, the blingier the better.
Saffron plan all sorts of events,
parties, functions,
not just weddings.
We do graduations,
we do hen parties,
we kind of do baby showers,
anniversary parties.
Saffron does it all.
Where there's an occasion,
Saffron's usually there
and a part of it.
So, with this month bulging
with bookings,
the team are being kept
on their toes.
Where did this even come from?
This is not in the diary.
It's not in the diary?
We can't take it.
Who's going there?
Hassan,
it's not as busy as last week.
We had, Sunday was so busy.
Anyway.
This was the busiest weekend.
Hassan can say what he wants.
Neela, yeah?
You know why he's saying it? Why?
It's because he's added extra
weddings we don't know about.
MARIYIA LAUGHS
One event that's definitely booked
is for 26-year-old Usman.
In just a couple of weeks' time,
he'll marry his fiancee,
Sabreena, who's from Cardiff.
After the wedding, Sabreena will
head north of the border,
moving in with her new husband
and his parents in Motherwell.
The baby of the family, Usman is
the apple of his mother's eye.
Oh, I've not seen this
in a long, long time.
A baby album.
Yes.
Wow. On the bike.
That's my first bike, isn't it?
No, third bike.
Third bike? Third bike.
Oh, loads of bikes.
HE LAUGHS
You look nice. I look nice?
Yes, nice.
Don't I look nice any more?
Very cute.
Only a mum would say that.
HE LAUGHS
The youngest always feels special.
They are the youngest.
Maybe they get a bit more
attention than the older
because they are the youngest.
And all eyes on them.
I'm the youngest in the family,
so maybe I think I'm the favourite.
Well, I'm the oldest
in my family, so...
SHE LAUGHS
I can't tell you what it
feels like to be the baby,
but if I put myself
in my sister's shoes,
because she's the baby of my family,
and there's 14 years
between me and my sister,
she always feels like
I make all the decisions.
She always feels that her opinion
doesn't matter that much.
But, on the upside, she's the most
spoiled member of the family.
That's her wedding, yeah. Pakistan.
Everyone looks so young and skinny.
She's 21 years old.
Shazia and her husband.
Because there is a massive age
gap between me and my sisters,
14 years, so, you waited a long
time for me, isn't it, Mum? Yes.
It's been me,
Mum and Dad for a long time.
Shazia and Nazia got married
when they were kind of youngish,
so they've been
out of the house for a while,
and so I'm looking forward to
another female
being part of the family again,
you know?
Even my mum's mum lived with us
as well for a good ten years.
Ten or 15 years, I think it was.
15 years. Yeah.
I mean, it is a cultural thing
as well, but I think nowadays,
people are kind of straying
away from that a little bit.
But we obviously didn't, you know?
Even once I get married,
when Sabreena moves up,
we will be living here.
It's, that joint family dynamic will
still continue on,
which is nice, you know.
I like it. Yes. I'm happy.
18 years old, we married.
Wow. I could never do that. I think
26 is a young age for me, but...
Mum was 18.
How are you feeling?
I'm happy.
I miss my mum.
Yes, my mum's mum passed away,
two years ago now?
And she would always say, you know,
"He's grown up now,
"when are you going to get
him married?
"When are you going to get him
married?"
And just when me
and Sabreena kind of met,
things were still kind of, you know,
in talks at that point.
But, unfortunately, she passed away.
She never got to kind of see that.
And this picture especially, this
picture was on my first birthday.
Shazia and Nazia
are obviously there,
and we were also watching the video,
isn't it, Mum?
My first birthday video,
we were watching it about a couple
of weeks back, and it was all,
like, my gran and my granda
were there, like, you know.
A big, big party. Yeah.
Very, very big party.
Yeah, it was almost like a wedding,
I guess you could say.
So, obviously,
watching that back again,
there was lots of people that,
you know, are not here any more,
you know?
But now, Mum wants grandkids.
Well, more for me.
HE LAUGHS
So she can do all this
all over again.
But it's just more nerves,
I think, for everyone.
Obviously, Mum, Shazia and Nazia,
they're all excited.
A bit of nervous too, because
it will be a change for everyone,
especially for, you know, me,
Mum and Dad, because obviously,
she'll be in the house.
So, everyone kind of has to adjust
in some sort of way.
Usman and Sabreena's wedding
banquet, the walima,
is being held at a hotel in Glasgow.
As Usman's fiance Sabreena
lives in Wales,
his sisters step in to help out.
Wedding planner Aneela
wants to finalise all the details.
Nice seeing yous again.
My sister, my mum and dad,
obviously. Hi, everybody.
Nice to meet yous. Hi.
So, I think the room's ready.
Do you want to come and have a look
at it? Uh-huh. Let's do it.
So, this is it, space-wise.
And, erm, the stage will go there.
So, your guests
arrive at five o'clock,
and that's... The bride's family
then arrive at six o'clock.
Then your guys' entrance is 6.30,
and then your dinner's seven, 7.30.
Yeah. Obviously, being an Asian,
nothing's going to be on time. Yes.
But that is the rough... The plan,
anyway. Try and stick to that, yeah.
Yeah.
With the 400 guests, we're doing
allocated seating as well, so...
That's the best thing to do,
I think.
I think we were saying by Friday
we'll have it all. Yes.
Like the proper numbers done.
Yeah, that's fine.
A week before the wedding,
usually we send it to the printers.
And I think that is the way
going forward.
I think a seating plan is quite
a recent thing
in the Asian community, and I think
it's a positive thing as well.
With Asian families, what usually
happens, or used to happen,
was, when you invite one person,
or two people,
five would turn up,
so there'd be a problem.
Are you nervous?
Definitely nervous, yeah.
Nervousness, excitedness, stress
as well a little bit, you know?
I'm sure that, on the day,
I'll be fine.
It's nothing to worry about.
I know it's hard for you guys,
because yous are the family,
and it's stressful trying to get
everything done,
but on the day, like,
try your hardest to just relax
and enjoy the day, because it goes
in a blur. You'll just enjoy it.
You'll be the one that will
be enjoying it the most.
We'll be stressed. We'll be
the ones that will be stressed.
He'll just be enjoying it.
Just can't help it.
You do, you get anxious, because you
don't know what's going to happen.
Yeah. You know,
it's one of these things.
Are you the only brother? Yeah.
Right, OK.
He's the baby of our family.
Your sisters'll have it organised,
and we'll have it organised
on our side.
They have done,
they have done, you know, so...
Do you remember
what your centrepieces are?
Just a wee quiz for you.
Although big sisters
Nazia and Shazia
are clearly in the walima
driving seat,
Usman wants to make sure his input
is taken into consideration, too.
I really had to sort of mature,
you know,
cos even though I trust
these two to get on with it,
obviously, they're not
going to know exactly what I want,
so that's why I need to step in
and be like,
"Right, this is what I want."
"I want to maybe do this
instead of that."
Things like that, you know?
So, I've kind of had to grab
the bull by the horns a little bit,
which, again, like I said,
it's unconventional
for a groom to be like that.
But I just want things to go well,
you know?
The walk-through went really well.
Nazia is super organised,
which makes my job a lot easier,
and Saffron's job a lot easier.
And we've worked with her before.
You know, we've done her wedding,
we've done her children's parties,
so it's a familiar face
to work with.
I'm looking forward to being
a part of this wedding, yeah.
Back home in Motherwell,
Usman's sister runs through
the finer details.
Although Usman will wed in Wales,
his pre-ceremony mehndi
and marriage will both be
held in Scotland.
Is this the Marriot table plan?
Yeah, yeah.
Make a start on that just now.
So, how are you feeling? Good.
Yeah, I feel OK about it, you know?
Nervous, still, but overall...
What are you thinking
about the mehndi just now?
Because, remember, you initially
didn't want to have one.
I mean, the idea has
kind of grown on me now.
I kind of get why you and Mum
and Shazia were saying to have one.
It's good that you've
come round to the idea,
but I think you would have
regretted it if you hadn't had one,
just because, you know, it's nice to
get all the events kind of done.
Yeah, I understand.
So, at the moment, we've got
410 guests coming to the wedding.
It's not a difficult task in the
sense that we know it's families
are getting invited,
so it's like kind of maybe
one or two tables per family.
We'd obviously put Sabreena's
family up at the front,
somewhere near their table, so we
kind of know the gist of what to do.
I think it's just time-consuming
for the number of people
that we're having to do it for.
But we're all just so excited.
The whole family's coming together.
We've got like cousins,
extended family,
and they've all seen
Usman grow up,
and they know he's the
little, the little spoilt child.
Yeah. Doted on in our family, so
they're all really looking forward
to his wedding as well,
just to be part of the big day.
And then you've got
the entertainment in as well.
That's a surprise for Sabreena.
Yeah, she doesn't know about this
yet.
They're both a big fan of this
singer, this entertainer. Yeah.
So he's booked.
..a Punjabi singer. Yeah, so, he's
booked this guy for his... Yeah.
..reception, but Sabreena doesn't
know, so that's going to be
a nice surprise for her as well.
And it'll be funny cos, as well,
one of her relatives had him, the
singer, at one of her functions,
so, obviously, when she told me,
she sent me some messages and that,
and I started making fun of it,
I was like, "No, not him, he's old,"
this and that, knowing that
I'd booked him already
and I didn't want to ruin the
surprise for her. Yeah.
Just keep her off the trail!
Yeah, yeah. Just knock off...
I was like, "No, I don't want him.
Who listens to him these days?"
But she has no idea, you know?
Apart from Nazia, my other
sister, no-one else really knows.
What if you'd been left to your own
devices to plan this?
How do you think you'd have got on?
It'd be a much, much
simpler and smaller wedding!
THEY LAUGH
If I had it my way... This is
going to sound embarrassing,
but if I had my way, I'd get married
at a mosque, I'd go to Nando's
and that would be it!
THEY LAUGH
You know? Sabreena's so glad that
we are...got him through this.
Probably, yeah. Probably.
I mean, first of all, a lot of them
don't really have a clue
about weddings or what they want.
When it comes to the decor and the
fine details, it's usually
the women, they are not really
bothered by it and often they say,
"Why do we need that?"
Or, "What's that for?"
I think the most fun bit for them
is the honeymoon,
so they look forward to the
honeymoon!
Throwing the biggest and best
wedding these days
is something of a competitive sport.
Everything from the bride's
outfit to the entertainment
has to have the wow factor.
And when you've gone to this
much trouble, you don't want to
forget those precious memories,
so a top photographer is a must.
Zach Ahmad is renowned for always
going the extra mile.
I'm the most creative person
in Scotland for Asian weddings.
I don't compare myself to any other
photographers, to be honest...
but I know when my work is the best,
you know?
I don't know if I've...
I don't know. Is it right to
say that... You think...?
But while Zach will do just
about anything to get a great photo,
it also means that couples have to
work a little harder too.
We're filming a post-wedding
photo shoot for a Muslim couple,
so it would normally be pre-wedding
photo shoots,
but in the Muslim community,
you're not allowed to do
a photo shoot beforehand.
They said they wanted something
different -
this is why we came to the beach.
OK, now, just walk
straight...for the shot.
Do you normally ask brides
and grooms to wade...?
HE CHUCKLES
..to wade into the sea?
I always try to do something
different, why not push the
boundaries?
Most couples, obviously...
If they know what they're getting,
they're getting a better result,
they don't mind going
the extra mile with me.
Terrifying. If this was
a pre-wedding photo shoot...!
THEY LAUGH
See, most of my clients,
they want me to do what I want,
so obviously,
they see what I do and they love it.
But in order to get the best
photos possible,
Zach really does push his
clients to the limit.
We're not going there!
This is one of my favourite
locations for photo shoots.
Which big stones?
Those big stones? Yeah.
Like, the ones at the far side? Yes.
If they're looking for something
different, then, yeah,
I am a bit demanding, to make sure
they get the perfect shot.
Oh!
THEY LAUGH
Oh, see? You're going to hurt
yourself, then what?
This dress... Come on.
With years of experience,
Zach has seen people's
perception of photography change.
Before people, like, used to have
photographers, they didn't know what
they were getting.
Now, they are very competitive.
They're doing a lot of research,
a lot of cameras,
so they know what they want,
basically.
Especially if the couple come
to me, they know what they want.
Yeah, perfect.
For me, wedding photography's the
most important part of their life
because wedding photos are going
to last them a lifetime.
OK, one, two, three, go.
It's quite nice, I love it,
you know? I love my job. Love it.
When couples book Saffron to help
organise their wedding celebrations,
this is just the start of a long
relationship
with Hassan and his team,
as people return needing help with
other important events
throughout their married lives.
Often, when we meet couples,
it is the start of a, kind of,
friendship-relationship between us
because what happens is, not only
are we planning
their engagement and wedding, later
on, they usually come back to us
for their, kind of, baby showers,
and their children's first birthday
parties and any other
occasion that they want to
celebrate, Saffron usually do it.
In Wishaw, Zahra's called upon
the team to help cater a special
upcoming event,
after they helped her dream wedding
come true a few years ago.
I just thought it'd be nice to
reminisce cos I can't believe
it was two years ago! To be fair,
I can't believe that either!
You probably see things that you
probably didn't even know happened!
Not really, just like looking at
myself.
I thought... Not going to
lie to you!
Syra met Amar at school.
Years later, they fell in love
and had a series of spectacular
wedding events...
I mean, look at that.
..which were made all
the more special
after she was given the all-clear
from cancer treatment.
It just shows how much he loves you,
and he still does.
I found a lump...
..in my...right breast.
It is quite an aggressive type.
I says to Amar I think it's best
that we don't get married and
he leaves me because I didn't know
if I was going to make it or not.
She said to me,
"I don't want you to be my carer,
"I don't want you looking after me,
I don't want you helping me
"go to the toilet and make me
food and stuff,"
and I go, "You're not going to.
You're going to be making my food
"cos we're going to get married,
we're going to make it to the end."
And he was true to his word.
When I was going through my
treatment, it was what kept me going
because Amar would always
keep encouraging me
and motivating me and saying,
"You're going to be fine,
"you're going to be fine,
let's look at honeymoon brochures,
"let's look at wedding dresses."
And that has actually
got me through it and kept me
really positive.
And now, just looking back at
these pictures, it just seems like
the proper fairy tale
and just a dream.
I love that picture.
Amar became father to Syra's son
Faisal from a previous marriage.
This wedding to me
is, like, absolutely everything.
Just like Syra and wee Fais.
That's cute.
Mum, look how handsome my boys look.
Like father and son.
How close are they?
Mashallah, you know... I actually...
Their relationship melts my heart.
Oh, definitely.
Fessy is closer to Amar
than what he is to me.
He goes to Amar for everything
and I'm always left out
or the last to find
out about everything.
Cos they two gang up on me!
When I was going through
my treatment,
I had discussed with my oncologist,
you know, I only have one child
and I would like to have more.
But he did say to me that the
chemotherapy that I was getting
can destroy...my chances of having
any more kids, but Amar and I
had spoken about it and he had said
to me, "Look, I'm happy,
"I've got you and I've got Fessy."
After the wedding,
we went away on our honeymoon
and when we came back,
I just wasn't feeling well
and I thought the worst,
"Oh, is the cancer back?"
And I went to see my GP
and the GP did a routine test
and asked for a urine sample and...
..I was pregnant.
You know, the best news ever.
Now Amar's a proud daddy of
two children, Faisal and Amaya.
Pretty flowers. Pretty flowers, yes.
I really didn't think this would
happen. And the minute, I just...
You know, that was it.
Totally, totally in love with her.
So, today's very exciting,
it's Fathers' Day
and we are planning
a surprise for Amar
since it's his first Father's Day
that he's got two children!
And we've got Fessy keeping him
away and occupied all day,
so he doesn't know what is going on.
To make the celebration even
more special,
Syra and Nazma have called
and Saffron to provide
some of Amar's favourite food for
the Fathers' Day surprise.
I hope we can pull this off and it
is a really nice surprise
for Amar and Dad, especially Amar.
He really deserves it.
And do you know what?
If anybody can pull it off, you can.
As with all cultures,
things move with the times,
so, while many of the old-school
traditions remain,
the younger crew are keen to put
a more up-to-date spin
on their upcoming celebrations.
There's always new things
happening here,
even regards to, like...
..favours...
What's the Asian word for it? You
know, like, when they do the...
..wee pocket things? Bidh.
Bidh. Even the bidhs...
It's like a little bag
and it'll have some Asian
sweeties and then chocolates
and people used to do them
as favours as well, but now,
people are doing things like...
..Krispy Kreme Doughnuts,
like Usman and Sabreena,
they're doing Krispy Kreme Doughnuts
as their favours.
And there's things like macaroons
and there's, like, tablets,
you know, the Scottish tablet
to eat, that,
so there's a Western element that
is coming through quite a lot now.
Usman's big day is drawing
ever nearer,
but there's been a blip in the plans
for the walima.
Not sure if I told you, but
the hotel for Usman and Sabreena,
they e-mailed and they said
they are getting refurbished
and it's going to be cream carpet
and they are not allowed Irn-Bru.
Nasia, who's the sister,
has already ordered the drinks
and it's also printed on the menu,
Irn-Bru.
So... And the printer's
away on holiday tomorrow.
The printer's away on holiday
tomorrow, yeah. So, I'm not sure.
He's got lots to do. When did we
find out? Maybe half an hour ago?
But we did have a walk-through with
them, no-one mentioned anything
about not having Irn-Bru...
..so I don't know what's going to
happen there, I don't know whether
to just leave it on the menu
or get printed again, but they...
We could get them printed, that's
no problem, but it comes down to
the printer. I know when I go to
a wedding, anyway,
when I look at the menu, I don't
ever really look at the drinks,
it's the usual kind of standard
drinks. I always look at what food's
going to be on the menu, so...
It's Irn-Bru!
Like, it's a wedding in Scotland,
like...
Yeah. People expect that,
that's why they don't read it.
Not with cream carpet they don't!
As Usman prepares to become
a married man,
one big adjustment is saying
goodbye to his boy-cave bedroom,
in order to create a perfect
place for his new wife to move into.
It has been changed vastly.
This wall used to be red. I'm very
much into my hip-hop music,
so I had, like, rap artist
posters all up there.
As you can see, it's all gone, so
very, very different. I like it...
It's brighter,
I guess, than it was before!
So, that's a picture of me
and Sabreena at our engagement.
Actually, that was a year ago,
cos on social media,
it came up as being a year since
we've been engaged,
I was like, "A year already?!
God's sake..."
So, that's, like, my favourite
picture from the engagement,
me feeding her cake,
so it's mad that it's been a year
and now we're getting married. Wow.
So, when I, kind of, knew Sabreena
was the one for me
was maybe about seven or eight
months later after we first met,
after we had that first discussion
and then, we took it from there.
I didn't really say anything
cos I was like...
You know, is this how I actually
feel? Or is this, maybe,
something else? I didn't know.
So I kind of kept it hidden
from everyone. I wanted it to be
special, that's why I waited
a few months after I kind of knew,
just to let my feelings settle
a little bit and just so I knew...
I didn't even tell my mum and dad
cos I knew they'd have got
overly excited
and they'd have started making
phone calls and phoned Saffron up
and you know, already, you know?
Obviously the distance doesn't
really help, you know? Like,
she has came up, I've went down as
well, try to spend time and stuff,
but obviously with work and things,
it can get difficult, you know?
We organise weddings for people
from anywhere around the country.
It can be tricky at times but
we make it work because we've got,
you know, phones, we've got WhatsApp
we can communicate through, e-mail.
Obviously FaceTime, phone calls,
that happens almost on a daily basis
but actually physically spending
time with each other,
probably only about 12 or 15 times,
to be honest,
in the last maybe year
and a half or so.
We've certainly done
loads of weddings where we've
organised it remotely
or communicated with families,
you know,
who are in different places or
different countries, so it's...
We make it work.
We spoke about obviously
nervousness,
sort of, first time
we actually met, cos obviously
she has to leave her own family,
come to a brand-new house and
live with people that she's only
known for like a few years,
you know?
Just about, you know, when a girl
has to move in with in-laws,
how different that's going to be.
Back in the day, it'd be quite
common for you to live with
your mother-in-law
and your father-in-law,
and for their mother-in-law and
father-in-law to be under the same
roof as well, so it'd be three
generations in the one household.
Right. So, this is Sabreena's stuff.
Her mum and her brother came round
last week to just drop
some of it off. I was like,
"Is this all of it?"
She's like, "No, there's still
some more." I was like, "OK."
I was allowed to put some of my
stuff in her half, you know?
I got permission for that.
HE LAUGHS
Thankfully for Usman though,
there is
still room in the wardrobe
for his wedding outfits
and they're way more elaborate
than he's used to.
This is what I'm wearing on the
actual mehndi.
Apparently this is not
elaborate for a groom.
And I was like, "What do you mean?"
Apparently it should've been more
sequins, you know, here and
everything, you know?
But I'm quite a simple person,
I'm more of a T-shirts
and jogging bottoms type of person.
The one that I most am, not scared
about wearing.
OK, maybe I'm scared
actually, is this one.
This is what I'm actually wearing on
the actual wedding day
down in Cardiff.
Again, I think it's pretty simple,
which I quite like.
So that'll come with like, sort of,
goldy kind of bottoms to wear
with it and one thing that I am kind
of proud about,
because I love my shoes, like,
trainers and things,
I got matching shoes made for that
as well.
So it's the exact same fabric as the
actual jacket there.
So I was more excited about these
than about anything else
to be honest.
I think that's pretty cool,
you know?
Same kind of design there,
same fabric, it goes well.
The thing I'm kind of scared of,
on the actual wedding day,
there's that tradition where
Sabreena's sisters and cousins,
like, female cousins, will
try and steal my shoes.
Just so they can get money from you
for that.
And it has happened before where
the shoes are broken or they get
lost or something happens to them,
so I'm kind of like, please, no.
In Wishaw, Saira needed help
with an upcoming event
and had called on Saffron to
cater it for her.
Mum Najma and Saira are en route
to collect the all-important
banquet for husband Amar's
Father's Day surprise.
Don't bite my phone.
I just hope that Fessy manages to
keep Amar away and Amar's not asking
too many questions where we are.
He probably will. Do you know
what... Ouch!
Saira, she just bit me.
She's hungry.
It's all right, once we get to
Hassan's office,
we'll give her a kebab.
Hopefully owner Hassan will have
something for Amaya to chomp on.
Hi. How are you? I'm good, how are
you? Good, good, thank you.
You saying hello? Hi!
We've been looking forward to
tasting your food.
It's a surprise for Amar and my
dad. Does he know? No, he doesn't
know. OK. That'll be nice. Yeah.
Fessy's keeping him busy.
Right, OK.
And as always we're
running on Asian time,
so we'd better get a move on.
Good luck. Thank you.
It saves us cooking.
Ah, there's the food ready.
Yep, got it.
That's great, thank you. That's the
desserts. Oh, they look delicious.
With less than half an hour
to spare,
it's all hands on deck to get
the place ready for the surprise.
What we'll do, Saira, is we'll set
the food in here...
And we can make our plates
and bring it through.
Make their plates, take them out.
No, Amaya, Amaya, wait.
Where shall we put these, Mum?
I'm just putting the confetti in the
balloons before I blow them up
and I'm just going to scatter
a few balloons everywhere.
Mango lassi! Everybody's favourite.
I really do hope that he's
happy considering he's thought
that we've forgotten about it.
Food and party decor in place...
Can you shout, "Surprise"?
You shout, "Surprise."
..son Faisal and dad Bobby arrive
with the unsuspecting Amar.
Surprise!
Happy Father's Day. No way!
Come to Daddy. She's not sure.
Oh, my baby.
This is brilliant! Guess what.
Went all the way to Hassan
and Saffron to get all your
favourite food. No way.
And he cannae wait.
He's already on it.
Are you OK, my baby?
I'm a wee bit hungry.
Happy Father's Day, Dad.
LAUGHTER
Here, we'll both hug.
Happy Father's Day! There you go.
Is he a special dad?
Well, obviously.
Got to say it to make him special.
Who do you think his favourite is?
You or Amaya? Me.
THEY LAUGH
There's no doubt about that.
There's no doubt there.
Are you hungry, Mum? I'm starving.
So am I, I'm going to make my plate.
Surprise a success, Saira and Najma
can relax.
So how does the doting dad feel?
Here you go. Oh, thank you.
Well, being a dad to Amaya is
different than being a dad to Fessy.
Fessy's a lot older, he's more...
more kind of chilling with me,
relaxing, having a laugh, a bit of
banter, carry on,
quite cheeky with me. Whereas,
Amaya, it's different.
It's right from the very beginning
and it's like nappies,
getting up early, feeding.
Couldn't have asked for two better
kids to be honest,
so proud dad definitely.
Wow!
That's so funny we were talking
about that!
HE LAUGHS
HE GASPS
More socks. Give me a hug,
give me a hug, give me a hug. Mwah!
Just feel like our family's
complete now.
We couldn't have asked, Amar and I
couldn't have asked
for anything else and I think that
is like the perfect
fairy tale ending
to our love story now.
With just four days
until the wedding in Cardiff,
it's time for Usman's mehndi.
It's very much the same as the
bride's side mehndi.
It's just a lot of fun, good food
and then just loads of dancing.
They can do it separately or
they can do it together,
it's just really a chance
for everyone to enjoy some food
and have a dance before the stress
really starts for the wedding day.
Although Usman may have been a
little reluctant to have a mehndi,
it's clear sister Shazia is
super excited.
He looks gorgeous!
He's just my wee brother,
he's like a wee green blub.
SHE LAUGHS
A wee teddy bear, you know?
He just looks so cute and he's
so chuffed that he chose that
outfit for himself. One of the
things he did himself, yeah.
I feel different. I don't know if I
feel handsome or smart,
but I definitely feel different.
It's quite a warm day today as well,
so it's a bit, you know,
hot in it but I think...
You know what? I do think I look
handsome actually, yeah, I do.
But I don't feel like a husband just
yet. I think that'll be
when I get to my actual
wedding outfit,
I think that's when that'll kick in.
Usman and his sisters are organising
the mehndi themselves,
which means added pressure to
get things right.
It is currently 4.35.
We were supposed to be ready by five
but we're running a wee bit late,
which is normal for an
Asian wedding,
but I was kind of hoping to
change that stereotype,
but obviously one man can't change
something like that, so just waiting
for everyone to get ready,
get set up and stuff and then,
hopefully, we should be ready
to go by about six hopefully.
That's the plan anyway. We'll see,
we'll see, fingers crossed.
So we're just preparing
the Indian sweets for Usman.
When he comes in with his friends
and cousins, he's going
to sit down and then the ceremony's
going to start.
So at the ceremony,
we put henna on his hand,
not directly on his hand
because boys don't like that,
but on his hand as a kind of ritual
and then, one by one we'll sweeten
his mouth as well with this.
Just something sweet to start
the beginning of his wedding preps
and his married life.
Doesn't feel like Usman's mehndi,
it feels like his wee birthday party
or something. That's how it feels.
SHE GIGGLES
You have a good side or a bad side?
Both are bad.
USMAN LAUGHS
I don't mind, either way,
man, either way.
Usman, just turn your body a wee bit
my way. Like that? That right?
Although his sisters seem in
control,
Usman has still managed to
make his mark on the mehndi.
Oh.
Looks good. Looks good.
Looks very official.
Right. Wow.
Looks bigger in real life.
I don't know what I was expecting
but it's good. It's exactly what
you wanted.
You didn't want the pink cos
it was too girlie, so you wanted
that blue, so that's all blue
and then all the other colours
as well. Yeah.
Yeah, happy with that, yeah.
As part of the celebrations,
Usman's
sisters and cousins will perform
a special dance.
Yes! Woo!
Right, you'll have to pin this back
a bit
and stop it flopping everywhere.
I couldn't dance.
Do you know the dance time?
Get this and get this.
Here. OK.
Right, I'll grab you then? Yeah,
yeah. Well, grab a safety pin then.
Have we got a safety pin? Yeah,
I've got loads if you need them.
No, not there.
Part of the mehndis is, I'd say
the biggest part of it,
beside the food, is the dances, so
that's something that starts getting
rehearsed like, it's not even weeks,
it's months, it's months in advance,
you know, and all the dances are to
perfection, and they're amazing.
When it comes to weddings,
the dancing must be on point
but the outfits are everything.
And it's not just the bridal party
who are under pressure to
look fabulous. It's also the guests.
Whether it's the sisters,
the cousins
or even friends,
you'll find that there's a
colour theme, you know,
just to complement what the bride
and groom are wearing.
But there are a few rules that
should never be broken.
A no-no is to wear red at a wedding,
unless you know the
bride's not going to be wearing red,
and you wouldn't wear the nose
thing unless you've really got
something against the bride.
And a good place to find
the perfect outfit can be
found on Glasgow's Southside.
Glasgow for years has not been
known for Asian shopping itself,
so a lot of people would go to
Birmingham,
to Manchester, to London and we
thought,
let's bring it all to Glasgow.
We thought we wanted to do something
different to stand out.
Here at Sehrina Couture, Sehrina's
bespoke designs take centre stage
while Adnan makes sure
the guys are looking sharp.
A lot of the guests
when they do come in,
one of the first questions
we do ask,
do you know what the
bride's wearing?
Because we don't want the bride to
obviously be upstaged by anybody.
After all, it's all about the theme.
I mean, I always have a joke that
when you go to a wedding, you can
see who the family members are
because a lot of them are probably
wearing the same outfit.
You can see the colour coordination,
so everybody's kind
of different in a sense, but it's
led mainly by the bride and groom.
And for many guests, it's not just
one outfit they have to think about.
You used to have the mehndi,
the wedding day and the walima,
which would be your reception
itself.
Now people are kind of taking it
a step further now,
so you've got the bridal showers,
we've got
things like the dower, and people
have like made more and more days,
so as a guest, if you're told,
right, you've got these five days,
you need to get five outfits
that don't cross over
in terms of the theme,
so you need to find five
separate outfits,
five different identities to turn up
to these five different events.
Though where guests can really go to
town is the mehndi.
It's kind of colours that make you
feel happy about yourself to
kind of look forward to the
wedding itself,
because the wedding in Asian
culture itself,
it can be emotional
for the females as well
because it's kind of obviously
leaving one family to join a family.
You can see the pinks and the golds
and stuff, things like this.
It's very loud and proud.
The waistcoats itself,
again you can see the cut work,
the detail work on this one itself.
It's beautiful, it's one of the ones
that I do like a lot.
It's not everybody's taste so the
biggest challenge sometimes is
trying to get the guys to physically
try on the clothes itself.
What shoe size? What shoe size?
But I think as a salesperson
and a person, a man,
I need to put my foot
down sometimes.
I like a person who knows what they
want but I also like the people that
don't know what they want as well,
because that's the challenge for me.
And personally, when somebody
comes in and me being able to
kind of dress them up
in a way and they feel
comfortable about it
and knowing the fact that, you know
what, I was right to trust Adnan,
it's kind of a rewarding kind of
thing to be honest with you.
As well as all the traditional
photographs that will get
taken during Usman and Sabreena's
wedding celebrations,
Usman has also organised a special
shoot just for the boys.
So, all my cousins are here and
my friends are here now,
so the plan now is to get a photo
shoot done with some smoke flares.
Just waiting for the camera guy to
now come out and we'll make a start.
Can I get a few guys on this side,
please? Two... Yeah.
That's nice, that's nice.
So the arms, everyone like that.
Everybody.
THEY LAUGH
Crib!
After getting inspiration online,
Usman's brought some coloured
flares to the photo shoot.
Walk towards us. Laugh and joke
amongst yourselves.
Have a joke, guys, have a laugh.
Just like that?
That was really good, yeah.
It went better than I thought it
would, to be honest.
So now the plan is for all the boys
to walk me in now with the drum
player and they'll be having that
flower veil on top of me as well.
With all the guests in place,
it's up to Usman's sister Shazia
to get the boys organised
for their entrance.
Just go at the back, innit? Come on.
Everyone. A bit that side, innit?
Move up, guys. Move forward and
make room for people at the front.
Everyone holds a piece.
Grab it from here, innit? Yeah.
Grab it from a bit further down.
The time now, it's seven o'clock,
so we're one hour behind
where we should be but we're going
to walk in now.
Man.
What the hell's happened to me, man?
Smiles. One, two, three.
No. I'm...
Groom to be, that's scary, man.
You ready? I'm ready
if you're ready.
This is it.
DRUMMING
When the baby of the family
gets married,
it's usually the kind of biggest
occasion,
maybe known that it's going to be
the last wedding.
Everybody goes out of their way
a little bit more
and the wedding tends to be
bigger usually.
DRUMMING
CHEERING
For a mehndi I feel the girls,
we kind of dance nicely,
quite elegantly,
we know we're being filmed.
I feel with the boys when they all
start dancing, they all just start
going crazy as if they're at
a rave.
They just start hurdling together,
jumping up and down, shouting,
egging each other on. I think they
forget that they're being filmed.
The boys might have screwed in
a light bulb or two,
but now it's time for the ladies to
shine.
It's just the sisters,
the cousins that are going to be
bringing these henna plates in.
It's just tradition, we go in
and we just put it in front of him.
What do you want? Oh, that's your
favourite.
Mum and Dad did a little dance as
well, my dad never dances,
my mum hardly dances either.
I haven't been dancing before,
but they pulled me in. Dad secretly
was really enjoying it.
You were having fun though,
weren't you? Oh, aye. Yeah.
I did not expect my family to
dance that much. We're not really
a dancing kind of family ever
but the fact that today
everyone was up on their feet,
you know, it was really good,
we had fun.
I kind of want to do it again
a little bit.
And the fun continued as Usman,
his family
and his friends headed down to
Cardiff for a private wedding
ceremony.
Where Usman and bride Sabreena
pledged their vows to each other.
With just one final wedding
celebration to go,
it's time for the wedding planners
to swing into action to get
everything ready for the walima in
Glasgow.
So I've kind of dealt with this
wedding from the beginning.
It'd be nice just to pop in
and show face
and just make sure everything's
gone according to plan.
When you're planning a large
wedding, it is... It's hard.
There's so many things that can go
wrong,
family members being late,
so it makes everything run behind.
There can be problems at the venue,
maybe a particular
piece of equipment's not working
and that has happened, where
maybe something in the kitchen is
not working properly, so that
we end up lagging behind on the food
then because of that reason.
That's why we give ourselves six,
seven hours before the wedding
to set things up so we can replace
or we can fix any issues before any
of the family members or the wedding
event actually starts itself.
Linda, can you just make sure that
there's a cake base, a cake knife
and some empty candles
around the cake table.
OK. Thanks.
It's going well.
We've only got one function on
today, so everything is very smooth.
Everything will be set on time.
The guests don't arrive
till, like, five, six o'clock.
It's half past three just now.
Tables are almost done,
stage won't take that long
and the reception will be
ready as well.
It is a working day, so I think the
guests might be a little late.
With so many guests attending
the celebration,
boss Hassan is
working at the walima too.
One case of 12. What? A case of 12.
One case of 12.
In a Scottish Muslim wedding,
we'd obviously, we don't drink
for a Muslim wedding,
so everybody just kind of enjoys
the main drink which is Irn-Bru.
It gets us all a little bit dizzy
with the sugar.
It's our go-to drink
but we're not allowed it in this
venue just due to the new carpets.
Everybody's going to
ask for it anyway,
so we're just going to have to say
we don't have it.
While the team are dressing
the room, upstairs,
Usman is getting suited and
booted...or at least trying to.
I'm definitely not used to
wearing cufflinks,
never had to wear them before.
I was not even going to wear them
for this,
but then I thought, might
as well, innit?
How does that even...?
OK.
The wedding in Cardiff was good.
The whole husband thing, I'm not
really used to it just yet
cos when, I think Shazia, phoned she
goes, "Can I speak to your wife?"
I was like, "Who's that?"
For a split second, I was like,
"I've got a wife?"
But it's only been, what, six days.
Er...
Oh, oh, I've got a knack for it now.
So, yeah, it does feel weird.
Those titles as well, you know?
It doesn't feel quite so real,
even though, I mean, it does,
cos, I mean, she's there
kind of all the time now.
I was thinking, "How will she cope
with my family, my parents?"
You know, just being in
a totally different environment.
But thankfully, touch wood,
sort of thing, she's been OK,
which I'm kind of surprised about.
In a good way, though. You know?
But like I said, I didn't think
it would be that easy.
While Usman is
conquering his cufflinks,
next door bride Sabreena
is joined by Nazia and her mum.
Assalaamu Alaikum.
Oh, my gosh. Ma sha Allah.
Look! You look lovely.
You look so nice.
Forget me, look at you!
Moving away from home and joining
a new family can be tough
but Sabreena seems to be
settled in already.
It's been really well.
I've not felt no awkwardness.
Like, it's just been
really, really good.
I'm so happy.
Home away from home,
you were saying. Yeah.
Remember you were saying people were
saying to you that you were going to
be sad... Yeah.
..and you were going to be upset?
It's going to be like,
you're going to be nervous,
you're not going to be able to
speak around everyone. Yeah.
No, I haven't had that. I'm just so
blessed. Relaxed? And relaxed.
It doesn't seem as if
Sabreena's a stranger.
It's just like she's one of us,
honestly.
She's so comfortable with us,
we are so comfortable with her.
It's been amazing, the last two
or three days. What a princess.
And Sabreena's new mother-in-law
seems pretty chuffed too.
Yes, I'm very happy.
SHE CHUCKLES
Very excited.
Yes, Sabreena's my favourite,
Usman's my favourite.
LAUGHTER
No anybody more favourite!
We're going home now! Sorry!
We're going to get forgotten now!
Sorry.
LAUGHTER
Sabreena is a very, very nice girl.
Happy her new sister is ready
for the reception, Mazia pops
downstairs to make sure the room
is up to her exacting standards.
Oh, I love this.
I absolutely love it.
Where's Aneela gone?
Hi, how are you? I'm OK. How are
you? You look lovely.
Thank you. Are you all set? Yes.
Can I just say, thank you so much.
I absolutely love it.
I know you guys are still
setting up.
Yeah, we're still sitting up
but everything's going well
and everything will be on time
and don't worry about anything.
When we're organising a wedding
we usually do - you know,
a lot of the guests are usually
friends or family.
Scotland isn't that big
of a place, neither is Glasgow.
Everybody knows everybody.
You bump into all sorts of people.
And, you know, people that you
know from different places.
Maybe from school.
People that, maybe brides
and grooms that you've just
done their wedding a year or two
years ago and they've got kids now.
Or just people that know your
family, friends of your family,
or friends of your mum's and dad's.
So, yeah, you always find somebody
you know at a wedding and, you know,
somebody to talk to.
I do know quite a lot of the people
that may be attending,
or the guests, because we have done
events for them or they're families
of our clients that we've done.
So you get to know a lot of people.
Are you all excited? I am, yeah.
Good. Good. Absolutely love it.
Stunning. Yeah,
it's all coming together nicely.
Usman and Sabreena
haven't seen the room yet,
so they're out doing a photo shoot
just now, but once they come
and make their grand entrance
they'll see it all.
But I think they might be
a wee bit nervous.
But all eyes will be on them
tonight.
But before that,
the photographer's taking
advantage of some of Glasgow's
stunning architecture for the shoot.
Yeah, the photos look really good.
Looking forward to seeing them.
Some, not awkward poses, but awkward
for us cos we're not really like
that, not very romanticy,
I guess you could say.
We're more like, you know, pose like
this and that's it, done, you know?
Yeah.
Just being so close to each other
in front of other people is not
really us.
We're more like friends, actually.
Yeah, just really, like... Buddies.
Yeah! More than buddies.
What are you saying?
Well, yeah, but that's
the kind of vibe, isn't it?
Oh, yeah, definitely.
We're just really connected,
you can just see that it just works.
Mm. So, yeah.
Sabreena, you want to
put your arms around Usman's neck.
His neck? Yeah, yeah.
And you want to put your arms
around Sabreena's waist
and just join your foreheads
nice and slow, OK?
I'm feeling OK about the walima, the
last function and then that's us,
we can chill after that. Yeah.
We can just carry on with rest of
our lives, I suppose. Yeah.
I'm feeling OK. I mean, excited,
I want to see everyone.
Yeah. I just want to have cake,
food. Cake!
And then, yeah. Yeah, so definitely
feel more relaxed this one
as opposed to the other ones,
isn't it?
Well, for me, it's more relaxed
cos it's your function, so... Yeah.
I don't know anything.
He hasn't told me nothing
so I'm looking forward to seeing it.
Let's go!
HE CHUCKLES
After months of planning
and preparation,
it's time for Usman and Sabreena
to enjoy their wedding reception.
I think just everything all came
together. That's...
The whole hard work for the last...
over a year now, with Saffron,
just trying to organise
the perfect wedding,
how Usman wants it and how we know
that Sabreena would like it.
The biggest moment was
they walked in
and they kind of looked around
and then just seeing the
reaction of everyone sitting there,
waiting on them, the decor,
the colour scheme, erm,
I think their smiles said it all.
When we walked in together,
it was, erm, very like electrifying.
Like, I just felt the rush and then
I was squeezing his hand, like,
"Come on, don't fall, don't fall."
But otherwise it was really,
really good. I loved it.
Feeding over 400 guests
all at once isn't easy.
But under the watchful
eye of Hassan,
it all seems to be going smoothly.
Just got the starters out,
about to put the mains out
so everything's on track.
It's just all go at the moment.
For months, Usman has been
keeping a big secret
from his new wife, Sabreena.
The time has finally come to give
her the surprise of her life.
A very, very special treat
for the bride.
Let's make some noise, please.
All the way from England,
Mr H-Dhami!
CHEERING
SHE SCREAMS
Ladies and gentleman...
Five, four, three, two, one.
It's not!
CHEERING
Let's go, let's make some noise!
MUSIC: Sadke Java
by H-Dhami
Absolutely amazing.
Oh, my God, I thought he was lying.
I thought he was lying.
You actually smashed it, like,
what... What did I smash?
H-Dhami!
HE LAUGHS
You've been... You are insane,
honestly. Oh, my God.
I couldn't be more happier. No?
That night was amazing.
Amazing!
Good. I'm glad you're happy.
The lead-up to today, it was just...
With all the surprises planned
and just being anxious
that everything's OK
because the walima we're hosting,
it's like our family,
representing our family,
so that was a bit nerve-racking.
Just to watch them together as a
couple going round table to table
and greeting their guests, that's
where I got emotional, thinking,
"This is it. That's
them married now."
So... I'm getting emotional
just now - sorry!
I'm the crier in the family.
It's definitely been worth
all the hard work,
it's been a great journey,
a great experience as well.
She's our number three daughter,
the last one to get married
and, er, she's very friendly
and she's got a big heart
and we love her to pieces.
So, another successful
Saffron event is done and dusted.
I can't imagine doing any
other job, to be honest with you.
It's something I like,
something I enjoy.
It's good to get that satisfaction
and that kind of appreciation
cos then you know you've
done a good job.
I feel proud to be his wife.
I feel proud to be
part of his family.
They're so loving and
I'm just so lucky. Alhamdulillah.
And I expect this the
rest of my life now.
Oh, God. You set the bar this high.
Yeah, maybe I should have started
it here then built it up, but...
No, no. It's fine, it's fine.
No, no, I expect this treatment
now for the rest of my life.