Neighbors credit publicity from the recent trial
as the reason for calling the police.
Jamie Willens' picture had appeared in local news reports
over the last few weeks,
and her image had been plastered all over the lnternet.
This stuff's awful. lt's too sweet.
And yet,l can't stop eating it. Pass me the remote.
... quoted as saying that he never doubted he would see his little girl again.
The family has asked...
Before we move on from this sordid episode,
there is a bit of unfinished business to deal with.
- He's gonna be insufferable, isn't he? - Yep.
The promised secrets.
Who spent two months in a Michigan rehab?
Stern,Lockhart equity partner R.J.Daniels.
Who was caught cheating on his 2007 income taxes?
Jason Michaels in acquisitions.
And last but not least,who's the closeted lesbian working at the firm?