You embarrassed me.
- What are you talking about? - You embarrassed me.
What did I do?
You kneW I Would buy that beer.
So What?
Because you know me so Well.
You know everything about me.
Bets, I use our life all the time in my Work.
They pay me for that.
And then you laughed.
You all laughed.
Must be so funny being in on it.
Come on.
You're taking this the Wrong Way.
You embarrassed me.
I’m sorry.
I didn't mean it.
You never mean it. You just do Whatever you Want,
and I put up With it because nobody knows.
No one is going to rember that. You know What they're going to remember?
Petra Colson missing her chair.
Come on. Leave this. You're tired. Let's go upstairs.
I’m not going to bed.
Not until you tell me Why you insist on humiliating me.
I can't talk to you When you're like this.
You're making a mountain out of molehill.
I know about you and that Woman.
Damn it, Don, I know you're having an affair.
You and Bobbie Barrett.
What?
How could you? She's so old.
Betty, that's ridiculous.
I’m just telling you I know.
Fine, Bets.
What do you know?
Go ahead. Tell me.
Jimmy told me everything.
- He hates me. - He told me everything.
Please. What the hell did he say?
So you can pick it apart? TWist all my Words?
I’m not going to dignify Jimmy Barrett
With a response. He's a big mouth.
And don't pretend I don't know how he looks at you.
I saW you tWo together.
You think you know me?
I know What kind of a man you are.
You think I Would sleep With that Woman?
You can't help yourself.
Admit it.
There's nothing to admit.
You're lying.
I’m going to bed.