The beauty of a rainbow..
the complexity of photosynthesis..
the impact of UVrays.
the mystique of an aurora-
these diverse cosmicphenomena..
all shed light on our relationship with the universe
We are anything but passive bystanders...
in this whole pageant of phenomena thatwe see...
between Earth and space
Life on Earth evolved in this environment...
of cosmic rays and aurorae and lightning..
and all of the kinds of phenomena that we see...
is just part of the environment in which we've evolved.
And so it is part of us, and we are part of it.
The beautiful atmospheric phenomena that we see...
rainbows and auroras and meteors flying by..
as well as the potentially harmful things.
like UVradiation from the Sun...
show us the Earth is notjust some isolated sphere...
detached from the rest of the universe.
No, we're part of it...
and thatmakes the Earth all the more beautiful.