You see all the wars in this world
are not fought
over money or material things.
They are all fought...
over belief.
More specifically,
the primacy of one man's belief
over another man's.
Harry has stolen my right to believe.
How did you fall...
for such a broken, worthless gambler?
I can't possibly imagine.
Your brother called.
He's on his way.
Good.
Harry won't be far behind.
Get them ready.
Take her upstairs.
I owe you an apology.
When I killed your mother, I was...
young, naive.
I really understand how much trouble
it would cause me later.
I will never put that bracelet on you!
Whatever our father...
might have told you in his last days,
he didn't want it to end like this.
Vincent didn't want you
NEAR the bracelet.
That's why he always kept you secret.
You have a lot of your mother in you.
She said pretty much
the exact same thing to me 15 years ago.
Ashton House is registered
to Lermontov Industries.
If Golding has Anna and Daisy there,
they could be hidden anywhere.
Detective Superintendent Winter to AR19,
we're 5 minutes from Ashton House.
What's your ETA?
ETA to Ashton House: 10 minutes.
Ashton House, next left, Sir.
Ah!
Huh!
Mum!
Take your hands off me!
Oh!
Mum!
Please, Nikhail! Please!
- Please!
- Harry will be here soon.
- Give me the keys.
- Please, please!
Please, let her go! Please!
Please, let her go!
Harry!
Alistair!
Harry, it's OK.
It's OK. I believe you.
And I'm sorry I ever doubted you.
OK.
NO, HARRY GET DOWN!
AH!
SIR!
Sir! Sir!
Ah!
Sir, it's gonna be OK.
It's gonna be OK.
Oh, God!
Alistair?
Stay with us.
Hold on. Hold on.
Hold on.
DAISYYYY!
Go! I got this!
D.S. Chohan. Officer down.
Shot to the chest. EMS required.
... shooter's AO.
He has Daisy and Anna!
D.S. Chohan, AR19.
ETA, 6 minutes.
No! Stop!
No! Stop! Wait.
Stop! Stop! Don't shoot!
Truth is, Harry...
I'm scared to fire this at you.
I mean who knows
what would happen if I did.
Even though I am a crack shot,
it'd probably miss you by an inch,
bounce off the floor
and end up in my gullet!
Or worse, gun could explode in my face.
Please.
Let them go.
I'll do whatever you want.
No, you won't.
Haven't you figured that out yet?
What?
The bracelet won't let you!
It protects your life,
in every way that it can.
It influences your choices.
It is the ultimate survivor.
That's why dad chose
the highest building in London
and why YOU are going to put
this gun in your mouth...
and pull the trigger.
No!
Ah!
Give me the key.
- Shoot yourself,
- Please!
- and I'll let her live.
- Please, just give me the key!
You're running out of time
to save her, Harry.
PUT IT IN YOUR MOUTH
AND PULL THE TRIGGER!
OK.
DO IT!
Harry!
Police!
Get down! On the ground, now!
Julian! Don't move!
I've got the Claytons.
Let's go after Julian!
Daisy!
Come on! Come on!
One, two, three, four, five.
Come on, Daisy!
- Come on!
- Please, wake up.
Wake up, come on!
Work for me!
Please, work for me!
One, two, three, four, five.
Please, wake up.
Daisy! Daisy!
I love you, God!
Transcription & sync: mielb
== Addic7ed.com ==