.
# We can laugh ha-ha We can sing la-la-la-la
# We can make anything
# Hold my hand
# Make a magical land
# When letters get together We go alakazam
# We can run, we can slide We can hide in a box
# Are you ready for some fun with the Alphablocks?
# Alphablocks! #
# Mmmm mm mmm
# Mmmmm mmm mmm mmm. #
THUNDER RUMBLES
Mmm? Hm!
Mmmm! Yum!
Mmmmm! Hmmm?
Aaaaaaaa!
Aaaa!
Yum mm mmm!
Yum mmm!
Aaaa!
Mmmm.
Mmm!
Mine!
Nnnn-nnnn. No way, M!
Me, N! To me!
Aaa!
Mine!
Mmmm mmm mmm!
Your turn in the middle, A.
M-A-N. Man!
GINGERBREAD MAN LAUGHS
Mmm! Marvellous!
Mmm, yummy!
# Run, run, as fast as you can
# You can't catch me I'm the gingerbread man! #
Come on, N!
No!
Woah! Ha ha!
Mmmm!
KISSING
Come on!
- # Tum tum...
- # Aaaa!
T, did you see the gingerbread man?
T! The gingerbread man?
- Mmmm...
- Aaaaa...
Time for you-know-what!
M-A-T. Mat!
Magic mat! Marvellous!
Catch the gingerbread man!
Zoom!
# You can't catch me You can't catch me! #
Aaaaa!
Mmmmmmm hmm hmm mmmmm!
Aaa! M, don't eat the mat!
Total tomfoolery.
I just popped in. Hold hands!
M-A-P. Map!
Aaa, what use is a map?
Terrific touchdown!
Aaaa!
Mmmm!
Let's take a peek.
# Run, run, as fast as you can You can't catch me
# I'm the gingerbread man. #
Aaa, aaa! The gingerbread man!
Mmmm mmmmm!
M, stop eating everything!
Mmmmm. I couldn't munch another thing.
# Run, run, as fast as you can
# You can't catch me I'm the gingerbread man #
Hee heee!
Except maybe...
Tally-ho!
# La la la la laaa laaa! #
On your tippy-toes, everyone.
# You can't catch me! #
Nnn-nnnn.
No, not playing.
# You can't catch me! #
Nnnn... Yes, I can!
# Run, run, as fast as you can. #
Oh! Ha ha!
# Mmm mmm mm mmmmm. #
- Mmmmm.
- Oh.
I can't eat any more.
Oh!
Mmmm? Mmmm-mmmm-mmm!
You're it!
Aaaa!
T-t-t-t. Time for my tea.
Perfect time to pop off.
# Run, run, as fast as you can... #
# You can't catch us...
# We're the Alphablocks! #
GIGGLING
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd