(Clattering)
(Woman gasps)
(Splash!)
♪ Theme music
♪ LIVELY JAZZ MUSIC
(Locomotive engine hoots)
(Aunt Prudence speaks indistinctly)
PHRYNE: Whoo-hoo!
♪ JAZZ MUSIC
(Seagulls squawk)
MAN: Beware the demon drink.
And the evils of alcohol.
Go away!
Beware the demon drink.
MAN: Hey, Frank!
(Tyres screech)
(Women gasp)
(Exhales) That was close, Miss.
I missed him by a mile.
What a ruffian!
MAN: Damn you, Frank!
Queenscliff used to be such
a select summering spot,
until all the daytrippers
and the riffraff moved in.
Didn't you say Dot was off
for a week in Queenscliff?
Uh, with Miss Fisher, sir, yes.
I wish criminals
would take a holiday, sir.
That way we could get a bit of peace
and quiet too.
You should know by now, Collins,
no-one has a quiet time
around Miss Fisher.
What's this?
A small fortune, Collins.
They've found Bonito's
lost treasure, again.
Hmm. You collect coins,
don't you, sir?
You ever seen anything
like this one?
Hard to tell from the photograph,
Collins.
But if I'd collected
a genuine Spanish doubloon,
I wouldn't be sitting
behind this desk.
(Honking)
Sorry, but Mrs McNaster is not home
for company at the moment.
Ah, what nonsense!
We're expected.
And we're not company,
we're old friends.
Perhaps you could ask Mrs McNaster
when she will be home.
Rightio.
Come back here
and fetch the baggage.
What are you doing,
greeting visitors anyway?
Where are the Johnsons?
(Door opens)
Oh, Prudence, I'm so sorry!
I tried to telephone you,
but you'd already left.
My dear Hilly,
I thought we were expected.
What on earth's the matter?
Well, I have no staff,
my house is in an uproar.
Mr and Mrs Johnson have taken
a sudden
and most inconvenient retirement.
Retirement?
And they've left me, yes!
We could telephone Mr Butler
and have him come down by train.
And I'm very happy
to make myself useful.
The burglary, too.
Kip.
What burglary?
GERALD: Sergeant.
Sergeant, why won't you take
my word for it?
You're not outback now, Mr McNaster.
We have rules.
That coin was handed in,
so unless you can prove ownership...
How can I prove anything
if you won't let me see it?
I'm a very busy man, sir.
So, in the absence of any evidence
of a break-in,
I'm afraid there's very little else
I can do.
Good day to you, sir.
Gerald.
Ah, Mrs Stanley.
Mother, I thought
you were going to telephone?
I'm afraid we'd already departed.
Hilly, my dear, you need help,
on all fronts.
You do realise that my niece
is a private detective
of the utmost discretion
and capability.
Indeed.
Is she really?
Specialises in murders. But I'm
sure she'll make do with a robbery.
Oh, well, I suppose
you'd better come in then.
PRUDENCE: I thought you'd never ask.
Hilly, so lovely to see you.
(Laughs) Good.
Here we are.
Perhaps we should leave the champagne
in the boot, Dot.
(Bottles clatter)
He rode a bicycle
to the top of the Andes,
drove a T-model Ford across India.
He's been attacked in jungles,
lost in deserts.
And once, he even had to drink
his own...
That's enough, young man.
Mr McNaster's activities are his
own business. More tea, thank you.
GERALD: Excuse my manners. It's been
a while since my last drink.
I always keep the study locked.
And the key with you?
Yes.
Though there's a spare one hidden
in a collar box in my bedroom.
I didn't even realise my doubloon
was missing
until I read this morning's paper.
Then when I checked,
I found my entire coin box was gone.
A doubloon? A souvenir
of your London to Peru attempt?
Yes, the only one.
We were flooded in.
I had to abandon the Oldsmobile...
At the foot of the Cordilleras.
Yes, I remember reading about it.
Really?
You have an interest in exploration?
I've dabbled.
So, the local police think
your doubloon is part
of the lost treasure of Queenscliff.
Yes, it's ridiculous.
At least he has more imagination
than I gave him credit for.
You and the local sergeant
don't see eye to eye?
Baxter? He bears a grudge.
My mother's Temperance Chapter
closed down his uncle's hotel
a year ago.
No mean feat to close down
a watering hole in a fishing town.
The Baxters were asking
for trouble,
doing a roaring trade
every night after six.
Really, Hilly, I can't believe you
let the Johnsons go without notice.
Since when do servants retire?
It's a vocation, not a job.
Where are those jade vases
I gave you?
Oh, they're in my bedroom, Prudence.
They suited my new curtains
beautifully.
Ahh.
Have you considered the theft
might be linked
to the Johnsons' sudden departure?
Well, I must admit, some things
have been going missing lately.
Just small things.
But the Johnsons have been devoted
to us for years, especially Mother.
What kind of things?
Some pieces of silverware,
some ornaments. Nothing like this.
Well, you do have
some tempting collections.
Do you like rocks, Miss Fisher?
I found this on a beach
in the Gulf of Carpentaria.
It took thousands of years
to create,
and you can hold it
in the palm of your hand.
Anything else missing?
Not that I've noticed.
Although I move things around a bit
while I'm cataloguing.
Sometimes I could lose track.
Yes, I can see that.
Clive and Moira Johnson, thieves?
One must never entirely trust
one's own staff, Hilly,
no matter how loyal they may seem.
But why would they suddenly start
stealing from us
after all this time?
Perhaps they need money
for some reason?
Ah, Mother knew them
better than I did.
HILLY: Well, Clive and Moira
weren't extravagant,
and they were utterly respectable.
They were the ones who introduced me
to the Temperance Union.
Oh, we have a thriving local chapter
here, darling.
You must come to a meeting.
(Chuckles) I must confess, Hilly,
even I have my limits
when it comes to the tambourine.
Perhaps the Temperance Union
landed them in some kind of trouble.
I'm sure not everyone in town
would agree with their views.
(Kettle whistles)
Do you think Mr McNaster would mind
if I had a look in his library?
Why don't you help me get the tea
ready first? We'll need more sugar.
Pantry?
It's up high. I'll get it for you.
Thank you, Kip.
(Whimpering)
What on earth is that?
JANE: Hello, boy.
KIP: Gaston!
What are you after?
It's the Johnsons' dog.
Mrs Jane dotes
on this little mongrel.
Shoo! Shoo!
What are you doing here, boy?
They'd never leave Gaston behind.
Whether they had a reason
to steal those coins or not,
the police should still be informed
of their departure.
No, no, I can't believe it.
They took their leave
and they went to the ferry.
Now, what robber would use
a getaway ferry?
And that Baxter will be no help
finding them.
He's delighted to have
my most valuable coin
in his lost property box.
What about your Inspector friend?
He's supposed to be a servant
of the people,
especially the right people.
Jack's supposed to be a servant
of the law, Aunt Prudence.
Excuse me? I think
you should come and see something.
Hey.
The Johnsons wouldn't leave
their dog. They're good people.
How long have you known them, Kip?
Four years I've been here.
They gave me work so I could look
after my gran and the other kids.
I could ask around and see
if anyone knows where he's been.
Good idea. I'll go too?
Excellent.
Come on, boy. Let's go.
Is that wise, Miss?
Are you worried they'll stumble
across a robber's lair,
or is it the twinkle
in Jane's eye that bothers you?
(Sighs) The whole world bothers me,
Miss.
You're sending her to the Continent
in a week.
It's an adventure, Dot.
A woman's rite of passage,
not an ordeal.
Will you at least chaperone her
on the beach?
Just as soon as I place
this telephone call.
Jack, I'm in desperate need
of a numismatist.
And I'm the only one you know?
I need your help
with a fellow coin collector
who's just been robbed
of his doubloon.
Anything like the one that's just
washed up from Bonito's treasure?
Sadly it's not pirate bounty.
It was stolen from Aunt Prudence's
good friends, the McNasters.
Gerald McNaster? He found a
Spanish doubloon in Peru, didn't he?
And his domestic staff
have mysteriously disappeared.
But it seems the local police
have a grudge against the McNasters,
and are refusing to investigate
the case at all.
Well, I'm not sure
what I can do from here.
Gerald has no proof
the coin belongs to him.
We need some sort of
archival evidence,
an entry in a journal,
a note from a museum?
And I have nothing better to do
with my time?
Well, you might,
but this is definitely more fun.
(Distant conversations)
JANE: What are they digging for?
They think that coin that washed up
is part of the lost loot of Lima.
Why would it be in Queenscliff?
A Spanish pirate ship tried to sail
from here a hundred years ago.
But the British got them
and hung the captain.
But Bonito outsmarted them
and hid the treasure first.
Could be anywhere here, buried
in the sand, hidden in a cave.
Over there.
I believe there's something curious
much closer to home.
How awful.
Do you think the tide washed him up?
I don't think the sea did this, Jane.
The water didn't come up
this far today.
Someone's covered him up
deliberately.
The police are on their way.
Thank you, Kip.
I've seen him before, Miss.
So have I.
That's Frank the Fish.
The fishmonger.
Do you know him, Mr...?
I'm Finlay Ellis.
We both knew him, Wally and me.
Frank used to crew on my boat.
Had to lay him off a while back.
A falling-out?
Couple of bad seasons,
as it happens.
Frank's had it rough himself
since then.
It's the demon drink.
That's what's killed him.
BAXTER: Alright, thanks. Move along.
Nothing to see. Constable, get these
people to stand back, thank you.
That's Mr Johnson's.
I'd know it anywhere.
Get that dog out of here.
And you too, madam.
This is a police matter now,
so thank you very much.
It's also the scene of a crime
and you're trampling all over it.
Sergeant Baxter, I presume.
Not now, thank you, madam,
and I'll decide
if this is a crime scene, thank you.
These gentlemen knew the deceased.
Is that right?
Then I'm sure that these gentlemen
will be only too happy
to remain here and assist
with any identification
after I peruse the body.
Isn't that right,
Mr Ellis and Mr Stirling?
Happy to help, Sergeant.
The skinny one was seen chasing him
earlier this morning.
And somebody covered up the body.
I will conduct the inquiry,
thank you, madam.
Now for the last time,
can you please just go home?
McNaster was right.
The man's a fool.
We definitely need someone
more competent.
A murder? I hope you didn't go
to any trouble on my account.
Well, I was tempted to do away
with the local sergeant
who has now proven himself to be both
incompetent as well as unpleasant.
I'm glad you resisted.
Though, strangely enough,
I did have my chance at the victim,
who threw himself in front
of my motor car this morning.
But survived?
Due to my excellent driving skills.
Only to be murdered on
the beachfront by the afternoon.
A local fishmonger
with an interesting connection
to our suspected coin robbers,
Mr and Mrs Johnson.
So it's 'our' robbers now?
If you leave immediately,
you'd be here in a couple of hours.
Some of us follow the speed limit.
If you insist. Two and a half.
Three.
Oh, good afternoon, Dorothy!
You're just in time, Mr Butler.
There's been a murder.
Will that be one less for dinner,
then?
One more, actually. Inspector
Robinson is joining us too.
Ah, you must be Kip.
Dot's told me all about you.
Can I take your bag, sir?
Oh, I can manage my bag.
But this is for you.
It's not new.
It used to be mine, when I started
out in service many years ago.
Thank you, Mr Butler.
Shall we?
PHRYNE (Whispering): Jack!
Shhh, Jack!
(Sighs)
(Pop!)
Jack, this is a temperance household.
The sound of a popping cork
could lead to my eviction.
More so than entertaining a man
in your private parlour?
A man? I thought
you were a police officer.
I'll try my best
to be less entertaining.
You should join Hilly's
Temperance Union.
Some of us are not here on holiday.
It doesn't have to be all work
and no play.
Besides, I'm not on holiday anymore.
I have a robbery, a body and two
missing servants on my plate.
I called into
the Queenscliff Morgue.
The fishmonger's body's been sent
to Melbourne for autopsy,
but Baxter's current view
is a drunken fall,
striking his head on a pier.
That man wouldn't know evidence if
he fell over it, which he almost did.
Luckily, I salvaged the treasure.
I saved it for you. You can have it
sent up to Melbourne for analysis.
(Clears throat) Pungent.
It could still make the night train
if we hurry.
Now, what time should I have
Cec and Bert pick it up?
Don't tell me,
it just fell into your hands.
After it fell out
of the dead man's pocket.
'My darling.'
Glad I'm forgiven.
'On our golden anniversary.'
Has it been that long?
From Mrs Johnson to Mr Johnson.
Presumed to have run off
with the stolen household items,
including the missing doubloon.
Any forwarding address?
They left with the ferry.
That's the last anyone heard of them.
Where's their quarters?
Already plundered.
The Temperance Union's battle plan.
'Lips that touch liquor
shall never touch mine'.
I preferred 'my darling'.
Two hotels closed, many more to go.
No wonder Baxter's
been dragging his heels.
The Johnsons were bad for business.
This town needs all the business
it can get.
Perhaps your view is clouded,
Sergeant,
because your family were publicans.
I want to know where
the Johnsons were going,
when they were last seen.
Friends, associates, enemies.
Start searching now,
that's an order.
And I want a proper report
on that dead body by the morning.
Yes, sir.
Very dashing, Kip.
So you think there's some connection
between those terrible murders
and the departure of the Johnsons?
What? How could they have anything
to do with the poor fishmonger?
Oh, m-mere speculation
at this point, Mrs Stanley.
The police are looking
into both matters.
Ah, I see.
Strange about the watch, though.
PRUDENCE: What watch?
Mrs McNaster, I was hoping
to speak with your son.
Do you know when he's available?
Oh, Gerald arrived home ages ago.
He's in the study. He's still
looking for the mould, I imagine.
Mould?
Well, I reminded him he took a cast
of the Spanish doubloon.
You know, the coin
the police are hanging onto.
So that would be proof of ownership?
Yes, but he seems to have
lost track of it.
JACK: I found the photograph
in the Geographic Annual.
Unfortunately, I doubt
there's enough detail
to identify the doubloon.
But your mother said
that you made a mould?
Well, yes.
I made plaster casts
of some of my collection
for the Larco Museum in Lima.
Perhaps we could help you
look for them.
Oh, don't worry, I've tried. But
I'm afraid I've disposed of them.
I've put out word in Melbourne,
in case it turns up
on the black market.
But I understand other coins
went missing.
Yes, my entire collection,
although nothing as rare
as that particular doubloon.
Did you notice anything unusual
on your return?
There was no supper laid out,
and the household staff had gone.
Eventually, Mother explained
that the Johnsons had left.
She was terribly upset.
And then?
I made some cocoa.
We played a few hands of cards.
I thought it may distract her,
but it didn't seem to help.
Which reminds me,
I should see to Mother. Excuse me.
(Door opens and creaks)
Have you considered young Kip in
all of this? He had the opportunity.
Jack, that boy can keep secrets
for about as long
as I can stand still.
Besides, what's his motive?
The same as anyone else
digging out there,
the hope of an easier life.
Then how do you explain
the fisherman with the fob watch?
Perhaps he wasn't acting alone.
You said he knew the fishmonger.
(Knocking, door opens)
This is for you, Inspector.
Thank you.
No head injury.
No sign of any injury,
apart from a broken front tooth.
The trickle of blood.
Cause of death?
Still to be determined, and awaiting
results on the stomach contents.
I think we need to take another look
at our crime scene.
The ferry leaves from here.
The coin was found in the shallows,
but if the whole box was dropped,
the coins could have fallen
through the cracks,
and been washed in by the tide.
What does this stain
look like to you?
Blood? Fish, perhaps?
There are no scales.
Could have been here a while.
It poured with rain
the day before we arrived.
(Sniffs) This has been here two days
at the most.
We need to find out who moors here.
Special delivery.
Ah.
Inspector Robinson in Queenscliff.
Good, I've been expecting this.
What's he doing in Queenscliff?
Having a holiday?
(Slurring) While the boss is away,
the workers play?
Not you, eh? Not you, Collins.
Our Dottie wouldn't put up
with that.
Bert, it's nine in the morning.
Never too early to fall off
the back of a truck.
Come on, get out. Now, come on.
A train!
It was a train. Fritz von Opel could
use that stuff for rocket fuel.
I should lock him up for drunk
and disorderly.
(Thud!)
BERT: Oh!
Could ya? Just for a bit?
There seem to be quite a few items
of silver missing.
Oh, dear! Well, we'll make a list.
Mr Butler, I know a good servant
doesn't gossip about his employer,
but what if it was something fishy?
Something that might have to do with
what Jane and me found yesterday?
Jane and I.
It's about Mrs McNaster.
Look, there are times
when discretion needs to give way
to common sense.
It's about the dead bloke, Miss.
Mrs McNaster used to buy
her fish from him,
but she used to pay him herself.
And one time I saw her giving him
a couple of candle holders,
silver ones.
Really?
I told Mrs J about it, and her
and Mr J went to talk to her,
but Mrs McNaster made a big fuss.
Crying and carrying on.
When was this?
Not long before
the Johnsons went away.
I hope I've done the right thing,
telling you.
You certainly have, Kip. Thank you.
I can't believe it!
Hilly in financial difficulties?
Surely she'd tell me.
Perhaps it's a matter of pride?
Perhaps the Johnsons
didn't retire after all,
but she was forced to let them go
because she couldn't afford them.
We know she was bartering
for groceries.
What?
Paying in kind.
Silverware, missing vases.
But she said they suited
her bedroom.
I checked, Aunt P.
They were my wedding present to her.
Exchanged for produce?
I suppose this means you...
you think that Hilly
killed the fishmonger?
No, Aunt P.
Oh, thank goodness!
But I do think it's all
somehow linked.
(Footsteps approach)
Ah, Miss Fisher.
Has your handsome friend
managed to retrieve my son's coin?
My...? Oh, the Inspector.
Ah, I'm not sure, Mrs McNaster.
Hilly, dear,
Gerald's expeditions
must have been very costly.
Well, of course,
but of course he's so well regarded,
he's always picking up grants
and patrons and such.
I wondered, with the household
so diminished...
Really, Prudence,
that is none of your concern.
You would tell me if you were in any
sort of straightened circumstances?
I... I don't know where
this is leading, Prudence.
I-Isn't your accommodation
satisfactory?
Isn't the catering up to scratch?
I know I have had trouble
with my staff,
but I... I will try harder
to meet with your approval.
Oh, you already have!
I... I've no complaints.
Oh! Well good, then.
Ladies, luncheon is served.
(Exhales)
Are you alright, Hilly?
Mm.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Any luck with the Johnsons?
JACK: Not yet.
Seems they bought tickets
for the ferry, but never caught it.
And Sergeant Baxter is giving us
the run around, as usual.
He says he's shipped that coin off
to Warrnambool
for authentication
at the Maritime Museum.
Would you like something to eat,
dear?
No, thank you, Mother.
I've lost my appetite.
Well, would you care to sit down
and eat, Inspector?
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr Butler.
Did you find out
about the next full tide?
Early morning. Very early.
What took you so long?
(Sighs) I was as quiet as a mouse.
A mouse who wears French perfume.
I'll wear less next time.
Is that the boat?
Yes, they're tying up now.
Let's go find a mouse hole.
FINLAY: Come on, Wally,
give us a hand, will ya?
Hey, come on! Get it up, get it up!
(Clattering, distant shouting)
Will you shut your gap! You'll have
half of Queenscliff down here.
The dead fishmonger
crewed for the big fellow.
Wally, get the cart.
And that's the one I saw chasing him
the morning we arrived.
Going over.
(Water laps softly)
(Small splash)
I think we've seen all we need to
for the moment, don't you?
It's only right
that I escort you home.
If you insist.
(Splashing)
The analysis shows it's a lot more
potent than standard rum, sir.
So it is bootleg?
Ah, yes, sir.
Grave potential
to cause alcoholic poisoning.
Back cell.
Collins?
Yes. No, yes, sir. I'll send
it down for you right away, sir.
Better still, Collins, come down
and bring those reports with you.
To Queenscliff, sir?
I need someone on the ground
I can rely on.
Hey! Hey, no, not so fast.
JACK: Collins? Collins?
Oh, no, we're not wearing that.
It was forced on us.
We were only there to do a job.
What's going on, Collins?
No, it's... no, it's nothing, sir.
It's nothing. I'll be on the next
train down. Thank you, sir. Goodbye.
The bloke said it was cheap 'cause
it came straight from the brewery.
No middle man.
We didn't know it was bootleg.
What bloke?
Some bloke.
He collected a cart load
from the guard's van, yesterday,
when we picked up the parcel
for Miss Fisher.
But this bottle was the parcel,
so this isn't your grog.
This was found on a victim
in Queenscliff.
Same bottle. Oh! Same grog.
Flint's Rum.
Victim of what?
We don't know yet.
He only died yesterday.
(Seagulls squawk)
Madam.
'Morning!
Oh. Oh, yes, I'm sure it is.
I... I can't seem to find
what I'm looking for.
'Morning, everyone.
That is the dinner setting, Kip.
Ah, we don't have a full service
breakfast setting.
You're absolutely hopeless.
Take off that uniform
and go back to the scullery.
You're not fit to be
in polite society!
He has improved, Hilly.
Calm yourself, please.
And the breakfast setting
is incomplete, Mrs McNaster.
Oh, I'm... I'm so sorry.
I'm... I'm not myself this morning.
I will go and fetch Mrs McNaster,
bring her down back to breakfast
again, and all will be forgotten.
'Morning, Jack.
'Morning.
DOT: I'll help with the tea.
So will I.
That bottle we sent to Melbourne...
Shhh!
So much
for the temperance household.
According to Collins,
your friends, Bert and Cec,
witnessed a crate load
of those bottles
arriving in Melbourne yesterday,
on the Queenscliff train.
So now we need to find a link
between those bottles,
and that clinking midnight cargo.
Constable Collins is arriving to
help us with inquiries this morning.
I said we'd meet him at the pier.
Good.
Who knows what we might reel in?
(Muffled speech)
PHRYNE: Oh, dear, I hope that's not
what I think it is.
Oh, my Lord, it's
Moira and Clive Johnson!
If these are our thieves,
they paid a terrible price.
The other night. I saw you haggling
for them and look at them now.
You've got something to do with it.
I'll take Ellis.
I saw you with my own eyes.
Don't know what
you're talking about.
Inspector Jack Robinson.
I'm keen to know about the cargo
you unloaded last night,
from the Kennocha.
I was heading home after our
meeting, when I saw them out here.
It must have been after eight,
because the ferry
was already heading out.
So Mr Ellis's fishing boat
was moored at the pier that night?
Yes, this side, where I could see.
The boats were in,
the tide must have been up.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I'm allowed to carry goods
and if I want to unload at night,
well, that's my business, isn't it?
Alright, stand back.
Is the blood on the pier
your business as well, Mr Ellis?
Next to where you moor your boat?
There's blood all over that pier.
It's a working port.
Fish, bait, blood.
And corpses.
What were you arguing about
with Mr and Mrs Johnson
the evening that they disappeared?
They wanted a ride to Sorrento.
I said no.
There's a ferry, isn't there?
They'd just missed it.
They offered a decent fare,
but I declined.
I had other plans,
like a drink with the lads.
And I suppose
you were drinking together
when the fishmonger
was killed as well.
What are you trying to say?
Those two were still alive when I
left the pier. Ask any of my crew.
Ask my deckhand, Wally.
We may just do that, Mr Ellis.
In the meantime,
please don't leave Queenscliff.
I've got fish to catch,
and a boat to pay for.
'Morning, sir. Miss Fisher.
Very timely, Collins.
It certainly looks like it, sir.
I'll go break the bad news.
I... I should have stayed
in my room.
PRUDENCE: There now, Hilly,
calm yourself.
Two more dead bodies?
Isn't that a little excessive,
Phryne, even for you?
I didn't put in a request,
Aunt Prudence.
Were any of Gerald's coins found
on the bodies?
Apparently not.
That's a relief.
BUTLER: A hot, sweet tea will help.
Thank you, Mr Butler.
They... They gave it back to me.
They brought me in
and simply handed it over,
as they should have done,
three days ago.
At least something good
has happened.
This doubloon, it's the only coin
that means anything to me, Mother.
The rest, they... they don't matter.
Baxter didn't tell you
about the murders, then?
Murders?
PRUDENCE: Try to relax.
The Johnsons' bodies
have been dredged up.
Good Lord, that's hideous!
How... how did they die?
Laceration to the forearm
from a large bladed implement,
and a major, rear penetrative wound
through the victim's stomach
and liver.
That would do it.
And the wife?
Some superficial bruising
to the face and lips.
Cause of death, suffocation.
If the Johnsons found out
that Finlay Ellis and his crew
were smuggling illegal rum...
And confronted him?
Or threatened to expose him,
Ellis wouldn't have been happy.
But unhappy enough to motivate
a murder, or two?
Or three. The fishmonger
could have been found out as well.
Local sales could just be the tip
of the iceberg.
Ships sail past here every day,
bound for America.
We need to prove
what Ellis has been up to.
Let's hope Collins has found
our middle man.
(Sighs)
And you don't have any other records
for parcel delivery?
No. That's the last seven days.
Everything loaded on here
heading east or west.
Mm-hm.
Anything else I can help you with?
No, that'll be all for now.
Thank you, Mr Redwin.
Good-o, then. I'm due on the 2:30.
Happy to assist, Constable.
That man was far too helpful.
Some people have no difficulty
cooperating with the police.
Dottie! Ah,
would you excuse me, please, sir?
Ah, go on.
Look over here, Jack.
Constable Collins is on duty.
Then you can blame Dot.
You mean that guard?
The man I was questioning.
About what?
Some boxes in Melbourne.
I need to tell Miss Fisher
something.
Excuse me, Inspector, Miss.
Hugh said he was questioning
that guard about some boxes
that ended up in Melbourne?
Go on.
Well, when I came to meet Mr Butler,
I saw that guard
signalling to another man
with a trolley loading some boxes.
Description, Dot.
You know him, Miss.
He was chasing that fellow
you almost ran over
when we arrived in town
two days ago.
Wally Stirling.
Finlay Ellis's deckhand.
As I said, far too helpful.
I want a signed statement
from that guard, Collins.
Everything he knows
about Wally Stirling.
And warn him we have a witness.
Yes, sir.
I think it's time
to divide and conquer.
I'll see how Finlay Ellis
likes the idea of his deckhand
confessing to a sideline
in rail deliveries.
And I'll tell Wally Stirling
it was Ellis who turned him in.
That's not what Finlay Ellis says.
He told the police
you were smuggling cheap rum
up to Melbourne on the train.
What? He could be trying
to save his own skin.
But he implied Frank the fishmonger
knew about it as well.
Look, I already told you,
I don't know nothing
about no smuggling, alright?
Neither did Frank.
Then I wonder what Frank's
connection was
to those bodies that were dredged up?
Frank had nothing to do with that.
Then how did he come across
Mr Johnson's fob watch?
I heard the police found it
in his pocket.
The problem is, Finlay Ellis
was seen arguing with those people,
and now they're dead.
I don't know anything about that.
The police think
they were murdered
because they found out
about a smuggling racket.
And Finlay Ellis told them
it was all your idea.
No. No, that argument had nothing
to do with smuggling.
No, from what I heard,
they missed the ferry,
they asked him for a trip
to Sorrento,
and he told me he wouldn't take 'em.
Now you tell me,
why would he killed them over that?
I don't know. Perhaps you should ask
Mr Ellis yourself.
(Sighs) This is taking a while.
Do you think we set a big enough cat
amongst the pigeons?
Depending on the pigeons.
FINLAY: Oi!
Wally! What the hell's
been going on?
You stupid bastard! You been
helping yourself to the merchandise.
So I passed Frank a few cases,
so what?
I didn't know he'll flog them
in town.
You've brought the coppers
down on us!
Not my fault. I tried to fix things.
By killing Frank?
Someone put the wind up him.
He was going to Baxter,
reveal the whole operation.
I had to shut him up, alright?
To protect you!
Protect your own backside, you mean.
Oh, come on.
(Grunting)
(Growling)
HUGH: Stop! Police!
Yes?
Hey! Hey! Hey!
I suggest you put that down!
Put down the knife, Ellis.
Aargh!
Don't try to get up.
I don't want to ruin my heels.
I'm arresting you
for the murder of Frank McKay,
also known as Frank the Fish.
And you're being
held under suspicion.
I didn't kill Frank.
Let me clarify. Suspicion of
murdering Clive and Moira Johnson.
I didn't kill anyone!
Move.
There are numerous witnesses
to your argument,
and it was clearly about more
than just a ferry ride.
Half the town hates them.
With their protests
and their preaching.
But what they were going on about
made no sense.
What were they going on about?
They were blaming me
for Mrs McNaster being in a bad way.
Said it was my fault
for supplying her with the drink.
But you didn't know
it was Frank's sideline, did you?
He let you down,
just like Wally Stirling did.
Frank was a fool. But he didn't
deserve to die like that.
Like what?
Dead drunk from illicit rum?
Or do you mean choking on a bottle
that was shoved so far down
his throat it broke his teeth?
Wally did it. He must have killed
the Johnsons, too.
Go on.
He heard me arguing with them
that night,
and he knew it'd all come out.
He was the last one
to leave the boat.
He must have stayed behind
to shut 'em up.
On the pier?
That's where we found them
when we came back in the morning.
Frank and me. Both of them.
They were already dead.
And Frank helped you
get rid of the bodies?
We carried them up to the end,
where we knew the tide
would take them out.
(Splash!)
So if Wally Stirling
killed the Johnsons,
where did you get that knife?
The one we saw you
throw into the water.
I found that on the pier.
Same time we found the bodies.
Constable.
Take Mr Ellis down to the cells,
thank you.
Considering we have no weapon
and no witnesses,
it's his word
against Wally Stirling's.
BAXTER: Ellis is guilty.
Let's face it.
What kind of fool would clean up
after a murder they had no part in?
That's the first sensible thing I've
heard you say. Pity if you're wrong.
By the way, Inspector,
somewhere here I have a telegram
that came for you
from the Melbourne Museum,
I believe.
Well, looks like a response
to our coin inquiries.
A doubloon minted in 1798
went missing from their display
three years ago.
Well, that doesn't help us at all.
No.
Different doubloon.
McNaster's was minted in 1790.
Hilly! Oh, Hilly!
My God! Help!
Somebody, come quickly!
Help! It's Hilly!
Oh, dear. Hilly! Hilly!
(Hilly moans)
Come on. We'll get you out.
Out of the bath.
(Hilly moans)
Lean on me.
There we go.
(Slurs while speaking)
What the devil?
Get back!
What the devil's going on?
Get back! You can't come in here!
What's going on in there?
Please, get out.
(Moans)
Hilly, it's alright now.
PRUDENCE: Get her into bed.
Get her a nightie.
I think they're in that drawer.
I thought she'd drowned.
She almost did, in rum.
I-It's my fault. It's all my fault.
What on earth's going on here?
Get Mr Butler to bring up
some coffee, preferably strong.
It was medicinal at first,
and then I just needed it.
I couldn't have you knowing, Gerald.
So you bought it cheaply
from the fishmonger?
Well, at first I was paying it
out of the housekeeping money,
but then Gerald likes to account
for every penny.
Mother, so that's where
all the ornaments and the silverware
were going?
Well, the fishmonger said he'd tell
everybody what a hypocrite I am.
I had to pay him as best I could.
And the Johnsons?
Well, they found out about it.
They tried to help me, they did.
And then I lapsed once too often
and they just resigned.
And you insisted on the dignity
of at least paying them.
With Gerald's coins.
Well, I couldn't let them go
with nothing,
after all those years of service,
and they'd been so good to me.
I had no idea.
The money, the corner you were in.
So... the night the Johnsons left,
you'd been drinking?
That's what was wrong with you.
You should have told me.
I'm sorry, Gerald,
it just got out of hand.
And I remember sitting down
to bridge,
and then it's all a blur.
The cards and the cocoa.
I just can't remember any of it.
Kip, on the night the Johnsons left,
Gerald made cocoa for his mother.
What time was that?
Cocoa, Miss? I don't understand.
He said he made a cup for his mother.
Ah, I don't reckon so.
See, of an evening
I'm meant to go home,
but there's no room at my gran's,
so the Johnsons let me sleep
in the pantry.
And I would have known
if anyone was at the stove.
Dot, do you suppose Hugh
brought along his bathing suit?
I can ask, Miss.
Found it!
What a feat, Hugh!
Worthy of a bronze medallion.
Well done, Collins.
You were under for ages.
I thought you'd drowned. (Chuckles)
So we've got a dagger.
Hm, looks like a collector's piece.
(Lock clatters)
Queenscliff Police Station.
Jack, the dagger belongs to Gerald.
So how did it get to the pier?
I'm not sure he's being
entirely truthful with us.
He lied about making his mother
cocoa the night of the theft.
Why would he do that?
Perhaps he was busy
doing something else.
Chasing up his missing doubloon,
for example, or doubloons, plural.
Do you happen to have
that telegram handy?
Um... Yes.
What year was
the museum's doubloon minted?
1798.
(Telephone tings)
Miss Fisher? Miss Fisher!
Nothing does get past you, does it?
You already had a doubloon.
Why steal the museum's one?
They deserved it.
They refused to fund me
because I couldn't promise
to bring back more precious curios
for their glass cabinets.
As if that was ever the aim
of true adventuring.
What about the Johnsons? You took
their lives for a box of coins.
Those coins were mine!
If only she'd told me,
instead of giving away
the greatest find of my career!
The Johnsons were people, Gerald.
I could not hesitate!
(Dog barks)
(Indistinct shouting, clattering)
You hesitate out there,
you're finished!
All he had to do was hand them over.
But he wouldn't!
(Gasps and pants)
I held her down.
And when the museum's doubloon
was dug up in the sand?
Instead of reading
about your murders,
all you read about was treasure.
It was my reprieve.
That's all I need, Miss Fisher,
one last reprieve.
JACK: Miss Fisher! Phryne!
Argh! Aaaargh!
Thank you, Jack. I don't think
there'll be any need for that.
More tea, madam?
Oh, no, thank you.
The motor car is packed, Miss.
Thank you, Mr Butler.
The Inspector had to leave?
He's gone back to Melbourne,
to return the illicit doubloon
to the museum.
I must confess to some relief.
I don't think I could face him
after the arrest of my son.
Oh, Prudence.
You know, I was never good enough
for Warleigh Grammar,
and this just proves it.
Oh, what nonsense!
No, it's true.
For this to happen with my son,
and now you know the worst
about me, let alone poor Gerald.
Hilly, do you remember
those hours spent over Virgil?
Omnia vincit amor.
Love conquers all.
I'm going to stay on here a few days
and we'll face society together.
Thank you.
Oh, darling.
What a shame. Gerald achieved
extraordinary things in his lifetime.
He was a true adventurer.
Pity his last great adventure
will be jail.
So, tell me, Jack.
Where did you collect your coins?
Amongst the ruins of ancient Greece,
or deep in the jungles of Patagonia?
I inherited my collection from Uncle
Ted and sold it at the age of 12,
so I could buy my first bicycle.
Now that's an adventure.
It was. It was.
I rode further
than I'd ever ridden before,
through the uncharted wilds
of North Richmond.
Where even Captain Flint
didn't dare tread.
And the pirate girls of Collingwood
ruled the waves.
To pirates, adventurers
and boys on bicycles.
(Ting!)
♪ Away, away, with rum, by gum
♪ With rum by gum, with rum by gum
♪ The song of the Temperance Union
♪ We don't step on grapes
♪ Because that's making wine
♪ And one little stomp
♪ Turns a man into a swine
♪ Oh, can you imagine
♪ A sadder defeat
♪ Than a man getting wasted
♪ By licking his feet
♪ Away, away, with rum, by gum
♪ With rum by gum, with rum by gum
♪ The song of the Temperance Union
♪ Away, away, with rum, by gum
♪ With rum by gum, with rum by gum
♪ The song of the Temperance Union. ♪