You have been found guilty of murder in the first degree.
I'm sentencing you to life in prison without possible release.
Noooooo!
I didn't kill anyone!
Good morning.
I'm not going to hurt you.
What is this?
You're not in prison anymore.
The world thinks you're dead.
Suicide.
This is your funeral.
Row 8, plot 30.
My momma... didn't come?
We've decided to give you another chance.
This is where you'll train. This is where you'll learn.
After two years, if everything goes well, you'll work for us.
Why me?
A woman with your looks, who can kill in cold blood...
I didn't, I didn't, I didn't kill anyone!
When you attack someone from behind, go for the kidneys.
It disables and they can't fight back. Consider that your first lesson.
- I don't want - I don't want lessons!
- We start tomorrow morning. 5 a.m.
And if I don't want to?
Row 8, plot 30.
- Where am I going?
- To meet your new mother.
So who are you? My father?
Wait here.
They seem to think you have potential.
Who's they?
Who are you?
I'm Madeline. They are Section One.
They own you now.
Didn't know I was for sale.
Please sit down.
If you want to live, it has to be on our terms.
So please, do sit down.
Look at yourself.
Admire yourself.
See your beauty.
You can learn to shoot.
You can learn to fight.
But there's no weapon as powerful as your femininity.
We're family now, Nikita.
- You're late
- Training went long
- Take a look at this.
- Van Vactor.
He's brokering an alliance between multiple anti-western terrorist groups.
Shining Path, Nezbolla, everyone from the Middle East to the Far East.
That doesn't make sense.
Half of them are enemies to each other.
But their biggest enemy is us.
He's coming here to put an operation in place.
Do we know the when and where?
No, but we think there's an itinerary downloaded onto a PDA.
Walter's on it, he'll update you.
Michael, about Nikita.
What about her?
I've been watching her.
She lacks discipline.
She needs a little more time.
It's been two years.
That's our policy.
We start making exceptions, we're no better than the CIA.
Cancel her.
I think that would be a mistake.
It would be a mistake to become emotionally attached to the material.
It has nothing to do with that.
I think she could be a good operative.
If she fails, you fail.
- How's it going?
- You tell me.
Have Madeline get something nice for you to wear. We're going out.
- What do you mean, going out?
- Dinner, tonight.
- Why?
- You've earned it.
Madeline taught you well.
It's hard to believe I'm here.
Where else should you be?
I don't know. It's just that I lived on the streets for so long.
- Why did you run away?
- I didn't.
My mother preferred her new boyfriend.
And he didn't like me.
So she told me to get out.
- Sorry.
- Don't be. I never was.
You've come a long way, Nikita
I... feel...
Go on, say it.
Happy.
Really?
The blond haired man sitting behind me has a PDA in his briefcase. Get it.
How?
When you get the unit, don't leave through the front.
There's a window in the ladies room. Use that.
It leads to an alley. The car will be waiting.
I - I thought we were -
If you're not out of there in five minutes, the car will leave without you.
- I can't do this.
- Five minutes.
- If you don't mind, wait til I leave.
- Michael.
Open it!
I've got my men everywhere. You'll be dead in a matter of seconds.
You knew?
We had to see if you could improvise.
Did you get the PDA?
Why didn't you tell me... this was a job... instead of pretending?
No matter what state of mind you're in, you have to be able to perform.
You're sick. You don't want a person, you want a machine.
I can't do that.
You just did.
Let's go?
- What's this place?
- You'll see.
No. Not until you tell me what we're doing here.
Nikita, please.
- You live here?
- No. You do. It's your’s.
Mine?
I hope you like it.
What do you mean, mine?
Everything you need is in here - I.D., driver's license, credit cards.
Tell no one who you are or what you do.
Anyone asks, you're between jobs and taking some time to figure things out.
Your codename is Josephine.
- What do I do now?
- Wait.
How long?
It depends. Could be a day, could be a month.
Goodbye.
Hey. Hi, I’m, I'm Carla. I live across the hall.
Welcome to the building.
It's a coffee plant.
Who sent you?
Who sent me?
Listen, if, if this is a bad time for you,
I can- I can always come back later.
Carla?
Hi, I'm Nikita.
Hey.
Do you want to come in?
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Okay.
I'm a carpenter. Yeah, I know, my mother still hasn't recovered from the shock of it all yet.
Whenever anyone asks her what I do, she tells them I'm an interior designer.
At least you like what you doing.
Yeah. Yeah, I mean, ever since I was a kid, I wanted to build stuff. So what do you do?
I'm-... I'm between jobs.
At the moment.
- Well what do you want to do?
- I don't know.
Hmm, well, you'll figure it out.
- Do you want to go get something to eat?
- Yeah, sure.
I know this great burger joint.
- Hello!
- Josephine.
Take off your clothes.
Okay, this opens like a normal lipstick.
This is your explosive right here. You jam it into the door,
and then you arm it right here.
Okay, target's name is Gideon Van Vactor. He's in Suite 2105 with his mistress.
We have a thirty-minute window. She's expendable, he's not. Take him alive.
Team One, you'll be the coolers on this one.
Stay in position as long as possible.
If you have to break, two pulses.
Team Two, you'll be working the rim.
Okay, one more thing.
We don't know what all these people are.
Be prepared for anything.
I need her now.
This is your com set.
Remember, try and keep your head still.
Team One in position.
Just two more on the left.
Good job, Nikita's confirmed. She has access to the room.
Housekeeping!
Now what?
Put the plastique on the door. And remember,
be quiet, he's in the next room.
On two!
Nikita, someone's coming in.
Who are you?
Hey, hey, hey - I'm leaving, I'm leaving now.
- Shoot him!
- What are you doing in this room?
Nikita, he's one of them. Shoot him.
Shoot him now.
Now Nikita, now!
Everyone abort! Get your teams off the perimeter now!
Let's move, let's move!
Get up.
Stand!
Section One is the most clandestine
organization on the planet.
It's our job to bring down the criminals
and terrorists that no one else can get.
I can't do what you want me to do.
Mistakes are not an option.
I can't pull the trigger.
Why not?
Because I'm not who you think I am.
I'm not a killer.
The moment I believe that, Nikita,
you're cancelled.
- I've got something!
- What is it?
It's Van Vactor.
He's on his way to the airport.
All right, find an intersecting point. Start sequencing.
- What's going on?
- Looks like a car accident.
It's a trap!
He's running!
Team Two and Three, neutralize the area. Team One, pursue.
He's in there.
Damn it.
We've lost team One.
Michael!
They don't work down here.
In here.
Why don't I know you?
See, I make a point of knowing my enemies, of which I have many.
Yes, I definitely would remember those eyes.
Okay, shall we end this misery?
Let's prolong the entertainment.
He's a friend of yours, isn't he?
Go to Hell.
Let's try something different.
Where do you come from?
You okay?
Josephine.