Krister - Lars Lind
The inspector - Frank Sundström
Tester - Jan Blomberg
Kajsa - Mona Andersson
Reverend Mild - Åke Grönberg
The Police inspector - Erik Hell
Nisse - Leif Nymark
Egon - Stig Törnblom
Pyret - Lars Hansson
Jingis - Sven Algotsson
Butcher("Slaktarn") - Torleif Cederstrand
Fish("Fisken") - Bo Andersson
Steva - LENA NYMAN
From a novel by Lars Görling
Director Vilgot Sjöman
(The play at the theatre is "A Dream Play" by August Strindberg)
English subtitles made from the soundtrack by Aliquis
A minute ago
I spoke to our inspector.
He's not happy with your attitude.
I wonder, can you imagine
the amount of effort and money
we've put into this?
This isn't a kind of police interrogation
if that's what you think.
You are to be enlisted
in a control group.
It won't be easy
to enrol Nisse to science, inspector.
I don't think he really understands
the importance we put on this survey.
Oh, you do, don't you Nisse?
Not a single word you utter
within these walls...
will ever get to the police.
This is a scientific survey;
purely scientific.
If you should find a question ...
too awkward, you can deny to answer it.
You know that.
We have a purpose, Nisse...
to create new and better treatments.
to prevent boys like you
from getting into the police records.
In helping us you're helping yourself.
and in the same time you help us
to develop the society one step.
The other guys might not realize that.
But you do!
A boy with an energy
and an initiative like yours ...
No, it'd be a loss...
to let such qualities
be worn down behind bars.
How is life upstairs?
Yes, it's a bit basic,
but the best we had on hand.
Are you getting along
with the other boys?
Well then.
I'll leave you now.
Don't forget this is to your own decision, Nisse.
Totally to your own decision.
No one in "The Objectivity"
would ever dream of compelling you to join.
My own decision?
Had I not accepted
I'd been handed over to the cops.
I had no options!
Egon had to face the same choice
and four of the others.
Well, we all work in different fields...
pinching cars, blowing safes, shop-lifting,
living with whores.
Now we're all put together
in a worn-down house on Mäster Samuel Street.
for a psychological survey
to a purpose we knew nothing about.
more than we had to be at The Objectivity
for tests every morning.
"The Objectivity
Juvenile Pension"
Doesn't anyone here
have one single buck to spare?
Shit, they're forcing us to break up everything!
No fags, no movies,
not a shit!
- You have at least a nice bed.
- A bed!
I have my quarters in Högdalen.
It's good enough for me!
They took it from me!
Hell, then at least I had some money.
Krister is coming.
Hi.
Were you late too?
Follow me and let's see
if we can make some kind of arrangement.
Did you visit The Objectivity today?
Did you go to college here?
Nowadays it's called 'university'.
- Bought this newly?
- Yes.
I'm curious of that one.
'Semantics'.
Do you know of that?
Semantics claims that most differences
of opinions do not really exist.
It's a matter of linguistic.
Many a conflict is due to the fact
that spoken language is such a blunt tool.
- Well.
- There's a point in that.
- Have you thoughts about the university yourself?
- No.
You've made a start already.
'A start', for being here one term?
Well ... how was The Objectivity today?
I don't want to appear repetitive, but in fact ...
I've told you many times.
So ... do you know what day it is?
Friday, payday.
Payment.
- Gifts of grace. Bloody charity.
- Be grateful. It's better than nothing.
What a bloody mess.
How the hell can you live like this?
Keep your position in mind.
You are everyone's voice here.
- You cannot bloody live like this.
- Easy now, I haven't settled down yet.
When the new furniture will arrive,
and I'll have the time for my studies ...
In this mess.
You heard.
It'll all be here within some days.
They promised the curtains
will be here tomorrow.
Egon, Egon please, calm down!
Splinted wood for you.
Speaking of cleaning up,
you owe me two bucks, and so do you.
- I conned you.
- You're conned yourself.
Who did you think cleaned up your quarters?
Kiss my ass!
What's the matter with you?
Please, hold up, will you.
- Pyret, is this really necessary?
- Every darn piece of shit.
Kick that hell of a box off my sight!
He's sick in the head.
Soiling everything in his way.
- What did he do to you?
- That's not the question.
Soiling everything.
What about payment?
Shouldn't we make the best out of t this situation?
- Egon, nothing will be better...
- Whatever, I will smash the other box too.
Where's Butcher?
I can sign on his behalf.
Don't let yourself be tricked by him, Krister.
'Tricked'?
Don't you think I'll give him the money?
All of us aren't a rotten egg like you.
Bloody bastard!
Ten bucks a week!
To hell with it.
Ten bucks a week to the guinea pigs.
That's quite a lot for a guinea pig ...
if it doesn't smoke.
So go on use your snuff!
You can afford that, you bastard.
«Pyret is a sleepwalker from time to time,
and talks in his sleep.»
«Egon sleeps like a ball.»
«If he was awaken too abruptly,
his arms bounced fiercely in all directions.»
«With force.»
«Jingis sleeps on a rubber sheet.
He's a bed wetter.»
«He use to piss either in the morning
or directly after he falls asleep.»
That darn old hag.
When she makes cocoa
it barely fills an egg-cup each...
at the most.
And tomorrow we'll have turnips...
with stewed concrete.
Get your pissed sheets out of here.
I could do some scratching
in the box of the old hag.
She's the boss, isn't she?
She should be removed.
She?
The whole bloody Objectivity.
We could do well on our own.
- Krister and we.
- And start a kind of labour union.
We have a chairman.
Not at all a bad idea.
Chairman of "United Thieves Union'...
with a salary.
Really...
Were do we keep the funds?
In the vault of The National Bank?
Well, don't you trust me?
Do you think I'd run off with the loot?
We must have four cashiers,
constantly watching each other;
grumpy, mistrusting blokes.
Two locks and two safes.
Two vaults and two of everything
to prevent every single bastard from entering.
Look at those poor,
bloody blue collars.
Bloody blue collars!
They are as good robbers as are we ...
only they don't call it stealing.
They call it 'fringe benefits', 'borrowing'
and bloody other names.
And drunken driving.
Could that be a habit?
"Some boozing every now and then."
"So what?"
What's the worst,
get your car and some money stolen..
or get a year for drunken driving?
...Or get juvenile reformatory.
A bloody car they'll get back in a couple of hours,
money they don't honestly own.
Do you believe in God, Krister?
I do.
Be careful with 'Godly'!
When he's hungry
he roams the streets and eats your kind.
Nisse!
Well, social developing merely tiptoes.
Our ability to take care of each other ...
does not develop in the same rate
as technology and standards.
Nisse. Nisse!
Eh ... leave that door, please.
Come, take part in our conversation instead.
I do see your uneasiness.
It's tragic that some people must suffer
due to this long-winded development.
They didn't care!
They didn't do a bloody thing to help me.
But now I only wish to be left alone.
You speak of The Objectivity,
and yet you've never been in their claws.
My God, what have you done?
Don't you stand the sight of blood?
Are you grinding mincemeat?
You scumbag,
can't you see the guy's wrecked himself?
Wrecked himself?
It's self-inflicted.
You complain of injustice,
told by others.
- Then you judge yourselves the hardest.
- That's our business, isn't it?
Who's complaining did you say?
Fish, go and get the first aid kit.
Hurry, please.
I made complaints
to point at the inequities.
Take it easy.
They love to whine.
Who do you mean?
Who's whining did you say?
Whine yourself, you puny,
bloody, shitty, rotten louse.
Stop this, Egon! Please.
- What the hell are you ...?
- Egon!
This was so very unnecessary.
Should I have let him
use his knife? Should I?
Shall I just be standing here
and take all ...
You know him.
You didn't have to be that brutal.
Bloody socialist, bloody ass,
bloody inspector, bloody superintendent,
bloody Djurgården-fan!
And I shall take all this?
He started!
Bloody chief editor, bloody clerk,
bloody custom officer, bloody criminal inspector,
bloody assistant secretary!
My father is a principal assistant secretary.
My old man's brain was so rotten
that he even had to rape my mom.
He had to fuck her for three weeks
before he could lit his fireworks.
And she was howling all the time,
because he bloody hurt her.
His dick was as large as a horse's dick.
My gosh!
If my father got to know
that I'd done such a bad thing, he'd hated me.
«...because she got syphilis,
and when I came ...»
«And it took three weeks
because it was so darn hot.»
«Then she howled because my old man
wouldn't leave her alone.»
«She was so tight,
that I had to creep out through her ass hole.»
She made no difference to your ol' man
when you'd arrived.
That bony bitch.
Your whore of a mother,
had to beg for a lay,
When she didn't get it,
she ran to the Monkeys at the Zoo.
She found a half-witted ape
and raped him ...
Your father!
Strange, isn't it?
Don't puke in here!
Do your puking in the bathroom!
If you think we'll wipe up,
you're dead wrong.
Lick them up yourself!
You bloody runt!
- Egon!
- You dumb-ass!
If you cannot stop fighting,
you'll end up at the hospital.
- Shall we...?
- No.
Something fishy about this.
Why does he keep it locked?
I bet he's keeping a whore in there.
Really?
But how does she get fed?
«If you want to make a key,
you must buy two or three blanks;»
«if you should file too much
on the first one.»
«The part of a key you are filing
is called 'the bit'.»
«It could do with an imprint.»
«After some filing,
cover the bit with molten wax.»
«Then you turn the key in the lock,»
«to see where the key does not fit.»
«If it doesn't fit already, that is.»
«Well, I made a key ...
to that door.»
«He had no right to hide things.»
«They feel betrayed,
all the time,»
by every person on every level.
There, there now.
Take some advice from an old colleague:
Pay heed not to identify yourself too much
with the objects we study.
What's the use
if I cannot identify myself with them?
Who else should put forward their complaints?
They cannot!
Good.
You keep your fangs sharp.
We need your ability to protest.
Our Swedish society would wither away,
if there were not ...
younger people ...
who could stand up for a cause.
Sometimes I dream about
a kind of Final Judgment.
Not of the judgment per se ...
but to enable everyone to see clearly ...
and to disable the ability
to close your eyes.
And then a great silence ...
so all ears could rest
from all explanations.
No investigations, ...
no denials.
Nothing.
No possibilities to escape,
to defend or to make excuses.
We have become so talented!
What are you doing in here?
How did you get in?
Who allowed you to ...
Jingis?
Jingis!
Stop!
Stop, Jingis!
Are you angry, Krister?
Not exactly angry but ...
Come forth, Nisse.
Krister is not angry.
This grand piano belonged to my mother.
I was just playing a little.
Go on playing, Jingis.
Krister is all happy if it's used,
and no longer is kept hidden.
- It belonged to my mother, Nisse.
- Where is she?
I just played from memory.
I never touched the music sheets.
Well, Krister didn't know
that you play the piano.
This is nothing.
I can play much better.
Jingis. Jingis, please!
Do keep on playing, Jingis.
He doesn't mean it.
He wouldn't make you second
to his dead old mother.
Of course you can play it sometimes.
Occasionally.
Well, it never occurred to me.
I'm sorry.
It never came into my mind.
It's nice in here.
Maybe we should leave.
Or we could invite the others.
Maybe you don't want to?
Why did you never mention,
that you had a secret room,
so nice that we could not be invited.
You'd better have the key.
If so, I can make a new one.
I don't really feel I've let your down,
by not mentioning this room.
Come on, Jingis.
Then I gave my opinion
of him, that bastard.
Of course he boiled over.
And the girl?
What became of her?
She? She had no options.
I was the only one left.
What the heck. She had to pay me
for fucking that guy.
So I sent her in the street
to work and get some money for booze.
You bet we had a nice time.
In bed, I mean.
It reminds me of that babe
I met in the Old City.
I remember an old lady
who tricked me into her flat.
I lived in the Kransen some years ago,
and there also lived this gorgeous babe.
One at a time please.
I have time for you all.
Let Pyret continue.
Oh ... What do I see?.
The later the day, the better the guests.
Do join us.
Here's space enough.
Do enter.
I was twelve; went to school.
There was this old hag
my mother used to talk to.
One day she invited me to her flat.
I had no second thoughts,
so I stepped in.
Well, I had noticed
her eager eyes on me sometimes;
and some fondling now and then.
So what?
She was an old lady for god's sake!
How old was she?
How should I know?
... Well, around 30 years.
Anyhow, she said she could mend my trousers.
No, it started with me
fixing a lamp for her.
What the fuck.
I didn't strip off my trousers that easy.
Then she started this fondling thing.
Of course I got exited!
I had never done it before.
And?
Well, I had a pretty nice time.
She must have felt the same.
She was moaning and all that.
Then she never left me alone.
She was watching for me every day.
If I said I wasn't in the mood,
she gave me chocolate and stuff.
When you didn't fuck?
She had had a hard life.
She and my mom used to talk about that.
Did your mom never find out?
Well, there were rumours.
Of course I denied it fiercely.
But I wasn't allowed
to visit people any more.
And you obeyed
your mother of course?
She never left me alone!
I hardly dared
to go home after school.
I know a similar girl.
Marie on Bastugatan Street.
I once met this hooker on Central Station.
I got her undressed and upon her bed.
When I should screw her,
she told me to go to sleep.
Then she grabbed a newspaper
and started reading the advertisements.
I was pissed, screwed her
and went home to sleep.
Listen to me!
I was waiting for the subway.
I was going to Stockholm from were we lived.
A girl came to me and said:
"You may if you want to", she said.
Well. What did you answer?
It was bright noon.
... Ouch, why are you pinching me?
Nobody is pinching anybody.
Yes, you did.
I could feel it.
You did like this.
Ouch, I cut myself!
I got a wound.
Why did you do that?
Why did you cut that poor boy.
He's done you no harm.
Let me have a look.
Did you do this?
- Do what?
- Jump on someone of your own size instead!
Stand up when I'm talking to you!
Nisse!
- Did you do this to him?
- No.
I don't have to ask.
I saw it with my own eyes,
but I demand an answer!
Well?
I know nothing.
You 'know nothing' of this?
Are you that disrespectful?
Do you deny it straight to my face?
Something that evident!
Deliberate sadism
is one of the most repulsive acts ever.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Answer me!
He might have been cut by this.
I was fiddling it.
- You pricked me with...
- Shut your mouth!
You do not order him
what to say or not.
He lies.
In this room there's only one liar.
Believe what you wish.
Watch your step, Nisse.
I will not tolerate this kind of behaviour.
What happened?
Bloody Nisse.
He cut Jingis' hand with a nail file.
This loony is totally brain-dead.
Lock him in for good!
«He understood nothing.»
«Nobody understood.»
How the hell can you sit here,
as a common laughing-stock.
You block-heads.
Don't you see he'll use
everything against you?
Do you think this survey
will last for ever?
Where will you end up
when this is over?
You'll go to Lövsta or Långanäs
or some other bloody reformatory where you belong.
The blame is yours.
They'll send you to some forestry
in the Lappish hell of a wilderness.
You know very well
where you'll end up.
"Sörsbro Mental Clinic"
To your comfort,
you'll be accompanied by Jingis.
Take good care of him...
to combine business with pleasure.
That damn queer.
- Do you think he is?
- What
- What you said.
- A queer?
Fucking, yes!
Do you mean we should...?
I don't know if it's possible.
But if...
We would do a lot better.
Lots of cash, fancy clothes and ...
But evidence?
Sneaking in with a camera,
taking some pics.
Who volunteers?
«Now we'll listen to Johan Fredrik Mellin Andersson...»
«born on 4th of February 1911.»
«on several occasions sentenced
to imprisonment with labour for theft.»
«Yes, reverend, my sins in life are many.»
«I was indeed a sinner.»
«But now Jesus is my whole life.»
«That's the plain truth.
Now, adultery and wickedness is history.»
«Well, it's long ago.
It was in summer 1977. I do remember.»
«I got six months.»
"I do long for the crown ..."
"... but I wonder some times ..."
"... will we have any ..."
Do come in.
You belong here too.
Enter.
"...heavenly ...
"... some good souls did I win for my God."
Thus even Jesus Christ
has made use of modern technology,
in the struggle against evilness.
This is a complicated device.
It's very expensive.
You must handle it with care,
not to let the delicate mechanism get ...
out of order.
«Once I was as simple-minded as Simon Peter,»
«when he asked his Teacher:»
«"Lord, what number of times
may my brother do wrong against me,
and I give him forgiveness?"»
«"Till seven times?"»
«But as Jesus taught Simon Peter...»
«He taught me at the same time, and said:»
«"I say not to you, Till seven times;
but, Till seventy times seven."»
«Seventy times seven ...»
«equals 490;»
«a high number and a big numeral.»
«490 times you can sin against Him...»
«and yet be forgiven.»
«You have His word because He loves you.»
But at the 491st ...
Then the devil will shake you,
and your bodies will tremble.
All your arrogance will be gone,
and you must pray for mercy.
Jesus Christ has promised
to forgive you 490 times,
whatever you have done...
because those were his words.
But about the 491st time ...
He has given no words.
None at all.
- Thank you.
Well, thank you, I enjoyed meeting the boys
and deliver The Message.
- Once again, thank you.
- We owe you thanks, reverend.
What a bloody jerk.
How could Krister invite such an idiot?
"... some good souls did I win for my God."
«- I'll have one with sausage.
- Cheese.»
«Cut it out!»
«Well, get out and get a lay.»
«Sexually deprived, poor boy?»
«- That reverend.
- He's got himself a fat meal ticket.»
«He's not a greater saint than I am.»
If we get it on tape, it's water proof.
He hasn't got a chance.
We give him a copy, and he'll know.
What did you get that day?
Eh... eight Sedisonal...
... six "P" and some Efinol.
- I was a bit dizzy.
- Bullshit.
You begin to look old.
A bit bald.
Are you a beauty yourself?
- So you're out for hookers?
- Yes.
Show him how to do it.
Would the inspector like this?
Why not?
He's a member of the B-team.
This is his favourite tune.
- He's been "dancing" many times.
- Maybe into your butt as well?
No, but if they'll queue up,
I'll give a party.
What do I charge?
It'll be a difference
once you've married the inspector?
We'll have a party.
Hey, we arrange an engagement party.
Invite the inspector!
Can I borrow your paddle?
«And when I felt that the inspector
was ready to pick ... after a week,»
«I made Krister take us to the theatre.»
«"We need some culture", I said to him.»
«Krister was immediately carried away.»
«And the inspector was so moved,
that he promised to baby-sit ... yes, Pyret!»
- When do I get my ten?
- You will, but I have no money.
- You promised me my money.
- I know but I have no.
- What the hell!
- Get a paddle of your own.
- Won't you come, Pyret?
- Hell no.
You'll regret it.
Ready boys? Hurry!
Stop playing.
Butcher!
In a second!
«Jingis. Have you taken a bath?»
Hurry Fish... Fish!
Hurry, please.
«It was the first time ever
I was at the theatre.»
«I didn't fancy it that much.»
«But I remember most of it.»
«It was the first time
for the others as well,»
«but for Jingis.
He had been at the opera as young boy.»
«He saw "Little Peter's Travel to the Moon".»
«This he shouted in the auditorium,
and made everyone stare at us.»
«They had already been staring at us,
so we felt a bit awkward.»
«Now to the play.»
«"Indra, Lord of the Heavens,
Hear us!"»
«"Unclean is the earth;
Evil is life;"»
«"Neither good nor bad
Can men be deemed."»
«Everything was exaggerated, unnatural.
I got lost in it.»
«I was embarrassed
and fidgeted on my seat.»
«They waved their arms with trembling voices,
and strolled back and forth.»
«Nothing of it was for real.»
«"Lies the fault then with them,"»
«Jingis alone liked it,»
«and of course Krister.»
"The Objectivity
Juvenile Pension"
Was it a flop?
No. Why?
- You did it?
- What do you think?
Say it then!
- Witch is the Play button?
- This one.
Ah, now I know.
Turn it down!
- You're jackass of an engineer.
- It wasn't my idea.
We must do it again.
Count me out.
I didn't get a cent from that bloody queer!
- Wait.
- Who babbled? What now then?
Fuck you, you cannot kick me out
from my own quarters!
Open the door!
It belongs to the revered, doesn't it?
So it was you.
You gave me your word!
It's a fine device.
What were your plans?
Nisse, please.
Do me a great favour, return it.
As a favour person to person;
and for your own sake.
Do it tomorrow.
If I promise this will lead to no fuss.
If I promise that the police report
will be withdrawn;
that no one will blame you for anything.
If nothing else;
for your own good.
Think it over.
If anything good will come out of this,
it must come from yourself.
"PAWNBROKER'S"
You go!
Why me?
You're next in line.
You must do something on your own!
I won't hesitate.
Really?
Dare you join me?
Hello! Seize the thief!
Dammit that it had a report!
I never thought he had had the time.
That was really close!
All this for nothing.
You hell of a bastard, Krister.
Pity you fear the inspector that much.
We have no proof.
Ask "him" and "he"
will raise and testify.
- And he would buy that?
- Yes, what?
- We cannot step up and just say "aha"?
- Not?
"Help the leprous".
"Cashier's office  Accountance"
»Enter.»
- The inspector, is he here?
- Yes.
It's Saturday; we close at one o'clock.
One of the boys from the Pension
wants a word with you, sir.
Let him in.
You may enter.
Ah, Nisse, do come in.
How nice to see you.
Everything in order?
Our dear Krister is doing all well.
Nothing but peace and quiet.
The survey works out quite well.
I've heard that you do really cooperate.
You have all shown maturity.
Be seated. Do sit.
You smoke, don't you.
Be my guest.
It can be a bit tiresome
in the long run.
But we will have to find
something out to ease it up,
since you downstairs
have all been so responsive.
Diligence must be rewarded.
This matter with Pyret.
So ... Anything particular on your mind?
He feels a bit downcast ...
at the moment.
So.
I thought you wished
to know about it, sir.
If you didn't know it already, sir.
Well ... why he's depressed, I mean.
Maybe you should express yourself
somewhat more precisely.
Did you make a bet?
It's about Pyret.
I think I fairly well can
figure out your point.
Sit.
It's all about what you had in mind
to get in exchange for your knowledge.
I only wanted you to know, sir.
Yes ... and now I know.
Anything else?
No, nothing, since you have already
promised us some benefits, sir.
Did I really make a promise?
Pity if I did,
since I in that case will have to break it.
Although I unwillingly do.
It would too easily be misinterpreted ...
as things have developed.
It's your decision, sir.
No ...
discipline would suffer from that,
and become a drawback
to our dear Krister.
I very unwillingly would take measures
that would harm him;
since he's so young
and inexperienced;
so inexperienced,
that he might not know ...
that a certain form of allegations
is a part of our profession;
far too common in fact.
He might misinterpret it ...
even if all the rest knows
about this phenomenon.
It would be a pity
to loose his friendship,
due to what some
unbalanced boys claim...
but ...
Well ... This isn't exactly atypical.
We have all heard it before.
So nobody is interested in
what you claim to know.
Except in a psychological
point of view, that is.
Let me change the subject.
I heard something about a tape recorder ...
You might recall reverend Mild
visiting you an afternoon some days ago.
We have had an inquiry from the police.
We haven't yet decided our steps.
We've got a description.
This deals with notably
more evident matters.
Our dear Krister ...
also shares this opinion.
We have been discussing this.
There, cheer up!
It wasn't my meaning to daunt you,
being my visitor.
On the contrary!
I only mentioned it for you
to know of our support.
When you laid your hands
on that tape recorder,
you did a great job.
Nobody noticed anything.
But afterwards, Nisse ...
That was not like you.
You must have been daydreaming.
Well ... we'll straighten this out,
with the tape recorder I mean.
Cheer up!
Nothing has happened
that cannot be overruled.
You are a nice boy, by the way.
You are in fact fairly handsome.
A thin face and these gentle features.
Your mouth has a beautiful line.
But you should smile more often.
You mustn't be that suspicious, Nisse.
You must learn to take
what life has to give.
A great deal, I'd think.
I think many a person
would do quite a lot ...
to help you,
if only you'd care to take
what they will give.
You can go far in life.
There must be a great many
who would like to help a boy like you.
We have grown apart for some time.
Pity, we were really friends.
Maybe this is a great loss to us,
to both of us.
But there is still time, isn't there?
A fine neck you have.
Like a soft arc.
Here's a cleavage.
Soft and nicely shaped.
Here it meets with your hair.
But you're far too skinny, Nisse.
I can almost count your ribs.
Here's one ... another one ... another one.
This is beautiful, Nisse.
Nothing of this is dirty.
It is beautiful.
It is pure.
If you get something on your mind,
you're always welcome back.
The door isn't locked.
«I couldn't get rid of it.»
«It came to my mind every dark night.»
«I tried to think of girls.»
«I choose pics from magazines.»
«"Pin-Up", "Cocktail" and others.»
«I chose among pics I had used»
«when I ... wanked.»
«Yes, I did.»
«I picked Kajsa at The Objectivity,
the dame with the breasts.»
«I removed her bra and almost
fondled her to death every evening.»
«But the inspector always interfered.»
«When I was thinking of Kajsa,
his head came in between and was poking around.»
«My nausea for it didn't help.»
«It was the other way round.»
Wouldn't you tell me
what has happened?
Did something happen?
I don't know.
You look troubled.
Did I hurt your feelings some way
without seeing it myself?
Wouldn't you tell me,
to prevent me from doing it a second time?
You had confidence in me before ...
at first.
... I think.
If you've done something
you fear I will report, then ...
Wouldn't you?
You mean ... to the inspector?
You shouldn't misjudge him, Nisse.
- He's saved your backs more than you might believe.
- He has?
You have to admit that?
Well, you shouldn't never poke
in old wounds, but...
This tape recorder.
You must admit he's the one
who got you out of it.
I mean ...
I too was under pressure,
since you'd promised to return it.
Well, I don't blame you, Nisse.
If the inspector had not interfered, so ...
I really shouldn't say this.
It was meant as a surprise.
You'll get new furniture
for the lounge next week.
A new radio-gramophone,
with an inbuilt tape recorder.
He's the mind behind that.
- I even think he's made a private contribution.
- I don't give a damn!
You rotten bastard!
Lifting Krister's books.
What did you get?
- 155.
- Give it me!
This'll be a starting fund.
Now we'll do real business.
Brännvin, booze!
We smuggle it and sell it.
We buy it for 15
and sell it for 30.
Not from a Svea ship.
They charge too much.
And they drink it all themselves.
Not really stylish;
smugglers on shitty bikes!
We should be
at the amusement park instead.
You could have a lot of fun for 140 bucks.
155!
140!
That bastard invested in a new hat.
Hesitating are we?
When things are getting serious?
Okey, back out! I don't mind.
Go and socialize.
I'll do fine on my own.
«Who's there?»
Excuse me.
Speak to them.
Say what we're after.
I do.
'Excuse me', is that German?
«No, I spilt it out.»
We want to buy Brännvin.
Twenty crowns a bottle.
Then you can have it.
Fifteen,
and ten bottles.
Eighteen.
They have got a chick.
No, look...!
- Move and let me see. Move!
- Don't push!
Look, they're fucking her!
Sixteen is we ...
I mean our highest bid.
No higher.
«Then beat it and close the door.»
Hell, let's enter.
They are so pissed up, they won't notice.
Be grateful for that.
Want some?
Me too.
Not you.
You're too young.
«Those scumbags made me pregnant!»
If it's a baby-chick,
name her after the ship.
I told you to get out!
- They could at least stop this.
- I pity her.
She's hurt.
Could she get some schnaps ... please.
Feeling better, are we?
Talk about the Brännvin.
What's his price?
Sixteen crowns and fifty öre.
Yuk, now she's vomiting!
You have no clothes on.
Come on.
You want it yourself.
Come on!
Not good!
But she wanted to.
What did he say?
He said it was no pleasure,
since she was too willing.
Eighteen.
"Achtzehn" what does that mean?
'Eighteen' isn't it?
Eighteen!
The bid was sixteen fifty a minute ago.
You can't keep on bargain
like an old hag.
We'll get that difference back
when we sell the bottles.
How many can we get?
Seven. 126 crowns.
Fine, that'll leave us some change.
Seven.
We'd better check the bottles.
They might have been opened.
You cannot do that!
They are buddies.
Take the bottles and leave.
I'll join you after I've fixed something.
- See anybody?
- No.
- Let's go on shore.
- Yes.
- Where's Egon?
- He should talk himself to that babe.
What the fuck, are you all sleeping?
Nisse, wake up.
A rotten style, Jingis.
Sleeping all morning.
- Is this your quarters?
- Yep.
In the upper bunk,
but let's eat first.
Guys, bloody wake up!
Open a bottle and let's have a draft.
Taste it and see for yourself.
- Do they bunk here as well?
- Yes. Have a sip.
- Cut that out will you!
- But it's plain water.
Wait ... be careful.
The same as in our glasses.
«At that time, Ray arrived.»
«That he was named Ray,
we had to find out in the newspapers.»
«But he never tried to leave us behind,»
«as he left the night watch, that is.»
«At the beginning we hanged out
in Gärdet and in Djurgården,»
«because I used to live there as a boy.»
«I had never been there since,
and I got this certain feeling.»
«I had never had a dog before.»
«Sometimes we lit a fire
and cooked something to eat.»
«Ray got his fair share.»
«Afterwards ... when we were grabbed,»
«I was said to have mistreated him.
But that's a lie.»
«Okay, we might not have been
grooming him that very often.»
«We roamed the city all through.»
«We tried to bathe once,»
«not far from Viggbyholm,
but it was too cold.»
«We visited Kallhäll and Norrviken.»
«We were gone all day long.»
«The Pension was for sleeping only.»
«We didn't give a damn
about the survey.»
«Of course they were confused.»
«Dogfood isn't that cheap.
We were short of money;»
«our pocket money I mean.»
«So I kept on stealing books from Krister.»
Excuse me, Nisse.
I cannot allow you
to empty my entire library,
without knowing
where it all ends up.
Sold.
You can call the cops.
- You very well know I cannot.
- Why?
I can do it for you.
Don't be daft!
If you're able to lurk in here,
you're able to call the cops as well.
Where's the dog?
Where does he fit in?
Is he stolen?
So what?
Is he unhappy?
No, but his owner might miss him.
He's paid for him.
Let's buy him then!
And the ethic aspect?
That's Ray.
And Steva?
Won't you speak
to the inspector about her too?
Maybe you're unaware
that she's living here?
Anything else?
Almost all my books.
- So.
- I have a need for some of them.
Something has gone astray.
I cannot pinpoint it.
And obviously I'm not given
an opportunity to make good.
Come here ... come.
Come. You can have me.
I want you.
Look at me.
Look at me!
Afraid of Egon?
Take no notice of him.
I dumped him.
And he won't be back
for an hour, by the way.
Deceived!
Did you really believe
you could have me?
I wouldn't touch you
with a barge pole!
Oh Ray ... Come here boy.
You may it you want.
No idea.
As you wish.
I don't care.
«Krister was my sole target.»
«I calculated his weak spots.»
«My mind was not really focused on her.»
«My plans for Krister
turned out just fine.»
«Everything went according to my plans.»
We didn't do this.
We would tell you
if we knew where he'd gone.
We couldn't stop him.
We can help you to search for it.
To prove we didn't do this,
we'll help you.
Where is it all?
- Where?
- Yes.
I sold it.
You sold it?
And of course
I am the one to blame,
though I don't know why.
Maybe you think
I'm having false pretensions.
At first I had in mind
to become a biologist.
I cannot recall
what made me study people,
if you don't mind me saying so.
Where's the money?
You cannot have spent it all?
What I got for the grand piano
is in the postal bank.
On what bank account?
Nine, zero ... , zero, zero, six, two.
Who's account is that?
The fund raise for the leprous.
The leprous ...
Where is the great piano?
At a piano shop.
The furniture?
At a buyer's.
If I can get that money,
will you show me?
I want it back.
- You don't have that money.
- I must have it all back!
Well, if you meet me early Monday morning,
with the money.
Honestly, do you have the money?
Search me if you wish.
Bloody hell.
Leave my pockets alone!
I've made phone calls
to everyone I know.
I'm short of 470 crowns .
There is a person
who might help you.
Who?
- No ... that would be improper.
- No, tell me. Who?
- No, I've changed my mind.
- Don't you trust me to pay him back?
- That's not the cause.
- What then?
Do you think he'll refuse?
'She' rather.
Does she have that money?
Ask her.
Wouldn't she find it odd, if I ...?
You ask her.
I don't need any money.
This fella has something to say.
She must think it's odd that I ...
She might misunderstand.
Please, Nisse, you ask her.
He needs money.
470 crowns.
Tell her why. What for.
To buy back his furniture
I stole from him.
- Can you get it for him?
- Tell her I will of course pay her back.
If you accompany me.
Is she in favour?
«He understood nothing.»
«We took a taxi from the Central Station.»
«Steva said we'd only stick to persons in cars.
Easier that way.»
«A great deal of car going that night.»
«First I bought her a bottle
at Norrmalm's Square;»
«for 25 crowns .. that I had to pay;»
«or should I say, Krister.»
«To provide Steva with customers was easy.»
«They swarmed like flies around her.»
«She could be choosy.»
«We were at Djurgården twice.»
«once at Lill-Jansskogen, »
«next to the gasometer»
«I saw her through the rear window.»
«Then once at the Engelbrekt Church.»
«She did it twice in the car.
Then I had to step outside.»
«She told them I'd let the dog loose,
if they tried to cheat her.»
«I once made use of you, Ray.»
«When a queer turned up
and insinuated that I ...»
«When I returned with you, he ran off.»
«We took a taxi downtown.»
«It was already light.»
«All the doves were cooing.»
Dammit, my back is aching.
If you want me to go upstairs,
you'll have to carry me.
And this bloody dog.
He should be put to death!
Carry me!
No bloody pimp must ever kick me!
Give me my money,
that I have earned.
The Money!
Shall we leave it there?
You said it's yours.
I won't pick it up.
Pick it up!
How much is it?
490.
Check her bag.
Not a penny!
What'll Krister say about this?
Krister!
He's the one to have the money.
I know another funny story,
about Bellman.
Ask him!
Come, let's go ask him.
Do you know what time it is?
You cannot be so drunk
that you've forget all about time.
Join us.
We'll deliver the money now.
You needed money.
There is 20 crowns too much.
Give it to Steva.
She's fixed them for you.
I don't know how to thank you.
I ...
I never thought this of you, Krister.
So that's your dark side.
Will you turn the whole Pension
into a brothel?
Steva is just a start.
And Nisse.
Because he sold your old furniture,
he too must work for you.
You was only thinking
of the furniture.
Your sole concern
was the furniture.
You might think that I will consent
to let my doll work in the streets for you.
You bloody pimp!
What's the big deal?
I'll get the money back.
I know another funny story,
about Bellman.
Get it back!
Dreamer!
You'll never have a penny.
On the contrary!
You nit-wit!
Had I only known.
What about me?
I cannot accept it.
I'm sorry, but I cannot.
What do you mean 'sorry'?
How about some gratitude?
I had a hell of a time getting it,
and now, nobody wants it.
Do you think I'll accept bribes?
This is so yucky
it makes me puke.
And afterwards
I don't even get a 'thank you'.
On the contrary.
So, the whole thing was in vain.
If you think you can get out of this,
you are so wrong.
I'll call the police!
I must thank you for the lesson
you've given me, Nisse.
I realize I don't know
that much about myself ...
or about life.
I had no idea
that I had these depths inside of me.
You have opened my eyes.
You earn the credit for that.
So, I want to thank you.
Hell.
So you'll start to whine.
What cause do you have to whine?
And I?
What should I do?
«- What time is it?
- Almost five o'clock a.m.»
«No use going to bed.»
Do you think Egon went to the cops?
Where's Krister?
That bloody guy.
I tried to help that pig.
Idiot!
You started it all,
by the way.
- Would you stop spilling the Brännvin!
- You cannot master me.
Buy your own booze
if you fancy it.
Sunday morning.
- You bloody whore.
- Bog off, wanker!
You bloody would if I'd let you!
Ray. There boy, come to me.
I would prefer you, Ray.
Do it, Ray.
It's for free!
Not for you.
What I want I take.
Do that! Do rape me!
You are all the same.
Stop shouting!
I'd better undress right away.
I want it too. It's my Brännvin.
Give it me!
- Give her a draught.
- Isn't she drunk enough already?
If you'll screw me
I'll have to be drunk first.
«That's enough.
Fish, relieve her from the bottle!»
«So, my little boys are shy?»
«I can wake the other boys up
to increase your number.»
«Then you might be less shy.»
«I don't care.»
One more or less is of no importance.
Not when little boys are fiddling me.
I don't feel it anyhow.
I'll never notice
if you are there or not.
But I demand a bed.
Remember that!
And a mattress.
I'm so dead tired
of laying on the ground!
No way that Egon will call the cops.
Do you think he will?
Well, are you fit for it?
Do you think you're capable?
Here's nothing to be found.
Pyret, get the tweezers.
Yes you hit!
Fine, you bloody sadist!
You're capable, when you can beat a naked girl?
Is this all you can do?
- That's a bloody sewer you've got.
- But it still makes you darn horny!
Don't spill your chances.
Pyret, go and get a bed.
But remove the mattress.
Ray, come here boy!
What's the matter?
Come here, Ray.
Come.
- I don't know how he ...
- Then show him.
«She had to pay the whole bill.»
«She had to pay for what she did to Krister ...
and for what I did to him.»
«She had to pay for my bad sides
and for Krister's bad sides.»
«And all of it was entangled
and simultaneous.»
Leave us alone!
Who was that?
Was it Jingis?
Don't come closer!
You'd better get dressed.
They are here.
Now you'll get nailed.
You'll have to deliver some answers.
Serves you right, you piece of shit.
No, wrong guys.
That's the guy;
in the bed.
Leave me alone.
Let me sleep.
Who are you?
Have a guess.
Do they look like charity nurses?
This boy have produced
severe accusations against you.
We are obliged
to make an investigation.
She earned 500 crowns to him.
490.
What difference does it make
in this situation?
I accompanied her
when she made the money.
She felt lonely.
See!
I told you.
You cannot do this, Nisse.
You cannot.
You wreck for everyone.
Don't worry, Krister.
I'll help you!
No, Jingis. No, please!
Seize him!
Wait. Wait!
They blamed me for everything.
They didn't blame me
for his death, though.