[A convenience store in Gangnam, Seoul]
Jae Suk, shouldn't you
take your glasses off?
I think it's better if I leave it on.
You look less like you
if you take them off.
I like them on!
[What are they planning?]
[Secretly... and greatly]
[Disguise]
[Undercover]
You'll start working after
putting on a disguise.
If someone recognizes you
and calls out your name
it's game over.
- It's not the right timing...
- They're here!
They probably think
they just look similar.
[Undercover part-time job,
100 percent real!]
[Will they get caught...
or succeed...]
[A nerve-racking mission]
[Undercover Yoo Jae Suk,
what's his fate?]
[A sunny day...]
[A lovely picnic area
at Han River park]
- Hello!
[What's this?]
What's this?
[Snacks]
Since you are university students,
have a seat and eat.
University students?
You're so casual.
You've got to have
an apple in the morning!
We had a great meal last time,
thanks to Jong Kook.
Oh yeah, that's right!
[Last week, Jong Kook paid
for the crew's dinner.]
Can't you take out 1,000 won?
- Thank you!
- Oh yeah, Jong Kook paid!
Are we university students?
Today, we will have a race with young
guests that make your hearts flutter.
I'm the only youth here.
You're thirty-one!
- Am I not not considered a youth?
- Your face isn't youthful!
Aren't I the only one?
Your face is so wrinkly,
what are you talking about?
[Aged Giraffe]
There are guests joining the race today...
The guests will be here then.
Are there any female guests?
Who is it?
[We will meet them now.]
[The young guests are approaching
underneath the sunlight.]
- Is that...
- Is that Ji Hyo?
[Guest number one, Lee Dong Wook.]
[With different characters, he showed his
top acting skills in movies and dramas.]
[An actor with sixteen years of experience
and the eyes of a young boy.]
[Fourth year at Running University.
Wants to hang out with freshmen.]
Is it Dong Wook?
It's Seo Jun!
[Guest number two, Park Seo Jun.]
[An actor that is on screen everywhere]
[from movies and dramas
to advertisements!]
[He's shown us his full potential
as a young star.]
[Second year at Running University.
Most handsome student.]
It's Yura!
Hello!
[Guest number three, Yura.]
[From a member of
the girl group Girl's Day]
[she broadened her boundaries
as an actress!]
[She's developing her potentials.]
[First year at Running University.
'May Queen' of the Running campus.]
- Hi!
- Hello!
[The two couples have arrived.]
- Yura!
It's Seo Jun!
[The picnic area became brighter]
[with their visit...]
Hello!
[It's been a while!]
[This is the spirit of a young man!]
Before, Kwang Soo was
sitting next to me.
And it feels so different.
[Same spot, different aura]
That's youth right there.
This is youth.
They're not that much
younger than me!
Seo Jun is like family now.
- Is this your third time?
- It's my fourth.
- Dong Wook is here often too.
- At Macao!
[Bungee-jumping at Macao.]
Why did you do it?
No one wanted to do it
so I thought I would be cool.
I hesitated a little,
but Han Hye Jin
and Song Ji Hyo jumped right
after me without hesitation.
[Sad...]
We will be having a mission
for the young people
who are stressing from school studies,
preparing for employment
and are tired of working part-time,
called the 'Beautiful Youth Race.'
[Running Man's special support!]
Beautiful youth.
[A special project for
the young who are tired of]
[school, employment,
and part-time jobs.]
[From an undercover mission]
[to visiting universities!]
[The Youth Guide To The 21st Century]
[Starting now!]
[Running university liberal arts
vs. Science Department.]
Did anyone have a part-time job
when they were younger?
- Part-time job?
- Yes, I have.
I used to work at the entrance
of Ewha Womans University.
I had an hourly wage of 800 won.
I used to work in a pub.
Popular shoe store in Myeong-dong!
It's best to work in a coffee shop.
A lot of celebrities got scouted
while working in a coffee shop.
- That's me.
- Ji Hyo?
- I got cast while working part-time.
- Really?
There was a small cafe
across the mall.
- Really?
- It's my first time hearing this.
They asked me to help out
for a week, and then I got cast.
[A coincidental part-time job
turned her world upside-down.]
Jung Woo Sung and Lee Jung Jae
were cast while working part-time.
Yura, did you do auditions?
I posted a picture on the internet site
called 'Attractive face.'
It put a selfie as my profile picture.
Many companies contacted me.
- You don't speak in your dialect much.
- Me?
- She does!
- It's cute when she does!
- Do it!
- All the guys will fall for you.
Yura, show us your charm!
[Blank Ji is getting ready.]
Ji Hyo, don't do it!
[No one asked,
why are you doing it...]
[Yura is also getting ready.]
I had a dream!
A dream about a ghost!
[The evolution of charm]
[Yura's charm made
their hearts flutter.]
[Yura is... love.]
[This is charm!]
It's so casual!
The camera man had an instant reaction
- right after she did it.
- It's Kwon Ryul, right?
- The Gyeongsang-do dialect, right?
- Yes.
You're so good!
You will be doing a secret mission.
[A secret mission?]
As soon as we arrive, you have to go
the second floor of the convenience store.
You can't let other people see.
Move as quickly as you can.
[What is the secret mission?]
- We can't be seen?
- Quickly.
[Gangnam, Seoul]
[Somewhere in Yeoksam-dong]
- Hello.
[They're coming in without
knowing anything.]
What could this be?
[Why a convenience store?]
This place is where
most young people
have their part-time job.
Oh, a part-time job at
a convenience store!
You will helping the young people
who work at the convenience store.
While you're on the mission
you'll be standing here.
Three people from each team will
start after putting on a disguise.
If a citizen
recognizes you
and says your name
it's game over.
What if a citizen is about to...
and I do this?
That's violence, so...
- What if they say 'Are you Ji Sang Ryul?'
- Then it doesn't count.
- It has to be your name.
- What if they say 'Are you Jo Woo Jong?'
[100 percent in sync!]
Each person must help five customers.
If there are three customers together,
they count as one group.
You pass when you've helped five times.
You have to count
'Grasshopper' for Jae Suk.
And 'Giraffe' as well.
- And Big Nose.
- We have to include our nicknames.
- We'll include Girl's Day.
- As long as they recognize...
- Girl's Day?
- Then X-Teen should be included, too...
- X-Teen works, too...
- And Smurf.
[There's Leessang, why are you
bringing up the past...]
Those count.
So, does it count if
they say 'Lee Sung Kyung'?
Pardon?
Their love will never die?
[I should just be quiet...]
When you're done,
you come back upstairs.
You'll feel a little upset
if you succeed though.
Was I only worth this much?
They don't really stare
at convenience stores.
But more than your face
- they recognize your voice.
- My voice is slightly noticeable.
That's true.
You shouldn't talk.
[He changed his voice,
but it's a fail...]
Say, 'It's 4,500 won.'
- It's 4,500 won, hello.
- That's it.
[That's more suspicious...]
People really don't know me.
They don't know that it's Lee Dong Wook,
they usually say 'Lee Dong Gook.'
I'm serious.
No way!
Dong Wook!
[Who will win
the convenience store mission?]
[Kim Jong Kook, Ha Ha, Lee Kwang Soo vs.
Ji Suk Jin, Lee Dong Wook, Yoo Jae Suk]
Which one of the three will go first?
I'm the least noticeable one, right?
Your arm...
[His muscles are too big
for scanning bar-codes.]
I could just be someone
who likes to work out!
Up to a certain point!
[He's too crazy about working out.]
[First challenger, Kkuk!]
He's going down.
He's already suspicious!
His walk is already suspicious!
[He arrived at the cash register.]
[His first time working part-time]
[at a convenience store.]
- How do I scan?
- First, press this.
[Just then, two female
customers arrived!]
[The first customers' visit
made him nervous.]
[He puffs his cheeks up so
that they don't recognize him.]
[Sigh]
[While the two customers
are picking their items...]
You have to act natural.
You don't want them to...
[He's blabbering out of nervousness.]
He's too obvious!
Why does he have
his hands in his pockets?
His hands are awkward.
Just pick your nose instead!
It's just Jong Kook.
But if the customers don't look up...
They can't imagine that
a celebrity will be here.
He's acting so weird!
[Awkward, awkward]
[I'm so nervous.]
Don't cross your arms!
He thinks that he's being casual!
[I'm doing a good job...]
[It's finally check-out time.]
[The distance between
them is fifty centimeters.]
[Will Kkuk be able to handle
the situation, casually?]
[Puff]
[They place the items on the counter,
without any suspicion.]
Please call his name!
They might see his arms
and be too scared to look up.
[Just then, she lifts her head up!]
[All eyes are on him.]
[He scans the bar-codes
without looking up.]
[Will Kkuk fail the mission?]
[Did she recognize Kkuk?]
[She didn't!]
She should have seen him!
Jong Kook can't scan well.
[Scrambling]
Would you like a bag?
That will be 8,900 won.
[He should have said
something after scanning.]
He's not talking at all!
[He isn't talking just
in case he gets caught.]
Thank you, come again.
[Eventually, they never found out!]
They didn't recognize him!
[Kkuk passed with his first customer.]
That's cheating!
They usually look at
the items or the scanner.
- They don't look at the person.
- I'm like that too.
[Just then!
The second customer is approaching!]
[He approaches without hesitation.]
[He doesn't look.]
I think the other employee
is doing very well.
[Thanks to his over-friendly co-worker]
[Kkuk doesn't have to say a word.]
[He doesn't stare during the check-out]
[or so we thought!]
[His eyes are fixed on Kkuk!]
[Does Kkuk's challenge end, here?]
[He takes his change and leaves.]
[He lets out a big breath
as soon as he leaves.]
It's good, there's a possibility.
Wow, this is so interesting.
[He finally catches a breath.]
[And another customer walks in, but...]
It's a foreigner!
Wow...
[He's so lucky...]
It's foreigner.
Thank goodness.
Hi!
[He's fixing his hat?]
[Full of confidence]
[He gets a point for free.]
[Huh?
He's laughing?]
- I think he recognized him!
- Why did he lift his hat up?
[But it's still a foreigner...]
[He can't possibly recognize him...]
- It'll be 5,300 won.
- Yes.
Oh, he can speak Korean?
[You can tell he has a lot
of experience just by his 'yes.']
- Do you know how to speak Korean?
- Yes.
[He immediately lowered his hat.]
[He pushes his hat down.]
[Scramble, scramble]
[Is he taking a picture
with his phone?]
- He needs to take it!
- He's out as soon as he takes it!
He's flustered!
Have a nice day!
- Bye.
- Let's take a picture.
[He got caught!]
Yay! He was careless!
One moment of carelessness and he failed!
Pic... picture...
Just take the picture!
Of course.
[It's not a fail because
he didn't say his name?]
One, two, three.
[From his pronunciation to his
selfie pose, he's just so Korean...]
- Fail!
- He didn't say my name!
You're Kim Jong Kook, right?
[The foreigner cleared up
the entire situation.]
How did you know?
Do you work around here?
What kind of work do you do?
- I work at a company.
- Really? You speak so fluently.
All right, thank you.
[Kkuk, fail]
What were you doing?
[Mr. Capable's shoulders look shabby.]
[Ashamed]
All foreigners in Gangnam speak Korean.
I was so surprised.
[Who knew he would be better
at Korean than Kwang Soo...]
I was trying to make it funnier because
he was a foreigner, but he kept laughing.
- Good job.
- He had his camera out.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Good job!
I'm so glad!
I said, 'He didn't say my name!'
and he comes back and asks,
'You're Kim Jong Kook, right?'
[Kkuk succeeded with two customers.]
[The next challenger is Big Nose.]
- Okay, good!
- Don't try to stick out!
I won't!
[The oldest part-timer is]
[going to work.]
He's very casual!
He looks like the boss.
When someone beautiful
walks in, he'll say
'You're so beautiful.'
He can't help himself.
[He's finally at the counter.]
How do you scan?
[The newcomer is being taught.]
[Less than a minute later,
his first customer arrived.]
[While she isn't paying attention.]
[He changes his face
by puffing up his cheeks.]
[Will she recognize him?]
I don't think she knows.
The customers don't
really look up much...
[Her gaze is following Big Nose!]
[Press change, then press cash.]
[She seemed like she was looking]
[but she turned her head away.]
[Did she see?
I think she saw...]
- Thank you.
- Thank you, come again.
[They left as soon as he was done.]
[Did they not recognize me?]
He's slightly hurt!
[He succeeded with his first customer,
but he's sighing for some reason...]
- I'm not that recognizable, right?
- Pardon?
- Yes.
- Right?
[Just then, she comes back!]
She came back!
[She was finished
with her check-out.]
[Why is she back?]
[The woman who didn't recognize me...]
[She's coming closer...]
[Huh? She isn't interested.]
[I'm still hungry.]
[Oh, that's what it was...]
[It's a relief, but he
still looks a little sad.]
[Don't cry...]
[His second customer
came to buy a drink.]
He's looking!
[He's somewhat familiar...]
It's 1,000 won.
[Big Nose's face must
be pretty common.]
It's 1,000 won.
[An incomplete voice
change just brings sneers.]
Why is he doing that?
He shouldn't do that kind of things!
He thinks he sounds perfect!
[His third customer doesn't
show any signs either.]
[The next customer is
waiting for check-out.]
[Peek]
[He looked!]
[He looks, and looks again.]
[Fixed gaze]
Maybe he's just in a hurry.
- A bag, please.
- Yes.
- I'll get it for you.
- No, I can get it.
Thank you.
[His fourth customer left
without recognizing him.]
I think he just stared
because he was slow.
The way he looked at him was
'What's wrong with this guy...'
'Why is he so sluggish?'
[Lift]
He lifted his hat up!
Did you see him casually
lifting his hat up?
[He's getting a little restless.]
Hello.
[Huh!
This person is...]
[The person who is
scanning my sandwich...]
[is it him?]
He can't take his eyes off him!
Press enter!
Please sign here.
It's my first day.
[What's that?]
I told him not to do that!
[He still doesn't recognize me?]
That will be 2,550 won.
Why does he talk like that?
- What is he doing?
- I'm not sure...
- Do you need a bag?
- No.
- Thank you, come again.
- He's lifting his hat up!
- Look at him.
- He's sliding it up slowly.
[Before, After]
Here you go.
Are you all together?
He keeps talking, on purpose.
He's talking more and more.
[By any chance]
Are you a celebrity?
Are you Ji Suk Jin?
[He called his name?]
He said impala before.
[He failed the mission
with a big smile.]
I look like him, right?
- Press subtotal.
Thank you.
[For recognizing me.]
You have a big nose.
[He failed, but he feels
good about this situation.]
We saw you lifting your hat up!
This is what you did.
[Fidget, fidget]
As time passes by,
you start to get slightly hurt...
And then he started talking more,
all of a sudden.
I thought I was going to succeed.
[The point of this observation was
to see Suk Jin's change of mind.]
- The point was his change of mind.
- You do get hurt!
After you were caught,
you smiled so big.
Ha Ha is just Ha Ha.
[No matter how much he disguises
himself, he's just Ha Ha.]
Ha Ha, please go down quickly
to help more customers.
When you go down...
I think you'll get caught going down.
Wearing it is better!
- Just be casual!
- I'll go down now.
[Ha Ha tries the most casual look.]
Good luck!
He's going!
[He just looks like Ha Ha.]
His walking is already so natural.
[He casually walks to the counter
as if he usually does.]
[He came, but he doesn't know what to do.]
- Would you like a bag?
- Yes.
[He quickly gets a bag.]
[He places the items in skillfully.]
[He's like a professional.]
He's good.
Ha Ha's good.
[He passed his first customer
so casually.]
They're looking at him as they leave.
[A heated gaze that makes him sweat.]
[Did Ha Ha fail on his first try?]
[Ha Ha, who didn't even disguise.]
[Is it him or not?]
[They left!]
That was so risky!
Ha Ha's so good,
he's like an actual part-timer.
Ha Ha's great!
Instead of sticking out
he's keeping it natural.
[There are still a lot of customers.]
[He calmly continues his task.]
[He passed with his second customer.]
[He scans the bar-codes, calculates
the subtotal, and takes care of change.]
[He adapted to the part-time job!]
[He is a hard working man indeed.]
[The king of part-time job,
Ha Ha succeeded in a flash!]
[Ace, Lee Dong Wook is
up for the challenge.]
People really don't know!
They usually say Lee Dong Gook!
[He sends off a foreigner
with quick hands.]
[When there are too
many female customers]
[and it gets risky]
[he stays in the corner
without standing out.]
[He responds based on
the type of customer!]
Thank you, come again!
Have a nice day.
[Lee Dong Gook succeeded!]
I think Jae Suk will get caught.
Jae Suk, shouldn't you
take your glasses off?
Is it better with them on or off?
- You look less like you with them off.
- I like them on!
- Just like Ha Ha...
- I can't recognize you like that!
[He successfully made his eyes big.]
It doesn't look like you, but it's weird.
You're so ugly.
I'll be back.
I don't think he should wear glasses.
[Run]
[He moves, casually
and without hesitation.]
It's not the right timing!
[Jae Suk gets to the counter safely.]
[Finally, his first customer arrived!]
[Huh?
That man...]
Oh my!
[He hasn't scanned one bar-code yet...]
- Yoo Jae Suk?
- Hello.
This isn't it...
How did they know?
- I'll help you do this...
- Please go up.
Yes, sorry about that.
Have a good day.
[He failed in thirty seconds.]
Not even one person!
[Devastated]
I'm embarrassed!
How did they know?
How did you know?
Wow... how did you...
How did he know?
I didn't even get to scan once!
I swear he didn't know...
I told you to take your glasses off!
- I should have done something...
- You need to take them off.
- I was so surprised...
- It doesn't matter.
I laughed, without realizing.
- If you didn't laugh...
- It just came out!
I was about to scan
and he called my name!
[The last challenger is Giraffe.]
[He's showing his team a new look.]
- Do it, do it!
- I didn't know it was you!
[Who are you?]
[A big laugh you can
get from a tissue.]
[It's a hit item.]
It's amazing!
[He puts on his hat, glasses,
and the tissue.]
- Thank you.
- Lower down!
[He lowers himself so that
he doesn't get caught.]
[Wide open]
Hello, welcome to Seven.
[His first customers are group of six.]
We have iced drip coffee.
Don't say that!
[His pronunciation is weird.]
Welcome to Seven,
we have iced drip coffee.
That will be 7,200 won.
[A female customer approaches
like she found something.]
[Stare, stare]
Get caught, get caught.
Please get caught!
Get caught, get caught!
[She just stares
without saying anything.]
You must have back pain.
[Did he recognize him?]
[Will he fail the mission?]
Yes, I have back pains.
Thank you.
He didn't know?
Welcome to Seven,
we have iced drip coffee.
Don't talk like that.
- Was that Kwang Soo?
- Yes.
Why is he doing that?
- It's going well.
- They probably don't know him.
[Will they recognize Kwang Soo?]
They're middle-aged men.
It's 3,000 won.
I think he'll pass more than two.
Two people won't be bad.
[The third customer appeared
from nowhere.]
I hope she recognizes him.
[He's busy bending his knees
and care about the tissue ball.]
- How come they don't know?
- Thank you.
We didn't think he could
trick three customers.
Kwang Soo lasts longer than we thought.
[Giraffe is drinking water.]
[Oh, no, I had a tissue ball
in my mouth...]
[No way...]
That's dirty!
[It's not like he's acting
for a horror movie.]
[Oh my god.]
[At that moment,
the fourth customer appears.]
[Embarrassed, embarrassed]
[He forgot to bend his knees.]
Lower your legs!
- Your legs!
- Lower them!
No way, is he going to pass?
He doesn't look at his fact at all.
[The fourth customer
didn't look at his face.]
You need to act confidently.
- It feels really good when you succeed.
- Do you need a bag?
I couldn't feel that even once.
[Even the fourth customer
passed him without noticing.]
He's the last customer.
He might succeed at it.
[Huh?]
[All of a sudden, the customer
looks at Kwang Soo.]
Please, please, please!
[Please, get caught!]
[What is he looking at?]
[It's the screen.]
[He was just checking the price.]
[Really?]
It's a miracle.
[No one expected Kwang Soo would do it.]
Which means people don't
pay attention to the cashier.
- Thank you.
- He did it!
He succeeded at it.
[He come back confidently.
Giraffe is here!]
That was awesome!
They looked at me
because I'm weird-looking.
You look so old!
[Giraffe's unbelievable success.
What are the current scores?]
[Department of liberal arts: 12
Department of science: 9]
['C' cafe in Chungdam-dong]
- Did you enjoy your meal?
- Yes.
It looks good on Gary.
That's perfect!
I think I've seen a man like this.
[Fighter in the Wind in a bob]
Customer number 108.
Two macchiatos are ready.
You're too scary.
Wear something different.
[They recommend a stylish hat.]
Gary!
I think you'll score the least.
[A stylish hat]
[and eye glasses]
[It's hair-raising!]
- I think you look fine.
- Gary looks nice.
Gary, are you going to go?
[Gary will be the first one.]
I hope you trick five customers!
I thought he wasn't on my team.
- Look, he looks different.
- Since he's not here...
let me ask who's the ugliest person.
[He doesn't hesitate,
but casually walks to the cafe.]
He's in!
Gary's in!
[His visual is even more
striking in the cafe.]
But he doesn't seem nervous.
I think he's going to act bold.
It won't be easy not to laugh for them.
Maybe they don't know he's Gary.
They're thinking who is this guy?
Gary looks like a guy next door.
No, he's rather ugly.
He looks like someone
in the history textbook.
- Who's he?
- I don't know.
The other workers are asking
each other who Gary is.
Really?
[They're so close, but still don't know.]
That's so funny.
Even the other workers
ask who that guy is.
They don't know.
The customers think it's just his style.
What kind of style is that?
Is this 'The Truman Show'?
Maybe everyone there
is making fun of him.
It's not going to be busy
as the convenience store.
- Is anyone here yet?
- Yes, coming!
Number 24...
the beverage you ordered is ready.
Number one, your beverage
and bagel are ready.
- It's Kang Gary's voice!
- He just spoke!
[He didn't even change his voice.]
[The moment of destiny!]
[Will he able to give it to
the customer without getting noticed?]
[Oh, he did it!]
[He passed the first customer.]
That doesn't make a sense!
- He's taking it to his table!
- Wow, he has guts!
He's serving.
- He saw Gary's face.
- But he doesn't recognize him.
How is this possible?
[It's like he's revealing
that he's Gary.]
He talks like a DJ.
[They can't imagine it's Gary.]
No one knows he's Gary.
Your bagel is here.
He's striking.
This is too weird.
To my eyes, it's obvious.
Doesn't he look like himself
more that I was?
You see guys like him in some cafes.
Number seven, your beverage
and bagel are ready.
That's definitely Gary's voice.
- It's his fourth customer.
- Just one more customer, and he's done.
Enjoy.
- Wow!
- That's incredible!
[He gets back the buzzer
and gives her the food.]
Number nine,
your beverage is ready.
[This time, two men walk toward Gary.]
[If he passes through these customers]
[he can complete the mission!]
[Will he be able to succeed?]
[He doesn't feel out of place at all...]
[They don't doubt him at all
and he passes it through.]
Gary completes his mission!
- This is weird.
- We didn't expect it.
It's weird.
I honestly thought it's too obvious.
You're right.
- No one's suspicious.
- It's ridiculous!
The customers are too generous.
This area is really interesting!
Who will try next?
Go ahead, Seo Jun.
[The handsome boy, Park Seo Jun]
No one doubted me.
Even the workers...
- They don't know who I am.
- They asked who you are.
- They think I'm a new worker.
- They asked each other.
I forgot this was the mission,
and I was working hard.
[Seo Jun is getting ready.]
Seo Jun!
- It doesn't look like you.
- But you're handsome!
People will look at you.
He's handsome, but they won't
be able to tell who he is.
[He's wearing a hat and glasses.]
Seo Jun walks bravely.
I don't know if he'll be able to pass.
[As soon as Seo Jun opens the door]
[this place becomes a flower boy cafe.]
[What an eye candy!]
Look, the ladies here
started to look at him.
These people just said
he looks like Park Seo Jun.
They are looking at him carefully.
The three ladies right here...
They were served by Gary.
They turned around to look at him.
People are only interested
in handsome people.
[Why are they more excited than him?]
No one will recognize me
even if I work here all day.
See?
They're still looking.
- Did he already serve one person?
- Is she an elementary student?
He passed through one customer!
[It's like an art book
even if he's not posing.]
They're searching on the internet
with the keyword 'Park Seo Jun.'
They've only searched.
She's pointing a finger at him.
She pointed a finger!
[Will his identity be revealed?]
But they're not really sure.
Why would he be working here?
They would have doubted
if there was a camera around.
- They think he looks like him.
- If they ask his phone number...
That'll be funny.
I kind of feel sad they look at Seo Jun
as soon as he enters.
People still would have looked
even if he wasn't a celebrity.
It's natural to look
at beautiful people.
[So handsome!]
- He passed four people.
- Already?
[A man enters the cafe at this moment.]
He'll complete the mission
if he can pass this customer.
[Seo Jun gives him what he
ordered and he take it out.]
He's succeeded!
Wow, he didn't get caught!
[A girl in a uniform
enters the cafe...]
[and she has bob hair?]
[A wig, glasses, and a hat.]
[It's perfect!]
[And a girl with long hair enters after.]
[She only wears a hat.]
[Yura and Ji Hyo went
to work at the same time.]
A customer is here!
Welcome.
How can I help you?
That's just Ji Hyo's voice.
Why didn't she change her voice?
They can tell right away.
Is she really taking orders?
Please discard the receipt for me.
She asks her to discard the receipt,
but doesn't look at her face.
They're good at acting.
They're talking to each other so much!
[But she doesn't recognize Ji Hyo.]
How can you not recognize Ji Hyo?
- They don't know.
- They don't know Ji Hyo?
Please, wait a moment.
[Yura and Ji Hyo are
working like a real employees.]
Even Ji Hyo and Yura doesn't seem
like they're doing the mission.
I think we need to work harder.
I think they forgot the mission.
[Dance, dance]
Yura is dancing.
I think she hopes for them
to recognize her.
She seems like it.
[Look at me!]
Yura is dancing.
She must have felt sad.
She's Ji Suk Jin among idols.
[She hopes her fans
will recognize her.]
Ji Hyo is holding her face up.
Song Ji Hyo!
Why did she wear a wig?
- I'll give you a buzzer.
- The weather's very hot, isn't it?
The weather's very hot, isn't it?
Yes.
[A pretty girl greeted me.]
[But he doesn't recognize Yura.]
By any chance...
[He comes back and asks...]
[Who did he recognize between the two?]
[Ji Hyo?]
[or Yura?]
[While everyone is holding
their breath, he talks...]
Do you have a bigger straw?
[A straw?]
[It's disappointing.]
Hope you enjoy!
- Hope you enjoy!
- Thanks.
Yura said it because she
wanted him to recognize her.
- She almost screamed.
- Hope you enjoy!
People won't be able to recognize us
even if we all go together.
[They might or might not know
even if they wear big name tags.]
They wouldn't notice
even if four of us work there.
This is shocking.
Can we let Suk Jin do it?
They're here. They're whispering.
They don't notice at all.
- Even when you talk to them.
- Let me see your face.
Yura and Ji Hyo spoke as usual.
I even asked if the weather is hot.
He answered back with 'yes.'
Then are we lost?
So the Science Department scored 22...
and the department of
liberal arts scored 19.
The Science Department won.
We won, but we're not very happy.
[It's time to go meet the youths.]
- We're in team uniforms.
- Now, it feels like Running Man.
You have a choice.
One team will go to
the universities on the east.
Sungshin Women's University,
Kyunghee University, and Korea University.
The three school are
close to each other.
And the other team
will go to the west.
Ewha Womans University,
Yonsei University, and Hongik University.
I went to Korea University many times.
Then you can go to
the schools in west.
- Then the Red Team will go to the east.
- We'll do that.
Let's go!
[Let's go to the campuses of youths!]
We'll leave now.
Can you move your seat a little?
We'll go to Ewha Womans University first.
- Ewha Womans University?
- What will it be?
They say we'll recruit a lot.
I think it'll be a power game.
- Maybe it's tug-of-war.
- I think so, too.
Maybe it's a group name tag elimination.
That's possible too.
Really?
Dong Wook, you got to know
about Suk Jin today.
I'm from the same town.
Oh, you are?
Yes, I told you that three years ago.
Wasn't my answer the same too?
Isn't that why you got goosebumps?
Honestly, Yura has the best figure
out of all the idols.
Of course, she insured her legs.
Really?
The insurance is not for anyone.
Before, Lee Hye Young
insured her legs.
You can insure only a part of your body?
Only when it's like a dream.
When they're second to none.
- Like Yura's legs...
- So her legs are matchless.
They are the best.
- Do they run in your family?
- My mom has the same legs.
Wow, that's amazing!
Seo Jun said 'that's amazing!'
That's a family treasure!
When Seo Jun say stuff like that,
you need to say no more.
I don't know if you noticed, but
Seo Jun keeps talking about you.
I don't know why I'm trying to appeal.
I must have fallen for
you before I knew.
- Is she number one for you?
- Yes.
- How old are you, Seo Jun?
- 28.
- Yura is...
- 24.
- She's 24.
- That's perfect.
Four year difference?
That's fantastic.
Seo Jun, this is good!
They say that a four years difference
are a match made in heaven.
- Don't we need to exchange numbers?
- We need to open a chat room.
- I like that.
- Under 'family' category.
We've already exchanged
numbers with Seo Jun.
Then, the second brother is
going to be the operator.
Be the operator, Second Brother.
Am I being too obtuse?
I came here a lot for blind dates.
I'll announce the rule.
Find a student who's attending
Ewha Womans University.
Just one student.
Make sure you check the student's ID
and bring them to the appointed spot.
Who has money?
No one has cash?
They're delicious.
Chicken skewer!
Wow, that looks good!
A lot of people are following us.
Hello!
Aren't you students of
Ewha Womans University?
Hello!
[He greets them in a loud voice.]
- You look so excited.
- I think he's enjoying it.
Hello!
[You know me, right?]
Suk Jin has a lot of memory
at Ewha Womans University.
I had a part-time job around
this area when I was twenty.
I had a date here.
At that chicken restaurant!
- Oh, here?
- Oh, it's this cafe.
It's here, if you go down the stairs
there's a cafe.
I used to work here.
It's been more than twenty years ago.
I was paid 800 won per hour.
I think they're the students of Ewha.
800 won per hour.
I don't know where
the final mission site is
but the person has to be at the place.
So let's be careful.
It's almost like a press conference.
She looks nice.
- Which school do you attend?
- Ewha Womans University.
- Are you free tonight?
- Yes, I am.
What were you planning to do?
We were going to practice
for a talent show.
- What talent show?
- We're going to be at a music camp.
- We're from the music department.
- Going on a music camp?
What are you practicing?
Can you show us a bit?
It's a dance to the song 'Why You.'
One, two, three, four!
How come you don't know yet?
You didn't practice it yet, right?
This is such an old song!
That's true.
We don't know where it is,
but this evening
only one person can come.
I recommend her.
You recommend her?
Let's take her.
- Let's just go together.
- Do you have free time?
Yes.
[If they complete the group mission,
they can invite her to the final site.]
[The Science Department arrived
at Sungshin Women's University.]
This is where the students of
Sungshin visit the most.
The air surely feels different here.
My heart is fluttering.
It feels different than
when we were at the cafe.
- Which school do you go to?
- I go to Kookmin University.
- It's Chung-Ang University.
Which school do you go to?
Not here?
- Which school do you go to?
- Sungshin University.
Can I see your student ID?
- I don't have it with me.
- No?
Do you have your student ID?
[They've found a student with an ID.]
Let me check your ID.
Majoring in Korean Literature.
No Yoon Jae.
What are you planning
to do this evening?
If you can't come this evening,
we can't take you.
Nothing much.
[They challenge the mission right away.]
Give us the mission!
Please, pick one, Yoon Jae.
She picked the blue one.
Please open it, one, two, three!
'Egg embracing the sticker'?
What's that?
Put an egg on a disk with stickers.
Move the disk until
the egg gets all the stickers.
Wait until the previous runner
finishes it, then take turns.
- Put the stickers upside down.
- It's hard!
- This is hard!
- How can we finish it in sixty seconds?
- We need to roll the egg.
- How is it possible?
- This is difficult!
- All three stickers?
Start!
- Just like that!
- No!
[A narrow escape!]
I flipped it.
[Carefully, carefully]
[Jong Kook did it.]
[It's Seo Jun's turn.]
[Rolls]
That's it!
[Seo Jun did it smoothly.]
[It's Ha Ha's turn.]
Reverse!
That's right!
Oh, no!
- No!
- You're almost done!
[Their first attempt fails.]
- Fight!
Yoon Jae, cheer up!
You can start it again.
Get ready...
start!
[Mr. Capable gets a grip on it.]
[He succeeds at it calmly.]
He did it!
[It's Seo Jun's turn.]
[Ha Ha attempts again.]
That's right!
[This time, it's nicely done.]
Yura!
Wow, how are you doing that?
[She's done it so fast!]
Good job, Yura!
[It's Yoon Jae, the heroine of
the Science Department.]
- That's good, do it slowly!
- Yoon Jae!
You're almost done!
[She endures the pressure
and succeeds at it.]
Kwang Soo, we can do it this time!
That's right!
[Two of the stickers are on the egg.]
[Only one sticker is left.]
[Kwang Soo successfully did it!]
Success?
Forty-five seconds!
[They completes the mission.]
I'm sweating!
This is a gift certificate
to support youth.
Later, we'll be doing
the final mission. Can you...
You need to come.
- Can you come?
- We won't ask for your phone number.
We just need to trust each other.
It's like a game of friendship,
you know.
- Do you have a boyfriend?
- No.
Maybe you can meet a guy tonight.
- Who's your type?
- Within the Running Man cast?
If you have to pick one.
Based on appearance only?
Then I would pick Kwang Soo...
Think again, he's popular
because he's celebrity.
You didn't see his face?
Why me?
[Is he included in the Running Man?]
I thought I had to pick
from fixed cast members.
Of course, I would pick...
I would pick him every time
I'm reborn, again and again.
- Then, of course, you'll dump him.
- Why do you compare Seo Jun and I?
I'll give this to you now.
- Can you come?
- Yes.
If you can't come, we might lose...
- See you later!
- Good luck!
[The Liberal Arts Department
is carrying out the same mission.]
You did it!
You've succeeded!
We did it!
It was nice.
I'm sorry I called you wrong.
I'm sorry.
We'll give Yu Bin something
to support youth.
Cultural gift certificates
for movies, music, and shopping.
This is for later.
You need to show this
when you come to the final site.
Come to the site.
We still have a final mission.
- Are you good at physical games?
- No problem.
- I think she'll be good.
- Do you keep promises?
Promise me that you'll
come to the site.
We'll see Yu Bin, later.
[The Liberal Arts Department:
Hongik University]
[The Science Department:
Kyunghee University]
[What's their goal this time?]
Are there any students
from Hongik University?
Do you go to Hongik University?
- Do you currently go to the school?
- Yes, you are?
Nice to meet you.
Only students of Hongik University.
I have her.
Come over here.
I found him.
Please come in the middle, students.
- Stand in line.
- I have a good feeling.
They're so handsome!
They all look so good!
These two are a campus couple.
This film will exist forever,
just say that you're good friends.
You don't know what will
happen in the future.
When we suggested to say you're
friends, ' why did you two nod?
We've been through
a lot of crisis together.
- I hope the crisis becomes a chance.
- I hope so too.
Who's prettier?
Yura or your girlfriend?
[Looking]
Yura is...
[He's risking his neck to be honest.]
That's why they're having a crisis!
There's a reason.
- How do you feel about that?
- I feel good.
[Creepy]
Who's handsomer?
Park Seo Jun or your boyfriend?
Park Seo Jun!
[You didn't have to ask that!]
Do you have feelings for each other?
[What's the mission for
the Liberal Arts Department?]
Wreath relay!
The first runner will put
a wreath around the neck.
The second runner has to get
it without using hands.
Repeat the relay until the last runner.
You should finish in sixty seconds.
- In sixty seconds!
- Do you understand?
Put it on your neck and
don't use your hands.
- Will he be able to do it?
- Try it.
I think he can do it.
It might be hard.
He's doing it.
- That's right!
- He did it!
- Let's do it!
- We can do it!
You can be the first runner.
[The Science Department are
ready for the wreath relay.]
Start!
Yura, take it out!
[It's a good start!]
Quickly, quickly!
[The Liberal Arts Department
are starting the relay too.]
This is good!
Just shake it!
[An unique way of relay.]
Take it out!
Lower your head!
[But they're pretty fast!]
Lower your head,
that's right!
Our team work is good!
Very good!
[The good friends are...]
[in perfect harmony!]
- Slowly.
- You can get out now.
[They look like they're
doing a bull fight.]
We're doing fast!
We're good!
[They're rough but good!]
- That's good!
- Just a little bit!
- Get in!
- Incredible!
[The Science Department
are finishing up!]
Okay, great!
Now hang it!
Put it over there
and walk away!
Hang it!
[The both teams finished the mission.]
[The same mission, different style.]
You did it!
[54 seconds]
Wow, it's incredible!
You've done it in 37 seconds!
Good luck!
It was possible because
we're in Kyunghee University!
Kyunghee University!
- See you later!
- Thank you!
This is a gift certificate
to support youth.
And a ticket to the final site.
Please, come to the place
by the time.
Our staff will tell you
where the final site is.
Please come to the spot.
This is the admission ticket.
Please come to the site.
[The Liberal Arts Department:
Yonsei University]
[The Science Department:
Korea University]
Let's go to Korea University.
We're here.
- Let's get off.
- Okay.
[They arrive around the same time.]
How many people should we get here?
[The last chance to invite
the youths for their final mission.]
I wonder how many people...
At first, it was one,
then it was five.
- Ten?
- I think ten.
How many will it be?
- You found ten people, right?
- Yes.
It's t-shirt relay!
For the t-shirt relay,
everyone will stand in a row.
The first runner who's
wearing the t-shirt
and the second runner
will hold both hands
the t-shirt will be moved
to the second runner.
You have sixty seconds.
It'll end when the final runner
wears the t-shirt.
Let's do it!
Just do the same as I'm doing now.
Head to head!
- You have sixty seconds!
- Korea University!
- Let's go!
- Ready!
- I'm nervous!
- Start!
- Go!
- Let's do it!
That's right!
[Mr. Capable and his
teammate did it fast!]
We're fast!
[Struggle]
Watch your head!
[The speed was greatly reduced
when the students are playing.]
- You have to take your head out!
- Take out your head!
Let me talk informally!
Take your head out!
Don't let your hands go!
Head!
It's not important to
keep your hair style!
[It's getting faster.]
Take off your glasses!
[He's taking off his glasses.]
Take it out!
- Seven, six, five...
- We failed.
- Three, two, one.
- It's over.
This won't do.
[What should I do?]
- We need to change the spot.
- Do I need to scold you?
Just look at me carefully!
What I kept saying was
put your arms and head like this.
[It's like a gym class.]
Just put head to head.
You don't have to pull
the t-shirt down!
Don't think about pulling it down.
Who are you going to show it?
[Giraffe is very enthusiastic.]
Make sure you don't hold the t-shirt
when you hold hands.
- Just hold the end of your hands.
- I see!
I'm not going to say it
in words any longer!
Did you see what just happened to me?
This could happen to you!
[After the endless nagging,
they challenge it again.]
Start!
Let's do it!
It's fast!
You need to take it off yourself.
Do it right!
You shouldn't take your head off!
[Their speed is increased.]
That's right!
[This is how Spartans train.]
Come forward!
[Only five runners are left!]
The next person!
Quickly, Yura!
[Seo Jun and Ha Ha did it in a flash.]
[Only Kwang Soo is left.]
Ten, nine...
[They succeeded at t-shirt relay!]
[The perfect harmony of Coach Kkuk's
nagging and the students' passion!]
[Only if all of them can
åcome to the final site?]
[The mission of
the Liberal Arts Department]
- Ji Hyo, hurry up!
- You'll pass if you stand on it.
One, two, three!
[The Liberal Arts Department
succeeded at their mission!]
[They've succeeded at their first try!]
[Will they be able to come
for the final mission?]
[Both teams move to the final spot!]
- Is it sixteen people?
- And we can have an extra member.
The fact having one more person
have an effect...
They're here already.
They're here!
Our teammates!
[Everyone is here already.]
Did you eat anything?
In a short while, we'll
have to fight against them.
I don't know who they are,
but we can win!
[The Science Department
heads to the final site.]
Let's go!
We're one!
[Youth vs. Youth
Who will be the final winner?]
[The final mission site,
Yeouido Park, Seoul]
[A mysterious set
in the middle of the park]
What's this?
What is this for?
Maybe we need to push it.
- We're here!
- Yoon Jae is here.
[The campus couple of Kyunghee University
arrived on time.]
[Welcome, everyone!]
- You're here!
- It's nice to see you again!
[There are a lot of people in
the Liberal Arts Department.]
That many people came already?
[Everybody in the department
of liberal arts came.]
- They're on the way.
- Is that so?
Are you a university student?
He's doing his fifth year in college.
He's majoring in architecture.
[I'm a student.]
[The members of
the Science Department arrived.]
- It's our team members!
- Many of them came.
They look strong.
[They become suddenly strained.]
[Who are you?]
[The members of the department
of science have superpower.]
[You're reliable, teammates!]
Where did they recruit
those strong guys?
You only recruited strong-looking guys?
- I can't say no...
- We can win this!
Can't it be counted as foul?
We only picked cute guys.
[What a cute boy!]
- Is everyone here?
- Yes.
Thank you for coming here, students.
Please don't call them students.
They're our siblings.
We're a family.
We're one.
Then we'll check
how many came here first.
- I think they have more.
- We're missing one.
We have fourteen members.
Fifteen, sixteen.
We have sixteen people.
All members have attended.
How many students are here?
- We have fourteen people.
- We'll start the game on time.
Instead, you've won the chance
to have an additional member.
- That's right!
- You can recruit a student around here.
Are you a college student?
Are you a student?
You looks strong.
[Ha Ha found a strong-looking student.]
He looks very strong.
You're a student, right?
[Their team is in excellent spirit
as they see the newest member.]
Don't be afraid, brothers and sisters!
There's no need to be intimidated.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm a biochemistry major
at Minnesota University.
We're a global team!
Are they allow to recruit
foreign mercenaries?
[There's no boundaries to play a game.]
So you have fifteen members.
The final mission is to
push the metal bar.
The metal bars are attached
to the cylinder behind you.
The team will get one point
when you turn
the metal bar around and get
back to your original spot.
From now on, you can start locating.
[Both teams are having
a meeting to plan strategies.]
I think ten of us should push one bar.
We need to push harder close
to the circumference than center.
We'll tightly stand on the outer side.
[Understood!]
Brothers and sister,
please come over here.
Don't give up.
Let's do it together.
We're a family.
Even though we'll be
scattered after this game
at this moment, we're a family.
- Let's do our best!
- Going down.
No, we'll go up!
One, two, three!
Fight!
All for one, and one for all!
[High in spirit]
[Who will be the final winner?]
[It's time for the final battle!]
- I don't know who will win.
- I'm nervous.
Honestly, I don't want to lose!
This will be the single round match!
- Ready!
- I'm so nervous!
[Who will bring joy to the youths?]
[Push the metal bar, starts!]
[The metal bar is bent?]
- We've pushed it too hard.
- We're too strong.
Why are we so strong?
Did you do too well?
[They can't control their energy!]
[They say things happen
where the youths are.]
[The iron bar is bent!]
[Therefore...]
[we've changed the final mission
with tug-of-war.]
Brothers and sisters, good luck!
The earlier mission
can't be carried out
so we'll replace it with tug-of-war.
Our two members have arrived.
- Are they here?
- Yes.
They can join you.
[What a nice timing!]
This will be two of three!
You will win when the red dot
on the rope goes over the yellow line.
Sit down and grab the rope.
Fight, Red Team!
[The first round will
divide the teams' destiny.]
Ready!
[Will it be the department of
liberal arts tied with friendship?]
[Or the Science Department
armed with physical strength?]
[The first round of tug-of-war starts!]
[Let's go, young men!]
[It's a direct confrontation!]
[But the department of
liberal arts get behind.]
[It's a critical moment!]
[Now is the chance!]
[The Science Department won
the first round of tug-of-war.]
[Soldiers! We won!]
[No one can stop them.]
We have a disadvantage.
We can't help it.
We can win one more round!
We shouldn't lose our pace.
Can we call this one off?
We have a lot more girls.
[We can't give up like this.]
We can do it!
[The second round of tug-of-war]
[Both teams are ready for a combat.]
Fight!
[Will the battle end here?]
[Or will it be turned around?]
[The second round of tug-of-war, starts!]
[The Science Department start
pulling hard from the beginning.]
[He tied the rope around
his waist and crawls!]
[This is the last change for
the Liberal Arts Department.]
[The balance of power between
the two teams was upset.]
[The Liberal Arts Department
are out-muscled.]
[They're slowly dragged
down into defeat.]
[To be pulled or not to be pulled.]
[That is the question.]
[What's the result?]
[The Science Department won.]
[Young men, be happy!]
[The battle field becomes a festival.]
It was impossible for us to win.
[It's fine.
You're still young.]
[Thank you so much!]
You did a good job!
We couldn't help it.
Kim Jong Kook will award
the winning team.
Please, give them
the money to support youth.
[It's an honor.]
[It's a small gift for the youths.]
I'm sorry.
- One by one.
- Don't worry, I'll personally award you.
I'll double the amount.
God Jong Kook!
[He becomes a big fan of Kkuk.]
- Yeah!
- Thank you for doing your best!
- Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you for the students
who came to help here
the citizens we met on the street!
Thank you so much!
Today's winner is
the Science Department!
[The youth will go on.]
[Case number: 150913-1]
[A special case that was requested
by a mysterious client.]
[Kwon Sang Woo]
[Sung Dong Il]
[Two legendary detectives
are here to solve the case.]
[The clue is in the city!]
[You need to solve the case
by using your sixth sense!]
[The story gets revealed
as they find more hints.]
[The huge case that's beyond
your imagination is coming!]
[What's the greatest secret ever hidden?]
[Next week, 'The Legendary Detective.']