All right, let's go.
That's my main man Pierce
coming back from the war!
Thank you! Thank you, man.
Hey, what's happening, Jack?
An unlicenced Club called
"The Blind Pig" serving
booze
Private party.
Pick another card.
There you go!
I see what you're saying.
There we go!
Damn it! Give me that shit.
Party's over!
Here we go. Move on out.
Move on out. Step out! Step out!
Everybody out! Out!
Let's go!
I know you can hear me.
Get the fuck up and go!
I don't care what you do
during the week. Get out!
Party's over! Let's
get it moving!
You know how this works!
Says who?
I'm sorry?
Man, take a hike!
Come in here smelling
like pig juice!
Excuse me, miss.
Thank you so much.
What'd you say?
I ain't said anybody
talking... Hey, man!
Come on, man! Let me
go, man! Let me go!
Hold on a second.
Get the fuck out!
Get out! Get out!
How many times you
want me to say it?
You're moving slow!
Come on, man!
Motherfuckers, man!
Look, Frank, man.
The owner split.
Man, I'm sorry, but
you got a room
full of open warrants
in there. All right?
Just make sure you search the
women, you lazy bastard.
All right. Watch your eyes.
Oh, shit!
You know that's not
right, brother!
No, no, no!
We gotta go through the front.
What? You wanna take these
guys out in public, Sarge?
We have no fucking option.
- Go tell them. Run.
- All right.
- You dirty pig!
- Get the fuck out of here.
Anybody else?
Why're we not moving?
You wanna go next?
Out, out, out!
All right, party's
over, folks. Let's go!
You heard him. Time to move out!
Put your drinks down
and step out the door.
I do not understand, I
thought I was very clear!
Let's go! Come on!
Out of here! Let's go! Come on!
Congratulations.
Get the fuck out!
How many times I gotta
say "Move out"?
Let's go!
I know your black asses
is faster than that.
Go!
Let's move! Come on!
Move! Let's go!
On your feet! Move it! Let's go!
We're taking them out front.
Out the front door!
Let's go! Now!
Taking them out the front.
Shit!
Out the front!
Guys, sir, both sides.
Up against the wall.
Against the wall.
Let's move it. Come on.
Let's go!
Here we go. Squad's here.
If they're not resisting,
don't push them.
Put it right there.
Right here against the wall.
Welcome home!
Thank you, sir.
Get out the way.
Get out the way!
Hands where we can see them.
We had to use the front door.
- Shit!
- Make it a public display.
I almost feel bad for them.
- We gotta get out of here.
- Quickly.
Let's go! Get them in!
All right! Start loading
them up! Let's go!
Okay, let's go!
Look at this shit!
Let's hurry! Get it out of here!
Get it out! Let's go!
Make sure we get those
guys at the back.
What are you doing down
here all the time?
We gotta get this moving!
Stop messing with us.
These people didn't do a thing.
Where's the other one?
It should be here any minute.
What did they do?
Please calm down!
Everything's fine.
Finally!
Over here.
This is our neighborhood.
You don't belong here.
That's not necessary.
Open the door! Get them in!
Arrests for a private gathering?
That's police overreach!
You got no liquor
license on this place.
Get the fuck out of my face.
- Let's just keep it calm.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
Come on! Get in the damn
van! Step in there!
Move, let's go!
Let's get them
moving, gentlemen!
Let's go! Get them in the wagon!
Hey, Dave! Told you you'd
get busted, you alcoholic!
The night's not over!
Go home! Go home!
Go home!
You go home!
- Get them in.
- Last one.
Get them in!
You punk-ass motherfuckers!
Let's go, get in!
Don't touch me!
Let's go! In!
I'm moving!
Get in! Let's go!
Get in the car! Let's go!
Check this, motherfuckers!
Bub, can't even ride that bike!
You know good and well you don't
know how to ride no bike.
Do it, man! Throw it!
Catch this!
Yeah! That's what
I'm talking about!
It's show time now!
Destroyers striking from
as far as three miles away
from this west side ghetto,
where it all began
early this morning
with a police raid on an
after-hours drinking parlor.
There have been some
reports of gunfire.
Police are under
orders not to fire.
More than 200 looters have
been arrested so far.
Police officials say they
do not have enough men
to worry much about the looters.
They are there to
protect the firemen.
But that is why you elected me.
To bring about change.
But during this time,
it's important that
we all settle down.
- Settle yourself!
- I know you're angry.
I'm angry, too.
This city has problems,
especially with the policemen.
We have problems.
However,
change doesn't happen overnight.
But change is coming.
Let's work together!
Nah! Bring Stokely
Carmichael down here!
We don't wanna hear
from your ass!
Look here. This is
what I need you to do!
I need you to not mess up
your own neighborhood.
This is your home!
Yeah, burn it down!
Burning it down is
not the answer!
Burn it down! Burn it down!
Settle down! Settle down!
Hoses up! Hoses up!
Get that engine in
a little closer!
Engine four, let's relay!
Come on! Roll it back!
You gotta roll it back.
We gonna let this
motherfucker burn!
What the fuck!
Let's move back! Come on!
Get out of here!
At the request of Mayor Cavanaugh,
we've made state police
and National Guardsmen
available to assist
in dealing with what is a case
of lawlessness and hoodlumism
and to protect the persons and property
of people in the areas involved.
Here in Detroit, a city of war
where snipers hide on rooftops,
the violence continues.
US Army paratroopers,
National Guardsmen,
state and local police
are continuing the fight
against a handful of snipers.
On the city's west side, a 150-block
area is off-limits to everybody.
This is no man's land, an area
of destruction and devastation.
ABC newsman Tom McIntyre says
it's hard to believe that
this could happen in America.
But here it is, in Detroit, the
nation's fifth largest city.
I am declaring a public
state of emergency.
And I am also indicating
that I will promulgate
such rules, orders
and regulations
as I deem necessary to
protect life and property.
Second unit, left lane!
18-40!
Rally point! Rally point A!
Sniper in the window!
Third floor window!
Move to cover!
Move to cover now!
Stand by! Hold your fire!
Don't move! All
right, he's clear.
Move back!
Hey!
I almost hit that one.
There is no American right
to loot stores
or to burn buildings,
or to fire rifles
from the rooftops.
That is crime.
And crime must be
dealt with forcefully
and swiftly, and
certainly under law.
LBJ tell you that, "Violence
never accomplishes anything,
"my fellow Americans."
Don't you see, the real
problem with violence
is that we have
never been violent.
We have been too nonviolent!
Excuse me!
Go back the way you came!
I need to go down this
road to get to work.
What did I say? Back!
I need to go down this road to
get to work, Ford Assembly.
Hold on! Where you going?
Hey! Let him go!
You cannot go this...
Take cover! We might
have a sniper on...
Boy, would you look at this.
So sad.
It's preventable, you know.
That's the worst part.
Look at this. This looks
like fucking 'Nam.
You believe this is the USA?
And we're to blame.
By standing by, the trouble
started. Now this.
What can you do with this?
They're crazy.
They're not crazy. They know
exactly what they're doing.
This is gonna be worse than '43.
No, we need to stop
failing these people.
They're looking to us, and
we keep letting them down
left, right, and center.
Take this motherfucker
right here. Halt!
Halt!
Get back!
- Stay off the street!
- Halt!
Back up!
Hey!
Come here!
Get back off the street!
Hey, Phil! Come on!
Hey, Phil! Forget him! Come on!
Fuck!
You're not supposed to
shoot the looters anyway.
Yeah.
How the hell are we
supposed to stop them?
What a fucking specimen, huh?
Confound it!
What... What are you
doing under there?
I just live down the street.
If you can go get
my wife Roberta?
You want me to call
the ambulance?
No, no police!
Just, please, Roberta.
Goodness!
Get me Roberta.
1,100 National Guardsmen
have been rushed
into as many areas
as they can cover,
protecting police.
Looters carry off thousands
of dollars' worth of goods
with a gay sort of leisure.
Many negro shop
owners put up signs
reading "Soul Brother"
to avoid damage.
But the fire bombers and looters
are indiscriminate.
Just cuff him to the chair.
I'll get to him when
I get a second.
Write your address and
your date of birth.
Talk to him!
Where am I supposed to put him?
I don't care. Take
him to your house!
Let's move these
negroes out of here!
There's no room!
Sergeant!
Homicide detectives wanna
have a word with you.
Quit pushing! You got room
for two more in holding or not?
Step back from the
goddamn counter!
Come on, move! Behind the door!
Hey! Whose prisoner is this?
Don't talk to me!
For God's sake.
Sit the fuck down and shut up!
Krauss, in here. I need you.
Go, come on.
Guys, come on. Out.
I got a young black, shotgunned
in the vicinity of Virginia Park.
Did I hear earlier you
shot a black guy?
I missed, called it in.
You missed?
I might've clipped
him. He was real fast.
Sit down, patrolman. Sit down.
What's the hold up?
Schools, city offices and many stores
remain closed today in Detroit,
and a 9:00 p.m. curfew has
been ordered for this evening.
- Hey, Ma.
- Hey.
I got it.
Hello.
No, I'm off.
I worked a double.
Okay. All right.
What? Back to work?
Yeah, Mr. LeFrank called.
I thought Vinny was your boss.
I got two jobs, two bosses, Ma.
Security company needs
me for the looting.
- Looting?
- Yeah, watch the news.
Nowhere to run to, baby
Nowhere to hide
Got nowhere to run to, baby
It's not love I'm running from
It's the heartbreak
I know will come
- What do you say there, Fred?
- Hey.
Yo, you're late.
Listen, I almost lost my job
getting here. I'm sorry.
I don't give a damn about
Ford Motor Company.
Bumper cars and sheet
metal motherfucker?
You about to be with the stars!
But I need to buy bread, negro.
Listen, it's gonna be good.
You sure?
Yeah.
All right?
- Thanks, man.
- Yeah.
- I need you here, man.
- I'm here!
What you need? Water
or something?
I know you're no good for me
But you've become a part of me
Is that A&R man out there?
Yeah, he out there, waiting
to get his mind blown, baby.
When it's so deep So deep
Deep inside of me
All right, folks, come on.
Let's get this
together. You ready?
Get these steps together.
Hold on. Let me get that
note one more time.
If you haven't got
Love
A traveling man once told me
That he didn't ever care
Watch your spacing.
That any time he wants to go
That he go anywhere
If you haven't got
love Love believe me
The traveling man once told me
If you haven't got love
Love will leave me
Then you're lonely So lonely
You're lonely So lonely
Oh, yeah If you haven't got
You're up next, boys.
Let's get it! Come on!
- It's Motown, baby.
- All right. Are we ready?
Give it up!
- Motown Records, baby.
- Motown, we're Motown tonight.
All right, settle down, cats.
Now, I know you guys
think that we reached
the top of this evening
but we have not.
Because we're about to take
this thing to another level.
Because the band of brothers I'm
about to bring to this stage
comes straight out of
Motor City herself.
He talkin' about you.
If you would, stand
up on your feet
and make some noise
for Detroit's own
The Dramatics!
You got to tell these folks that
they got to go home right now.
These folks is out here rioting.
Hold on. They're doin' what?
They out here rioting.
- Right now?
- Right now.
Tell these folks
they got to go home.
Excuse me.
We're ready, right?
Listen, you boys can't
go out there tonight.
What do you mean we
can't go out there?
These folks is out here rioting.
You cannot go out there tonight.
We're on the schedule, brother.
Well, y'all gotta get the
hell out of Fox tonight.
Now, ladies and gentlemen,
I'm afraid I have some bad news.
What's going on?
It seems like we're all gonna
have to exit the building
and head to our homes.
Come on, just one song,
man! Motown's right there!
This is Detroit, we're
no stranger to this.
Now, the police said we have
absolutely nothing to worry about.
So if you would, just
grab your things.
Ma'am, grab your purse.
Slowly, slowly.
Exits to your left
and to your right.
- Damn it!
- What the hell?
We gotta go, boys. We gotta go.
I'm going on that stage.
We're going on that
stage, y'all hear me?
People are leaving, man.
The band's leaving.
Ma'am, your purse.
We won't get another
shot like this.
I'm sorry.
We need to get out
of here, Larry.
Watch your step, sir!
Now, boys, I'm sorry.
But we've got to go.
- I'm sorry.
- All right.
Larry, I mean...
What can we do?
Larry, there's
nothing we can do.
Another day... Another day, man.
Listen, I know you
want it bad, man.
Larry, we gotta go.
We gotta go.
Come on.
Larry!
Larry.
You might be a rich man
With the world on a string
But with all your riches
You haven't got everything
If you haven't got love
Love
If you haven't got
love Ooh, love
You're lonely
So lonely
Ooh, baby
We were so close.
Yeah, y'all looked good,
y'all sounded good.
There'll be a next time.
There will be.
Bus driver!
Hey, now! Bus driver!
Hey, y'all seeing this?
Clear the street.
Go back to your homes now.
Disperse or you
will be arrested.
I say we go up to 12th Street
and be a part of this.
We're working musicians, man.
I can't be singing when I'm supposed
to be out there swinging, brother.
Hey, look. We're not too
far from the Algiers.
Let's just go there till
all this blows over.
We gotta get off this bus!
Everybody out! Let's go, now!
- Come on, man!
- Sit the fuck down!
I didn't do anything!
I'm sorry, I've been working straight
shifts since the riots started.
Yeah, that guy you shot
at didn't make it home.
Ambulance found him
bleeding out under a car.
Are we sure it's the same guy?
He's the only Virginia
Park shooting today.
You carry a shotgun,
he had shotgun wounds.
You wanna play ballistics?
Jesus Christ, I'm sorry.
That's it?
What else?
You shot him in the back.
Right. He was... He was
running away from me.
Where else do you
want me to shoot?
My point was him being
no threat to you.
In hindsight, but I'm thinking,
why is he running away from me, if
all he did was steal some groceries?
What if he killed somebody
in that grocery store?
He's avoiding the police.
What do you assume from that?
You don't assume.
If he had a weapon in his
hand, that's another story.
We don't shoot for robberies.
Detective, you know it's a
war zone out there, right?
Yeah. 10th had to shut down.
They're destroying the city.
We're facilitating that
with the message we send,
which is that it's okay, go
ahead, burn down your houses,
rob a store.
It's total chaos. And...
Where does that lead us
long term, Detective?
All right, kid. Thank you.
Anytime.
I'm recommending murder charges.
You go back to work, wait
to hear from the DA.
Yes, sir.
And kid...
Calm down out there.
Thank you, Detective.
All right?
Forget about it.
- Are you in trouble?
- I'm fine, so forget it.
He's doing his job,
same as you and me.
Stand up. Let's
go. On your feet.
Go home, now! All you
people, off the streets.
Yo, we need to split up, man.
I mean, the police are going
crazy out here right now.
Five brothers together, you
know they gonna say we a gang.
Come on, man, we're
not splitting up.
Shit!
Where do you think you're going?
- We're going home, man.
- Get off the street!
Hands on the wall!
- Keep them up!
- Okay!
Oh, shit!
Keep moving!
What the hell you talking about?
Look at this mess, man!
Hey, come here! You!
Stop! It's after curfew!
This is the Detroit Police.
There is a curfew.
We're going home!
Assalamu alaikum, my brother!
Disperse!
Leave using the
streets behind you.
This direction!
This is our street!
Go back to your homes!
Disperse
or you will be arrested.
Hello, hello.
Hello.
How you doing? Just
need to get a room.
Y'all at the wrong
hotel, though.
Ritz down the street.
Yeah, well, the Ritz ain't got
you behind the counter, so...
Look, all I got is a room in the annex
out back down through the breezeway.
$11 a night, you pay in advance.
That's cool.
A8, A8.
Voila!
What you expect for 11 bucks?
Hey!
With the exception of a
few isolated snipers...
You know what fucking
time it is, boy?
- Let me have a little fun with you.
- Come on, man!
- What time is it?
- I ain't got no watch.
How am I supposed to
know what time it is?
It's past curfew and you
know it, Goddamn it!
You gonna shoot me because
I don't have a watch?
Get the fuck off my street!
- What you gonna do? Shoot me?
- Get off my street!
Do it! Go ahead.
I will kill you
right the fuck now.
So sorry!
I'm guarding that grocery store
right there. I'm guarding it.
This my nephew. I'm so
sorry, I apologize.
I'm gonna take him
away. Come on.
I ain't your nephew,
motherfucker!
Just get across the
street. Calm down.
- They let you out, Uncle Tom?
- Just get across the street.
Keep on walking.
Don't look back.
Keep on moving.
Dumb jacky giant,
I'll beat your head
to the white meat.
You won't kick my ass.
I'm a black belt in karate,
I'll whoop that ass.
Besides, even if you did win,
those ten guys over
there would be on you
and behind them is 10,000.
Now, you smart. Go home.
So you the cool brother, huh?
Dismukes.
Okay, Tom.
This is the Detroit Police.
There is a curfew.
You cannot stay on the street.
What the hell was that?
You checked the
windows and doors?
- I checked them already.
- Check it again.
I don't even wanna see
graffiti back there.
Hello.
Everything is fine.
No trouble here.
I'll sleep when they stop
rioting. Good night, sir.
Hey, hey. Hey. Look at this.
Miller, with me. Ready,
Title 32? Let's do it!
You got it!
You know what?
I'm gonna go talk to
those white guys.
I'm gonna stay here,
if that's okay.
I'm gonna make sure they
don't start shooting at us.
All right, boys.
Relax here.
Hey, you sure you
want them white boys
- to know where we are?
- I'll be right back.
Jefferson, Wood, head in
there and take the roof.
We're on it.
Hey, fellas.
Melvin Dismukes.
I'm with United Security,
I'm guarding that grocery
store across the street.
I come bearing gifts.
Thank you.
Isn't this nice, boys?
All things considered,
this is pretty good.
Thank you. I don't have
my usual appliances.
You got any sugar?
Don't push it, man.
It's good to have some quiet.
We were at Black
Bottom earlier today.
We actually took sniper fire.
Had one, right by here.
Ain't no snipers here,
man. Just you and me
and the people partying
in that motel.
How long do you think
this is gonna last?
Yeah, how long till these
negros, people, quit?
What do you think?
How the hell am I
supposed to know?
Is Morris home? It's Larry.
I can't find those
guys anywhere.
No, no, no. No, he's fine.
Just when you see that cat, tell
him to come down to the Algiers.
We're rehearsing.
Bye.
No luck?
His mama don't even
know where he is.
He's probably all right.
Look in my eyes
And don't you see water?
And it's all because of you
So look at me
I ain't acting like I ought to
And it's all because of you
So look in my eyes And
don't you see water?
And it's all because of you
You're gonna get
back on that stage.
Yeah, it's not that
simple, brother.
Listen, when they hear you
blow... Money raining.
And I want a cut.
Look at me.
In the eyes.
I'm looking at you
in the eyes, Fred.
You're gonna get a record deal.
All right?
Look in my eyes
The Fox Theatre
welcomes The Dramatics!
Yeah?
Yeah.
You know what, Fred?
I think it's time to fix that
little problem of yours.
What problem?
- I don't have a problem.
- Yeah, you do. Come on.
- We're not doing this.
- Yeah, we're doing this.
Come on! Don't give me a no.
Come on.
You're gonna look in her eyes
I don't need it,
I don't want it.
And she's gonna get you off
Come on.
Okay, no. Man, I'm doing
you a favor, okay?
- Okay?
- I'm going.
We're going.
Look at this nice little
scene right here.
- There you go, Karen.
- Thank you.
Enjoy it because we are
now officially broke.
There's rioting outside, and I'm
not writing to my parents again.
Look at this. That right there.
It's perfect.
- Larry.
- What?
They white.
So, they white.
Beggars can't be
choosers, all right?
What does that mean?
You know what I say?
What?
Let freedom ring.
I've had that freedom,
thank you very much!
No, you haven't.
Because freedom doesn't mean
giving it away for free.
Only you could make
prostitution sound high class.
Come on.
I'm not trying to
do this, brother.
Hey, stop.
Why won't you just
leave them alone?
I think those boys
are eyeballing us.
Okay, stop.
Come on, man. Follow my lead.
Okay, so we do it together
and it's like a co-op.
Excuse me, ladies.
I'm Larry Cleveland.
I wouldn't be interrupting a private
conversation here, would I?
We must be neighbors.
I'm Julie, Ohio.
Karen, Ohio.
No, my last name is Cleveland.
We're actually from Ohio.
Okay, so what y'all
doing in Detroit?
Well, Julie here is a
professional prostitute.
- Okay...
- She's kidding!
I'm a hairdresser.
And a hoe.
What do you guys do?
I'm a singer in The Dramatics,
and Fred here is my bodyguard.
The Dramatics?
Yeah.
Never heard of them.
But I love... I love Motown.
The Supremes are my favorite.
Well, if you love The Supremes,
you'll definitely love The Dramatics.
Larry.
Sing something to her.
Baby
I'm for real
I said I'm as real
As real can get
Oh, my God! He can really sing.
It's who I am, you know. I sing.
It's who he is.
We were just gonna go
get something to eat.
A friend of ours is
staying at the annex.
Would you like to join us?
I mean, yeah. I could eat.
Fred, you hungry?
Yeah, I can eat.
Let's go.
How you doing?
Good.
How are you?
We looking good!
Hey, Carl!
We're starving.
You know I got something
for y'all to eat.
Okay.
- Hey, babe.
- Hey!
Hello!
Hi, guys!
Come on in.
It's a nice joint, man.
Sit down, man.
Say what?
Sit down, take a seat.
Hey, Aubrey.
How you doing?
Hey, Karen.
Okay, where I grew up,
when you meet someone new,
you're supposed to
say "Hi, hello!"
"How are you?"
It makes them feel comfortable.
Nice duds, man.
Thanks, man, I appreciate it.
We were performing earlier.
Watch out.
Total bull.
This guy. Okay.
Food is served right there.
Yeah, all right, man.
Hey, Julie,
the air conditioning's
real nice over here.
Real nice, huh?
The bed's comfortable, too.
- Yeah, that's nice.
- Yeah?
Maybe roll up one
of these joints.
Aubrey, man, turn that radio up.
Come on, fellas, please.
Can we please let Trane speak?
What the hell?
That's beautiful.
So sad that he died.
He was young, right?
He was 40.
But he used his years.
Let me tell you, that man lived.
Unfortunately, it was heroin.
Now, we know Trane
did not overdose.
Don't put a rumor on that, man.
I didn't say Trane overdosed.
But John Coltrane was
a junkie for years.
Love Supreme Trane
was high on dope.
I'm not saying that's
taking anything away
from the man as a
spiritual example.
He's one of my many saints.
But heroin is what
killed his liver.
I heard the FBI poisoned him.
FBI. You wanna know how I know?
John Coltrane's wife
is a Detroit musician,
same set as me.
So now you a trained
expert on Coltrane?
Continuing coverage tonight of
the rioting here in Detroit.
The National Guard
has been called in
and more than 3,200 people have
been arrested, most of them negros.
Updates will continue
throughout our broadcast...
Why is everything
always so violent?
You ask your people that?
Try a little revolution
with the English,
all that "liberty or death"?
That ain't so
non-violent at all.
Man, she from Ohio.
I highly doubt she understands your
logic about liberty and death.
Well, let's put it
in layman's terms.
Slide over, stripes.
You see,
you white, ain't you?
Brother.
You white, right?
See, y'all don't have to deal with
the police nearly as much as we do.
Unless, of course, you're some
Uncle Tom handkerchief
head, you know?
It's like... When you're
black, it's almost like
having a gun pointing
right at your face.
You understand that?
It's like this.
Hey, boy! Get your
hands off my plate.
Put the hot dog... Step
away from the mustard!
Put your hands down!
Don't... You nervous?
- You're making me nervous!
- You got a gun on me.
This like police brutality
or something, man.
So you gonna tell me
how to do my job now?
- I'm not...
- So now you're the police officer
that tells me how to do
my job on my street?
What you doing on
my street, nigger?
See, that's the way they
like to express themselves.
You know, "My street,
my house, my car."
That way they can take
everything from you.
- Larry.
- So again.
What you doing on
my street, boy?
Did I do something
wrong, officer?
Did you do something wrong?
I ought to blow your
head right off.
Get that gun off me, man.
- Or what, boy?
- I said, get that gun off...
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! You shot him! Carl!
- Lee!
- He shouldn't have made a move.
Lee?
Hot dog, please!
- You're nuts!
- What?
- Oh, man!
- You're nuts!
You're nuts!
It was just a starter pistol.
It just starts races.
It don't kill nobody,
- it don't hurt nobody.
- Crazy!
I'm just demonstrating
white power.
So am I, honey.
Sweetheart, baby,
it was just a joke.
Y'all can go and
get the hell out,
you and your partner.
Thought they could take a joke.
I'm performing.
Sorry, Larry, they're
usually nice guys.
No, come on. Don't let
those fools bother you.
Why don't we all go to my room
and relax for a little bit?
We told a friend we'd drop by.
Maybe later.
Come on.
Find me later.
See you!
I thought everybody should know.
But you scared them off, man.
But Karen though...
She was looking at me.
- Karen wasn't looking at you.
- Karen was feeling me, man.
She was like, "Hey, Aubrey!"
I was like, "Hey, Karen!"
Disperse or you
will be arrested.
Julie!
We should teach these
pigs a lesson.
What you talking about, Carl?
Them right down there.
You know if you shoot them, they're
gonna shoot us back, right?
How they gonna know where
it came from, Lee?
- It's not even possible.
- Just calm down, man.
Man, you chicken.
It's already crazy
in here enough.
Look. They need to understand
that they can't be picking
on us all the time.
Y'all gotta be with the program!
We're gonna get our asses beat!
- One, two.
- Would you...
Get down! Hit the deck!
You guys okay?
- Who's shooting?
- From down there, maybe?
It could be any one
of those buildings.
Did you just hear
that gunshot, baby?
No, I didn't hear anything.
Anyway, you know if I
get a record deal,
we gonna drive a
Cadillac, right?
Look, check him out!
Run, Mr. Cracker, run!
Get down!
Muzzle flash!
By the Algiers,
could be a sniper.
- Mike?
- I'm okay!
I didn't get hit!
Keifer Command, this is
Warrant Officer Roberts.
Take cover!
Army taking sniper fire.
Algiers Motel vicinity,
on Virginia Park.
Yeah, keep running.
- That was bad, brother.
- That's crazy, man.
Now everybody know what
it's like to be black.
Police 2-4, potential sniper
- in the area.
- Army taking fire.
Near the Algiers Motel
on Virginia Park.
Sniper on the roof.
Sniper fire, sniper
fire, Virginia Park.
Sniper fire near
the Algiers Motel.
10-4, on the way.
Shots fired, Virginia
Park, sniper on the roof.
Sniper out there!
Lock the whole place up!
Let's find that motherfucker.
Anyway, my boy Fred was just telling
me that the rioting is getting so bad,
even Ford's thinking about
shutting down assembly for a day.
Larry, that's terrible.
Yeah, I know it is.
Maybe we should make
the most of it.
In a time of hate, love
does become more important.
Maybe the most important.
Why don't you come over
here and visit me?
We got a swimming pool and I think
we need to spend some time together.
My mom says I can't
leave the house.
But I want to.
Your mama, right.
- Give me some shells.
- Here.
Thanks.
Move, move, move! Move forward!
Left hand, top window!
Spread out to the side!
Hey, y'all, there's a bunch
of police outside right now.
Quit playing, man!
Why would I be playing?
Yo, is they lost?
Come on, move!
I hope so! What you
mean? I don't know.
I don't know, man, but it look like
they coming right toward the house.
Go! Don't just stand
there! Move up!
Get in position!
- Close the windows!
- Window!
Hide everything!
Turn the lights off!
Sniper!
Oh, shit!
Baby, did you hear that?
They're shooting at us!
I gotta go! They're shooting us.
Larry!
Fred, you good?
You good?
I don't wanna die, man!
We gotta get out of here!
- Man, don't get up!
- Carl, stay down!
- They can't do this to us.
- Stay down!
They can't do this to us.
- Carl, stay down!
- What're you doing, man?
Here we go!
Go. Go. Go. Go.
Going up.
Clear!
Police!
Hey, do you hear that?
Fred, stay low!
Police! Get on the floor!
Get the fuck against
the wall right now!
All right, all right!
I didn't do nothing!
Have you got a weapon?
I don't have a fucking gun!
Put your hands behind your back!
- Have you got a firearm?
- No!
Have you got a fucking weapon?
Go, go, go!
- Come here! Come on!
- Why you doing this?
Get him the fuck downstairs now.
- Get the fuck out of here now!
- Get out of here!
- Come on!
- Take him!
Put your hands on your head
and relax. Just calm down.
Sit down. Put your
hands on your head.
Move the fuck downstairs! Go!
I don't have a gun!
Don't pull, man!
Police! Put your
hands on your head!
They already are.
Against the walls and doors!
All of them! Against the wall!
Fred!
Walls and doors!
I didn't do nothing!
I don't have nothing!
I don't got no gun!
Anybody in there?
No, sir.
Get the fuck up! Get up!
Get downstairs! Go!
- Get him downstairs!
- What's going...
What're you doing here?
Down on the ground! Get down!
- I'm not resisting!
- Get up!
Yeah, keep goin'!
Don't look at me!
Against the wall,
bring them all down!
Hey! You got him?
Against the walls and doors!
Turn around and stay
against the wall.
Let's get them down here!
Let's go!
Don't you fucking move!
- Get them, go!
- What did we do?
You better shut your mouth!
Get them! Get the fuck...
Get out of here!
Get the fuck downstairs!
Go! Let's get them down here!
Go! Down the stairs! Let's go!
- Let's go!
- Okay, okay!
Come on, man! My arm, man! Stop!
We didn't even do anything!
Shit!
Where's Carl, man?
Where's Carl?
What happened?
Fella here had a knife,
tried to go for my gun.
Yeah, I heard him shout,
"Get off my gun!"
Yeah, it all happened
pretty fast.
I guess you had to
defend yourself.
Aubrey, get back!
Get back against the wall! Move!
- Chill!
- They killed Carl!
Don't be stupid, boy!
Stay against the wall!
Okay, okay.
He has his face filled with
blood. They killed him, man.
Shame. A young kid like that.
Still, he might be the
shooter. We need to find out.
They killed him, man.
They killed our friend.
What's the deal with the girls?
I found them with the big
nigger down the end.
Same room?
- You find anything?
- Nothing.
No gun?
No.
Some bad news.
One of the guests is dead.
He tried to take a
police officer's weapon,
ended up getting shot.
Carl Cooper.
He killed Carl.
May he rest in peace. Amen.
Amen.
Now let's not be stupid
in this situation.
We still have a crime scene
here and you're all suspects.
Each and every one of you.
Don't look at me!
Turn around, face the wall!
Was Carl the one
doing the shooting?
Somebody better start
getting honest with me.
Hey! I want that gun!
We looked around, we
didn't find a gun.
Doesn't mean it's not
here! Go find it!
You, too!
I got nothing
against you people.
But you need to tell
me where the gun is.
You need to tell me
who was doing the shooting.
I'm only gonna ask
so many times.
Who did the shooting?
We don't know.
You do fucking know!
You were upstairs, who
was doing the shooting?
- Who was doing the shooting?
- You doing the shooting, man!
Lee!
No, man.
Carl ain't got no gun.
What's that?
You're the ones out
here killing people!
Say that to my face!
I said, Carl ain't
shoot nobody, man!
Yeah, all right.
Fuck.
Stop your goddamn
crying! Face the door!
You, too. Face the front!
Why don't you pick that
up and defend yourself?
It's easy, look.
You sure you don't
wanna try and stab me?
I'm not gonna play your game.
Well.
That would just give
me an excuse to do
what we both know is
gonna happen anyway.
Right?
Man, y'all some crazy crackers!
Shit!
Get off of me.
You still a cracker.
Shut the fuck up,
all right? Shut up.
There's a goddamn
shooter in this house.
Was it Carl?
Let me tell you something.
If you think that you can
shoot at innocent people
and get away with it,
you are dead wrong.
My partner said, "Stand up."
- Look, I'll take him.
- So stand.
Go search the place,
I'll take him with me.
Come on, come on.
- Come on.
- Get the fuck outta here.
I got all night, people.
Nobody's gonna talk?
Nobody knows who the shooter is?
Please, God. Please, God.
Nobody's going to admit shit?
All right.
Then start prayin'.
Start praying. What's the
matter, boy? You don't pray?
You don't go to fuckin' church?
- Start praying!
- Oh, Lord.
Forgive our trespasses as we forgive
those that trespass against us.
'Cause I will kill
you, one by one,
until you tell me exactly
what is going on here.
Cover us with the
blood of Jesus, God.
I'm just gonna assume
you're all criminals.
Because if we're honest,
you probably are.
So let's hear it.
Let's fucking hear it!
Pray! Do it loud!
You don't sing that gospel shit?
My way
There you go, now
we got two of 'em.
Take the hate out
of our hearts, God.
What about you?
Your grace is with me
You are not praying. I'm not
hearing shit out of you.
- Mary, full of grace...
- I don't give a fuck.
You may need a little fuckin'
help to know how to pray.
You are near me
Hail Mary, full of grace.
When my life
He's really fuckin' praying.
It's not bad.
All right, check the room.
Under the beds and in
the drawers. Okay?
They're gonna kill us, man.
Why? You gonna be crazy?
They the ones that's
acting crazy.
They lost they mind
when they seen
a couple white girls in a
room with a black man.
They're lookin' for
a sniper, okay?
But Carl wasn't no sniper, man.
So if a guy goes for your gun,
you gonna let him have
it because he's black?
Come on!
A cop has a shotgun
like yours, right?
You hold that tight
with two hands.
How you even gonna
try to take that?
Lotta ways.
There's no guns in this whole motel
except the ones these cops brought.
There's no guns.
We takin' something
for those crazy boys.
Pick 'em up.
What's the point?
Look, I understand. Okay?
But don't antagonize those guys.
I need you to survive the night.
Survive the night.
All right?
You don't think
you're gonna talk?
I'll fucking make you talk.
Where's the fuckin' gun?
Get up! Get the fuck up!
You gonna tell me
where the gun is?
- I don't know.
- Bullshit!
Stop fucking lying to me!
Where's the fucking gun?
I swear to God, I'll pull
the fucking trigger!
Where is it?
I don't know, I swear...
Bullshit!
Come here.
What's going on?
I gotta tell you, Detroit
PD is going nuts in there.
What do you mean?
Looks like they're
terrorizing suspects,
beating and so forth,
trying to get a confession.
Well, that's not correct,
they got their civil rights.
That's what I'm saying.
Don't look right to me.
Where's that fucking gun?
Don't lie to me!
Where's the gun?
All right.
Let's let them have the case.
I don't wanna get involved in any
civil rights mix-up, you know?
Let's go.
- Where's the fucking gun?
- I don't know!
Bullshit! You people
are always lying!
Who's the shooter?
Find it?
No.
All this looks stolen.
I searched the whole
room, myself.
He wouldn't even tell you, huh?
All right. Get Demens
to watch the line.
Come with me.
Get in there. Quickly.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Lie down.
Come on! We need you in here.
Get the...
Get on the goddamn floor.
You don't have to do this, man.
We're gonna hold the line.
Why you gotta fuck them, huh?
What's wrong with us?
Listen to me.
You need to tell me
where the gun is and
who the shooter is...
I swear to you there's no gun.
There's no gun, man!
Or I swear to God,
I will kill you.
There's no gun, man.
Okay.
I don't know nothing, man.
No!
He shot him. He shot him.
Face the fucking wall.
Be still and stay quiet,
or the next one is for real.
Understand?
This'll make 'em
talk. Watch this.
That one didn't even kick.
That's what happens
when you lie to us.
Who else wants to kill one?
You wanna kill one?
Okay.
All right.
Officer, wait! I
didn't shoot nobody!
- Officer, wait!
- Shut up!
Fuck!
Shut up. Get the fuck in there.
I told you I don't know where
the fucking gun is, man.
- You looked for it, right?
- Shut your mouth!
Hey, man. You gotta tell me where
the gun is so all this can stop.
- Where's the gun?
- I don't know.
- You can't do this shit!
- Shut the fuck up!
Michael. Michael.
You think we're bluffin'?
This is Detroit.
We don't bluff.
Now, be quiet,
or the next one
will be for real.
I killed that nigger.
There you have it.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Get your goddamn hands
off her. Turn around.
What's your part
in all this, huh?
Probably know where the gun is.
Probably know who
the shooter is.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Yes, you do.
And you're lyin' to me.
Get away from me!
You think you'd get a
pass 'cause you're white?
No, whore. You don't.
Find out what she knows.
It's okay. Easy, easy.
Face the goddamn wall. I'm
not gonna tell you again.
It's just you and me.
Take a seat.
Sit down.
Ouch.
You all right there, miss?
Is everything okay?
You're okay though, right?
Don't touch me.
Try to keep calm.
What are you doin' living here?
It's a hotel, isn't it?
Yeah.
So you're up here for a while?
Some
prostitution, maybe?
I'm visiting from Ohio.
My father is a judge.
And your father, he knows
you're here, right?
Living amongst the blacks?
Are there black people here?
I didn't notice, I'm colorblind.
Really?
What color am I? Blue?
You look yellow to me, sir.
- You're working prostitution.
- No!
Look at me.
You're fuckin' these
black guys, right?
They're kids.
What's the matter with you?
I'm trying to protect you, miss.
Stay there.
She's a hooker.
All right, fuck it. Come here.
So, you are the pimp.
No, sir. I think
you're mistaken.
- Fuck!
- Listen.
We've got all the
time in the world.
We are gonna get to
the bottom of this.
So think very carefully about
how you answer our questions,
or you're gonna end up like
your friends in the next room.
How long you been pimpin'
out these young girls, huh?
Destroying their
bodies and minds.
I just met 'em. I ain't pimpin'.
I just got back from the war.
You're a veteran?
Yes, sir.
Fuckin' stupid do
you think I am?
You wear army green,
you try to be a
fucking serviceman.
We don't need pimps in the army.
Probably drove a
fucking supply truck.
I was airborne.
Look out!
Take cover!
Move to cover!
Get down! Get down!
Go, go, go!
- Take cover!
- Sniper!
Down, down!
Across the street! They're
running up Euclid!
- Three houses up.
- I see him!
Who's got eyes on him?
Don't worry about it. If it
was anything, they'd grab us.
Larry, what are you doin'?
Larry.
Get back on the wall.
Let's get the fuck
up outta here.
They're gonna come back.
We can. Let's go.
No.
What are you doing, man?
Come on. Come on.
Fred, let's go.
No, Larry. Stop.
Who's got eyes on him?
Watch the roof!
Just breathe, just breathe.
It's okay. I'm here, I'm here.
Come on, come on.
Stay the fuck away.
Check all those windows!
Hold your perimeter!
They're shooting. You hear that?
Shut up!
Fall back! Covering
fire! Put it down!
Fire! Fire!
Oh, shit!
- We got 'em!
- Hold your fire!
All right, it's clear.
Snipers everywhere, tonight.
Clear!
Is that your buddies
out there, huh?
Is that who was shooting at us?
Huh? What do you gotta say?
Fuck!
Says right there.
Paratrooper, eight years.
Two deployments.
Honorable discharge.
- This is a fake.
- No, sir.
- This your girl?
- I just met her.
What's his name?
I don't know.
His name is Karl Greene.
I wasn't asking you,
I was asking her.
You just said,
"What's his name?"
You're lucky I haven't broken
your fuckin' neck, yet.
Okay.
All right, man. I see
what you're trying to do.
I'm not gonna cause
any trouble, okay?
But I'm not gonna lie
down for you, either.
What are you doin'
in Detroit, huh?
Like everybody else,
I'm lookin' for work.
Left one war zone
and joined another.
Yeah.
All right. Get this
motherfucker back in line.
Give me back my
government card, man.
Why don't you get outta here?
Run out the back door. Run.
Right now, go!
You know the one
who was praying?
He's okay, it's not him.
And you can scratch
off G. I. Joe.
That little twerp with
the big, fuckin' prayer.
Yeah, it's not him.
That leaves us with the big
motherfucker who's in that room.
I like him for it.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Flynn.
Fuck!
He's escaped.
Well, we need another one.
I know.
Still... Still no gun.
So, who wants to go next?
Please, please, please.
Please. Just, please, please.
Officer, can I say something?
There we go.
Yes, you can.
I think you have
the wrong house.
'Cause nobody we saw...
'Cause nobody we saw here
was shooting at the police.
Please.
It's possible we made a mistake.
But I need to know for sure.
Can't let a cop killer
get away with it, can I?
Please, please.
How about you, sweetheart?
- You wanna be next?
- No.
No, I don't, please.
- I think you know something.
- I don't.
- You wanna just die now...
- No.
Or watch me kill
the others first?
Which one, huh? Which one?
Get her outta here.
Jesus! And her! Up!
Upstairs!
No!
Shut up!
You wanna cry, huh?
Jesus Christ!
You wanna cry?
I'll give you something
to cry about.
Watch them. This one's
coming with me.
Shut up!
You wanna cry, huh? I'll give
you something to cry about.
Leave her alone!
I guess there are no
weapons on your person.
Stay over there and keep quiet.
God.
Aren't you ashamed
of yourselves?
You're the one
checking out my tits.
You're having sex with niggers.
It's 1967, asshole.
Honestly.
It doesn't bother you?
The Afro Sheen in their hair?
The way it smells?
You're on some trip.
You think you can come into my city
and pimp out a bunch of young girls?
I said it wasn't like that.
I don't care if you
were in the army.
I'll drown all you pimps in the
river until the city's clean.
You gonna question them or I'm
gonna take 'em outta here.
Just hold on.
Look.
You might not be such
bad girls after all.
But be straight with me.
Who was shootin' at the
National Guard out there?
Mister?
I didn't see anybody shoot
at the National Guard.
I would tell you if I had.
You would?
You can think I'm a slut if you
want, but I was raised right.
All right. I'm gonna
get 'em outta here.
Let's get you covered up, okay?
You too.
Come on.
Hey, can I get a hand?
Fuck.
Fuck those fuckers.
You're fucking
murdering those kids!
Why don't you stop them?
This animal did it too.
He shot one of them!
Don't concern yourself.
They're just scaring them.
It's an interrogation tactic.
Are you nuts, Mister?
I saw the bodies!
Those guys are getting
murdered in cold blood.
I didn't really shoot the guy.
It's not real.
I didn't shoot that guy,
and neither did the other.
It's to get the guys to fess up
about the location of the gun.
Who said they even had a gun?
I don't know.
If they did, it was just a
toy. It wasn't a real gun.
Well, thanks for saving us.
We gotta head out.
Are we safe here?
She means, are you gonna tell
the police where we are?
No.
Karen.
We're gonna be okay.
But those boys...
Fucking stay there.
You see that? See that shit?
That is your fault right
there. Look at it.
You don't talk, that's
what happens. Look at it.
At ease.
That kid. Him.
He was up there in the same room
as those other two delinquents.
Yeah. Let's get our confession out of
him, vacate the premises, all right?
- Okay.
- Demens should do it.
Do what?
You haven't killed a nigger yet.
Well, I don't know about that.
Sure you do.
What's the matter,
partner? Problem?
Whatever you say. Which one?
Come with me. I gotta
ask you some questions.
Please.
Please don't kill me, please.
Please don't shoot me, please.
Where is the gun?
I don't know. Please.
I don't know. I swear to God,
I don't know. Please. Please.
I got no cause to shoot you.
Please don't shoot. Please.
Where's the gun?
Please don't shoot me, man.
I ain't never shot anybody
before in my life.
Please! I don't know
where... Please.
Please, don't...
Turn around.
They fucking killed him.
So that's done.
Good. Great job.
I didn't think I could
do it, but I did it.
Boy, I feel funny.
Yeah. It's the right
thing. He'll talk now.
What do you mean?
Another one bites the dust.
I bet some of you thought
we weren't serious, huh?
Well, we still don't have our gun and
we are running out of time, people.
Who was the sniper?
Just be honest with us
so we can all go home.
You shot him, Demens.
Yeah, I got him.
Jesus Christ, Marty.
We weren't actually
shooting the other guys.
We're playing with them.
What do you mean?
Playing.
Playing what?
A game.
A game to get them to talk,
scare the shit out of 'em.
Interrogation tactics.
Fuck.
This is strictly
police business.
Hey, boys, let's move out.
Have you got... You
don't have a knife.
- Fuck me.
- Oh, fuck.
Okay, listen. Listen.
- Listen to me.
- Oh, fuck.
He grabbed your gun, all right,
and you warned him, okay?
And you were forced to shoot
him, okay? Line of duty.
- Get your fucking story straight.
- Oh, fuck.
Hey, get your head
straight. I'm serious.
All right, just take a minute.
Stay here.
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck.
- Marty shot the guy.
- What?
- He did?
- Yeah.
Point blank.
We need to wrap this up
and get out of here.
We don't have a suspect.
Should we just arrest them all?
No, no, not now. We just need
to get out of here, you know?
And... Us and them.
If they're smart, they're not
gonna say anything, all right?
All right. Let's do this.
You come with me.
Listen to me.
You're free to go.
But you don't talk about
this to anyone, ever.
You understand?
'Cause I got your name,
and I know exactly who you are.
I don't got your name.
I don't know nothin' about you.
Please don't kill me.
Please don't kill him.
What's this here?
I don't see nothin'.
All right.
Get going.
Hey, we don't know nothin'.
We don't know nothin'.
No, no, no, no!
Relax.
Listen.
What if I told you you can
run out that door right now,
but you never talk about
what you saw here?
Understand?
Please don't kill him.
No, no, no!
Listen to me.
What do you see here?
You killed him.
We're gonna try this again.
I don't see anything.
There's a dead guy right there.
Halt!
Please, please, please...
Hey.
Oh, my God.
Who could do this to someone?
Hey, hey, hey. I'm here
to help you, all right?
Come on. Hey.
I'm gonna get you to
the hospital, okay?
All right? Relax.
Okay? Hey, hey, it's all right.
Come with me. Come on.
Come on. Come on. We're
gonna get you there.
Come on, brother.
Don't you go on me, all
right? Come on. Come on.
We got him.
Let's go.
Aubrey! Phone call!
Aubrey, hey!
You got phone call!
- Say again?
- You got a call from home.
Something's wrong.
Kid's in trouble or
hurt, or something.
Bet it's my youngest.
He's always googy-googy.
Yes?
Well, Aubrey...
They found Aubrey dead this
morning at the Algiers Motel.
No. No. Aubrey's
supposed to be at home.
It's got to be somebody else.
What is this, Ma?
A mistake?
It's got to be a mistake.
Aubrey's got more
sense than that.
Well, baby, you never know.
Let's go see.
Dismukes?
Is he there?
Looking for a Dismukes.
Appreciate it.
Any of you fellas
named Dismukes?
Yeah, that's me.
I have to ask you to
come with us, sir.
Is there a problem?
No. I don't think so.
Rather not have to
ask again, though.
Y'all tell the boss.
You got this?
- Take care of yourself.
- This way.
Come on, I ain't got all day.
Take a seat.
I'm sorry, I...
I assume this is about
what went on at the motel?
What happened at the motel?
If you don't know,
I'll tell you.
I was working security
by Wisconsin.
And on Tuesday night,
we heard gunfire
coming from the area
near the Algiers.
In that direction.
Police was there. State
police, National Guard.
It was a lot of shooting.
And when I went in there,
three kids had been killed.
No.
- Yes, sir.
- This right there, right?
Is that what you're
talking about?
Yes, sir. Yeah.
He was lying just like
this. The blood was fresh.
It hadn't congealed yet.
So they were killed right
before you got there?
Yes, sir.
You carry a .38, right?
A revolver. Do you
carry a revolver?
I do have a .38.
You ever shoot anyone?
- No.
- Strike anyone?
- Not the way you mean, sir.
- What do I mean?
Fellas,
you know, sometimes,
when a black guy's put in
a position of authority,
other black guys, they like
to single you out, okay?
Because I'm not supposed
to tell 'em what to do.
When we have these
conversations,
we do them in stages, okay?
Stage one, witnesses.
Stage two, suspects.
What stage are we in?
You don't know what
stage we're in?
No. Could you specify for me?
Yeah, we're in stage two.
You're a suspect.
I didn't do it.
- The police...
- Here we go.
The police shot those kids.
See, how the hell
do you know that
when you weren't inside the building
until after the shooting stopped?
So, are you lying to us now,
or were you lying
just a minute ago?
That's a good
question, Detective.
You need to think real hard.
You need to answer me.
All due respect, I am
telling the truth.
I'm not lying.
I told you what I saw.
I saw these kids...
- Melvin.
- Okay. Okay.
- We're here to help you, okay?
- Yes, sir.
Melvin, do you wanna go home?
Yeah.
Can we let him think about it?
- Yeah.
- You think about it, okay, Melvin?
I didn't do it.
Number four, step forward.
You're doing a real
good job, honey.
Eddie...
Has he woken up?
No, man.
Hey.
Larry.
Hey, wake up, brother.
Hey.
Be gentle.
It's all right, man. It's us.
You know where my
little brother is?
The police are
saying Fred is dead,
but I can't get nobody to
tell me what's going on.
What's going on?
You tell us, man.
The police...
The police?
They...
- You have children?
- Yes. I have three boys.
The oldest is twelve.
Then nine and seven.
You know how
youngsters are then.
Oh, boy...
The way they communicate,
grunts and groans.
My little cavemen.
Especially boys.
It's like they don't know if
they wanna be slick, you know?
That's right.
They're still trying to
find their place in life
and we have to allow for that.
Oh, yes.
Well,
I can see you want
to go back there.
Sure.
We helped put out fires.
We helped try to keep the riots
down and keep the corner clear.
What can you say
about having all this
murdering and confusion?
Everybody isn't thieves
and murderers.
I wish that things could be
better for the negro people.
Just...
Remember what I told you, and this
whole thing's gonna blow over.
All right? You did
nothing wrong.
I think I got to say somethin'.
Hey. You made...
Demens.
Something that took one minute
should not define
your entire life.
You understand?
You made a mistake.
You say what you need to say,
and you move on.
That's how you get
out of this thing.
- All right?
- All right.
All right?
Yeah. You don't have to lecture
me, I know what to do.
There you go.
You were doing your job.
You first, knucklehead!
All right.
Flynn!
All right. Let's go, ladies.
I'll be with you
in a few minutes.
Well?
Some things were said in there.
Such as?
You stupid... You
motherfucker, you're dead.
You're fucking dead.
You too?
We're all going down.
Phil, listen. It's...
- No. No.
- Just listen to me.
- Get the fuck out of my way.
- Phil!
I got nothing to say
without my union lawyer.
Are you kidding me,
you racist fuck?
Get out of the car before
I break your neck.
I couldn't say for sure who
went inside the building first.
There were five,
maybe six state police.
We have complete statements
from your partners.
We know you shot those kids.
So just go from there.
No. No. I don't
recall doing that.
Bang his head against
the table. Might help.
Hey.
I'm trying to help here.
I'm trying to be thorough.
So, you wanna know
how many state police
were on the scene,
how many National Guard?
I can't tell if you're
stupid or smart,
but I'm willing to find out.
Don't say another word.
Come on.
What's the point?
Coercive testimony
will be tossed.
Larry!
Yo, you sure he's home?
Give him a minute.
Man, what? What's so important?
The record company called, baby!
They wanna hear our
music at the studio!
And they called you?
Yeah, man. They said they tried to call
you but you never called them back.
This is what we've
been working for, man.
They wanna hear The Dramatics!
So what? You Mr.
Show Business now?
This isn't professional.
Call at business hours,
not 3:00 in the morning.
But Larry...
Larry! It's a record company, man.
They don't keep banking hours.
Come on.
Listen, you guys had better
sound good because I'm broke.
Let me hear that blend.
Yes, sir.
- Are you guys ready?
- Yeah.
One, two. One, two, three, four.
Look in my eyes And
don't you see water
And it's all because of you
Well look at me I ain't
acting like I oughta
And it's all because of you
George, can we get a minute?
- Come on.
- Yeah, hurry back.
Look, what is in your head, man?
'Cause you ain't singin' in there.
How am I supposed to sing
with what happened to Fred?
Look, you just do it.
Sing while my boy is lying dead?
Look, a song ain't
words on a page, man.
That ain't music.
Music is what you put into it
and you can make that
whatever you want.
I'm not singing so white
motherfuckers can dance!
Well, them pale motherfuckers
ain't dancing for free!
Since when do you care if
white folks dance anyway?
During the week of
rioting in Detroit,
three Negros were shot to
death in a motel room.
Police and the Guardsmen
had raided the motel,
searching for snipers.
Later, witnesses
to the shootings
said the three Negros
had been lined up
and shot in cold blood
by the officers.
Today, two police
officers were arrested
and charged with the murders
of two of the Negros
shot in the motel.
The officers, one with
two years' service,
the other with four
and no previous
misconduct charges,
were ordered held without bail.
They pleaded not guilty.
Their attorney said
the arrests were a
shame and a pity.
Police Commissioner,
Ray Girardin,
refused to discuss the
facts of the case,
except to say the
two officers...
Who do you got mail for?
Larry Cleveland Reed?
Larry!
Larry, you got a letter.
From the government.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I didn't do nothin'!
- Lie down.
- Please, man!
I will kill you one by one
until you tell me exactly
what is going on here.
Don't look at me. Turn around.
Start praying!
Get down! Get up!
Get the fuck up! Get up!
Bullshit! Stop
fucking lying to me!
Carl ain't got no gun.
One of the guests is dead.
Please don't shoot. Please.
Where's the gun?
Please don't shoot me, man!
Officer, can I say something?
I think you have
the wrong house.
In the Algiers Motel case,
both the prosecution
and the defense
in their opening statements
reminded the all-white jury
of the racial violence
that seared Detroit
two summers ago.
Now, Mr. Reed, before the police
or military personnel
started firing,
to your knowledge, had
there been any sniper fire
from inside the Algiers
Motel or annex?
No.
And did you see anyone
in the motel that night
with a gun of any
kind in their hand
outside of police officers
or military personnel?
I saw someone shoot a toy
gun at one of his friends.
A toy gun.
Mr. Reed.
Isn't it a fact that your head
was against the wall for
most of the evening?
No, sir, it is not.
My hands were against the
wall for most of the evening.
That's a fact.
I asked about your head.
My head is attached to my neck.
It moves. This way, and that.
And yet, it cannot
turn completely around
to see what's behind you?
Unless you have a special skill
this courtroom should know about?
You said you saw the flash
before you heard the gunshot.
Was that your testimony?
Well, it was pretty confusing.
Well, which is it?
Which came first?
Did you see the flash?
When did you hear the
body hit the floor?
I can't say for sure.
You said you were just
outside the door.
You also said you
might be confused,
that you don't know
what point in time
these things happened.
So, are you confused?
I saw the flash, just
through the door.
What I need to know is,
did you see Aubrey Pollard
make a threatening
move toward my client?
Or are you perhaps confused
on that point as well?
Yes, sir.
Being a military man,
you would be able to distinguish
between the uniforms of
a National Guardsman
and that of a Detroit police
officer. Is that correct?
I suppose.
And so you say
that the man who took one of
the victims into the room,
that he was a
National Guardsman?
So I presume you
know that because
he was wearing a uniform
of the National Guard.
Well, yes. I saw a guy in
uniform take him back there.
Did you see anybody else
go back into that room?
No.
Would you have been able to see
if anybody else went
back into that room?
At the time, wasn't your
head turned back around
by the police officers
that were still standing
there with you?
Yes.
And so in one of the lineups,
when you were asked to identify
the officers who beat you,
who did you identify?
Do you see him here
today in court?
Him.
And him.
You just identified two
of the defendants.
Why would you identify
only one of them
at the time of the lineup
if both of them took
part in beating you?
Which recollection
for the record
would you say is the
correct recollection?
I just said I couldn't
tell at first.
When I went down to the police
station, I was very nervous.
And so now, you are calm?
And you will not be changing
your story again then?
This is it? This is the one
you want us to work with?
Objection. Asked and answered.
Overruled.
So, you were led into a room,
and then what happened?
He fired off a shot by
my head and told me...
To keep my mouth
shut and lay still.
Or the next one for real.
And what did you do?
I lie still.
And were you mistreated
in any way after that?
Mistreated?
Have you ever been
arrested, sir?
Sure.
Ever spent a night in jail?
Yeah.
How many times have
you been arrested?
- I don't know.
- How many nights and days have you spent
in prison for crimes
you've committed...
I don't know, a few...
Or alleged to have committed?
Criminal acts.
I don't know. A few.
Are you certain?
Yeah, you don't forget
a beating like that.
So you're certain
that these three men
beat you and the others?
Yes, I'm certain.
Up until some army guy
pulled me in a room
and told me to lie still.
Then you heard him go out
and tell them I was dead.
And this is what's
being referred to
as the "death game"?
What did you see next?
I didn't see nothin' lying
face down on the floor,
but I heard Aubrey
yell, "Don't shoot."
And he shot. I heard that.
Your witness, council.
Now we've already talked
to your cohort about,
friend, Lee, about
his criminal past.
Have you ever had
trouble with the law?
I'm not on trial here.
No need to introduce
a new crime, sir.
Just the ones already known.
Or maybe you can
start by telling us,
how did the night begin?
Party? A few drinks?
Man, why? Why y'all
talking about me at all?
Man, y'all see a black man in court
and assume I'm the one on trial.
Man, they killed
my friends, man!
They beat us!
Lined us up and abused us and
y'all doing the same thing!
There's no justice here,
man. Go fuck yourself, man.
- Man, no, get off of me!
- Take him out.
This is bullshit!
What? What you lookin' at?
I think what is clear
here, Your Honor,
is that these men were under
an intolerable situation.
They were under this duress,
which we say was inherent,
and for that reason,
had no other choice.
All right.
All they had to do
was keep quiet.
If they kept quiet, they
wouldn't be here today.
But they made a statement,
and that statement
should be admissible.
Not if they were made
under duress, Your Honor.
Not if the taking
of those statements
violates constitutional rights.
These policemen were
owed an obligation.
Advising them that they had
a right to remain silent,
they had a right to counsel,
and that anything they said
could be used against them
in a court of law.
I don't think these defendants,
because they're police officers,
have any right to expect
anything more from us,
but they have a right
under the Constitution
not to settle for anything less.
I therefore rule the
statements inadmissible.
Wasn't that just a
load of bullshit.
Wow, man.
That was...
You know as well I do,
those kids shouldn't have
been killed like that.
Yeah. It's a shame.
Should've complied
with a lawful order
and relinquish their weapons.
But you're a solid guy though.
Really.
They know what they're
supposed to do.
Jury entering. All rise.
All rise.
Has the jury reached a
verdict in this matter,
with regard to the
charges of murder
in the first degree and assault?
We have, Your Honor.
On the assault,
not guilty.
As to the murder charges,
What we have witnessed today is a
disappointment to the justice system,
to the state of Michigan.
Excuse me, would you
like to comment?
This wouldn't have happened
if they had found black girls
in a hotel with white men.
No, sir. No way
would they do this
to white men. That's the truth!
And I don't care who knows it!
Thank you, ma'am. Mr. Pollard, how
do you feel about losing your son?
How do you think he feels?
How would you feel?
It's a terrible pain.
- A pain that never goes away.
- Come on.
Thanks, man.
Listen, sir, will you
conduct yourself
with a little bit of empathy?
We are here today to witness
the justice system at
work and we demand
that police criminality be
treated the exact same way
as any other form
of criminality.
Some people would say it's wrong
to judge the police
for doing their jobs.
Nice try.
- You have my statement.
- What a shame.
Police criminality
needs to be treated
the same as any other
form of criminality.
Some people are
made of plastic
You know some people
are made of wood
Some people have
hearts of stone
- Some people are up to
no good -Some people
But baby
I'm for real
I'm as real as real can get
And if what you're looking
for is real lovin'
Then what you see
Is what you get
We have a contract, Larry.
We got to snatch this, brother.
Not like this.
Look, Motown is a
black-only company.
But you know what I mean.
Who listens to this music?
This ain't easy for me, man.
We all a long way from easy.
Well, then you do what you need.
I'm gonna lay low.
Come on, man.
- Excuse me, brother.
- Yes, son.
I submitted an application for
the church choir director
and I never heard anything back.
Speak to the choirmaster.
Okay, thank you.
Excuse me.
I submitted an application for
the church choir director
and I never heard anything back.
Larry Cleveland Reed.
Larry.
I remember. You're with
The Dramatics, right?
Yes, sir.
You're a little bit
overqualified.
We're just a
neighborhood church.
Well, yeah, I am
overqualified. So?
Why don't you go try some
of those clubs downtown?
I'm sure they'd be
happy to have you.
And I guarantee you, the
pay will be much better.
There's police at
those clubs downtown.
And it's dangerous.
Sir, can you please
help me? I need a job.
Do you sing any
liturgical music?
Yeah, I know something.
Let me see if I...
Okay.
♪Master
♪The tempest is raging
♪Oh the billows
♪Are tossing high
♪The sky
♪Is overshadowed with blackness
♪No shelter or help
♪Is nigh
♪Carest thou not
♪That we perish?
♪How can thou lie asleep
♪When each moment
♪So madly is threatening
♪Oh a grave A grave
♪A grave A grave
♪In the angry deep
♪Get up, Jesus Because
After receiving death threats
Melvin Dismukes moved to
the suburbs and
worked as security guard
for department store Sears Roebuck
Although the three Officers were
found not guilty
of criminal charges, they
werent returned to active duty
Years later a civil court ruled
against one of the officers
He was ordered to pay a fine to Aubrey Pollards family
of five thousand dollars
Fred Temples family sued
the city of Detroit
for wrongful death
As part of the settlement,
the city did not admit any guilt
Carl Cooper's starter pistol
was never found
Julie Ann Hysel left Detroit
and worked as a hair dresser
raising four children
The "Dramatics" broke out
in the seventies with several hits
and continue to perform to this day
Larry Cleveland Reed never
rejoined the band
He still lives in Detroit
singing in a church choir
The facts around the murders at the Algiers Motel on July 25th 1967
were never conclusively established in a criminal proceeding
As a result, portions of this film were constructed and drmatized
based on recollections of the alleged participants and supporting
documents