In prison, people often ask
how you ended up there.
After answering
the same question over and over...
your memory becomes hazy.
They say it's a process of forgetting.
That once you're out,
you forget it all.
And you can start over.
Hello? Still at the shop?
I've already got the tickets.
I'm not waiting if you're late.
ARE YOU LONESOME TONIGHT?
MISSING
Excuse me!
I'd like to file a criminal case.
What's it about?
My husband's been missing for days now.
That would be missing persons.
Fill out the form.
Any news?
Not yet.
Hello?
Liang, is that you?
It's your lucky day!
We provide free air-con maintenance--
I don't need it!
It's him.
Honey, is dinner ready?
Mom, where's my white shirt?
Hi. I'm here to fix the air-con.
Just a second.
Hello?
Yes, speaking.
The air-con's in the living room.
Hang on. I'll write it down.
Xin.
It's spelled...
X-I-N.
Restaurant.
Okay.
Wipe your shoes.
What's wrong with it?
It turns on, but there's no cold air.
Did you find him?
I did.
Hey, Fatso!
Where are you going?
Is it ready?
Yes.
Who the hell are you?
Are you 18 yet?
Think you're all grown up?
Smoking at your age?
Leave him alone!
Give me one.
Lighter!
- I want to turn myself in.
- You want to do what?
- What did you do?
- I hit someone with my car.
- Please hold.
- Where's that person now?
- I don't know.
Do you know who you hit?
Xiaoqin! Come here for a sec.
Wait here.
What's got into you lately?
You don't even go to work.
I'm looking for someone.
Who?
I don't know.
I have something that belongs to him.
I just want to give it back.
You must be hiding something.
Are you hiding something from me?
No.
You missed the movie
and didn't apologize.
Typical.
Who knows
what's going on in your head.
I'm off.
Mrs. Liang,
have some watermelon.
- I'll pay.
- My treat.
Give me a quarter.
Any updates on Mr. Liang?
I think I'll brave it.
Take care!
PROFESSIONAL AIR-CON REPAIR
Hello, I'm the air-con technician.
I ran your husband over.
I'm sorry.
Hi, I'm the air-con technician.
I ran over your husband.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
I'm the air-con technician.
I ran over your husband.
I'm sorry.
Did you find him?
I did.
Mrs. Liang!
What a time to be mopping the floor!
- We're from the Residents Committee.
- That's very kind!
We've come to see how you're doing.
Sisters!
Let's sit in the living room.
So sorry for your loss.
Let me get you some water.
I'll get you some water.
We can manage.
It's so hot in here!
The air-con's broken and there's no fan.
Let's bring some chairs in here.
Please, take a seat!
Sisters!
We've all heard the sad news.
Lord, Huifang's husband
left all too suddenly.
She is distraught. And devastated.
The police asked me
why I acted the way I did,
going to her home.
I have no idea why.
The strange thing is,
she didn't look that sad.
As if she expected it to happen.
Don't keep it all inside.
Cry as much as you like.
I can't cry.
I just can't.
Look after yourself.
- Make sure you eat.
- Thank you.
How much will it cost?
Don't worry, I'm almost finished.
Free of charge.
Even you are taking pity on me.
It's not that.
It's okay, really.
I just have too much time now.
When they were around,
I had to cook, do the laundry.
Barely had any time to myself.
And now,
I don't know what to do with myself.
Can I have a cigarette?
Light.
Liang used to smoke three packs a day,
but he wouldn't let me smoke.
She said so many things that day.
Things she could only tell strangers.
Things she'd never tell her friends.
I wanted to tell her.
But I held back every time.
What on earth am I doing?
- Have you eaten, Mrs. Liang?
- Not yet.
If you're ever bored,
feel free to come over.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Told you her husband was up to no good.
See how it ended?
I just saw two suspicious-looking men
standing outside her door.
- Said they were looking for her.
- Stop being so nasty.
She's had a tough enough time as it is.
Nasty?
It's not like I'm shouting it out
in public.
All fixed.
Mrs. Liang?
Your husband owes us 50,000 bucks.
Would you rather transfer the money or...?
- I don't have any money.
- No money?
Let's see if there's anything
valuable in there.
- You can pay us in kind.
- I don't have anything of value!
Hey, you!
This is all I have.
Take it for now.
You get into fights a lot, don't you?
There's a scar on your nose.
Car crash.
Why don't you stay for dinner?
I don't cook much for myself.
If it's the two of us,
I can cook something nice.
He always shows up when there's food.
Dig in.
- Not great, eh?
- It's good.
You're a nice man,
but why the long face?
Something bothering you?
What are you doing?
Get out.
You should leave.
I can never fall asleep at night.
I walk around aimlessly.
I don't know when the cops will find me.
I think I'm actually waiting for them.
Who the hell are you?
Prison is the same every day.
Even the nightmares
don't change much.
The Feng Shui is great here.
Who would this be for?
I need two plots.
One for my husband and one for me.
How about these two?
They're cool in the summer,
warm in the winter.
And sheltered from the wind and rain.
Anything available in Zone Two?
You mean here?
I'm sorry.
There's only one left here.
Put my name on it
so I can be buried with my son.
We'll find something else for my husband.
How did your son die?
He had heart problems from a young age.
But...
the doctor said...
he could've been saved.
I was away that day.
He managed to get up
and call his dad.
- The ambulance took too long?
- No.
Liang was drunk.
He didn't answer his call.
The morning Liang left...
we got into a fight.
The last thing I said to him was...
"You might as well drop dead,
for all I care.
I won't be here when you come back."
But I waited for him all night.
Maybe if I hadn't said that,
he'd still be alive.
Let's go.
If the person who ran over
your husband apologized,
would you forgive him?
No.
What good would that do anyway?
How did you know he was ran over?
Because I did it.
My husband was shot with a gun.
He had two bullet holes in his body.
I've stashed the money away.
We'll split it when the job's done.
We'll steal what we can.
And use force if necessary.
Earlier this morning,
the Yuexin Police Bureau was informed
that a male body was found by the river.
A police investigation is now underway.
This is a popular leisure destination
where both the young and old
can enjoy tranquility and relaxation.
But this morning's discovery
will likely change everything.
Detective Chen, can you tell us
about the crime scene?
Our investigation is well underway.
The police are taking this very seriously.
That Northern dancer was looking for
Liang, claiming he was going to kill him.
Now everyone knows
Liang had a large sum of money.
Freeze!
What did you want from Liang?
Well...
I just wanted to buy a cheap car.
I heard that was the place to get one.
I finally found him.
He said it was tax-free and cheap.
You planned to kill him, right?
Nothing like that--
So how come we found
a dozen machetes in your room?
The machetes?
We'd gone all the way to Guangzhou,
so we wanted to buy some souvenirs.
But there wasn't much choice.
So we bought the machetes.
You call yourself a man?
- You stab people over an insult?
- They can insult me, but not my family!
Think you're special, eh?
You won't talk?
Mrs. Liang! Have a seat.
What did you fight over?
Something silly.
Very silly. I forget.
Do you know what kind of company
your husband kept?
A month ago, he mentioned
he was going on a long trip
with some big boss.
Do you know this big boss?
I rarely asked that kind of thing.
He never gave me any details.
So you haven't seen him
since your fight that morning?
You two...
don't get along, do you?
Stop standing around like an idiot.
There's work to do!
We're closing soon.
But you can order here.
Was it you who called
Mrs. Liang the other day?
Lee!
Here's another one looking for someone.
Have you met the missing man?
I thought he was dead.
A bunch of fuckwits came that night.
They took off when the power went out.
I lost a bunch of money.
Was he alone?
Or with someone else?
How would I know?
Care for a song?
Only five bucks a tune.
The person you're looking for
asked me to sing a song once.
He sat right
where you're sitting now.
There was a blackout that night.
It was hot.
Everyone was feeling the heat.
When it's hot, people get edgy.
But those two kept on talking
about some money.
One of them refused to pay the other.
Then the man said the money
was in a locker at the train station.
He dared him
to check the lockers one by one.
They didn't say anything else after that.
A bit later, a person got up and left.
Another followed,
a gun in his hand.
Are you really blind?
I'm blind...
and not blind.
Same song, then.
SOUTH RAILWAY STATION
Train 049 will arrive shortly.
Keep an eye on your luggage.
Keep moving.
Watch your children and the elderly.
No spitting!
No urinating in the station!
Come here.
I'm talking to you.
Yes, you! You finally showed up.
Think you can avoid paying
the late collection fee?
Are you Liang Mo?
Locker 19. You're Liang, right?
You're two weeks overdue.
I'm keeping your deposit.
Pay me another 180,
then take your stuff.
That much?
No spitting!
No urinating in the station!
Be civil.
Walk in an orderly fashion.
Hands off my car or I'll kill you!
Drunken idiot!
Don't move!
Take a look.
Can't see the license plate clearly.
There are cars like this everywhere.
It was parked there
for just a short time.
Is tomorrow morning's meeting still on?
Of course. The chief's coming, too.
Hope I don't sleep through it.
It's so late.
Drunken idiot!
Call an ambulance, quick!
Let's go!
Lieutenant Liu here
reporting a carjacking
and attempted murder.
The suspect's heading towards Nanshan.
Requesting backup.
Don't move!
You go that way.
- See anything?
- No.
This way!
Grab some food while you can.
This shipment has to be
in Hong Kong by Friday.
Here to buy pineapples?
- Yeah.
- Got the cash?
Here.
Take a bite!
Here's a US 1639 knock-off.
Robbery or murder.
Revenge.
All covered.
It's for self-defense.
Let's go. This way.
This eight-barrel bad boy's
my own creation.
Fires eight rounds in one shot.
You don't even need to aim.
I'll pass.
People shouldn't be ashamed
of the dark side of their humanity.
They should instead reflect
on how they dare not face the truth
when presented with the facts.
The evolution of human society is,
on some level,
a process of our false sense of dignity
being constantly peeled away.
Darwin's theory of evolution
revealed the intrinsic links
between humans and animals.
Whereas Freud uncovered that,
beneath our rationality,
lie powerful natural
impulses and desires.
I'm looking for someone.
Does Wang Xueming live here?
Upstairs.
Where's your rent?
I already gave it to your daughter--
Stop!
I heard the whole thing.
Two dark figures were shouting outside.
One asking for his money,
the other saying he didn't have any.
- He wouldn't give him the money.
- So it was just about money?
Yeah, money.
One was on the ground.
The other was smashing his head
with something.
What with?
A brick? No, not a brick.
A club or something.
- He told you to call the police?
- That's right.
I saw a gun on the ground.
A handgun.
So I picked it up
and took a shot into the air.
Both suspects are now
in police custody.
You don't have to cover for him.
Let us know if you remember anything.
Is this the right place?
Yes.
Are you sure?
I told them I buried the money
under a palm tree.
But some drunkard must have
passed by and taken the money.
Wang Xueming is being released today.
Thanks for letting me know.
At the time, I just felt like letting go.
Not because I particularly wanted to die,
but because I didn't have
anything to live for.
And then...
when I stepped into the water,
a stone flew in from behind.
But when I looked back,
there was no one there.
Could it have been Wang Xueming?
I don't know.
It's ironic, wouldn't you say?
The same man who ran over my husband
might also be the one who saved my life.
Did they catch the murderer?
He was sentenced to be executed
by a firing squad.
What about Wang Xueming?
He should be out soon.
So I heard.
Let me take you out to dinner.
We can continue our chat.
You never told me
what happened to the money.
Next time.
I've already bought my dinner.
- Coming next week?
- I will if you are.
I could keep you company.
I only bought dinner for one.
I thought you were afraid
of eating alone.
Not anymore.
See you next week.
Bye!
Please sign this.
Bottom left-hand corner.
Here are your personal belongings.
- I don't need them.
- Take them anyway.
Anyone picking you up?
- Do you know which bus to take?
- Yeah.
Your allowance and
remuneration for your work.
Here's your release certificate.
You need to apply for a new ID
and residence card.
Thanks, Officer.