Up you go.
Increase your rate of climb.
Our communication equipment's
been destroyed.
And if your radio and satellite phone
were in those trailers--
-They were.
-Then we're stuck here.
And stuck together, thanks to you people.
We came to watch.
You came to strip-mine the place.
-Back off.
-At least we came prepared.
Five years of work and electrified fence
couldn't prepare the other island.
-You think your Marlboro men will help?
-You're looters. You came to take.
You have no rights.
An extinct animal brought
back to life has no rights.
It exists because we made it.
We patented it. We own it.
-You looking for a problem?
-And I found you, didn't l?
I know you.
You're that Earth First bastard.
-What's Earth First?
-Professional saboteurs.
-Environmentalists!
-Criminals.
Knock it off! Listen to me.
moving the baby to our camp may have
changed the adults' perceived territory.
Their what?
That's why they attacked the trailers.
-They're defending this entire area now.
-We have to move now.
To where? Our boat and their airlift
are waiting for orders we can't send.
There's a communications centre here
near the old operations building.
Everything ran on geothermal power.
It was never meant to need replenishing.
If we can get here,
we can send a radio call to the airlift.
-You know the frequency?
-Here in this book.
-We'll mind those.
-How far is the village?
A day's walk, maybe more.
-That's not the problem.
-What is?
What is the problem?
Velociraptors.
Their nesting sites are
in the island's interior, which is why...
-...we were keeping to the outer rim.
-Wait. What's a Veloc--
Velociraptor. Carnivore. Pack hunter.
Two meters tall, long snout...
...binocular vision, strong forearms,
killing claws on both feet.
The Rexes may track us, too,
if they feel we're a threat to their infant.
No, we'll lose them
once we leave their territory.
Don't bet on it. Tyrannosaur has the
largest proportional olfactory cavity...
...of any creature in fossil record,
except one.
The Turkey Vulture
could scent up to 10 miles.
Right. This is all very thrilling,
but I say we should head for the village.
We could head back down to the lagoon.
And sit out in the open,
near a heavily used water source...
-...hope that your captain comes back?
-He won't. He knows better.
Then we head for the village,
find shelter and call for help.
Rex just fed, so he won't stalk us for food.
Just fed? You mean Eddie?
Show some respect.
-He saved our lives by giving his.
-Then his troubles are over.
my point is predators don't hunt
when they're not hungry.
-No, only humans do.
-You're breaking our heart.
Saddle up!
Let's get this moveable feast underway.
Excuse me, cowboy.
You want some gum?
You seem like you have common sense.
Why the hell are you here?
Somewhere on this island
is the greatest predator that ever lived.
The second greatest predator
must take him down.
-You going to use that?
-If he doesn't surrender, yes.
-Let me see it.
-No.
The animal exists for the first time
in tens of millions of years...
...and the only way you can express
yourself is to kill it.
Remember that chap about 20 years ago?
I forget his name.
Climbed Everest without any oxygen.
Came down nearly dead.
They asked him,
"Why did you go up there to die?"
He said, "l didn't. I went up there to live."
I didn't wish you luck on your new venture.
You're off to a promising start.
my team is intact.
I'm sorry for the loss of your man.
It's easy to criticise someone
who generates an idea, assumes the risk.
When you try to sound like Hammond,
it comes off as a hustle.
It's not your fault.
They say talent skips a generation.
I'm sure your kids will be sharp as tacks.
Hammond's reach exceeded his grasp.
mine does not.
Taking dinosaurs off this island...
...is the worst idea in the long,
sad history of bad ideas.
And I'll be there when you learn that.
Take a break. Five minutes.
Are you injured?
No, it's the baby's. I set its broken leg.
It won't dry in the humidity.
Roland, a word?
I'd love to know where we are.
making friends with Ahab?
Carter, I'm going to the ladies' room.
Wait for me here. Okay?
It's not polite to sneak up on people.
Carter! Where are you?
I got turned around in here.
Shit!
Carter, let me hear from you!
Okay, break's over. moving on!
Carry me.
Get off!
-When did you last see him?
-10, 15 minutes.
Come with me. And you.
If he's alive, we'll find him.
The rest of you go on.
You'll reach the ridge in 10 minutes.
Wait for us there.
No one tells the little girl.
Right. Let's carry on.
Everybody up.
Come on. Up, up.
All right guys, let's get the hell out of here.
Did you find him?
Just the parts they didn't like. map.
The operations building
is right down in there...
...about a mile and a half
from the base of these cliffs.
-How do you know that?
-I've seen it.
The climb down won't be easy.
We'll let them sleep one more hour.
Then we hit it.
What is that?
Stay down! Don't move!
Don't run!
Don't look, just run! Run!
Bastard!
You son of a bitch!
He can't reach you! Stay back!
He can't reach us!
Oh, my God! A snake!
Stay back!
It's okay.
It's coming back!
Dad!
Thank you.
Don't go into the long grass!
Not into the long grass!
Look at this.
-What is it?
-I think it's Ajay's bag.
Go, as fast as you can.
Go!
I see structures there.
They said the communications centre
is in the operations building.
I'll get in there and send the radio call.
See you there.
-Wait for us.
-Every second counts.
If you can keep up, you're welcome to try.
-Okay, here we come.
-No! Rest.
Damn it!
CQ, this is InGen Operations
Harvest Leader to Harvest Base.
Repeating, I'm calling
for InGen Harvest Leader...
-...seeking InGen Harvest Base.
-Go ahead, Harvest Leader.
The operation has suffered
severe casualties.
The survivors are now in mortal danger.
I need you to send rescue immediately.
Our co-ordinates here are...
...9?58' north, 85?...
Here, here!
Inside! Anywhere!
Go.
-Where do I go when I'm out?
-I'm right behind you--
Look out!
Up here!
Hey, you!
The school cut you from the team?
Get out of here!
Come on. Let's go!
Let's go!
-What about the other survivors?
-Another chopper's coming.
It's okay. It's over.
That's one souvenir
they won't be taking with them.
Find the infant tyrannosaur.
Roland knows where the nest is.
I want it on my jet.
I'll take it directly to the infirmary
in San Diego.
Hurry. I want to be airborne
before the female knows.
You probably saved InGen.
We lost everything
we came after on this trip.
But this animal
and its infant will bail us out.
Congratulations.
You've got your trophy!
A buck.
But it's alive! Everyone will line up
and appreciate it and what you did for us.
What's the matter?
He didn't make it. Ajay.
I'm sorry.
Really, I am.
I remember the people who help me.
There's a job for you in San Diego,
if you want it.
No, thank you.
I've spent enough time
in the company of death.
Oh, my God.
Fifteen years ago,
John Hammond had a dream.
Like John himself, the dream was grand.
It was outsized. It was bold.
It was impractical. It was not to be.
Half an hour from now...
...John Hammond's dream,
re-imagined, will come true.
For .01 of the cost
of building a destination resort....
Is this the Ludlow affair?
-This is private property.
-We're on the list.
Turn around, get back in your car.
-This is Dr. Harding, I'm Dr. Malcolm.
-We have Mr. Ludlow's test results.
There's good and bad news.
Tonight we will christen
Jurassic Park, San Diego...
...a mega-attraction
that will drive turnstile numbers...
...to rival any theme park in the world.
I want to thank each one of you for coming
in these wee small hours of the morning.
-The ship is here.
-It's early?
You better come now.
It's so exciting!
-See that couple?
-Sir, you need to look at this.
Let them see this up close.
I need a direct line to the Coast Guard.
Look. That's their transponder signal,
Venture 5888.
-They're coming in, but I can't raise them.
-Try again.
Skipper, SS Venture, this is InGen
Harbour master. Do you copy? Over.
Skipper, SS Venture, you are approaching
the breakwater at flank speed.
Reduce at once. Over.
SS Venture, reduce your speed at once.
SS Venture, this is InGen Harbour master.
You are entering a docking area.
What's everybody looking at?
We should've stayed in the car.
-You okay, Mr. Ludlow?
-I don't know. How do I look?
-Oh, my God.
-Where's the crew?
All over the place.
I smell a fuel leak!
Check the cargo hold!
-There may be crew down there.
-Everybody off the boat!
No! Get away from that!
Now you're John Hammond.
-Why wasn't it tranquillised?
-It was hit it with two darts of Carfentanil.
-It was over 10 milligrams.
-That'd put it in a coma.
It stopped breathing.
We gave it naltrexone to counteract.
But we didn't know how much.
You gave an antagonist
without knowing the dosage?
You put it in a narcoleptic state.
It's a locomotive now.
-We're prepared here.
-Any more dinosaurs on the boat?
No, the infant was flown in.
We had this to tranquillise it.
Do you have the infant?
It's safe.
The animal's dehydrated.
First, it'll go to a water source...
...then look for the next thing
its body needs.
All the containment equipment is here.
We must get it back to the boat.
I know what you're gonna say.
When we brought the baby to the trailer,
it came.
There's no reason why it won't do
the same thing here.
Where's the infant?
In a secured facility. Why?
Where's the facility?
There's a dinosaur in our backyard.
Benjamin, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
What?
Come on. There's a dinosaur
in our backyard.
The problem is, you need to read to him.
If you serve him dinner,
he won't be up all night.
It's the stupid fish tank!
He needs a proper nightlight.
-It may as well be daytime.
-Just turn it off.
Slow down. Slow it down!
There it is.
He's sedated.
Really heavily. Give me a hand.
When the adult sees us again
with his baby, isn't he going to be like:
"You!"
There may be some angry recognition.
Who knows?
He may be just happy to see us.
What the hell are you doing?
We're taking the kid.
If you really want to stop us, shoot us.
-How will we find the adult?
-Follow the screams.
-There.
-Oh, my God.
It's too drugged.
He won't know we have it
unless it makes some sound!
Wake up. Come on.
He knows.
Ian, slow down a little.
I don't think so.
This guy's almost fully awake.
You know where you're going?
The waterfront's on the other side
of these warehouses.
-Is there a way through?
-There could be.
There we go.
You have to follow me now.
-Got him?
-Yep.
-Ready?
-Where's the Rex? Is it still behind us?
There's the water.
Shoot it. Tell them to shoot it.
No, you idiot, the adult. Shoot the adult.
I want the baby back alive.
What have you done with it?
I want that infant!
Are you there?
There you are.
There's a first-rate shot
of the deck of the ship...
...and the cargo hold that,
for the moment...
...contains the animal itself,
presumably with the infant alongside.
By our calculations, they are nearing
the halfway point of this trip.
Jim, can you hear me there?
Yes, I can, Bernard.
We are halfway to the island.
It is 206 nautical miles
from our present location.
The ship is moving at 20 knots...
...which will put it in at about 11:30 a.m.,
Eastern time.
One of the Navy's primary concerns
has been safety.
If we look at the ever-growing escort
around the ship...
...they're taking no chances of a repeat
of the San Diego incident.
Let's take a moment to run the tape...
...of our interview earlier today
with John Hammond.
He's the former head
of InGen BioEngineering...
...the man who is now spearheading
this movement...
...not only to return the animals
to their island...
...but to keep the island itself intact.
It is absolutely imperative...
...that we work with the Costa Rican
Department of Biological Preserves...
...to establish a set of rules...
...for the preservation and isolation
of that island.
These creatures require our absence
to survive, not our help.
And if we could only step aside...
...and trust in nature...
...life will find a way.
Subtitles by SOFTITLER