(Tale of The Nine Tailed)
I told you to sit tight, didn't I?
And so we meet again. How long has it been exactly?
I didn't have to torture the traitor to get my answers.
I wanted him to tell you where and when to meet me.
I see the blade won't kill you.
Back then, I wore the skin of a mortal.
Not this time though.
You have some cute tricks.
I wanted a chance to measure our powers.
Sounds good to me.
Not bad.
You know nothing about me, Lee Yeon.
I've lived far longer than you think I have.
I existed long before you were born.
The past is just a past.
And I'll outlive you.
Don't dream of an unrealistic future.
In order to become a deity...
and finally be free of this world's darkness,
you endured 1,000 years beneath the black water.
This world would've been mine...
had I not been spotted by a human while ascending as a dragon.
I feel bad for you. It's like...
getting kicked out of an exam...
because you got caught with your phone.
How sad.
But that's how your fate has been designed, Imoogi.
You really should get a proper name.
You haven't changed at all. You're still very arrogant.
You must think you have the world at your feet.
I don't know about anything else, but I do think that way about you.
You make me want to trample on you.
Your brother, your woman,
and the life of her parents.
I have control over them all.
What do you have?
Let me make a reasonable offer.
Lee Yeon, if you give up your body, I will let everyone else live.
What do I look like to you?
Seogyeong Traitor.
You're the one who took my parents!
This is the carnation I folded for them.
Flip it over.
(Ji A, why won't you save us?)
Ji A, why won't you save us?
Are they alive?
- Where? - Bring me the mountain spirit,
and I'll return your parents to you.
- Tell me where they are! - You saw them,
but failed to recognize them.
What do you mean by that?
You'll soon find out.
I won't let you get away with this.
Call the cops then or perhaps your boyfriend.
Any option will do,
but you won't ever see your parents again.
Why? Why my parents?
Because I knew this day would come.
You would do anything to save your parents.
Just like how you saved your father in your past life,
I hope that you'll once again make a wise choice.
You'll let everyone go if I give up my body?
Ji A, her parents, and even Rang?
I'd like the entire package,
but just the heart will also do.
Are you serious?
I am.
So what will it be? Yes or no?
I...
I don't want to.
- Why not? - Because you seem like the type...
to go back on a deal.
I don't do business with those kinds.
I'll personally free them all from your grip.
Then enjoy...
trampling on those you treasure.
I know this isn't appropriate to ask,
but why did you come back?
As if anyone would welcome...
the symbol of calamity, plague, and war.
If you're asking me my view of the world, I don't have one.
All I want is one thing.
I want that woman.
The woman who was supposed to be offered to me as a sacrifice...
but ended up saving you and killing me.
I like her.
How dare you?
That's enough. I just wanted to test your power.
For me, this is just the beginning.
"I want to die. Now."
Do you feel it?
I knew it. You're connected to him.
- What? - You are his shell.
Why are you doing this?
You're also human.
I'm human, so I don't want to die, and I have so many desires.
Was committing treason not enough for you?
All I did was dream of a new world...
after having been born as a lowlife.
My kids, wife, and mother.
All I wanted to do was make sure they could eat proper food.
But they called it treason and threatened to behead me.
And that's when I met him.
I'm sure it wasn't for free.
What did you have to give in return for being able to stay alive?
My kids, wife, and mother.
I offered my family to Imoogi and was able live in return.
You're crazy.
You must lose something in order to gain something.
So you want me to sell Yeon out?
You want me to become someone like you?
The choice is yours, Ji A.
Because of you, your parents were gone for half their lives.
You can either see them at their funeral or...
One drop of this will be enough...
to make him fall into a deep sleep.
Put Yeon to sleep.
Then you can get the life you've always dreamed of.
(Chapter 11: Ground Cherries)
I told you we should've gotten a massage chair.
We'll only end up using it as a clothing rack.
It's a waste of money.
I'm old now, so my body isn't as healthy as...
Will you put some strength into your hands?
Got it.
Bok Gil used to give great massages.
He was also worried that you were always working day and night,
so he'd gather the bark of hardy rubber trees and Siberian ginseng...
and boil them for your joints...
I don't want to hear you talking about that unfilial son.
Don't call my son unfilial.
Get out.
Why do you keep acting like you're the only one...
who's heartbroken because of our son's death?
I said get out!
It was because of you.
He wouldn't have committed suicide...
if you hadn't killed his wife.
She was possessed with a ghost that causes plagues.
I couldn't just sit back and watch the entire nation...
suffer from a plague because of her.
Exactly.
That's who you are.
You're neither Bok Gil's mother nor my wife.
You're just the gatekeeper of the Samdo River.
Meanwhile, I've been trying so hard...
to understand you for so long, but I guess that was foolish of me.
I don't even want to look at you. Just leave!
(132 people committed suicide in Geumran-gu.)
(Grim Reapers are required to gather at the Temple of Death.)
It's Imoogi, isn't it?
You have two days to bring me Lee Yeon.
It's his body I need.
Rather than thinking about breaking the deal,
think of a way to untangle the mess.
Imoogi, that scumbag.
What in the world has he done?
("Unprecedented Mass Suicide, Citizens in Shock")
Can you believe this?
It's like a horror movie.
How could 132 people in the same district...
all commit suicide at the same time?
Do you think they were some kind of a suicide group?
There wasn't a single will found.
People who commit suicide normally feel the urge...
to let people know why they chose to die.
Or maybe it was a cult.
In the 1970s, a group of cult believers in Jonestown...
committed mass suicide.
They all drank poison,
but this time, the causes of death are all different.
This is so weird.
I'm back.
Hey, Terry. You're back.
Hey, wait. You were at Geumran-gu. Hey, are you...
Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
- Pardon? - Didn't you see the news?
An hour ago, a group of people died there.
- Really? - Where is Ji A?
Didn't she come with you?
She left early saying something urgent came up.
- Isn't she at the office? - Really?
I didn't see her come back.
- Here's the footage I took. - Thank you.
How was it today?
Did Ji A give you a hard time?
No, not at all. She's really kind.
(Nam Ji A)
Bring me the mountain spirit,
and I'll return your parents to you.
(Lee Yeon)
(Ji A, why won't you save us?)
Come in.
My goodness.
This place is nice.
The living room is spacious, but there aren't a lot of rooms.
I guess vets make a lot of money.
Come this way.
Have a seat.
This is...
It's borscht, a traditional Russian dish.
I know you probably didn't grow up eating this.
But I thought you might miss the smell of where you're from.
Don't you like it?
I sometimes miss the forest where I was born and grew up in.
Right now, it's turned into an apartment complex.
I know this smell. I also like it.
On top of that, it's delicious.
Eat up.
I'm sorry.
Geomdoong?
Mister.
You brat. Get back here.
Don't annoy me. I will kill you.
Who's this?
My stepdad.
Come out. Get over here.
You choose.
You ask me for help,
I'll make sure you never have to see him again.
Or I'll just go my way.
Hey you. Do you know him?
Why are you butting into our family matter?
Quiet. I'm waiting to hear his response.
What are you? Are you a cop?
So...
I...
Soo Ho. Answer wisely. Got it?
I have to go home.
Okay.
Yu Ri, who has no friends or family.
- What? - I can't live without chicken,
but if you want to eat Russian food at every meal,
I'm willing to change my preferences.
What are you talking about?
I'm saying I want to become...
your family and your friend.
Family... Well,
I have something similar to that.
Your fake mom and dad that Lee Rang gave you?
The department store owner?
Yes.
I'm their dead daughter's fill-in and just an empty shell,
but they can't live without me.
People say...
they'd like to throw away their family if no one was watching.
Because they make life hard on each other.
But then again, you end up going back...
and taking them back.
Like Lee Yeon and Mr. Lee?
Right.
So...
Let the department owners have their lives back,
and become a true family with me and...
What are you guys doing here?
- Mr. Lee! - Yeon?
What are you doing here?
I live here.
Hey. Have you seen Ji A?
She wasn't here. Why?
She isn't at the office either. Where is she?
Anyway, keep doing whatever it was with the necklace thief.
This is Yeon's house?
It's okay. His house is my house.
Did you just laugh?
Sorry. Let's eat.
Mr. Lee?
What?
What are you doing here?
I felt like I could see you if I hung around here.
You weren't answering your phone all day long. Did something happen?
Yes.
Me too.
What happened?
But first...
Ta-da.
Open it.
Something that makes you happy just by thinking about it.
You remembered.
Of course.
The smell of freshly cooked rice, a complete set of world literature,
Dad's handmade gimbap, new sneakers,
and me.
Buy one, get one free.
They say if you buy your girlfriend sneakers, she'll run away.
Even if you run away, I want you to wear new sneakers...
and only go on nice paths.
Why are you smiling so sadly?
Do you not like them?
I do.
I never knew that the word "sneakers"...
had such a sweet meaning.
I like you.
So much that I wouldn't regret exchanging my life for you.
Should we take a walk?
On a nice path.
Together.
What's this?
What else? A fresh human.
Who is he?
None of your concern.
Turn him into a ground cherry for emergency food.
Much obliged.
He moved the ground cherry pot somewhere else?
Do you want to watch?
Are you allowed to show me?
There's nothing to hide between us.
It looks like an ordinary seed, doesn't it?
It traps the body and soul,
so I call it a latch for the body and soul.
Only Imoogi can create it.
What an evil soul.
He was in and out of prison...
Did you save a little kid?
I need at least one good deed...
to defend myself with when I enter the Afterlife.
- Do you want more milk? - Yes.
Eat up.
Stop eating already. That milk is mine.
Why doesn't that lady go home?
You go home.
Or I'll eat your liver.
I don't have a home anymore.
Stop acting all pathetic.
Thousands of people in Seoul don't have a home.
- Are you homeless too? - Not me.
Stop fighting.
Soo Ho, right? Where's your mom?
My mom got beat up every single day...
and ran away with some guy I don't know.
That's why my stepdad was so mad at me.
So you must have nowhere to go.
Oh, my gosh.
Mr. Lee, why are you doing this to me?
Eat up.
What are you thinking about?
You know the story "The Little Mermaid", right?
Andersen?
Yes.
Ever since I was a child, I hated the ending.
She could've lived if she had killed the prince.
So why did she turn into sea foam?
What about you? What would you do if it were you?
A long time ago, I thought I'd definitely kill the prince...
and save myself.
But? Have you changed your mind?
Now that I've met the prince,
I grew to like him much more than I imagined.
Although if the prince were gone,
the fairy tale could end with a happy ending.
If I were the little mermaid,
I'd kill the sea witch.
I'd rather not be her plaything.
I've been cursed.
I could have my parents back if I sell you out.
I've heard their wish,
so tell me yours.
I want my voice back...
and find my prince.
All while not turning into sea foam.
So come witch-hunting with me.
Are you sure you can spare such time?
Our deal expires in 24 hours.
It may very well be my last living day,
so what's it to you whether or not...
I let it go to waste?
You'll just throw your life away?
For the brother you loathe?
Imoogi met with Lee Yeon today.
He let your brother know of our three hostages.
Ji A, her parents, and you.
Where do you think he is right now?
Has he even called you in concern?
Liar.
You've been abandoned once again.
You're right. I did abandon you.
I'm sorry...
for saving you after your human mother abandoned you.
Yeon...
I never abandoned you.
He said he never once abandoned me.
You of all people know that it's a lie.
- Hey, kid! - Yeon?
He saved me from the Forest of the Starved.
He had to in order to save Ji A.
You're nothing but disposable.
Shut it!
Lee Yeon will do anything for Ji A...
even if that involves killing you.
If you go after her,
I'll kill you for real this time.
Will you give up your life...
for a brother who only cares for his girl?
Yes, Mr. Lee.
What? Shin Ju?
He wants to talk to you.
This is Shin Ju.
You know, right? Where's Yeon?
He went to see Ms. Nam.
So where?
I'll call you back with an answer.
It's 132 people.
The number of dead people who aren't on the list is...
There will be more.
- What? - He is chaos itself.
We're only getting started.
Then let's bring him in. Tell me how, and I'll do it myself.
It's beyond your capacity.
In order to bring him in,
you'll have to do what you hate with passion.
And what may that be?
Hey, Yeon. You're here.
What? My gosh, you...
Hello, sir and ma'am.
I'm Nam Ji A.
Well, Yeon told us a lot about you.
It's nice to meet you.
You!
How dare you bring a living person here?
I know she's a living person,
but she's also at the center of the argument you were having.
You have stepped in here far too early. Go back.
I'm well aware that you highly value rules and principles.
I came here knowing the risks because...
Do I look like your fairy godmother?
- What the... - Hold it.
Or maybe...
you'd like to know when you die.
No. I stay away from fortune tellers since I hate spoilers...
even about my own life.
- Then what? - I lost my parents at nine.
This isn't a place for your sob story.
I hear that I possess something that belongs to Imoogi.
That's also the fate you were handed.
I plan to defy that fate until my last breath.
It is why I came here knowing that it wasn't a place...
for living people.
- She's just like you. - Yes, we were made for each other.
I admire you not being intimidated by me.
So tell me why you're here.
Let me borrow Clairvoyance.
I wish to know where my parents are.
- What? - It won't be for free.
As if you have anything to offer in return.
I'd let you overcharge me knowingly,
but I don't have much to spare.
Then with what will you strike a deal?
We'll bring you Imoogi.
Yeon and I.
Gosh, I made it out alive.
Didn't you see me trembling in there?
It hardly seemed like the case.
I thought that past lives and the Afterlife...
only existed in comic books,
but they're real.
Sinners only have better lives...
until they take their last breaths.
Do you help the dead cross Samdo River from here?
I give a presentation about what to expect in the Afterlife,
catch those who refuse to cross the river,
and keep my wife happy.
I'm glad...
that someone as considerate as you is the first person...
people meet after passing.
You grew up well even though...
you lost your parents at a young age.
They'll be incredibly proud of you.
Will I ever get to see them again?
Let's trust Yeon and believe that he'll deliver.
This isn't like you, Granny.
Why do you say that?
Because you would've turned Imoogi into stone...
way before he became a problem.
I remember how you turned...
the northern mountain spirit into one...
just for getting on your wrong side.
So why...
is Imoogi an exception?
Because I don't want to see you go crazy.
- What do you mean by that? - A piece of him lies with her.
The Imoogi.
Is there a way...
to free her from it?
No.
Either she dies...
or the Imoogi leaves her voluntarily.
I don't believe that. How can a piece of it be with her?
You must've heard something about it.
Despite your best efforts, Imoogi was awoken.
The girl will be sacrificed,
and the rest of your life will be nothing but painful.
That...
is your fate.
Now I get why you didn't want me to find her.
From the start, you said we shouldn't meet.
You didn't want me to get hurt again.
You didn't want me dragged into that fate again.
Thanks, Granny.
But still, I choose her.
My only purpose in life was to meet her again.
It looks like...
you'll always end up making the same choice.
The ground cherries.
That's where her parents are.
Let's go.
- We'll be off now. - Oh, okay.
If anything happens,
come here and repeat my name three times.
I don't know if you'll win or lose the fight against fate,
but I still want to bet on you guys.
Thank you.
You should go now.
Did you find out?
The ground cherries.
"Ground cherries"?
I've never seen ground cherries in Seoul before.
Are these ground cherries?
That's where my mom and dad are?
How?
That plant can trap the body and soul of a living person.
And he used that to lengthen the lives of his followers.
Let's go. It was in the living room.
It was in the center of the living room.
He probably moved it somewhere else.
It wasn't there when I last went.
Our deal expires in 24 hours.
You drove a wedge between the two brothers.
Do you think Rang will fall for it?
Yes, he will.
Rang has a deep-rooted obsession for his brother.
It's a lot more twisted than you think.
You think he can kill him because he loves him?
Leave this to me.
I'll bring you Yeon's heart.
Don't look down on him.
The reason I got defeated by him long ago...
was because I underestimated him.
That's why I set up three traps.
We just need one of them to fall for it.
Once this is over, I'll go into politics.
I'm sick of pretending to be the CEO of a broadcasting company.
- And I deserve a reward. - Whatever you want.
You little monster.
Where do you think he is right now?
Has he even called you in concern?
You've been abandoned once again.
Will you give up your life...
for a brother who only cares for his girl?
- Yeon. - Were there ground cherries...
at Imoogi's house?
Ji A's parents are trapped inside there.
Do you know anything about that?
Is that all you have to say to me?
Did you see the cherries or not?
I did.
Where did he hide the cherries?
I don't know that much.
- Bye. - I can find out.
The CEO values it as much as his own life.
- Really? - Let's meet tomorrow.
Let's talk about it then.
Rang told me he'll look into it. I'm going to meet him tomorrow.
Where? What time? Should I go with you?
Leave it to me.
I need you to do the thing that only you can do.
What are you guys doing here?
We got too worried about her...
after knowing her boyfriend is a nine-tailed fox.
- Ji A. - What?
How did you know where I live?
Director Nam once did a background check on you.
Why did you come all the way here?
We came to see if you're safe.
I won't ever approve of a nine-tailed fox...
Actually, I take that back. How big is this living room?
I didn't think it was right to visit empty-handedly.
- What is it? - It's just a snack.
Mealworms?
I asked a friend who directs an animal show,
and he told me foxes love it.
I had trouble choosing between mealworms and crickets.
You can go ahead and enjoy it.
Did you guys eat dinner?
- No. - I'll order.
Only the fox's death can break a deal made by a fox.
(Goboon's Tripe Restaurant)
They wrap it in a bundle?
Let me eat with them first.
The CEO was the accomplice of the mummy case?
I asked him about the nail I found, and he admitted everything.
Why don't you call the cops?
And say what?
That our CEO is from Goryeo?
And that he's a follower of Imoogi and goes around killing people?
You think they'll believe that?
You're right.
Then why not let Detective Baek put on those glasses...
that show you people's past lives?
Once he sees people's past lives,
he might believe that there's a guy from Goryeo.
Are you sure he graduated from the best university in Korea?
He's a nice guy.
Why aren't you eating anything?
You didn't eat the mealworms, and you're not eating any tripe.
Do you eat people's livers?
You're making me crave it a little.
It's pretty good.
I know this is rude, but do you have a tail?
Why would you ask if you know it's rude?
I still can't believe that you're a nine-tailed fox.
Yes, he has one. I saw it.
Unbelievable. Then do you also put a leaf on your forehead...
and transform yourself?
That's a raccoon.
And I do know how to transform, but I don't because it's not classy.
Show us! Show us!
You punk.
- My gosh, just eat. - Just eat the food.
I'll do it.
What made you change your mind?
I want to live.
Do you really think you can take out your brother's heart?
You can take out his heart.
I'll lure him to you.
You have such a tender heart.
Take this.
And lure Yeon to the location I tell you to.
From now on, we'll be moving together.
You can sleep here tonight.
He's so fit to work at a broadcasting company.
- You should keep working here. - You're too kind.
Did you buy everything this morning?
Yes.
- Eat up. - It looks good. Let's eat.
When did you get so close?
Hey. He's a real piece of work.
He knows history, literature, arts, religion, everything.
He's a walking encyclopedia.
He was useful on the field too.
Remember the foreign language papers on past lives?
He translated the English, French, and Chinese papers...
all last night.
What's your secret?
I never left home when I was young because of my health.
I was alone other than for my babysitter.
So all I did was read.
Good morning. So this was where you all were.
Nice. Who picked up sandwiches?
- It's mine. - Just one. Don't be cheap.
Urban Legends team, we have a team dinner tonight.
- I'm out. - Me too.
No, no, no. No investigations, no editing,
no excuses will work today. Why not?
Because it's Terry's welcome dinner.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Making coffee.
What's with these flowers that don't suit you at all?
So that you can enjoy the scent of our old home.
Pick one that you like. Women love this stuff.
That was thoughtful of you.
So? Where are the ground cherries? Did you find out?
What's the rush?
I don't have time to chit chat.
- What? - I don't have time either.
But still, listen to what I have to say.
What is it?
What am I to you?
Where did things get twisted again?
I've done all I could.
What's the problem this time?
Answer me.
What am I to you?
You're family.
Sickening family that thinks just because we had the same dad,
you had the right to do all sorts of wicked things to me.
Don't think I'll feed you flowery words...
just because you surrounded me with flowers.
I'm sick of your whining at your age!
You're so mean to me...
when you're endlessly magnanimous to her.
Yes. Because she's much tougher than you.
She doesn't cling onto her family tragedy like a loser...
and whine like somebody.
Isn't it odd?
You were never once a nice brother,
but shone in my eyes as if you were.
You seemed perfect.
I wanted...
to become like you.
Drink it.
What if you spiked it?
Calm down. I'm just kidding.
So? Where are the ground cherries?
Wait. We'll find them soon.
Don't you dare try anything funny.
After you saved me from the Forest of the Starved,
I thought...
I should die for you someday...
in order to save you.
But you know, I realized I couldn't.
I want to live.
That's why...
I need you to die, big brother.
Do you want to fight?
I can't beat you if we fight fair and square.
The coffee.
If you cared for me even a fraction of how much you worry about her,
I wouldn't have done this.
I could never.
You idiot.
We got Lee Yeon.
Wait until I get there.
Don't call me on this phone again.
Darn it. Does he think I'm his lackey or something?
Hey. Here. Come here.
Sit down. Sit. Okay.
Okay, then. Fill your glasses everyone.
I'll fill yours, Terry.
Okay. Here you go.
- Thank you. - I'll pour my own.
- Welcome. - Welcome.
- Thank you. - Drink up.
Gosh. I wish I had a son like him.
He's handsome, smart... He's so...
My gosh. He's so fit. He's solid.
He's totally... Sure. You're a good kid.
I'm starting to respect Mr. Choi now.
How is he so unchanging?
I'm going to get some air.
Terry, where are you going?
I need to meet someone for a bit.
I'll be right back.
Where did you learn such manners?
- Sorry? - Who leaves a dinner...
without saying anything?
Especially the guest of honor.
- I'm sorry. - I have a lot of questions for you.
Like what, for instance?
What's your favorite book?
- "A Lover's Discourse: Fragments". - By Roland Barthes?
Have you read it?
I got baited by the title.
I thought it'd teach me about love,
but to understand his language of love,
one needs at least a master's degree.
He wrote many beautiful phrases.
"He praises her perfection..."
"and praises himself..."
"for choosing pure perfection."
Meanwhile, I praise cocktails.
Come on.
I have five minutes left. End our deal.
Our deal ends when I have Lee Yeon's heart.
I brought him to you as promised.
Now announce the end of our deal.
Can't you see I'm waiting for Imoogi?
Being rude, are we?
I bet it drives you crazy.
You can't kill the one who you owe a favor.
Once a slave, always a slave.
You can't do anything without your master's approval.
Watch what you say.
You're still bound to me by the favor you owe.
You serve a creature that sucked the blood of your family.
Shut it.
How did it feel...
to watch your parents, wife, and children die?
Did you cry?
- I told you to shut it. - Then say it!
Say that our deal is over.
Fine. I'll end our deal...
in my own way.
You've lost your mind.
No can do, I'm afraid.
I may be a worthless piece of trash,
but I can't sacrifice my family to get what I want.
You... Then you'll die.
I won't.
Foxes die when they go back on a deal.
And foxes...
can change their appearances.
Although, I find it distasteful.
You and your desire to seem graceful.
I thought you said you'd only take a sip?
What's going on?
Since when...
Since your place last night.
What are you...
doing here?
I'm sorry.
I only thought you were one of the hostages.
I didn't think he'd kill everyone.
So how about you keep living by my side?
No matter what I do,
I can't be free of my deal.
There's a way.
How?
Swap places with me...
and bring me to him just like he wants.
I'll do it.
Take this.
You can sleep here tonight.
Darn you. How dare you!
You. Kill Lee Yeon right now...
Stop harassing my brother...
or I'll have to snap your neck.
So, the choice is yours.
Kill Rang and have your life ended by me. Or...
change his deal.
Save me and our deal will be over.
The ground cherries... Take me to where they are.
- Here. - We drink to get drunk.
- Darn it. - But you're wasted, sir.
- But... - Please drive safely. Bye!
I'll get going then!
Take my car instead. I called for a designated driver.
- It's fine. - But I'm not.
Sorry about that. You can get going.
Ms. Nam.
- Yes? - Are you seeing someone?
Yes, I am.
What's your boyfriend like?
Like someone from a fairy tale.
Break up with him.
- What? - Fairy tales for grown-ups...
tend to have savage endings.
So long. Thank you for everything.
What a blabbermouth.
I no longer am bound.
Nice acting, by the way.
You were good enough to be an actor.
Maybe I'll give it a shot.
Terry.
Don't pretend with the romantic feelings.
Because to me,
you're nothing...
but the thing that took my parents from me.
I see you've known all along.
Is that why you've been keeping me here?
I need you to do the thing that only you can do.
What only I can do?
While I search for the ground cherries,
keep Imoogi occupied.
Imoogi?
Where is he?
Someplace...
much closer to you than you think.
Much closer to me?
No way...
You seem unprotected...
for someone who knows my true identity.
Yeon told me...
that you can't kill me.
He's right.
I'm quite fond of you.
Mom.
Dad.
(Tale of The Nine Tailed)
You probably wanted to warn me.
I'll save your life no matter what.
You're going to attack Imoogi directly?
I'm going to find his weakness.
I'll kill those who are precious to you.
A bigger disaster is on its way.
Don't touch them.
Look carefully. I am you.
Where is Ji A? Where is she?
A plague will hit this world.
No one will be happy.
Why does it have to be Ji A? Why?
Turn everything back to where it belongs.