(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC INTENSIFIES,SPEEDS UP)
(OMINOUS MUSIC ENDS)
- (WATER DRIPPING)
- (OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(WOMAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(WOMAN 2 SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(WOMAN WHIMPERING)
- (ROPE CREAKING)
- (CHOKING)
(WOMAN 2 CONTINUES IN RUSSIAN)
(CHOKES)
(WOMAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(OMINOUS MUSIC INTENSIFYING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
- (WATER SLOSHING)
- (MUFFLED CHATTER)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
GIRL 1: No way.
That’s so crazy.
GIRL 2: No,
you have had Snapchat.
GIRL 1: I’m not on there.
Are you on it?
GIRL 3: No.
(GIRL 3 GIGGLES)
No! There’s no way...
GIRL 1: I’m so jealous! Yeah.
GIRL 3: ...she posted that.
GIRL 1: She’d be
so embarrassed.
GIRL 3: No, the fact that
she’s trying to be you, but...
GIRL 2: ...she’s like
a millennial!
GIRL 3: Yeah,
she genuinely is.
Hey, are you guys
going to the city?
Yeah.
You meeting
some friends there?
GIRL 1: Yeah.
GIRL 2: Why?
BOY: Piper!
You were supposed
to wait for me.
- I don’t know who this is.
- (BOY SIGHS)
- Such a pedophile.
- I’m not... What the...
I’m her brother.
Uh, stepbrother.
Um, Kimmy.
- Let’s go.
- KIMMY: Oh, thank God.
BOY: Okay.
- Come on.
- (GIRLS GIGGLING)
They didn’t like me, did they?
(MOCKINGLY) "Are you guys
going to the city?"
BOY: No, no, they liked you.
- No, they didn’t.
- No, they did, they did.
There was three of them
and they all had
sort of dark hair.
And they were nice.
(BUS ENGINE STARTS)
They didn’t dress
very well, though.
Where’s your cane, Piper?
It’s in my bag. Shut up.
All right. Jeez.
- You ask me all the time!
- Okay!
How was goalball?
Uh, we lost.
(MUSIC PLAYING
OVER CAR SPEAKERS)
(SIGHS SOFTLY)
- PIPER: Andy!
- Hmm?
- Andy!
- Yeah?
- What?
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
ANDY: Dad?
(PANTING)
Dad, can you answer me,
please!
(PIPER PANTING)
- Andy!
- Here, here, here, here, here.
Dad, I’m gonna come in, okay?
PIPER: He always answers.
ANDY: Uh, okay,
we’re coming in, Dad.
PIPER: Not answering!
- (WATER RUNNING)
- (DOOR CREAKING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
PIPER: Dad?
Dad?
What’s happening?
Andy?
(BREATH TREMBLES)
Andy!
What’s happening?
Dad?
Dad!
Andy! (SCREAMING)
(WATER DRIPS)
POLICE OFFICER: Yeah.
Now, take a breath.
PIPER: He’d just
finished chemo. He was...
He was supposed to be better.
OFFICER: Okay.
And, Piper, did your brother
try to help you?
- No?
- (GULPS)
PIPER: He didn’t want me
in there.
OFFICER: Okay.
PIPER: He told me
Dad would be okay.
- OFFICER: Okay, that’s okay.
- (STRETCHER RATTLES)
That’s okay.
You’ve been so brave, Piper.
MAN: Lift it up a little bit.
Just...
(SIGHS WEARILY)
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
WOMAN: Hmm.
It says here you’re partially
sighted. Is that right, Piper?
I can... I can only see shapes
and light. That’s about it.
I’ve talked to an amazing
foster mum
called Laura.
You’re gonna love her.
And, Andy, we’re gonna put you
in your own supervised unit.
- What?
- Wait, hold on,
you’re splitting us up?
ANDY: But I look after her.
You can apply for guardianship
when you’re 18.
Okay,
I-I really don’t want her
to move in with a stranger.
She needs me.
PIPER: Why can’t he
just come with me?
Laura’s had issues
with troubled kids
in the past, and...
PIPER: What?
Nothing.
Grapefruit.
I got into trouble
when I was younger.
But it was ages ago.
I was, like, eight.
Can you, um...
(GULPS, SIGHS SOFTLY)
Can you talk to her
and just tell her
that we are not splitting up?
If she agrees, can you behave
yourself for three months?
Oi.
(SIGHS)
You hear that?
(PLANE FLIES OVERHEAD)
That’s Dad going to heaven.
Shut up.
No, seriously though,
that’s...
That’s what happens.
You don’t get burned
or buried, you just...
(INHALES)
catch a plane.
(PIPER CHUCKLES)
You don’t have to make
everything
nice for me, you know.
Yeah, I know.
The room
still smells like him.
Oh, Pipe.
(ANDY EXHALES DEEPLY)
You could take
some of his clothes.
They’re washed.
Don’t smell like him.
His pillow, then.
That’s not been washed yet.
(PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Uh, we are... here.
(THUDS)
Shit!
PIPER: Thought
I was the blind one.
Oh, shut up, Piper.
(PIPER LAUGHS)
(ANDY SIGHS)
(UPBEAT MUSIC
PLAYING IN DISTANCE)
PIPER: Smells like
Mum’s garden used to.
We’re not here for long, Pipe.
Come on.
(ALIVE BY EMPIRE OF THE SUN
PLAYING LOUDLY)
PIPER: (SHOUTING) Hello?
LAURA: (SHOUTING) Come in!
- What?
- The door’s open!
Just let yourselves in.
♪ Can’t you help me see ♪
LAURA: Excuse the music!
Whoo!
♪ Loving every minute ♪
♪ ’Cause you make me
feel so alive ♪
♪ Alive ♪
♪ Loving every minute ♪
♪ ’Cause you make me
feel so... ♪
LAURA: Oh, here you are!
- Oh, my God.
- (MUSIC STOPS)
- Look at youse! Look at you!
- ANDY: Say hi.
Oh, gorgeous.
Come in! (LAUGHS)
Oh, welcome to your new home!
Mi casa, your casa!
- I’m Laura and you’re...
- Hi.
- Piper?
- Yeah.
And...
- Andy.
- That’s right.
Hey, you know what we need?
A photo. Yeah?
Shall we get a photo?
- Yeah?
- I think so. I’d love that.
- Smile.
- Here. Yeah. Yeah.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY) Aah!
Hey, that’s great.
That’s lovely.
Look at that. (LAUGHS)
Oh, someone...
needs to meet Pompom.
- Oh, who’s Pompom?
- That’s my dog.
- Yeah.
- (PIPER CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Come here.
He’s a bit shy.
- (BARKS, LAUGHS)
- He’s stuffed, Pipe.
Yeah, no, he’s dead.
I know I’m a weirdo.
(LAUGHS) Row-row, Piper!
Row-row, Andy!
PIPER: Hi, Pompom.
LAURA: There’s a house cat
around here somewhere.
Junkman.
Haven’t stuffed him. Yet.
- But I will do.
- (CHUCKLES)
Where’s your cane, love?
Oh, I don’t like using it.
Oh, how come?
Uh, don’t want people
treating me different.
LAURA: How do they
treat you different?
People start to baby me, so...
Oh, yeah, no.
People can be judgmental.
But you know
what my nan used to say?
"Fuck off,
you fat fucking fuckers."
- (LAURA WHEEZES)
- (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
She did!
She was always swearing.
I never swear.
I loved her.
Is this for Piper?
Oh, no.
My daughter’s blind.
ANDY: Oh, is she here?
No, she’s passed.
Sorry.
No, it’s all right.
You didn’t know.
- It’s not your fault.
- How’d she die?
- Piper!
- She’s okay.
She drowned.
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Oh, who’s calling?
Oh, it’s Wendy.
She is so needy.
- Hello, Wendy?
- The kids get in?
- Yeah, no, they just arrived.
- You know the drill.
Yeah, no, all good. Yep.
Make yourselves at home.
Wendy says hi.
- Hi, Wendy.
- Yeah?
- (ANDY SNIFFLES)
- LAURA: Okay.
- Does she have a backyard?
- It’s a bit inconvenient.
- She does have a backyard.
- Don’t worry.
Do you wanna see it?
That’s all right.
Oh, bloody hell.
- (MEOWS)
- Oh, if you’re going outside,
don’t let the cat out.
Oh, fuck.
- Idiot.
- Piper!
Right, wait here.
LAURA. Yeah, no.
(CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
(WHISTLES, CLICKS TONGUE)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(JUNKMAN MEOWING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
INTENSIFIES)
(JUNKMAN MEOWING)
(JUNKMAN SHRIEKING)
- Oliver! Excuse me.
- (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC ENDS)
Oliver! No.
Give me the cat.
Let him go.
Got you. I got you.
- Let him go, Ollie.
- PIPER: Andy.
- Careful.
- LAURA: I got ya.
What’s happening?
Um...
(WHISPERING)
The cat got in the pool.
Laura’s sorting it out, though.
I think her kid’s...
holding it.
LAURA: Yep.
(INHALES) Yeah.
It’s your new sister
and brother, Oliver.
Piper and Anthony.
Andy.
Handy Andy. (CHUCKLES)
Oliver lost his family,
just like you guys.
Needed someone that could
give him special care.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
You’re done, darling.
Oliver?
Oliver.
Yep, quick as you can, darling.
Good lad.
Here you are.
Oliver’s been mute,
selectively mute
since we lost Cathy.
So we try not
to overwhelm him.
Isn’t that right, darling?
Taking one step at a time,
aren’t we, hmm?
Okay, you’re done.
It’s your turn.
Quite tall, aren’t you?
What’s he look like, Andy?
Oh, he’s cute.
He’s smiling at you.
(CHUCKLES)
- What color’s his hair?
- Red.
Yeah, and curly too.
He’s a beautiful boy.
(THUDS)
(SIGHS)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
There we go.
Good girl. And there’s a wall
on your right.
And straight down
to your bedroom.
Just watch out
for this step, Pipe.
LAURA: Yep, old news, Andy.
- ANDY: Okay.
- Straight ahead, love.
There you are.
It’s Cathy’s room.
You okay, Pipe?
PIPER: Yeah, I’m okay.
Grapefruit.
I’m all good, Andy.
Yep, sorry, uh,
your room’s in there.
It’s just up there.
- Okay.
- Okay, great.
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
(WHISPERS) Fuck.
(LAUGHS SOFTLY)
Not much of a room.
Oh, no, no, it’s fine.
Wendy tells me you’re applying
for guardianship. That right?
Yes, yeah,
in, uh, three months.
When I’m 18.
I’m supposed to report
how safe and reliable you are.
So stay safe.
Stay reliable, yeah?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
- (SOFTLY) Yes.
- (PHONE BEEPS)
Oh, girlfriend?
Oh, no.
Boyfriend?
Just a friend.
So what are you talking about?
Nothing. (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Your dad?
- No.
- (WHISPERS) Hey.
(IN NORMAL VOICE)
Hey, I’m a counselor.
People pay to talk to me,
you know.
Oh. That... That’s cool.
So you don’t have
to be so defensive, Andy.
Am I... Am I being defensive?
Oh, come on, look at you.
Arms crossed.
Clutching onto your phone
to tell me you want me to go.
- (CHUCKLES)
- PIPER: Hey,
I think I can hear you guys.
(KNOCKS ON WALL)
Can you hear me?
(SHOUTING) Yeah! Yeah, um...
- Yeah, yeah, you okay?
- PIPER: Yep!
- LAURA: She all right?
- You need anything?
PIPER: Yeah, uh,
a better brother?
Okay.
Hey.
Laura! Get off my phone!
What are you doing?
- (OBJECT CLATTERS)
- (GASPING) Sorry.
- I’m so sorry.
- No, I’m... Uh, I’m sorry.
No, you’re all right.
It’s my bad.
I just don’t like people
going through my stuff.
Absolutely,
it’s just you had a message.
I didn’t mean to yell.
Cool.
So Oliver’s
a fucking weirdo, is he?
No.
Oh.
Excuse me.
(SIGHS)
Oh, fuck.
(THE RIOT BY VIOLENCE PLAYING)
(GRUNTING)
(MUFFLED MUSIC CONTINUES)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(LAURA EXHALES)
(EXHALES)
(WHISTLING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(TINKLING)
LAURA: (WHISPERS)
Wait in your room.
(VCR WHIRRING)
(T.V. STATIC HISSING)
(WOMAN CRYING)
(GASPING)
(WOMAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(JUNKMAN MEOWING)
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS IN EXASPERATION)
- (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
- (BIRDS CHIRPING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
- (FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
- (KNOCK ON DOOR)
- (GASPS)
- LAURA: Up you get!
(GROANS SOFTLY)
(FOOTSTEPS RECEDE)
Ugh.
(SIGHS)
Oh, you...
(WASHING MACHINE WHIRRING)
(WHIRRING STOPS)
(WATER SPLASHING)
(SHOWER RUNNING)
PIPER: (WHISPERS) Dad.
I wanna come too.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
PIPER: (SHOUTING) Andy!
Andy!
(PANTING)
No, please!
Please!
(SHOWER RUNNING)
Hey, Ollie.
We’re going out
for a little bit.
You’ll be all right?
Good.
(KEYS JINGLE, LOCK CLICKS)
(BOSTON BY DERMOT KENNEDY
PLAYING)
PIPER: (WHISPERS)
What’s he look like?
♪ We were swimming out
so far this time ♪
He looks good.
Grapefruit.
He looks good, Pipe.
♪ Pretty intimate so far ♪
♪ So I ♪
PIPER: (SOFTLY) Goodbye, Dad.
ANDY: Thank you.
- Sorry for your loss.
- PIPER: Thank you.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
LAURA: Andy, sorry.
ANDY: Mm.
Andy, I can’t let you do this.
What?
Leave without saying goodbye.
Okay? It’s the last time
you’ll be able to look at him.
PIPER: You didn’t look at him?
You said he looked good.
Pipe.
I said, "Grapefruit."
I didn’t want
to see him like that, Pipe.
LAURA: It’s better than
how you saw him last.
Look, some people believe
the spirit stays in the body
for months after death.
If that’s true,
then he’s still in there.
(COLLAR JINGLING)
(DOOR THUDS)
(THUDDING CONTINUES)
(MEOWS)
(THUDS)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(LOUD THUDDING)
(CHICKENS CLUCKING
IN DISTANCE)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CHITTERS)
(ANDY BREATHING HEAVILY)
LAURA: You see?
He’s so peaceful.
Yep.
(GULPS SOFTLY)
You should kiss him goodbye.
(BREATH TREMBLING)
No.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SIGHS WEARILY) No.
Kiss your father, Andy.
It’s a custom.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SNIFFLES)
(WHISPERS) There we go.
His lips.
(SHUDDERS)
Yeah. It’s custom.
- It’s not.
- It is, darling.
It is.
Let me help you.
Come on.
- I can’t.
- It’s okay, it’s okay.
- I can’t do that.
- It’s okay, I’ve got you.
I’ve got you.
Yeah?
Don’t worry,
you’re in good hands.
(ANDY SIGHS)
(ANDY SHUDDERS)
(TUTS) Oh, come on, it doesn’t
have to be like this.
Seriously, a funeral isn’t
supposed to be all misery.
It’s supposed
to be a celebration.
Let’s have some fun, huh?
Piper, what do you do
for fun, eh?
Kick Andy in the balls.
(LAUGHS WHIMSICALLY)
Yes!
What about you, Andy?
What do you like to do?
Huh?
I don’t know. Get hammered.
Hammered? Okay.
Well, let’s get hammered.
(LIVELY ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
- LAURA: This one?
♪ Now, listen ♪
(DOOR RATTLING)
ANDY: So, the game is called
Odds On.
You’ve got to pick a number
between one and ten.
- Yep.
- You got one?
Seven.
Well, no, you’re not meant
to say it out loud yet.
- LAURA: Oh!
- Yeah, keep it in your head.
Now, on the count of three,
you do say it out loud...
and then
if I guess your number,
- you have to drink.
- Got it.
Piper, hit us
with the countdown.
Mm-hm. Three, two, one.
BOTH: Seven.
(LAUGHS)
- Why’d you say it again?
- Bloody cheater!
- All right, it doesn’t matter.
- That was so stupid.
- I can take a shot.
- Okay.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
(MAKES CHOKING SOUNDS)
(GURGLES)
ANDY: Oh, no!
- (LAUGHING)
- LAURA: All right, I’m sorry.
All right, Piper, Odds On.
- Really?
- LAURA: Yeah!
With the whiskey?
(WHISPERS) Say four.
Three, two, one...
- BOTH: Four!
- (LAURA LAUGHS)
Oh, calm down, muscles,
it’s just one drink.
One little drink.
All right, but you’re not
going to like it, Piper,
- I’m telling you.
- We’ll see.
- Do you like it? Yeah?
- (COUGHS)
- Oh, it’s good, right?
- (LAURA CHUCKLES)
Oh, that’s disgusting,
you drink that!
- (BURPS)
- (LAUGHS)
Yeah, I’m more
of a vodka slut, eh?
You go for it. I hate vodka.
One for Dad.
- (SIGHS) Yeah, okay.
- Hm.
- Piper?
- Yes.
All right, but last one.
(WHISPERING) First one.
- (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
- LAURA: Cheers.
Cheers.
(FREAKS BY TIMMY TRUMPET
PLAYING)
Piper, come on,
I need back up!
- I need back up, Piper!
- LAURA: Come on!
- Piper, get over here!
- This is it!
- Yeah!
♪ Tell me ♪
♪ Where the freaks at ♪
♪ Freaks at, freaks at ♪
♪ Tell me
Where the freaks at ♪
(CLUCKING)
LAURA: Okay.
ANDY: Oh, my God!
- Bedtime, young lady. Yes!
- No!
(FREAKS BY TIMMY TRUMPET ENDS)
- LAURA: What’s next?
- Andy, play Dad’s song!
- Yeah, play Dad’s song!
- Oh!
ALL: (SINGING)
♪ What about me? ♪
♪ It isn’t fair ♪
♪ I’ve had enough
Now I want my share ♪
♪ Can’t you see? ♪
♪ I wanna live ♪
♪ But you just take more ♪
♪ What about me? ♪
- LAURA: Piper, sing it!
- (SCREAMS)
(SCREAMS) ♪ What about me? ♪
LAURA: No! Sing it properly!
(ALL LAUGHING)
(IN DEEP VOICE) Sing it!
Sing it, Piper!
(SNORING)
- You’ve still got one left.
- Yeah.
Whoops!
(LAURA GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Thank you for today, Laura.
It’s okay, Andy.
I’ve been through it.
Don’t you want
to talk about him?
Yeah, but it’s...
- I don’t know, it’s hard.
- Well...
we don’t have to look
at each other.
(CHAIRS CREAKING)
Yeah, you can...
ask me something.
(ANDY SIGHS)
You can ask me anything.
How did you, um...
How did you cope...
with Cathy being gone?
Oh.
I didn’t.
When we buried her, I, um...
I didn’t want to leave...
’cause it felt like
I was abandoning her.
You know?
Mmm.
How could I go home
without my daughter?
(SHUDDERS SOFTLY)
How could I sleep in a bed
when she was in the ground?
I used to stay at the cemetery
for days...
just so I could feel
close to her.
ANDY: Yeah.
(SIGHS)
I’d give anything to hear her
call me Mum one more time.
Just one more time.
That’s all.
You know, we’d only, uh...
we’d only ever talk
if it was about Piper.
LAURA: Because she was
the favorite, huh?
(ANDY CHUCKLES)
Yeah, how could she not be?
Is that why you hit her?
- Who told you that?
- Oh.
Wendy.
Were you jealous of her?
(SIGHS) When my...
When my dad...
married her mum...
(EXHALES)
...it felt like he finally
found the family...
he actually wanted.
I used to get in trouble
at school
just so that he’d notice me
and he... he hated me for it.
(SIGHS)
He’d turn on the shower
so Piper couldn’t hear
and he’d...
He used to hit me so hard...
I’d wake up and...
I wouldn’t even know
where I was.
(BREATH TREMBLING)
That’s awful, Andy.
And you know what?
(INHALES)
He never touched her...
once.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
LAURA: You awake?
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
Andy?
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
INTENSIFIES)
(JUNKMAN MEOWING)
(GASPS)
(JUNKMAN MEOWS)
(WATER SPLASHING)
LAURA: I know you’re hungry.
You just have to wait
a bit longer, okay?
Are you in there?
Is this part of it?
Did I do it right?
(EXHALING)
How can I believe
you’re in there
if I can’t see you?
(LAURA’S BREATH TREMBLING)
- (RATTLING)
- (WATER RUNNING)
(GASPS)
(JUNKMAN MEOWS)
(MEOWING CONTINUES)
- (JUNKMAN GROWLING)
- (BREATHING SHALLOWLY)
(JUNKMAN YOWLS RASPINGLY)
- (SHATTERS)
- (SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
Oh, fuck!
- Oh.
- Andy!
- Is that dirty?
- PIPER: Morning, Andy!
I’m putting a wash on
before we head out.
- No, I’ll come back.
- I’m not wasting water, Andy.
- No...
- Let’s see what you’ve got.
PIPER: Andy’s hungover!
- You going out?
- Yeah, girl shopping.
- Sorry, just the two of us.
- Yeah, no boys allowed.
- Oh, keep Ollie in his room.
- Mm-hm.
He’s mucking around
and doing my head right in.
Yep.
LAURA: Oh.
Piss.
(PIPER CHUCKLES)
I don’t know what...
what happened.
Andy, seriously?
(SIGHS)
LAURA: Hey.
Why don’t you try
and take a shower?
Okay.
Um...
- Sorry.
- LAURA: You’re all right?
Oh, your brother’s
not very well, I don’t think.
I’m quite concerned.
Became quite aggressive
last night.
I’ll tell you about it
in the car.
(VEHICLE DRIVING AWAY)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(FLY BUZZES)
(THUDS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR RATTLES)
She lock you in, Ollie?
- (FLY BUZZES)
- You hungry?
How long you been like this,
mute, or whatever?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
You wanna write?
I think you should, actually.
So then, uh... then I can...
then I can talk to you.
And you can talk to me.
Okay, well, Ollie,
this fruit is not free.
It’s gonna cost you
some writing.
There we go.
Here.
Careful.
Just take the fruit, Ollie.
Okay, I’m gonna
get you a plate.
I don’t want Laura
yelling at me...
- (SIGHS) ...for making a mess.
- (RAPID CLINKING)
- (GASPS)
- (CLINKING)
Ollie! Ollie!
Hey, hey! Ollie, Ollie, Ollie!
- Stop! Stop! Stop!
- (GROANING)
- (SQUELCHING)
- Stop!
Fuck! Fuck!
Come on!
(PANTING)
Come on! Come on!
Hey, come on! Ollie! Ollie!
What are you doing?
We need to go
to the hospital, okay?
Come on, just follow me.
It’s okay.
- Just come on! Ollie! Come on!
- (OLIVER GRUNTING)
(OLIVER SCREAMS)
Shit!
(SCREAMING)
Hey, look at me.
What’s wrong? What’s wrong?
- Hey, hey. Hey!
- (GASPING, CHOKING)
- Fuck, Ollie! Hey, hey, hey.
- (COUGHING)
- Breathe, breathe, breathe!
- (SCREAMS)
(CHOKING)
Ollie.
(OLIVER CONTINUES GROANING)
(LOUD THROBBING)
(GASPING)
Help me.
(TIRES SCREECH)
What’s going on?
Why is he outside?
No, no, no, no!
Get away! Get away!
- Why is he outside?
- (GASPS)
Get your sister inside now!
- Piper, come inside.
- Andy. Andy!
- Piper!
- What the heck is going on?
- Just take her inside now!
- ANDY: He hurt himself.
PIPER: What?
LAURA: Why is he outside?
(MUFFLED) Andy, what happened?
What did you... Andy!
Why is Laura screaming?
Do I call an ambulance?
LAURA: (MUFFLED) Piper, no!
I can fix this!
(ANDY WHIMPERING)
PIPER: It’s okay, it’s okay.
Shh, it’s all right.
You’re okay. You’re okay.
(EXHALES)
(IN NORMAL VOICE)
Andy, we can help you.
Laura wants to get you help.
ANDY: What?
(WOMAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(VHS WHIRRING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WOMAN GASPING ON TV)
You’re all right.
OLIVER: Where am I?
(BREATH TREMBLING)
Who are you?
- What?
- What do you want?
- Shh!
- Please! No!
It’s all right, Ollie,
it’s all right!
- Let’s get you bandaged up!
- (LOUD MUSIC PLAYING)
You’re all right. Shh!
(LOUD MUSIC CONTINUES MUTED)
It’s okay. It’s okay,
it’s okay. It’s okay.
OLIVER: (SCREAMS) Help!
(OLIVER SCREAMING)
You’re all right!
No. No, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
It’s all right!
No, no, no, no, no!
Stay. Stay!
You’re all right, love.
You’re all right!
No, no, no, no, no.
You’re all right.
- You’re okay.
- (MUFFLED SCREAMING)
You’re okay now!
Shh! You’re okay.
(MUFFLED MUSIC CONTINUES)
- (OLIVER GROANS)
- Shhh.
ANDY: Laura?
(MOUTHING) There we go.
ANDY: Is Oliver okay?
(MOUTHING) You’re all right.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
ANDY: Laura?
PIPER: Hey, Laura!
PIPER: Laura!
ANDY: He said he needs help.
(MUSIC STOPS)
Should we take him
to a hospital or...
So you broke into my room?
Respect my fucking privacy!
Come on, love.
You’re all right.
PIPER: Please don’t be
too mad at him.
(DOOR SLAMS)
PIPER: Will he be okay?
LAURA: Yeah, he’ll be fine.
Got to him just in time.
Is he sick?
He’ll be all right now.
It’s Junkman
I’m worried about.
Think your brother
let him out.
PIPER: Junkman!
Junkman!
(WATER SPLASHING)
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
(RATTLES)
(GASPS)
MAN: (MUFFLED) Rain.
She’ll die in the rain.
(BREATHES WEAKLY)
(WHIMPERING)
ANDY: Dad.
(GRUNTS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHITTERING)
- (GASPS)
- DOCTOR 1: Nice deep breaths.
Focus on the light. That’s it.
DOCTOR 2: Just breathe
normally. That’s it.
DOCTOR 1: Two...
DOCTOR 2: Now, this time,
I want you to push on my hands
with your feet
as hard as you can, mate.
ANDY: What...
ANDY: What’s that sound?
(RAIN PATTERING)
(ANDY BREATHING HEAVILY)
I need... I need to go home.
- I need to go home!
- Hey, hey. No, mate.
Hey, hey, it’s all right.
- She’s...
- Nurse, nurse!
- She’s gonna die!
- Nurse!
- NURSE: Yep, yep.
- My sister’s gonna die!
- Hey, hey.
- Fuck. Give me the fuckin’...
(ANDY YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
- Get off me! Get off me!
- DOCTOR: Andy.
- Andy!
- Calm down.
(THUNDER RUMBLING,
RAIN PATTERING)
(A.I. VOICE SPEAKING)
Message: Laura said
you don’t want visitors.
Hope you’re okay. Miss you.
Miss you less than three...
(THUNDER RUMBLING,
RAIN PATTERING)
(LAUGHTER,
INDISTINCT CHATTER ON SCREEN)
(LAURA SOBBING)
- Laura?
- Hey.
I’m worried about Andy.
I couldn’t sleep.
Me neither.
Come in, love.
Follow my voice?
Straight ahead.
I’ve got you.
Sit here.
- You all right?
- (SNIFFLES)
- Oh.
- You’re upset.
Yeah, it’s the rain.
Cathy loved it.
The sound, the smell.
PIPER: That her on the T.V.?
LAURA: Yeah, that’s her.
- Can we keep watching?
- Yeah, sure.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON T.V.)
FRIEND: (ON T.V.) The first
cat-witch ever to swim.
CATHY: You’re okay,
you’re okay.
PIPER: Can you describe her?
She’s 12 here.
Long brown hair.
Freckles.
God, she’s beautiful.
- Here, look at your ears!
- Oh!
I’m sorry.
CATHY: Look at my new earrings
Mum bought me.
It’s all right.
LAURA: Thank you.
Yeah, ah, Ollie? Ollie! Ollie!
- Yeah?
- Get her cane.
- Okay, Aunty Laura.
- Thank you.
- LAURA: Hey, Andy.
- Mm?
Handy Andy.
Mmm.
- Hey.
- Where’s... Where’s Piper?
She’s at home with Ollie.
It’s okay.
(ANDY SIGHS)
Look, they need to keep you in
for another day.
You have a concussion.
You just need to rest.
ANDY: What?
Yeah, they need to check
your brain isn’t leaking
or something.
Where... Where’s Piper?
Where...
It’s okay.
- Yeah?
- (SIGHS WEARILY)
Shh. Shh.
(SMACKS LIPS) Oh.
Brought you a present.
Piper got you this.
Your body spray.
You can’t let her out, Laura.
- What’s that, love?
- You can’t let Piper out,
not while it’s raining.
Something could happen.
Like what?
I saw my dad in the shower.
(SIGHS) He said something.
(EXHALES)
What’d he say?
Andy?
He said,
"She’ll die in the rain."
You don’t think it’s ’cause
your dad died in the shower
when I killed him?
What?
Your dad died in the shower.
What...
You’re associating rain
with that.
(SCOFFS)
What is happening to me?
Hey, don’t worry.
I’ll keep her inside.
I’ll keep her inside,
I promise.
(LAUGHS)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
You can take it.
(BOTH SQUEAL)
(LAUGHS) It’s just water!
(PIPER LAUGHS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
LAURA: Cathy? Cathy!
I’m filming you!
- Piper!
- (MUSIC FADES)
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
I want to show you something.
This was Cathy’s favorite.
Oh!
You like it?
Uh-huh. Thanks, Laura.
Hey, you can call me Mum,
if you like.
Um, maybe.
Hey.
She always used to...
wear her hair back like this.
She didn’t want her hair
sticking to her face
or getting in her mouth.
There you are.
Hey, you like
living here with me?
PIPER: Yeah.
Yeah, you’re really nice.
You think you like it enough
that when Andy turns 18
you maybe want to stay?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Stay here when Andy goes?
Yeah.
I was...
I was looking forward
to getting our own place.
But we’d still visit you
on weekends.
(WHISPERS) Okay.
- (SHUDDERS)
- (DOOR CREAKING OPEN)
Who’s that?
It’s just Ollie.
- (CHUCKLES) Hi.
- (CLATTERING)
Not just yet, my darling.
I want to show you
something else.
- (CHUCKLES SOFTLY) Yeah.
- Yeah?
This way.
That’s it, straight ahead.
PIPER: Oh, it’s cold.
LAURA: Yeah,
it’s a freezer, love.
PIPER: Feels crusty.
What is that?
Oh, my God, what is it?
Just meat.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING,
RAIN PATTERING)
LAURA: This is unbelievable!
You had a psychotic break
and they just let you go?
Piper’s worried, too.
It’s honestly dangerous.
- (MUFFLED SPEAKING)
- (WIPERS SQUEAKING)
God forbid something happens.
(DOOR SHUTS)
(BEADS TINKLING)
LAURA: What are you
doing in there, Andy?
Bit creepy, isn’t it?
- (WEIGHTS THUDS)
- (ANDY GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
It’s only when you’ve
just woken up.
- (ANDY GRUNTS)
- (PIPER LAUGHS)
(GRUNTS, STRAINS)
(SPLUTTERS)
(COUGHS)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
- (METAL CLANGING)
- (CHOKING)
- (GROWLING)
- (SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(IN ENGLISH)
Enough to hold the soul.
(CHITTERING)
(GURGLING, SLAVERING)
(IN RUSSIAN)
(GROWLS)
(CRUNCHING)
(WOMAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(GASPING)
(SPLUTTERING)
(COUGHING)
(BRENDAN SOBBING)
(CONTINUES SOBBING)
(CLICKS)
(SPRAY HISSING)
(BEADS TINKLING)
- (BLOW THUDS)
- (PIPER GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
(PIPER CRYING)
LAURA: Well, here he is.
Anything you want to say?
ANDY: Huh?
Show him, love.
Oh, Piper, what happened?
Huh? What happened?
Someone hit me.
- You hit her?
- Don’t be ridiculous.
So Ollie hit her?
I put her to bed and then
you went into her room.
Didn’t you?
Huh?
(SCOFFS)
You can’t even remember.
Piper.
Who did this?
I don’t know.
But I smelt you.
You’re abusive, Andy.
Just like your dad.
He hit you, so you hit her.
What do you mean, Dad hit him?
Yeah, he abused Andy.
That’s why he didn’t save him.
ANDY: That’s not true.
- He hit you?
- No, he didn’t.
I’ve tried to help you, Andy,
but I can’t.
You’ve butchered
Oliver’s mouth.
You’ve been
seeing your dead dad.
I hate to think what you’ve
done with Junkman.
Stop, Laura.
You’re the only one
strong enough
- to leave that kind of mark.
- Laura, stop.
You take those steroids
or hormones or whatever.
It’s creatine.
Well, your testosterone
is out of control!
Laura, you’d better
fucking stop right now.
Or what?
You’re gonna hit me too?
PIPER: Please guys, enough.
LAURA: Andy?
ANDY: The fuck
happened to Ollie?
- The fuck happened to him?
- Andy.
Andy, no.
No, no. Andy, look at me.
- LAURA: Hey!
- Laura, what’s happening?
- Give me that! Give me that!
- PIPER: Laura!
No!
- Wait, what’s going on?
- Get off me!
(LAURA SCREAMS)
PIPER: Andy, what did you do?
LAURA: He attacked me!
She’s hurt, Andy!
She’s not fucking hurt!
Come on, we’re leaving now.
- LAURA: You’re dangerous.
- Fuck off!
I’m not gonna
let you hurt her again.
- I have to protect her.
- Oh, what,
like you protected Cathy?
(SCREAMING)
Get off!
- (GRUNTS)
- (THUDDING)
What the fuck
do you fucking...
LAURA: No!
- You fucking...
- Come on, then.
Fucking what? What?
(PIPER SCREAMS,
BREATHING HEAVILY)
Andy, stop!
(SIGHS IN EXASPERATION)
(SCREAMING)
(CRYING)
Please, Andy, stop.
Please.
Come on, Pipe, we’re going.
(SOFTLY) Grapefruit, Pipe.
It’s okay. It’s okay.
It’s okay. Shh.
Fuck me.
- (DOOR SLAMS)
- You’re okay, love.
You’re all right.
- You’re okay.
- (PIPER CRYING)
Yes, I got you.
I got you, darling.
- (LOUD CRASH)
- (CHICKENS CLUCKING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
I need to see Wendy, now.
It’s urgent.
Um, if you take a seat,
I’ll let her know you’re here.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
All right, let’s go.
Grab your bag.
I don’t really
feel like playing.
Oh, it’ll be good
to let off some steam.
Come on. Here’s your bag.
That’s it.
I could be
a few hours, darling.
Call the cops.
Laura told me...
you hit your sister
and attacked her.
Oh, she’s fucking lying!
She’s full of shit, Wendy,
I swear.
You’ve been wetting the bed?
Oh!
Would you say your grief
over Dad is getting better
or worse?
It’s not about my fucking Dad!
Laura kidnapped
a fucking child.
I mean, did you do
any fucking checks on her
before you sent us there?
How do you even know
who the fuck she is?
’Cause she worked here
for nearly 20 years.
She was the best
counselor we had.
And believe me, love,
she would never hurt a child.
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(SNARLS)
(GASPS)
Ollie.
No.
Not yet.
Ollie, it’s me.
It’s me. No!
No, Ollie, stop!
- (OLIVER GRUNTS)
- (LAURA SCREAMING)
Ollie!
Get off! Get off!
- (FLESH TEARING)
- (LAURA SCREAMING)
Get back! Get back!
Get away! Go away!
No!
(WHIMPERS)
(MIMICKING LAURA) Get back!
Get away! Go away!
(MIMICKING LAURA’S SCREAMS)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
(OLIVER SCREAMS)
ANDY: She calls him Oliver.
That’s her nephew’s name,
the red-haired kid.
Yeah, but he doesn’t
have red hair. It’s him!
- Who are you calling?
- Laura.
No, Wendy. No.
She might hurt Piper.
Let me take you there. Please.
(TEETH CRACKING)
(WOOD SNAPPING)
(CRUNCHING)
(GASPS)
(GULPS)
(GROANS)
(PANTS)
(THUDS)
(DISCORDANT PIANO MUSIC
PLAYING)
(LAURA SCREAMS)
- (PEOPLE CLAPPING)
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
REFEREE: Quiet, please!
WOMAN: Quiet, please.
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
- REFEREE: Play!
(CELL PHONE RINGING, BEEPS)
ANDY: (ON VOICEMAIL)
I’m sorry, Pipe.
(SOBS) I know you think
that Dad was great, but he...
He hurt me bad.
But only when you were asleep,
or when you weren’t home.
(RUMBLING)
(PIPER BREATHES)
(PEOPLE CLAPPING)
(ANDY SIGHS)
You couldn’t see
how much he hated me.
And I lied because...
because I didn’t
want you to know
how ugly the world was.
And when I was eight...
uh, I hit you.
(ANDY INHALES)
And I regret it
more than anything, Pipe.
I’d never do it again.
(FLY BUZZING)
But I just need you
to understand that
that bruise on your face
right now, that wasn’t...
wasn’t me.
It was her.
She’s bad, Pipe.
She’s hateful.
And just like Dad, she’s not
gonna let you see it.
I didn’t tell you then
but I’m telling you now, Pipe.
There’s something wrong
with Laura.
She kidnapped Oliver,
and you’re in danger.
You’re probably not fucking
listening to this, but...
(EXHALES)
I love you, Pipe.
Grapefruit.
WENDY: Don’t worry,
I’m gonna sort this all out.
(HEAVY DISCORDANT ROCK MUSIC
PLAYING)
Fuck.
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
- REFEREE: Play!
- (PIPER GRUNTS)
- (THUDS)
- How’s my ball taste?
- REFEREE: Piper, relax.
Wait in the car.
Why?
You are this close to getting
a restraining order.
- All right?
- Fuck!
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
LAURA: Shit!
WENDY: Laura!
- Yep, coming!
- It’s Wendy.
- Laura!
- All right!
- Hi, love.
- Hi.
So he’s brought you, has he?
Yeah, he’s been saying stuff.
I’ve gotta check it out, love.
Yeah, I know.
(GRUNTS)
(CLUCKING)
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
WENDY: You know the drill.
LAURA: I do.
(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
- Excuse the mess.
- Oh, don’t worry about it.
Yeah.
Oh, there’s no one
in there, Wendy.
- I just had a shower, so...
- Okay.
- Kids’ rooms are this way.
(GASPS)
I told her she could have it
any way she wanted,
but she loves this.
Lucky, the kid’s blind.
- What’s that?
- Oh, nothing. It’s lovely.
- Want to see Andy’s room?
- Yeah.
(GRUNTS)
- (YELLS)
- (METAL CLANGS)
Does the weights
when he’s angry.
Not that it’s helped.
Oh, sheets are dry
for a change.
- Ready?
- Um...
Can you have
a look at this for a sec?
This is the kid that Andy’s
been banging on about.
You seen him?
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
ANDY: Ollie?
WENDY: So, I’m guessing
you want him out.
LAURA: Oh, hate
to split ’em up
but you know, I’ve got
to think of Piper now.
Don’t worry,
we’ll take care of him.
Oh, cheers, Wendy.
I just hope
he gets better, you know.
I’m sorry for interrupting
your shower.
Oh, no, no, no, it’s all good.
You’re all right.
You’re bleeding.
Are you okay?
ANDY: Wendy!
Don’t.
- Please, Wendy. Don’t.
- Laura?
Don’t... Don’t go out there.
- I’m doing something.
- What are you...
I’m doing something for Cathy.
We’re good friends, aren’t we?
How long have we known
each other now?
It’s okay, love. Let go.
It’s Cathy.
- We can bring her back.
- What?
- Wendy!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Where are you?
- No, shh!
- Listen, listen, listen.
- What have you done?
- Listen. Listen!
Piper... needs to go...
- the same way Cathy did.
- Jesus.
We always used
to fill the hole...
- Let go.
- ...with rain.
- ANDY: Wendy!
- Let me go, love.
I didn’t think it would work,
- but it’s working.
- It’s okay.
- It’s working!
- Let me go.
He’s gonna bring her back!
- He’s gonna bring her back!
- Let me go!
- (SCREAMS)
- Let me fucking go!
- I don’t have anyone.
- What the fuck?
- (LAURA CRYING)
...fucking pullover.
Let me go!
(SCREAMING)
(SOBBING, WAILING)
Hey! You need to come outside!
- Now!
- (GASPS)
- Here.
- What’s going...?
Oh, shit! Go!
- Fuck, go!
- Run!
- Let me get in the car!
- Come on!
Lock the door. Jesus!
(THUDS, SMASHES)
(ENGINE WHIRRING)
(WINDSHIELD WIPER SCRAPING)
(THUDDING)
(GASPING, WHEEZING)
LAURA: Andy.
(CONTINUES WHEEZING)
(LAURA SHUSHING)
You’re okay.
(MUFFLED GRUNT)
Shh, it’s okay.
You’re okay. Shh, shh, shh.
You’re okay.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Righto, darl, let’s go.
You ready to go? Come on.
- What’s wrong?
- Hey, Piper. Come on.
You’re all right. Thank you.
GIRL: Bye, Piper.
- Bye.
- Did I leave my phone at home?
- I didn’t notice.
- COACH: Are you Laura?
- Yeah.
Laura, hi, we spoke
on the phone earlier.
I wanted to ask you
about Piper’s eye.
Yeah, no...
- Yeah, what happened?
- Not now, all right?
PIPER: Have you
heard from Andy?
LAURA: In you go. Quick.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
In you go, love.
(UPBEAT JINGLE PLAYING
OVER PHONE)
Whose phone is that?
Mine. Changed the ringtone.
- You like it?
- Oh, can you call mine?
Yeah.
(UPBEAT JINGLE CONTINUES)
OLIVER: (MIMICKING ANDY)
Piper.
Andy?
(UPBEAT JINGLE PLAYING
OVER PHONE)
(RINGTONE TUNE)
♪ How did I get my face ♪
♪ To look
so wonderfully divine ♪
(GROANS SOFTLY)
♪ Why do I appear
so picture-perfect ♪
♪ All the time ♪
(GRUNTS)
(RINGTONE TUNE GETS LOUDER)
(RINGTONE STOPS)
OLIVER: (MIMICKING ANDY)
Piper.
PIPER: Andy?
Why are you in here?
PIPER: Can you smell that?
Piper...
Andy?
- LAURA: Hey.
- (GASPS)
What are you
doing in here, love?
I heard Andy.
Oh, no, he’s down here.
He’s come to apologize.
Come on.
Who is this?
It’s just Ollie.
- But I heard...
- Come on, love.
I’ll take you to Andy,
come on.
I got you.
He’ll be fine.
Ollie’ll be fine. This way.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Just, um, this way.
What color’s Ollie’s hair?
Red. Thick and curly.
Why?
Hey.
You okay?
(OBJECT SHATTERING)
(GROANS)
Where you going, love?
Piper! No!
Piper, what’s wrong?
Come on. (KNOCKS ON DOOR)
Open the door, sweetheart,
come on.
- (PHONE VIBRATING)
- Don’t be silly now, come on.
- (BREATH TREMBLING)
- What’s wrong? Huh?
Piper.
Piper, open the door, love.
Come on, don’t be silly.
- Open the door.
- (BREATHES SHALLOWLY)
PIPER: No.
No, Andy!
Andy, come on.
Grapefruit. Please!
Come on, Andy!
Get up, grape...
Grapefruit!
Andy!
Please!
(SOBBING) I’m sorry.
(FOOTSTEPS POUNDING)
(KEYS JINGLING, DOOR RATTLING)
(GASPS)
Hey.
What’s wrong, love?
What happened to Andy?
He had an accident.
Listen.
I’ve got to tell you a secret.
Something I’ve been
scared to say
because I didn’t want
to frighten you.
I’ve spoken with an Angel.
It’s a beautiful Angel.
It does beautiful things.
I’ve put him inside Ollie.
And now...
he’s going to put
Cathy inside you.
Because you’re just like her.
Just as incredible...
and just as perfect.
What are you
going to do to me?
I’m going to drown you
in the pool now, love.
- (SCREAMS)
- (GRUNTS)
- LAURA: Don’t!
- (PIPER SCREAMS)
- (BOTH SCREAM)
- (GLASS SHATTERING)
(PIPER YELLING)
(THUDS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(STRAINS, YELLS)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(LAURA GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(WOMAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(INHALES)
(EXHALES)
(MUFFLED GROANS)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(SHUSHES)
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
- Please let me do this!
- PIPER: No, stop, please!
- Let me do this!
- (SCREAMING)
Please, Piper, please!
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCREAMING) No!
(GROWLING)
More rain!
Hold on. Hold on.
Please hold on!
No! No!
(INTENSE MUSIC BUILDS UP)
(CRIES OUT IN PAIN)
Mum!
(GASPS)
(CATHY’S VOICE) Mum.
CATHY: Mum.
(CRYING)
(SOBS)
(COUGHING)
Oh, no!
Piper!
- Piper!
- (GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS) I’m so sorry!
(SCREAMS)
Piper!
(CHITTERING NEARBY)
(OLIVER SNARLING)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREECHING)
(GASPS, GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GASPING, CHOKING)
(VOMITS)
(COUGHS, RETCHES)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING)
DRIVER: Are you okay?
Where did you come from?
LAURA: Cathy.
Cathy?
Sweetheart?
Hey.
Hey, gorgeous.
There you are.
Are you all right?
(SOBS)
(GRUNTING)
(WHISPERS) Here we go.
(SCREAMING)
Stop!
(TRAIN RUMBLING)
ANDY: (ON VOICEMAIL)
You’re probably not
fucking listening to this,
but...
I love you, Pipe.
Grapefruit.
(AIRPLANE ENGINES WHOOSHING)
OFFICER 1: Hey, guys!
Over here!
- There’s a boy!
- (SOBBING)
We’re here to help, mate.
We’re here to help.
OFFICER 2: Get a blanket!
OFFICER 1: Hey.
OFFICER 3: Kira, call ambo.
- Help me.
- OFFICER 2: Hey, it’s okay.
Request ambulance,we’ve got a 117.
OFFICER 3: It’s okay.Can you tell us your name?
I’m...
I’m Connor.
Connor Bird.
So brave.Connor, hey, hold onto me.
Hold on to me. It’s not going to be long, okay?
(MUSIC FADES)
(INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)