In 2015,China has stopped using organs from prisoners of death row
So the donation from citizens is the only leagal organ source now
Take a bowl
In this year alone,2699 people donated their organs after their death
We don't know the donator
For every donator there is a sad story
We have suffered a lot
The donators have enabled more people to live on
Every effort people made in donation is telling us that
The hope of organ transplantation lies in the hospital but not the execution ground
Reunion
We can go to anywhere as long as there is liver source there
Show me some confidence,not to panic,not to fear
The liver transplantation is our only hope
I was in great anxiety that I almost cried
I'm been always thinking about what can I do
Icteric index is used to indicate the level of
waste accumulated in our body
A healthy man's icteric index is below 17
But Guohong Xu's icteric index has reached 700,
which is 40 times the standard
Now Xu's liver has been badly hardened
Xu's life will be over without immediate liver transplantation
There are a lot of patients like him in this city
There is nothing we can do,we liver source are not enough
We can't find any other solutions either
Since there's no supply of liver,Xu's wife's brother
decides to donate a part of his liver to Xu
We have registered in the infestion department
We have searched a lot of hospitals
We can't find liver source
I as his wife wanted to donate my liver,but found mismatch
His son's liver also don't match his father
We were worrying when finally my brother stood out
He said he'd be the donator
He must save Xu's life
My brother is really a great man
Really
This is my youngest brother
He is the donator
Yes,he is.He has passed the examination
The transplantation would have been done
if not for the examination
The operation was scheduled yesterday
The operation room is also really
- Ready to cut his liver
- Yes,ready
We are lucky everthing is really now
She is his wife
- Then do you agree to your husband's donation?
- She totally agreed that
I must agree,it's for saving a life
When he is about to be sent into operation room
Liver source has been found
Thank you for your donation,you have done great contribution
to your country and all the human society
Now let's mourn
The one lying there is a man aged 50
He was declared brain dead
After making sure he was unable to revive
His parents with great sorrow decided to donate
all his available organs to hospital
His blood type is O,which matches that of Guohong Xu
We are really grateful to the donator
But we don't know who the donator is
According to regulation,both sides can't know each other's information
So Xu's families don't know who is the donator
We have met the families of the donator
His elder sister told us that their parents who are
80 years old made the decision to donate
That night the two elders really have
considered for a long time
But they finally signed it on the paper:We are willing
to donate all the available organs of my son
Ying Yang works in the donation department of Ruijing hospital
She is the only medical personnel to come into
contact with donator's families
She eyewitnessed the moment when they made
the decision of donation
I see a lot of papers with words been crossed and
revised for many times
Maybe because they were hestating,they were wondering if
they should make the decision or not
Despite of this,they all made the right decision
that is to donate organs
They want it to be confidential,they don't want more of their
families to know it in case they object
The anaesthesia is used for taking away organ
Other than his liver,the donator also donated both his kidneys
According to the result of matching test and evaluation of severity
The hospital has informed two other patients
Xingsheng Sun,aged 60,with double renal failure
He has been taking peritoneal dialysis for ten years
The hospital phoned us,we were quite excited and came here immediately
The principle is to save the young ones first,we understand that
So we already had prepared to accept that
Assume he is not to live for long
We want him to live happily everyday
Jianyong Zhang,age 48,is a uremic patient
He has been taking hemodialysis for five years
I'm from another city,I was so thrilled
My families drove me here,it took three hours to come here
He is the support of his family
He has both his children and parents to raise
We really can't lose him
- Everyone's life is precious,we will save all of their lives
- Thank you
Three lives,which was about to be gone
Just because of the donator,the candle of hope light up again
With the agreement of the donator's families
We are allowed to shoot the transplantation scene
This is the first time I eyewitness the organs being taken out
The red lines on the sphygmomanometer has become a straight line
The belly of the donator begin to sink in
He has donated almost all of his available organs in his body
After the transplantation,the doctors sew up the cut
and wipe his body
Change new clothes and shoes for him
When the donator is carried out of the room,everyone
spontaneously stand beside his both sides
They make a final farewell to the body
Now comes to the real chanllege for the doctors doing
transplantation operation for the three patients
Xianghui Wang and Peijun Zhou are two of the surgeons
doing transplantation
Oh my god,my fingers are gonna freeze
Hold it tight,be careful
The interface of blood vessels and ureter in the organs
must fit with that of patients
Every single move tolerant no minor mistake
He must have been on dialysis for four or five years
More than that
Two hours of work,finally the patient has got new kidneys
after waiting for two years
Look the urine,we are happy to see that
It's the great reward to us
We made it
What surgeons see as the most valuable thing is the urine bag
Because it means the recovery of the patient's urination functions
- Let's have a close-up
- This is very important
It's OK,he can do the urine nomarlly
The speed is also good
We are reassured to see him peeing,it claims our success
We can have a nice sleep at night
Peijun Zhou is smiling while holding the urine bag of the patient
The patients are still unconscious
After twenty minutes,the two patients wake up
- When does the operation begin?
- The operation is done,it's successful
He can't feel that he has been transplantated
But Guohong Xu and his families are still waiting anxiously
High on jaundice and poor coagulation function
He also has thrombocytopenia
His number of platelet is one tenth of that of a healthy people
Under these circumstances,the operation will be rather difficult
The liver is the central organ of the digestive system
It connects the gallbladder through the bile duct
It also has countless blood vessels in it
A minor mistake may lead to hemorrhea
The risk of this operation is very high
Guohong Xu's liver has been cut off finally,
his liver is hard and black
At 1:34 in the morning,Xu has been transplanted a new liver successfully
For us doctors the operation is finished
But for the patient he still has a lot to do in the future
He has to take care of himself in the best way
As a doctor this job is really tiring
Even my child told me he would never be a doctor
because it's way too tiring