Ó²×ÖÄ»
×ÖÄ»
Please...
Please.
×ÖÄ»
Please, no.
You don't want to do this.
×ÖÄ»
You're not a killer.
Damn it.
Ó²×ÖÄ»
×ÖÄ»
Really? He said flight risk?
The man is not a flight risk because he is innocent, okay?
×ÖÄ»
Innocent men do not run. Daddy, I'm hungry.
Okay, sweetheart.
×ÖÄ»
Really?
No.
×ÖÄ»
I disagree. And you know what?
I think Judge Ogden would disagree as well.
×ÖÄ»
Why? Because I took the man to Pebble Beach to golf,
and you know what you did, Carl?
×ÖÄ»
You dated his wife in law school.
For breakfast? Shh.
×ÖÄ»
Ha, all right.
Go for it.
×ÖÄ»
Yeah, I got to go. See ya.
Shit.
×ÖÄ»
Mommy's here. I got to take this away from you.
Daddy, I'm not done! I know, I know, but you know,
×ÖÄ»
you can't be havin' birthday cake all the time,
because Mommy doesn't want you to, and remember one thing,
×ÖÄ»
Mommy ruins everything.
Hold on.
×ÖÄ»
Hi. Hi.
It's not even 7:30 yet.
×ÖÄ»
I have early clients, so I...
Yeah.
×ÖÄ»
Your pear tree's dying.
It's a quince tree. You wanna come in?
×ÖÄ»
You've been decorating. Yeah.
How was she?
×ÖÄ»
She's good. Hi.
Hello.
×ÖÄ»
Hi, sweet pea.
What have you got on your hand...
×ÖÄ»
Nothing. And your face?
Birthday cake. She had birthday cake for breakfast.
×ÖÄ»
Anything else? Not this morning, no.
Well, do you have anything else?
×ÖÄ»
I haven't gone shopping yet, Laura.
Okay. All right, El',
×ÖÄ»
we'll get you something on the way, okay?
Mom, Daddy said "Shit."
×ÖÄ»
Did he?
Okay, why don't you get your bag.
×ÖÄ»
What's that?
Trial separation usually means make an effort.
×ÖÄ»
I thought it meant "Here's your balls back.
Thanks for the loan."
×ÖÄ»
Okay, that's nice. Yeah.
Not in front of my daughter. Nice.
×ÖÄ»
She doesn't know what I'm talking about.
Let's go.
×ÖÄ»
Bye, Daddy. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
No hugs? Kisses? Thank you for the Chinese food?
×ÖÄ»
And the awesome movies?
- I love you. - I love you, too.
×ÖÄ»
Okay. Have a good day at school.
Bye. Bye, babe.
×ÖÄ»
Don't forget about soccer.
30. Yeah, 6:30, I know.
×ÖÄ»
Okay, let's go.
Bye. Bye, babe.
×ÖÄ»
Let's go, let's go.
Come on.
×ÖÄ»
Finally.
What does she want now?
Ó²×ÖÄ»
×ÖÄ»
Damn it. Damn it!
Okay, just... Excuse me.
×ÖÄ»
How much longer is this gonna take?
He's-he's just gonna have to wait, okay?
×ÖÄ»
I'll be there when I'm there. Bye.
Mr. Mitchell... Yeah?
×ÖÄ»
Can we chat for a second? Sure.
Have a seat.
×ÖÄ»
No idea where this came from?
×Ö
No.
Ä»
Like I said, I... my doorbell rang,
×ÖÄ»
I went to answer it,
nobody was there, but this was sitting there.
×ÖÄ»
And the next thing I know, it's like Fallujah.
At first, I thought it was a former client,
×ÖÄ»
someone who wasn't happy with me.
I'm a criminal defense attorney.
×ÖÄ»
Yeah? Yeah.
Not just white collar, but street crooks, too.
×ÖÄ»
So, sometimes the verdicts don't work out
and they'll come knocking. Hey...
×ÖÄ»
you don't know who Daniel Easton is?
No.
×ÖÄ»
Never seen him before? Nope, never.
He's a dentist.
×ÖÄ»
Has a private practice in a medical center downtown.
14301 South Figueroa.
×ÖÄ»
Okay.
But you don't know...
×ÖÄ»
who this belongs to?
No, I don't.
×ÖÄ»
It's a Beretta 9-millimeter.
92-a.
×ÖÄ»
It has no serial number,
no identifying marks.
×ÖÄ»
Okay.
Wow, barrel's been smoothed out,
×ÖÄ»
so any ballistics report will be corrupted.
Could you just not point that at me, please?
×ÖÄ»
Thank you.
I'm not joking.
×Ö
Just you work things out. I'm playin'.
Ä»
Okay. I'm just playin'.
×ÖÄ»
We're done here.
Wait, don't you need that for evidence?
×ÖÄ»
Excuse me, I...
In case you need to reach me.
×ÖÄ»
Hey, that-that isn't even mine.
Yeah?
×ÖÄ»
Are you close? Yeah, I'm downstairs. Why?
Mr. Valverde's waiting for you. Already?
×ÖÄ»
He's been here for 30 minutes.
He ate all of the Skittles.
×ÖÄ»
Okay, I'm on my way up.
That's one, that's two,
×ÖÄ»
three, four,
five, six.
×ÖÄ»
That's half, and I'll get the rest to you next week.
But the real reason why I came here
×ÖÄ»
is because I want to thank you, man.
You did a lot for me and my family.
×ÖÄ»
You kept me out of jail.
You kept food on the table for my kids,
×ÖÄ»
and I want to tell you from the bottom of my heart,
anything you need, man. I got your back, you feel me?
×ÖÄ»
The same way I got your wife's front.??
I was havin' sex with her last night.
×ÖÄ»
She's pregnant with my kid, so I'll be family.
What? I... You listening to me?
×ÖÄ»
I'm sorry... I owe you my life.
I appreciate you comin' in.
×ÖÄ»
I'm-I'm havin'...
You ever have... You're out in fantasy land,
×ÖÄ»
thinkin' about that new Benz you're gonna buy this weekend.
No, I just... That's where you're at.
×ÖÄ»
Just havin' one of those rough days, you know?
Ó²×ÖÄ»
×ÖÄ»
Ian Mitchell, you have two days, 17 hours, 14 minutes
to expire Daniel Easton.
×Ö
Yo, what was the Tony Montana doin' here, man?
Ä»
Hey, keep your voice down.
×ÖÄ»
The guy's long gone. Don't worry. Asshole.
What? It's fine.
×ÖÄ»
Close the door. All right.
What's up, man? We gonna go grab lunch or what?
×ÖÄ»
You know, I'm gonna stay in.
I'm gonna stay in. I'm behind.
×ÖÄ»
I got to tell you about this date I had last night
with this performance artist.
×ÖÄ»
Stripper? Hey, man, she's a nice girl.
And she's got the greatest ass I have ever seen.
×ÖÄ»
I'm talkin' an 18-year-old girl's ass...
Is she 18, Raj?
×ÖÄ»
What's up, man? What?
I mean, are you okay? I'm good.
×ÖÄ»
I'm good.
Good. Okay, all right.
×ÖÄ»
Thanks. No, cool.
Yeah, man, I-I'll talk to you late-later.
×ÖÄ»
Hey, Raj. Yo.
Close the door.
×ÖÄ»
Sit down. I want you to...
listen to something.
×ÖÄ»
What is it?
Just... Is it ringing? Are you hearing it?
×ÖÄ»
It's just ringing.
×Ö
We're sorry, your call cannot be completed.
×ÖÄ»
Check the number and dial again. Awesome.
I must have dialed it wrong.
×ÖÄ»
We're sorry, your call cannot be completed as dialed.
What the hell?
×ÖÄ»
Um, have a good lunch, man.
All right.
×ÖÄ»
You...
All right, yeah.
×ÖÄ»
I'll see you in a bit. Mm-hm.
Yeah. I called North Hollywood.
×ÖÄ»
I called Van Nuys, Devonshire.
My address? My home is Los Angeles, a Los Angeles address.
×ÖÄ»
Yes, I realize this is Burbank. I'm trying to...
Well, that's what I did.
×ÖÄ»
I called right away, right when it happened,
and... and they sent a guy.
×ÖÄ»
LAPD, yes, they sent a guy.
No, I understand that, okay?
×ÖÄ»
You're... You're confused.
Something doesn't add up, because whoever you sent out...
×ÖÄ»
Mother...
Son of a bitch.
Ó²×ÖÄ»
Ó²×ÖÄ»2
×ÖÄ»
Hi there.
Hi. How can I help you?
×ÖÄ»
Hi. Um, I'm looking for Dr. Easton.
He's getting ready to leave for the day.
×ÖÄ»
Are you a patient?
I'm gonna need to schedule
×ÖÄ»
- Mrs. Tapper for next week. - Okay.
Dr. Easton, there's a gentleman here for you.
×ÖÄ»
Oh. Hi.
Hi.
×ÖÄ»
I'm Ian, Ian Mitchell.
Can I help you? Yeah.
×ÖÄ»
This is gonna sound a little strange, but I thought maybe...
This was placed on my doorstep this morning.
×Ö
I thought maybe you might know why or where from,
Ä»
if there was any...
×ÖÄ»
I thought maybe you...
Ah, excuse me, you can't go back there. Hey.
×ÖÄ»
I just wanna talk! Hey!
Hey!
×ÖÄ»
Okay, okay! It's okay.
You don't need to do that.
×ÖÄ»
You're new, aren't you?
You were outside my house this morning.
×ÖÄ»
Who... Who are you?
My name's Mara.
×ÖÄ»
I live in Torrance.
I teach 3rd grade.
×ÖÄ»
I killed four people in the last six months.
Two men, two women.
×ÖÄ»
You were supposed to be my fifth.
Why didn't you?
×ÖÄ»
I've never done it from that close up before.
I could feel you starting to go.
×ÖÄ»
What's happening?
It's a game.
×ÖÄ»
A game?
Yeah.
×ÖÄ»
What kind of game?
Not the fun kind.
×ÖÄ»
Yeah, well, how was I...
I mean, why... why am I...
×ÖÄ»
No one knows why they're chosen.
One day the box just shows up and it starts.
×ÖÄ»
After that, there's no getting out.
Where does it come from, the box? I...
×ÖÄ»
The Watchers.
The Watchers?
×ÖÄ»
Wait, wait, wait, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
×ÖÄ»
No, no, no, no, no. Please.
Just please. No, no, no, no, no, no!
×ÖÄ»
Please don't. You don't have to do this.
Please. No, no, please don't.
×ÖÄ»
Don't, don't. Please don't.
I can't do this anymore.
×ÖÄ»
I'm done.
But you just said there's no getting out.
×ÖÄ»
Hey.
Hey, wait. Hey. Wait, stop! No!