(KRS-ONE's
"Step Into A World" plays)
* Step into a world
* Where there's no...
Eighth grade done, son.
I made it.
(music stops)
Can you do that again
for the camera?
(scoffs) No, man.
And put that away.
The graduation ceremony
is over.
The end of
another school year.
(door closes)
I have to say,
I'm starting to think
moving to Orlando
was a good idea.
We've been here
for three years.
Eddie finished
middle school...
It's been a long haul
since starting
on that Wednesday.
...Cattleman's
is going great...
Well, pretty soon
Golden Saddle
will be copying me
copying them.
...and I just got
my biggest listing yet --
a house
in Gulf Mist Estates.
That fancy
gated community?
Damn, woman.
Right?
We should celebrate.
Turn on the A.C.
(gasps)
EVAN: Yes.
O-oh!
We're doing it, Jessica --
We're living
the American dream,
just like --
the landlord!
Quick,
hide your grandmother!
You still haven't
added her to the lease?
No, it's 100 extra bucks
a month.
Are you gonna pay it?
Move, move!
Put her in the pantry!
Go, go, go, go!
* Fresh off the boat
* I'm gettin' mine
everywhere I go *
* If you don't know, homey,
now you know *
* Fresh off the boat
* Homey, you don't know
where I come from *
* But I know where I'm goin'
* I'm fresh off the boat
**
Another
debate team victory.
I still haven't heard
one good reason
why we shouldn't
have capital punishment.
You'll never sell me
on the electric chair.
That power bill
must be so high.
I have to make a quick stop
to meet my new client.
By all means, by all means.
Whoa.
This place looks nice.
Eddie Murphy's mistress
lives here.
Oh.
We've had a lot of trouble
trying to sell this place.
It's a tough market
for high-end real estate.
I'll still find you
a buyer.
(sighs) Okay.
I like your debate blazer.
The gold buttons
whisper power
instead of shouting it.
It's actually
my everyday blazer.
I go to
St. Orlando's Prep.
Private school --
Do you love it?
I bet you love it.
I love it.
Every two years,
they refresh
all of the library books
so the pages
are always crisp.
Girl.
For real.
My mom's
a librarian there.
Did I mention they give us
briefcases?
They have uniforms,
an amazing debate team...
JESSICA: (sighs)
...a science lab
that is an actual lab.
They even line up
for the water fountain,
unlike the savages
at my school.
(all kids shouting)
GIRL: (screams)
Can I please go to
St. Orlando's next year, Mommy?
"Saint"?
Sounds expensive.
But I really want to be with
a higher echelon of people.
Did you just learn
the world "echelon"?
Yes, and I would have
learned it sooner
if I went
to St. Orlando's.
Private school
is a waste of money.
It's for parents
who outsource their discipline.
But the private-school kids
call each other "Chum"!
I don't need to pay people
to push you guys to succeed.
(sighs)
I already do that
myself.
The Menendez brothers
went to private school,
and look what happened
to them.
Who are they?
Doesn't matter.
The important thing is
they didn't
get away with it.
**
Check out my new weapon
against the scourge
of dead palm fronds --
my telescopic pruner.
Mm! Heh.
(laughs)
I'll tell ya.
The right tool
can make yard work a hoot.
Hmm.
(laughs)
I've always dreamed of owning
a sit-down lawn mower.
I'd cut grass,
reenact scenes from
"Can't Buy Me Love"...
Well, do it.
Your restaurant's
doing well.
You can afford one.
My yard doesn't
belong to me.
I rent.
I can't pluck a dandelion
without hearing about it
from my landlord Murray.
I can't wait
to be a homeowner.
A man should own
his own house.
Murray's open to selling,
but Jessica and I
are very strict
about our long-term plans.
We agreed for
the next three years
we reinvest everything
into our businesses.
(Crunch)
Oh, man!
That was Honey's
favorite flamingo.
She's gonna be P.O.'d.
Aw.
(Door bell chimes)
Hey.
Evan said
he'd pay for my manicure
if I talked to you
about St. Orlando's.
I'm an alumna -- I --
EVAN: Will you please
hear her out?
I know private school
is expensive,
but we only
have to send me.
The "Others"
don't need to know.
Come with me.
These...are life plans.
I made one
for each member of the family,
and I update them
every five years.
I've mapped out
all the classes and experiences
you boys need to be successful
and lead good lives.
Emery's good
at so many things,
so I left
his career plan open,
and I focused on
his personal life.
Eddie's plan was easy
because the goal was simple.
* Yeah
And here is your plan.
I've thought of everything.
I've already seen
these boards.
What do you mean?
I use the garage
as a cartwheel zone
when I want to express joy
in private.
But I wasn't planning on you
finding them
for another two years.
You're ahead of schedule.
And I'm ahead of everyone
in my class, too.
That's why I want to go
to St. Orlando's.
I could just give you
more C.L.C.
I've already done
all the workbooks --
even the French one.
(speaks French)
**
JESSICA: You have five minutes
to convince me
why private school's
better for my son
than public school.
I'll only need four.
EDDIE: Emery, that squirrel
was on the porch again.
We need to bean him in the head
with your marbles.
(mouse clicking)
Is that a Pentium II?
Yep.
I borrowed it from the A/V club
for the summer.
Check it out,
I'm editing
your graduation video.
We are gathered
to say goodbye
[voice breaking]
to the class of 1997.
Whoa,
it's like "Pop Up Video"!
Isn't it cool?
As the great Boyz II Men
once said,
"It's so hard to say goodbye
to yesterday."
(clicks)
So funny, right?
Sure.
Snack break --
You guys want anything?
You know we do.
You guys want to have
some fun?
-Yeah.
-Mm-hmm.
Lou, I've been thinking
about what you said.
About dandelions?
I know.
I regret sharing that
with you.
It felt very personal.
No, no, no.
About you wanting
to own your own house.
I have a friend
that can help you
free up some cash.
He's outside right now
waiting for my signal.
Now!
(soft music plays)
Oh, my God.
(chuckles nervously)
Michael Bolton.
(Chuckles nervously,
clears throat)
Um, what are you
doing here?
Recording my new album
in Orlando.
I got to be in Florida
183 days out of the year
for tax purposes.
Savvy in
and out of the studio.
(chuckles)
I've got a proposal
for you.
Do you know how many women
would kill to hear me say that?
So many women!
My wife for one.
(chuckles)
JESSICA: I already pay taxes
for public school.
Why would I spend an extra
four grand a year on private.
Well, first of all,
St. Orlando's
is a year-round school.
No summer vacation?
I could just stick my kids
in public summer school
for free.
Certainly, but half the kids
are forced to be there
because they're, forgive me,
"Dum-dums."
Is that really
what you want?
Well, what I don't want
is to help pay
for your school's
football program.
There's no football here.
We teach only
the "Networking" sports --
golf, squash, birding.
That's great.
But I'm sure the teachers here
are just as lazy.
Oh,
we don't have teachers.
We hire specialists
in their field.
We call them
"Consultants."
Continue.
We're private,
so we can easily fire
any underperforming
consultants.
(exhales sharply)
Did I mention that
99% of our students
go on
to Ivy League schools?
The other 1%
go straight to med school.
The first step
to doctor-president.
We have relationships
with all the top universities.
We send more kids
to Harvard
than any other school
in Orlando.
And with a student
who is already
academically strong,
like your son?
We could send him
into the stratosphere.
The astronaut
holding the camera
is also
a St. Orlando's alum.
One tuition, please.
Yes!
Goodbye, Mommy.
Tell the family
I'll see them in six months.
W-We're not
a boarding school.
Ah.
I'll pay for everything
but P.E.
Evan can just learn tennis
from his brother.
We can't do that.
Okay, fine.
I'll pay for P.E.,
but no English.
He gets that free
from life.
We don't offer private school
à la carte.
I'll pay
the whole year up front,
but you have to give me
a substantial
early-bird discount.
It's not that simple.
First your son must be
accepted into this school.
There is an application.
Okay, sure. Whatever.
I'll fill it out
right now.
It's more involved
than that.
We need
letters of recommendation,
transcripts,
an interview.
We're highly selective.
But...
...Diversity.
Oh, we don't have to worry
about that here.
We're private.
So,
I have to earn the privilege
to pay
your ridiculous tuition?
If my son
doesn't get into Harvard,
I want a full refund.
Headmaster.
**
You want to buy
my restaurant?
Well, I've already
conquered music,
and it's time to diversify
my brand.
And Kenny Rogers
is doing so well
with his
chicken restaurants --
so well.
He never lets you forget.
I carry this around with me
just to give me
motivation.
(sleigh bells jingle)
Hmm.
(chuckles) Yeah.
Well, I'm flattered,
but my restaurant's
not for sale.
I moved my whole family
down here for this,
put a lot of work into it.
I built it from nothing.
What if I come in
as a silent partner?
You could still
run the day-to-day,
I'd get
a stake of the company,
and you get
a big cash infusion.
Which you can use
to buy your house.
Ayy!
Hmm.
That does sound like
a good deal.
But Jessica and I
have a rule --
We don't deviate
from our life plan.
And it's worked out well
for us so far.
(sighs)
Sorry,
but the answer is no.
(exhales sharply)
Michael, I am so sorry.
I don't know what happened.
I'm s--
It's okay.
It was worth a shot.
How do you guys
even know each other?
Oh, I did some
emergency dental work on him
during his
Time, Love & Tenderness tour.
Oh.
I slipped on a bouquet
of white roses.
**
(computer bleeps)
(laughter)
DAVE:
It's not funny, dude.
(laughter)
I always wear underwear.
Look.
Oh. No. Never mind.
What's going on?
We're turning
your boring gradation video
into gold.
(laughter)
Trent, I can't believe
you're a Sparrow Scout.
That's so lame.
I know
how to filet a trout.
What can you filet?
You know I don't eat
anything that has a mama.
(computer bleeps)
BRIAN: Wait, what?
What the hell is this?
(laughter)
Who wrote this bubble?
Who thinks this?
No, I want to know.
**
We should probably update this
to include private school.
Should I get
the Wite-Out?
In this family,
we don't hide mistakes.
We look at them,
feel shame,
and never talk about them
again.
Hey, what are you guys
doing out here?
I'm just showing Evan
our life plans.
Oh, great.
You know,
I was just thinking about
how well
we've done with those.
Yes, because
we're very strict
about sticking
to the plan.
Uh, we sure are.
(laughs)
Never stray no matter what.
Otherwise, what's the point
of a plan, right?
Right.
(chuckles)
Uh, Evan, I don't know
if your mom mentioned this,
but I did
all the collage work.
I didn't.
Hmm.
You're not gonna tell him
about private school?
Not yet.
Let's get you in first.
If I'm gonna stray
from the plan,
it can't be
for just a "Maybe."
(Notorious B.I.G.'s
"Mo Money Mo Problems" plays)
Evan got a kangaroo sticker
in math.
Does kangaroo mean "A"?
We don't believe
in letter grades.
Well, St. Orlando's does,
so if you had to say
what grade
a kangaroo represents,
would you say "A"?
I'd say a "B."
* Can't no PhD hold me down
"A"?
* Cudda schooled me
to the game *
* Now I know my duty
* Stay humble, stay low,
blow like Hootie *
Your daughter attends
St. Orlando's, right?
As the parent
of a current student,
I need you to sign
this letter of recommendation
I wrote for my son.
* I don't know what
they want from me *
I will if you lower
your commission.
* It's like the mo' money
we come across *
* The mo' problems we see
You're an alumna
of St. Orlando's, right?
I need you to sign
this letter of recommendation
I wrote for my son.
Oh, I really
can't sign anything
with my nails
so jacked up.
* I'm the D to the A
to the D-D-Y *
* I know you'd rather see me die
than to see me fly *
* I call all the shots,
rip all the spots *
* Rock all the rocks,
cop all the drops *
So we agree.
We pool our graduation money
so we can turn
this driveway into a gym.
We'll have all summer
to get ripped.
We show up to high school
yoked out,
and people will think
we're sophomores.
I know a great
preacher curl workout.
Two of my sisters
work at GNC,
so I can hook us up
with some creatine.
It's really
coming together.
My step-brother
has the video.
What?
I took it home
last night
to work on some more
mean bubbles about you guys,
and he found it
in my room.
That dude is a tool.
He's gonna show the tape
to everyone.
It won't matter how buff I am
when we start school
if people know
I'm a Sparrow Scout.
People will think
I want to do it with a tree.
I'm ruined.
I was gonna
go out for football.
I just want your support
on this.
Which part, man?
We have to get
that tape back.
We can't start high school
as losers.
Royce:
This is the interview portion
of our process.
We just have a few questions
to ask you.
It's my pleasure.
So, Evan, what's a current item
in the news
that interests you?
Sheep cloning.
I think it would be a boon
for the sweater industry.
Who do you admire?
Whom do I admire?
Why are you interested
in our school?
I'd come for your blazers,
but I'd stay for your
International
Baccalaureate program.
Tell me about your family.
They're all good eggs.
We rent a house
in North Orlando,
my parents
run a steakhouse.
We're just your typical
American family
who's overcome
incredible odds
to achieve big dreams.
(chuckles)
Well,
that's all of our questions.
No red flags.
(inhales sharply)
We'll be in touch with you
very soon.
**
(whispering)
Hey, great job.
Evan, it's here.
It's so big!
That means they're sending us
parking instructions,
reading lists,
bumper stickers for the car...
"Dear Mr. Huang,
sorry to inform you that"...
The hell?!
Oh, you didn't get in?
And they still sent us these?
How could you not get in?
You have perfect grades,
you killed your interview,
and there is no way they
could tie you back to Eddie.
Well, I guess they don't think
I belong in their echelon.
No.
Someone made a mistake.
(knocks at door)
You messed up, Deidre.
Evan didn't
get into St. Orlando's.
It was your
letter of recommendation.
Uh, you mean
the one that you wrote
and I just signed?
W-- It was not
a strong signature!
It tapered off at the end,
conveying doubt.
Jessica, look,
private schools are picky.
Unless your family
has gone there for generations,
or you're the child
of someone who works there,
there's really
no guarantee.
But Evan
is overqualified.
How could
they reject him?
Maybe it's not him.
Maybe it's you.
These schools don't just
evaluate the student.
They evaluate
the whole family.
Why would my family
be rejected?
We're doing great.
We live
in a good neighborhood,
we own
our own restaurant --
Word in
the birding community --
St. Orlando's
saw you as renters
who work
in the service industry.
And I heard sometimes
you hide you mother-in-law
in the pantry?
Mm.
(car door closes)
Murray,
what are you doing here?
I already sent you
this month's rent.
Ah,
just inspecting my property,
and I happen to notice
that there's some damage
to the driveway
which I'm gonna
have to charge you for.
Did you have
an above-ground pool out here
or something?
We did not.
And I notice that the lawn
looks a little different.
Have you been
tampering with it?
What? No.
Well, someone's been
weeding this yard,
'cause I don't see
any dandelions.
You know they help indicate
whether the grass
is getting enough moisture,
so someone better not
be messing with them.
(inhales sharply)
You know what, Murray?
I did pick the dandelions.
I picked 10 dandelions,
and I made 10 wishes,
and you know
what they all were?
To own my own house.
You know, you don't have
to keep making the same wish
over and over.
God hears you
after the first one.
(sighs)
(Video plays,
Tyler laughs)
Are you sure
your step-brother's only 16?
No. Tyler could be 30.
I don't know
much about him.
I'm just gonna go talk to him,
young man to young man --
ask him to remember
what it was like
when he was a freshman,
how hard it was
starting high school
when all you have
is your friends
and how I'm asking,
as Brian's friend,
for that tape back.
(inspirational music plays)
(music stops)
Well, that'll never work.
Yeah, put that
in the "Stupid idea" file.
You guys are too quick
with that file.
I don't know why my
"Poison him" idea
is in there.
Unless someone
comes up with a better plan,
I'm going in.
(door opens, closes)
(laughs)
(knocks at door)
Mom, I don't want
any muesli.
I recognize you
from the video.
Your pop-up said
you ate string cheese
that fell in the gutter.
It was lying
on a bed of leaves.
It was clean.
What are you doing here?
I'm one of your
step-brother's friends.
I'm here to talk to you
young man to young man,
and to ask you to remember
what it was like
when you were
a freshman --
(glass shatters)
-What the hell?
-Get the tape!
Poison him
before you leave!
**
Nope.
What's this
two-tone one?
They're all the same,
Michael.
Okay, let's do it.
Is my receptionist
not out there?
Rebecca!
I don't care if it's not
in my life plan.
I can't be a renter
anymore.
I need to own my house,
so I'll sell you
a stake in the restaurant
and take you on
as a partner.
And together,
we'll destroy Kenny Rogers.
That's more your thing,
but I like that
you're motivated by revenge.
My wife will love that.
(all chuckling)
Mom, I've had time
to think about it,
and it's gonna be okay.
I thought you said
you weren't feeling challenged
in your regular school.
And I'll make that
my new challenge.
I'll do extra C.L.C.,
audit some
junior college classes,
take an immersion trip
to Montreal
to work on my French.
Michael Bolton
offered me a partnership deal
for the restaurant,
and I think
we should take it.
What?
I know it means
straying from our life plan,
but we should make exceptions
for good opportunities.
I want to own our house,
and this deal
will let us do that.
You're right.
Maybe we can be less
strict with our plans.
But we're not buying
this house.
We'd like to buy
your house.
You want to buy
this house?
But with
one stipulation.
You get our son
into St. Orlando's.
Your wife works there,
right?
She gets our son in,
you've sold your house.
We can work
something out.
I'm going
to private school!
I'm not in the garage,
but screw it!
(chuckles)
Are we sure about this?
You want
to own your own home,
I want Evan
in private school.
Michael Bolton
will get us both.
**
DAVE: We did it!
We got the tape back.
Are you gonna get in trouble
for throwing a rock
through your
stepbrother's window?
Eh, if things get heated
I can always fake a seizure.
Guys, we're entering high school
on a win.
Things are gonna be okay.
Yeah!
Divorce.
What's going on?
Pack your things
and say goodbye
to your friends.
We're moving.
Time to make new friends.
EMERY:
Hold that look, Eddie.
I'm trying
to find the zoom.
Ah, there it is.
**
-- Captions by VITA --