马男波杰克中
着重描写了关于抑郁的部分
and if this was a different show it
might have been the series finale
for five seasons we saw bojack's
selfishness and toxicity permeate
throughout his life and the lives of
those he cares about but now
after a stint in rehab we actually start
to see important growth
from a man who didn't think that he was
capable of change over the course of the
face of depression bojack starts to
understand what it means to be a present
and caring friend and not unlike his
toxicity this change starts to have
tangible effects that permeate his
friends lives
and though we know that the show would
go on to hold bojack accountable for the
ways he hurt and abused people
this was still one of the most important
stops on bojack's journey one that tells
us
it's never too late to change for the
better
[Music]
the episode begins with bojack cleaning
up the mess left behind when he went to
rehab but in doing so it dredges up all
kinds of painful memories
memories of the ways he hurt and abused
people in his life we see the echoes of
his mistakes across the house
his fight with gina driving his car into
his pool throwing his mother's babies
all over the balcony
when he can't take it anymore he gets in
his car and he drives but the memories
continue as his own words and the words
of his friends echo through his mind
please don't make me go back to la you
can count on me you are all the things
that are wrong with you now that he's
sober he has no way to drown out the
memories of those regrets
he has to live with sarah lynn's death
and the events of new mexico and is
falling out with todd
and it all ends on one haunting but
exceedingly important memory of himself
and diane
i haven't changed at all yes you are the
last person to get that i'm not gonna
change as mojack arrives at his a.a
meeting he realizes sharona
the stylist from horsing around is there
too and once again he's flooded with
memories of his mistakes forcing the
blame for cereal and getting drunk onto
sharona back in the 90s
and getting her fired after this bojack
goes out to eat with todd who casually
says something important it can't be at
my house
just reminds me of what an i've
been makes sense your house reminds me
of what an you've been to
the sequence illustrates that bojack
cannot escape his mistakes but in the
end
bojack shouldn't be escaping his
mistakes he should remember
the lasting effects of his own actions
because if he doesn't he'll simply be
doomed to repeat them
i'm not gonna change i wanted to thank
you for jack's memory of his fight with
diane as i've said before
is exceedingly important you haven't
changed at all yes congratulations you
are the last person to get that i'm not
gonna
change bojack was unwilling or felt he
was incapable of changing he felt that
he was doomed to repeat his cycles of
abuse and toxicity no matter what he did
so he didn't even try
but through his time at rehab and now
his reacclimation to a sober life in the
outside world we begin to see change
actually take hold though it is a
process we even see him still fighting
some of his old tendencies throughout
the episode when he's eating lunch with
todd todd actually
tries to open up about his difficult
relationship with his mother but bojack
doesn't really recognize that todd is
reaching out
moms are weird right um yeah moms are
weird
at his a.a meeting he seems exasperated
by the act of admitting that he's an
alcoholic i'm bojack
and oh god it feels so
dumb and i'm an alcoholic
when he goes to visit princess carolyn
he makes up a selfless excuse
even though he's actually there for a
selfish reason i also have a favor to
ask
of course you do but these things slowly
start to fade as he visits his friends
and family and he actually starts to
learn more about himself and the process
of forgiveness
the metamorphosis mostly begins with his
visit to see diane in chicago dan
is going through an incredibly difficult
time in her life and doesn't want bojack
to see the mess that she's living in but
through their heart to heart bojack
admits something that he's learned about
himself
and does something that we haven't seen
much of from him i bought into this idea
that i was the thing that couldn't be
changed bojack acknowledges that he had
stifled himself in his ability to change
and then immediately does something that
showcases that change he thanks diane
but this is more than just a typical
thank you
bojack is effectively thanking diane for
the events of their fallout so
the reason i came to chicago is
i wanted to thank you for believing in
me when i didn't
because in the end diane's frustrations
and anger towards bojack in season five
all stemmed from her belief that he
could and should be better
that he can and should be able to change
bojack was the one who wasn't willing
but now he is he's willing to learn and
grow the next morning before leaving
bojack cleans up diane's apartment and
leaves before she even wakes up
he does something selfless simply to
help his friend without the expectation
of anything in return or even
acknowledgement of his good deed the
change is taking place
and through his next trip to connecticut
to visit hollyhock bojack actually
learns more about his own tendencies
while spending time with his sister he
witnesses hollyhock fighting with her
best friend tawny
you could say sorry would it even matter
no words are meaningless this showcases
bojack's belief that asking for
forgiveness
isn't enough he is like tawny in this
situation
so firmly confident that his mistake
can't be made up for that he is
unwilling to even apologize but then he
sees how hollyhock responds
you do this thing where you don't think
you can ever be forgiven so you don't
apologize but i can't forgive you if you
don't say you're sorry
bojack sees that though mistakes can't
necessarily be fixed
showcasing remorse and acknowledging
your mistakes can go a really long way
okay i'm sorry thank you
that's all i wanted i'm sorry i love you
bojack starts to become less
self-absorbed and more cognizant
of the people around him this is pretty
blatantly hinted at when he gives his
narcissist portrait to princess caroline
the narcissus myth is specifically one
of an attractive self-absorbed person
who falls in love with his own
reflection
to the point where he is unwilling to
leave the water to stop staring at
himself this is actually where the word
narcissism comes from
narcissist i thought the painting was
about me so bojack giving away the
physical representation of his
narcissism
is obviously alluding to him beginning
to give up those tendencies himself
and in his aaa meetings bojack starts to
open up about how uncomfortable he is in
his house
and how he has a hard time feeling like
a changed person in this overly familiar
location
but it's the same house the same city
just nothing's changed
so how am i supposed to but the fact
that bojack is even saying this
is proof that he is changing because the
old bojack would have just let his old
lifestyle reinfect him and sharona
actually sees this change in bojack as
well she sees that he's actually trying
and because of this
she forgives him even before he has a
chance to apologize but of course he
still insists on apologizing
please just let me say it i'm sorry
i'm so sorry and with this change in
bojack's behavior and attitude there is
a physical change as well
shirona gives bojack's hair a trim
revealing his natural grey hair
bojack is a character who effectively
stopped growing in his early 20s when he
got his role on horse and around
that success stagnated his growth in
maturity for years as he tried to relive
his glory days
but now 30 years later as his growth
actually takes hold
the physical growth follows suit he
ditches the old get up that is
reminiscent of his horse in a round
sweater and he looks like a new person
because in a lot of ways he is and as
these changes within bojack take place
he starts to have tangible positive
effects on the people closest to him
i'm sorry i'm so sorry as bojack
undergoes his metamorphosis the effects
of his new attitude start to affect
those around him
at the beginning of the episode we see
how bojack is still fighting some of his
selfish tendencies but the moment things
start to change is when bojack visits
diane
diane is struggling immensely in chicago
she's secured this book deal but hasn't
been able to find the creative
motivation to write her psychiatrist
says she's depressed but because of a
prior experience with antidepressants
she isn't willing to acknowledge this
tried the medication your doctor
prescribed well i'd feel worse
they put me on prozac in college and i
was so calm and boring i didn't even
want a live journal diane relays how she
felt creatively bankrupt when she was
previously on meds and even brings up a
couple specifics
and then dawson's creek got bad because
there was no one to speak truth to power
it made me break out i gained weight
diane is struggling with starting her
path down the road to recovery
and this is actually something a lot of
creatives feel that things that make
them damaged
actually make them interesting and they
fear that by fixing those problems
their creativity and career will suffer
when bojack visits diane she expresses
her fears about how that path to mental
wellness might reveal that she's
uninteresting that there isn't anything
of substance underneath her trauma
because you keep thinking under all that
nothing there's got to be
something but all you find is nothing
but bojack does something incredibly
helpful
though i'm not sure if he recognized
just how helpful it was
i wanted to thank you for believing in
me when i didn't
and for encouraging me to accept the
help i needed in thanking diane for
helping him down his road to recovery
he's effectively doing the same thing
for her bojack and diane have
a lot of similar tendencies by relaying
his own experience
bojack is helping diane see her own
demons and encouraging her to seek the
help she needs at the end of the episode
when guy returns from his trip we see
diane
who like bojack has also undergone a
change in wardrobe but she also is
looking a bit heavier and she's holding
a sign that says dawson's creak was
always bad with a huge smile on her face
diane sought help
she took the meds she was prescribed and
it was all set in motion by bojack's act
of genuine friendship
an act we probably wouldn't have seen
from the old bojack
something similar happens with princess
caroline who's struggling with her fears
about returning to work after spending
so much time with ruthie i'm gonna miss
everything we have this connection now
what if that goes away when i go back to
work the old self-absorbed bojack
probably wouldn't have taken much of an
interest in pc's problem
but not anymore he actually showcases
intimate knowledge of pc's life and
responsibilities and gives her prudent
advice
you are producing a show running a
company
catering to your clients raising a child
a tod
you need your own princess caroline to
take care of you at the end of the
episode princess caroline takes bojack's
advice and rehires judah as a partner at
vim
by splitting major responsibilities
she'll be able to have a fulfilling
career and spend time with her daughter
as well
she would even go on to marry judah at
the end of the series bojack's change is
already showcasing major tangible
positives in the lives of his loved ones
and this is when bojack actually starts
to go out of his way to help his friends
earlier in the episode todd talked to
bojack about his asexual dating app but
lamented that there was nobody else on
it bojack actually recognizes in passing
that it might be something that mod who
works at cinebuddy is interested in
i don't want to presume anything but
there's an app you might be interested
in
an app todd of course matches with mod
and the two start dating and they even
end up moving in together but the most
charming and memorable way that bojack
helps his friends has got to be with mr
peanut butter we've known from the
moment the show started that mr peanut
butter loves bojack and desperately
wants to be his friend
this was mr peanut butter's very first
line in the entire series
mr peanut butter and bojack horseman in
the same
room what is this a crossover episode
obviously bojack has never really given
him the time of day
but not anymore well looks like you
finally got your crossover episode
what uh oh my god okay is this real
bojack
actually gives mr peanut butter that
crossover episode something we can
without a doubt say that the old bojack
would never have done
and mr peanut butter's happiness cannot
be understated the way that the face of
depression showcases bojack's change
in turn showcases the positive effects
he has on the world around him an
incredibly important message
[Music]
peace be with you peace be with you
though bojack has actively undergone
this change throughout the episode the
result of lots of work and
self-reflection in rehab
you know that his regrets and mistakes
still haunt him but bojack shouldn't be
looking to escape his past
he can't move forward without accepting
it so while waiting for his next flight
bojack visits old horseberg and stumbles
upon a reenactment of an old church
service
the words of the pastor really resonate
with bojack it is only when we show
ourselves forgiveness and mercy that we
truly live a life of grace that we are
reborn the pastor tells the congregation
to offer grace
and peace to one another peace be with
you peace be with you peace be with you
peace be with you peace be with you
peace be with you
you can tell how much this affects
bojack in the moment and it's a huge
step for bojag moving forward
as he heads off to his new life at
wesleyan having changed bojack forgives
himself
he doesn't forget about what he did or
run away from his past
he simply accepts that it happened and
allows himself to move forward
this episode operates as though it could
be a series finale
we see bojack make the changes in his
life that we've wanted to see for five
seasons
every main character gets their happy
ending that hints at where they could be
heading moving forward
and the entire episode is incredibly
cathartic
it's the tension release that we've
learned not to expect out of bojack
horseman
while we know that in the following half
of season six bojack would show
regression as his life starts to fall
apart this episode is still a vital
piece of bojack's journey
it shows that bojack is capable of
change it shows that he can be
a fundamentally better person when he
puts in the work
and though the show rightfully held
bojack accountable for the things he had
done
we can remain hopeful that he will
continue down this path
after the end of the series but for now
as james henry jr's song take me down
easy plays us out
we know something else is on the horizon
and now i see
storm clouds
up in the distance
a terrible omen
a beautiful show
so take me down easy
take me down easy
let me land softly
back in your arms
thanks so much for tuning in to another
bojack horseman episode breakdown also
if you didn't know i started a podcast
called cartoons that curse with my
friend tunrific tariq we cover our
favorite adult animated series one
season at a time and we will definitely
be covering bojack horseman in the
future so feel free to check it out and
as always let me know what episodes you
want me to cover
next on these bojack breakdowns and stay
tuned for the next one peace
[Music]
you