The Premier League
run-in kicked off today.
We have eight games on the way.
Martin Keown and Stephen Warnock
your Easter egg-sperts.
We begin at St James' Park.
Newcastle needed a win
to boost their chances of European
football next season.
West Ham, one of the
teams they're chasing.
Commentary comes from Alistair Mann.
They both enjoy the unique challenge
European football provides.
Games like this seem pivotal.
Eddie Howe has described this
campaign as challenging
and his latest injury headache
is in need of surgery.
There are three key league
matches for West Ham before
the Europa League quarterfinal
as they seek a fourth
successive European adventure.
The James Ward Prouse
is in instead of Alvarez.
Just one clean sheet in 11 league
games for Newcastle.
None in their last
nine for West Ham.
Encouraging statistics for the
neutral, if not the head coaches.
Gordon.
Effervescent, I am sure
after his England debut.
Is that a penalty?
Yes, it is.
We have barely started this game
and Newcastle have the penalty.
There isn't much in the way
of a protest, to be truthful.
Coufal misses the ball and catches
the ankle and Rob Jones
has an easy decision.
VAR are checking for
the offside in the build-up.
Gordon is beyond Coufal and then
comes back to try and win the ball
and is brought down.
It is confirmed, it is
a Newcastle penalty after all.
It is not offside, it is a penalty.
Five goals in his last seven
Premier League appearances.
Newcastle in front.
A penalty awarded
within three minutes.
He has had plenty to
contend with, Eddie Howe.
He has been talking up how
significant these remaining matches
are and that has given him
the perfect platform
and Newcastle ahead already.
Following that injury,
Byrne has gone to left centre-half.
Antonio looks to take advantage.
Over the bar.
Newcastle were doing
a little readjustment
following injury.
While all that was taking
place, Antonio got in
and lifted it over the bar.
Ward-Prowse.
Antonio.
The flag is down.
Antonio for the equaliser...
1-1.
You felt it was coming.
Newcastle were looking disjointed.
They were giving the ball away.
It is onside, a great
decision from the assistant.
There will be no VAR over rule.
It is level once again.
Murphy.
Not above Gordon and
put his header wide.
Golden opportunity to score not
taken by Anthony Gordon.
Newcastle fans like the appetite.
Gordon is onto it.
Gordon.
And the shot against the angle
and the post by Guimaraes.
Muscled out of it.
It is a terrific game, it really is.
Both sides having a go at the other.
And Bruno Guimaraes within a whisker
of giving Newcastle the lead.
David Moyes said penalty.
Rob Jones said no.
The West Ham free kick.
Bowen is onto it.
Kudus hits it in and West Ham score.
Newcastle say the free
kick shouldn't have been
allowed to be taken.
But it was and West Ham in front.
Paqueta plays it and Kudus
puts it into the net.
There is the foul on Kudus.
2-1 West Ham.
Half-time change to change
the injured goalkeeper.
Lukasz Fabianski is on.
Away from a couple of challenges.
A massive gap in the middle.
The ball reaches Jarrod Bowen
and he has the chance
to make it three...
And he has.
Jarrod Bowen with a devastating
counterattack for West Ham.
It is his 19th goal of the season,
his 15th in the Premier League.
It is all of a sudden,
West Ham three, Newcastle one having
trailed to the earlier penalty.
If anyone can open West Ham up...
What an opportunity.
Longstaff can't believe
it and neither can
the Newcastle supporters.
He was in a wonderful position.
He had half a goal to go
at and he just placed it wide.
It is quite extraordinary,
what is going on.
Newcastle with a catalogue
of injuries this season.
They lose Lascelles,
Craft has gone down.
Dangerous ball.
It was a terrific opportunity
for Harvey Barnes, who met it full
on the side foot volley.
Great save by Fabianski.
Off the line by Fabianski.
He is there again and
it is scrambled away.
Newcastle win it back
and there is a claim of a penalty.
It's not away and then
Coufal gets away.
Rob Jones is going to
make a final decision.
And Newcastle do
have a second penalty.
In the first half, he sent
Iraola the wrong way.
Newcastle have renewed belief.
Great skills from Kudus.
The body movement, left
and right and Gordon felt
that was the only way to stop him.
It is a good ball,
the flag stayed down.
3-3!
Back from injury, back
with the goal, Harvey Barnes.
He had the chance that he hit goal
bound that Lucas Fabianski saved.
This time, Harvey Barnes has found
the back of the goal.
Momentum is a huge thing
in professional sport.
When West Ham had it there seemed
to be only one winner.
Newcastle have arrested
the initiative back again.
Gordon...
The shot is in!
Sensation, Harvey Barnes has turned
this match around with a quite
magnificent brace of goals.
And St James's Park erupts
with noise after a quite
stunning comeback.
The only bit of good
news on a day of bad,
was the return of Harvey Barnes
from injury and this goal sums up
a quite superb cameo from a player
who will emerge as the Man
of the Match, despite only coming
on with minutes to go
in the second half.
It has been the most stunning
football match and Newcastle have
turned it on its head and they have
won it with a brace
from Harvey Barnes.
If Newcastle do qualify
for Europe next season,
they will look at this game
as a major factor
in that achievement.
A yellow card has
just been brandished.
Is that to Gordon?
It was Gordon, he has gone.
He just got yellow carded
for the second time, Anthony Gordon.
He has been sent off.
Ball in towards Soucek.
Gone wide.
It goes into the side netting.
At that moment you have to make
a split-second decision
on what you think is best.
That's all I try to do.
Yes, maybe it was too many
people changing position.
We took time to adjust
and by the time we had
adjusted we were 2-1 down.
Then we had to reshuffle
and thankfully the substitutions
made a positive impact
and we were much better.
A small margin once again.
A couple of decisions the referee
gives on penalty kicks.
I think the second one actually,
Gordon restricts Kalvin Phillips
from kicking the ball.
Put your foot across him,
he's going to kick the ball,
he's not doing it deliberately.
I think it is the wrong decision,
but we had so many things
which didn't go in our favour today.
But the players did
a lot of good things.
Large parts of the season
where myself and many players
missed through injury.
It has been frustrating
for the manager, not
having players available.
I miss the feeling of being out
there and when I am out that
I want to make up for lost time
and help the team as much as I can.
Today was a great
step forward in that.
Incredible comeback for Eddie Howe's
men but they did it the hard way.
He talked about the changes he made.
As defenders you want continuity
on the pitch and it's something
they didn't have in the game.
They started off with the back four
which was Schar, Byrne,
Livramento and Lasalle.
You have burned, the left footer
in the left-back position,
Livramento on his natural right
sided position but then
they have an injury to Lascelles.
You think that's not too bad
because you can play a player
in a like-for-like position but that
isn't how Eddie Howe did things.
There was a lot of movement.
When a midfielder doesn't
have pressure on the ball,
when he doesn't pick the pass,
you have to drop deep.
This is four minutes
after the change.
That lack of communication
and understanding what's going on.
Jones, it is his discretion
whether he wants to carry
on with a head injury.
He decides he can carry on.
Newcastle players switch off,
Willock switches off.
Paqueta is always looking forward.
Jarrod Bowen is alive
to the situation.
All because they switch off.
I'm being very harsh.
Anthony Gordon is a centre forward.
Look at Jarrod Bowen
and the position, 16
yards between them.
Gordon has set off, look at the pace
with which he gets back.
A fraction earlier on the run.
He would get back.
That's the small margins
for the Premier League and how easy
it is to be punished.
It was a really strong performance
from West Ham until that point.
This is Newcastle's problem,
they concede a lot of goals,
too many, although they score many.
They are conceding too
many and that will be
disappointing for Eddie Howe.
What I like about what he has
done, he owned up to it.
I got it wrong and I
tried to correct it.
It was a bonkers game for Newcastle,
a lot of injuries, disruption,
two players on, two off
and when you look at them
it was Harvey Barnes,
the star of the show.
He only came on because
Almiron was injured.
He's been out, Harvey Barnes,
and a barnstorming finish.
3-1 at this point.
David Moyes, he's taken off Antonio
and Kalvin Phillips came on.
Straightaway, he's
on the left-hand side.
He looks up for it and that's
a really good finish.
Great save from the keeper.
Newcastle didn't panic.
3-1 down, you would have thought
they might have done.
Look at this run, fantastic.
This is the equaliser.
Really composed,
through the keeper's legs.
Good for his confidence.
Then this one, the ball across,
Longstaff, he can't quite
get on the end of it.
They kept playing, kept
trying to progress.
Gordon here, he made his
England debut this week.
He has two penalties
in the game, he is involved
in virtually everything.
Harvey Barnes lets it
roll across his body.
Kalvin Phillips diving
in, what's he doing?
He whipped it, right
into the belly of the ball
and it is beautiful from that angle.
That's 4-3.
Such an eventful game.
Keeping the noise
away from Eddie Howe.
Look at the pressure he was under
and they deserved it.
Much needed win.
I'm sitting in his
seat this evening.
Gary Lineker scored twice the last
time Spurs hosted Luton
in a top-flight game.
It must have been a long time ago!
Mark Scott was at the
Tottenham Hotspur Stadium.
1991 was the year with Gary's double
coming in a 4-1 win for Tottenham.
It was a long time since Spurs
failed to score in a league game
prior to their disappointing defeat
at Fulham last time out.
Ange Postecoglou says it is public
the first time that their intensity
levels weren't what they should be.
The only change from the starting XI
is Timo Werner for Johnson.
Van de Ven starting on the bench.
Former Spurs man
Andros Townsend is in.
Jordan Clark moves to the bench.
Kulusevski is onto it.
Making a mess of the pass.
Andros Townsend surging
away for Luton.
Chong!
1-0, Luton.
What a start for the Hatters.
Three goals in his last
five games now, Chong,
and Luton are off to a flyer.
When it broke down here there
didn't look to be too much
on for Andros Townsend but he ate up
the ground in front of him.
Barkley took up a useful position.
He picked out Chong,
picked out the corner.
A well-worked Luton goal but Spurs
will feel they should
have done a lot better
there, wonderful
start for Luton Town.
They've come from behind to win
in the last three home
games against Palace,
Brighton and Brentford.
Timo Werner, brilliantly done!
Oh!
The approach work was wonderful.
The finish was wasteful.
He absolutely did
Kabore but couldn't do
the business with the finish.
Ooh, given away.
Kulusevski, it is Son.
Oh!
Werner!
Blocked by Kabore.
Son, off the line.
Absolutely incredible.
Chong is blocked off by Bissouma.
Given away by Mengi.
Kulusevski feeding Son.
The effort coming off both posts.
On the follow-up, Sarr
was kept out by Mengi.
Good recovery by Porro.
Barkley might have a pop.
Vicario had to get
down to make the save.
A poor clearance, seized
upon by Doughty, who fed Barkley.
I think that was coming
in until Vicario got down.
That's well worked.
Oh, 1-1.
I think it's an own goal.
Spurs won't care.
They're back on terms.
Johnson might actually
be offside, here.
They'll have to have a closer look.
Doing very well after the quick
exchange of passes.
Kabore tried to get it away
but he had an absolute mare.
VAR checked it and it is good.
Porro motoring forward.
Son!
Saved by Kaminski.
One-way traffic at the moment.
Kaminski preventing Son
from putting Spurs in front.
Lovely move.
Werner was trying desperately
to get a touch on it.
But Kabore got there first.
Jordan Clark, who has just come
on and has immediately
forced a Luton corner.
Vicario has come a long way,
getting a fist on it
only as far as Clark.
That nearly snuck in.
Vicario had to get down
and palm it behind.
Dragusin surging away from Townsend.
Johnson!
That looked like it went
over the line to me.
Apparently not, though.
Johnson is still scratching his
head about this one.
The ball somehow
didn't cross the line.
How close was it to
going over the line?
Wow.
I don't think you can get
much closer than that.
That's deflected and Luton
will have a corner.
Son!
Spurs are in front.
Son Heung-min.
Have they come from behind
to win at home once again?
A landmark goal for Son
who is getting the 160th goal.
More importantly they have
come from behind to win
in all of their last
four victories here.
2-1.
I was disappointed with the goal
we conceded, it was preventable.
You are looking for a reaction.
A bit of anxiety around the place.
Every win is so important.
The boys kept calm heads and kept
playing our football.
We are maxing out, the boys
are giving everything,
we are working to have a good plan
and give ourselves an opportunity
to win the game of football.
Turn around quickly,
it doesn't get easier,
Arsenal on Wednesday.
It is tough because we hate losing.
We have lost this year
but we are winners.
We want to win games of football.
We don't always want to go 1-0
behind and chase the game.
Could be another good lesson.
We hope we can continue to have work
in a way from the start of the game.
At 1-0 down we put in a lot
of effort to get ahead.
Luton putting up a good fight
but Spurs finding a way
to get the job done.
You think Johnson coming
on at half-time made the difference?
Without doubt, with Kulusevski
being left-footed, he wants to come
in and it was getting clogged up
and Postecoglou could see that.
This was the position that
Kulusevski was taking up,
with Johnson much wider.
He is right-footed so he will
invariably be across the box.
They paid 47 million for him,
quite a lot of money.
A special player.
He had the disappointment of not
making it to the Euros in midweek.
Didn't affect him.
He has really good pace.
It's the change of pace
that they can't deal with.
Kabore has a nightmare.
Look at the movement,
checking inside.
Whipping it across and somehow
that doesn't go in.
This pace is electric.
He just stands people up.
Should have put that in.
Threatening from deep.
His intensity, I like his work
ethic as well, going
after the Luton goalkeeper.
He put it out of play.
A matter of time before
they were going to get a goal.
How this doesn't go in is beyond me.
Incredible.
It really is.
Unlucky, that would have
been a goal for him.
He plays a major part
in the winning goal,
which is tough on Luton.
They were gallant
in their performance,
putting on a good fight.
On the right-hand side.
Werner the left.
There is nothing for Kulusevski
in the first half, no shots
or crosses and then he comes
on and he changes the game.
Burnley were five points from safety
ahead of a trip to Chelsea.
Your commentator at Stamford Bridge,
Simon Brotherton.
Chelsea made three changes from
the FA Cup quarterfinal line-up.
Raheem Sterling drops to the bench.
David Fofana is out
for Burnley this afternoon.
Muric keeps his place in goal.
They're trying to keep
a good atmosphere inside
Stamford Bridge and there has been
a changeable atmosphere lately.
Jackson, for the first time.
Fernandez, and the deflection
is pushed behind by Muric.
First test of the afternoon
for Burnley's goalkeeper.
Chelsea threatening,
the sting taken out of the shot
but it almost took it
past the goalkeeper.
They will be hoping
to build on the 2-1
victory against Brentford.
Fancied his chances.
The fingertip save.
Brilliant play.
Superb and then sent to the ground
by the left hand of Assignon,
who will get a telling off
by the referee.
Fernandez, looks for
the run of Jackson.
Palmer is in the middle for support.
Jackson...
Great chance.
Good save.
He looked odds-on to score, Jackson.
Did everything right.
Apart from apply
the finishing touch.
Good angle to deliver...
Turned in.
Chelsea make the breakthrough
after 20 minutes.
Disasi in the right
place to knock it home.
The goal is going to
be disallowed here.
Frustrating for Chelsea,
they thought they were ahead.
Gallagher leaves it.
Has got to be careful, Assignon...
It is a penalty.
It is the second yellow card
for Assignon, he is.
Burnley are down to ten
men with five minutes
to go to half-time.
A match in which Burnley
were hanging in there and
it is more difficult.
He is absolutely steaming.
There is the challenge.
It wasn't a strong one,
hence why it is being checked.
It is a penalty kick,
it has been confirmed.
Vincent Kompany, I think
is going to be sent off here.
Yes.
For his vehement protest,
Vincent Kompany has been shown a red
card by the referee.
Cole Palmer against Muric.
The most nonchalant fashion,
supreme confidence.
Burnley, by the way now have more
red cards than any other team
in the Premier League this season.
It is the sixth player
sent off and another
one with the manager,
up to seven.
Josh Cullen, superb strike.
What a great start to the second
half for the ten men of Burnley.
Josh Cullen's exchange
with Josh Brownhill.
A really good finish and Burnley
back in the game on level terms.
Josh Brownhill, sending it forward.
Josh Cullen.
Good ball in.
Save by Petrovic.
And then blocked to deny Foster.
It looked for a moment
as though Burnley were
going to snatch the lead.
Josh Cullen with a lovely ball
in towards Lyle Foster,
who had two goes at it.
Almost a remarkable
moment there for Burnley.
Raheem Sterling.
Cole Palmer!
Really good finish.
Cole Palmer at the double.
Finally the ten men
of Burnley concede.
Little flick from Raheem Sterling
into Chelsea's number 20.
And suddenly the opportunity
there for Cole Palmer.
Chelsea lead for the
second time today.
Rodriguez, in towards
Josh Cullen who is challenged
and fouled by Cole Palmer.
Josh Cullen sending it in.
Behind for a corner.
The header!
It is in and Burnley
will not lie down.
For the second time today,
the ten men hit back at Chelsea.
Great header, Petrovic I think
got his fingertips to it
but couldn't keep it out.
And Dara O'Shea with
a massive goal for Burnley.
Chelsea, pegged back again.
Cole Palmer sends it
in and Raheem Sterling has missed.
What a golden chance that looked.
After setting up Chelsea's
second goal, he could have
scored their third.
But it wasn't to be.
It is cleared behind for a corner
with Rodriguez waiting to pounce.
It's not just Chelsea asking
questions later in this match.
And it goes and Jay Rodriguez hits
the bar and then puts it wide.
That was a great chance for Burnley.
It thundered against the crossbar.
Both teams will feel
they could have, should
have scored a third goal
in the last few minutes.
It was incredible, really was.
Sensed at half-time the players
were galvanised, they were together.
It was very easy,
they were determined.
They should be so
proud of themselves.
But the staff are
beyond proud of them.
I feel it is so easy for them to get
a third and even not defensive
enough in open play.
That is the thing we need to realise
if we want to be competitive.
What was your view of how
everything unfolded?
I have to be honest,
it is not my position to be able
to talk about the incident
and the manager, he is my boss
as well, and when the time is right,
he will talk about that.
For me, it is clearly
about the players and what we
were able to witness.
It was a hard-fought point today.
Craig Bellamy, always diplomatic.
Hectic Stamford Bridge.
Let's get straight
to the controversy.
Craig Bellamy doesn't want to talk
about it, but we will.
They have got the wrong
decision, Darren England.
Assignon defends it well,
arm across him and make sure he's
strong and there is no diving in,
if you like.
Just a strong arm across,
Mudryk goes down too early.
He wasn't in control
of the ball either.
Look at it again in the VAR
and I can understand why
Vincent Kompany was furious
with this decision.
Cole Palmer is so comfortable
in those positions.
Just shows the class and composure.
Pocchetino not happy,
Burnley showed the fighting spirit
despite the red cards?
It seemed to somehow make
them better, Burnley.
The space they were getting
in the midfield, and Josh Cullen,
who sits deep, plays one, two.
Unbelievable effort.
The space he's got is ridiculous.
Josh Brownhill gets into his path
and that was magnificent.
They just kept producing,
as they said in the interview.
Foster does really well.
Terrible marking in the box.
Not able to find a partnership
in there and there was no dominant
player on set pieces.
O'Shea gets one in there.
Some of the marking
and some were in zonal,
they were all over the place.
The manager has to
play a part in that.
They have to do it
better on the pitch.
Rodriguez should have buried this.
Hits the bar and he really
should put that away.
Lots of work to do, Chelsea.
It is the younger players
struggling right now.
You think of the history
of the football club
and they are not comfortable
at Stamford Bridge.
Two ex Villans in the studio.
Martin still looks like one now.
Aston Villa have a top
four finish in sight.
They faced a Wolves side with
European ambitions of their own.
Jonathan Pearce was at Villa Park.
Diego Carlos is back
for Villa since mid-February.
They haven't won in six league
meetings with Bulls.
-- Wolves.
Gary O'Neil has distanced himself
from rumours linking himself
with Manchester United makes one
change from the cup
defeat to Coventry.
Real control about the way
Wolves are playing in
the opening 15 minutes.
Space down the left,
causing problems.
What a save that is.
Somehow came through,
who had to snatch at it
because he saw it late.
Didn't realise he had
more time than he did.
Splendid save.
Fantastic job he has
done this season.
Why would he want to step back
from being the number one man
to just being a coach somewhere
in the order at Manchester United?
Watkins for Aston Villa.
Draws the goalkeeper.
Hits the side netting.
That's the closest he came.
He will know he should
have hit the target.
Could only shoot wide.
Watkins to Douglas Luiz.
Foul.
It has become a spiky Derby,
but a more even one.
Stopped him in his tracks.
This is a decent run up.
Edged out by Doyle.
Splendid goal, his
eighth of the season.
It is a horror show for Wolves.
Lovely run by Leon Bailey.
Wolves didn't see it.
Absolutely buried by Diaby.
Aston Villa lead.
Ollie Watkins, presumably injured.
That is a worry with
the midweek game against
Manchester City away in mind.
Moreno, keeping a tighter check
on those runs in the second half.
He has given the ball away.
Ezri Konsa did just enough.
His glare at Moreno told a story.
Going nowhere fast.
Losing possession cheaply.
Ezri Konsa did just enough to hold
off the challenge of Lemina.
Signs of mental weariness
from both sets of players.
Eight of the Wolves
starting XI were involved
in international games.
Seven of the Villa players were.
Doyle, good challenge
to win it back.
Really good challenge.
It's gone in!
I think it might have
gone in off Jhon Duran.
Villa don't care, they're two up.
Diaby had a look.
Here is Ezri Konsa, floating it
the far post it's gone in.
It hit Jhon Duran but I think
it's already gone in.
Off the post and in.
Ezri Konsa celebrates
and caps a fine week.
I don't think he'd scored
since December of 2021.
20 minutes against Brazil,
90 minutes against Belgium,
his first international football
and his first goal in a long while.
Wolves are all over the place.
Good stop by Sa, going the wrong
way and readjusting.
On loan from Galatasaray,
only their for six months.
only there for six months.
As come back and had some
impact since coming on.
Gary O'Neil will be pleased with how
they started the game.
Fairly pleased with how
they started the second half.
Apart from that, Villa have
been the better side.
Doherty!
A big chance for the substitute.
A rare Wolves second-half
chance, there is.
Would have made
a game of it late on.
They need to be
organised to press well.
We had some good chances
on the left-hand side
with Semedo and Sarabia.
Disappointed with the result but
proud of the players to come here.
Everyone knows some of the issues
we have but there was no giving up,
no excuses made, just the team
giving everything and
today wasn't enough.
We must accept that
and get ready for Tuesday.
Did you mean that goal?
I meant it.
It was one of those ones,
I saw Jhon on the back post
and I wanted to give him the assist.
I said if you score today...
Today he scored and I have
to think which watch I'm
going to buy for him.
I'm happy for him, he's a friend.
It is the result that keeps
Aston Villa in fourth place.
A big result at a man
who hasn't featured that much.
Are you impressed with him?
Very much so and I wish I'd played
with him because I'd have loved
to have watch myself.
Super intelligent with his movement
and where to be on the pitch.
What he does so well,
he asks questions of the defender.
Do I stand on him or do I leave him?
If you are tight you can move him
back which is what they do
but if you leave him and give him
space, this space now,
now Ollie Watkins can make runs.
He goes slightly earlier,
he is offside but that's
the danger that he possesses.
He's at the bottom,
number 19 but it's all
about concentration on the strike.
He doesn't do much in the process
of getting in position but he makes
sure he makes great contact.
The power and precision is perfect.
Making sure he holds position,
makes sure he knows that his mate
is coming around him.
Konsa will tell you he meant it
but he didn't, he's trying
to stand it for Jhon Duran.
It is a cheeky pass.
He has started the season well
and then the rigours
of the Premier League catch up
with you, he's had a break but now
he's back and we see
what he possesses.
Aston Villa very organised today.
Foden, brilliant finish!
What a title race this could be.
Oh, my word.
Arsenal getting the points.
Sending a message.
Oh, brilliant.
Great return, what a goal.
Lovely strike.
Listen on BBC Sounds.
Chelsea take on Arsenal
in the Women's League Cup Final.
And if you missed the start of the
show it's available now on iPlayer.
The whole programme goes
up first thing Sunday.
We are going to have a little look
at our nutrition and diet today and
talk about breakfast. Can you talk
to the person next to you and just
have a little conversation and tell
me why breakfast is so important? Us
and the school work together to
identify the need, the children were
coming in, eating junk food, sweets,
having energy drinks. And I just
really think it was good to show
them that having breakfast and
making healthy breakfast isn't hard
and it's something they can do both
at home and in the kitchen when they
come in in the morning. How
important is West Ham a's
involvement? They are recognisable
organisations and having their
branding around our trust really
helps to inspire the children.
They've been really instrumental in
developing some healthy eating
programmes in school. It's about
nutrition. Especially when you are a
kid, you have to know what is
important for your body, when you
have nutrition, you can get the best
out of your body during the day. I
think it's really important for
young people to have positive role
models around the school. To
actually connect what's on TV in the
Premier League to them in person
it's a good thing to inspire them
and motivate them. It tastes nice. I
was actually working on a primary
school before joining West Ham so
it's not too much of a change for
me. It's good to give them the
education about healthy food and
breakfast. That's pretty good. The
timing of the meals for us changed
as well so if you have a late kick
off, it's easier to manage what you
eat for breakfast. And pre-match, if
you have an early kick-off, it's
more or less like breakfast. I'm a
big believer in eating healthy,
eating in the right way. A lot of
these guys don't eat breakfast,
don't like eating breakfast. What
advice would you give to them on
that? I can only give advice that my
mum gave to me which is breakfast is
the most important meal of the day
really. I know how to make a healthy
smoothie at home and how to keep my
diet healthy. I just met West Ham is
most famous goalkeeper. I'm really
excited. I think it's a privilege to
be part of it. Trying to share my
personal feelings about what I think
about food. The great thing to do.
Manchester United were beaten 4-0
on their last visit to Brentford.
Steve Bower was at the
Gtech Community Stadium.
Brentford who have lost 12
of their last 15 Premier League
games, led again by Ivan Toney
in a week where he marked his full
England debut with a goal.
He's searching for his second in his
career against Manchester United.
Kobbie Mainoo was the player of
the match on his full England debut.
He's recovered from illness to start
in the same team that had a dramatic
cup victory over Liverpool.
Casemiro is back as a substitute.
Four clean sheets for the Bees
and only one here at
the Gtech Community Stadium.
Still going, the Ukrainian.
Kobbie Mainoo in the way.
Important interception.
United might have a counter, here.
Going wide in the end
from Fernandes.
That's the danger for
Brentford, a United break.
It is the captain's
shot that went wide.
Ten points from 54 available.
This weekend, the joint fewest with
Sheffield United, the bottom club.
Ivan Toney!
So close.
Still alive with Roerslev.
The Brentford skipper
thought his wonderful week
was continuing, there.
Carrying the ball
a long way, Potter.
Off the head of Varane.
Important interception.
The seventh Brentford corner
in just over half-an-hour.
Free header!
He knows, Jorgensen,
that it was a huge opportunity.
A fraction too high
off the crossbar.
For the second time in this half,
Brentford hitting the woodwork.
Rashford.
There's a chase on, here.
Toney against Lindelof.
Still Toney!
Slamming the turf in
frustration because he created
space for the shot.
Passing Lindelof.
He got right underneath it.
Brentford, who had 34 touches
in the Manchester United penalty
area in the first half.
That's the most they've ever had
in a Premier League game.
Hojlund.
Flekken's first save of the evening.
Looking for a flag
that wasn't raised.
Trying to score in seven
Premier League games but is denied.
Wissa, just wanting it more again.
Going down easily there, though.
That came off Lindelof.
Onana, brilliant save,
and the follow-up as well.
A double save, Onana.
Fantastic stop from
the Manchester United goalkeeper.
Lewis-Potter with the follow-up
was also thwarted.
Clawing it back superbly.
Superb volley from Wissa.
Again off target.
They were knocking
on the Manchester United door,
now they are banging on it.
Look how close that was.
Trying to find Toney!
The flag is up.
Brentford's joy is short lived.
Simon Long, the referee's
assisted, raising the flag.
VAR will double-check.
A very tight one.
The stadium awaits the line,
and there is the line.
That is confirmed.
Manchester United somehow
still have their clean sheet intact.
Martinez with a foul.
Quickly taken by Flekken.
Another woodwork hit by Brentford.
How Brentford haven't scored so far
this evening, nobody knows.
His side have been far
from the standards that he's after,
and he'll know that.
We've had five out
of the added nine.
Mason Mount!
It is Manchester United with a goal.
Mason Mount's very first
strike for the club
and what a time to get it.
Brentford hearts broken.
The ultimate smash and grab
from Manchester United.
And it's the substitute,
who's had so much frustration
since signing from Chelsea,
who has finished it off.
Casemiro put him in.
It's a lovely finish,
with his second touch
come onto his left.
Tucked it away into the far corner.
And Mason Mount putting the smiles
back on United faces.
Mount, the goal-scorer, away.
Here is Toney.
Surely there's the equaliser!
Ajer.
Nothing more than
Brentford deserved.
It's only his third
ever goal for the club.
They did have it in them.
What a response.
Great work from Toney, here.
Lovely laid-back.
And the central defender,
dispatching it like
a centre forward.
Slipping at home.
Under Onana's body.
What an ending, 1-1.
How we are not winning this game
is incredible but when you go 1-0
down after 96 minutes,
maybe I wouldn't be able to smile
because that's the most
one-sided 1-1 we are winning.
Brentford were better today,
they showed more passion, desire,
determination than we did.
Is that acceptable
from Manchester United?
It is mental, psychological
and I can't tell.
I can think about reasons,
like we are returning
from the international break
but Brentford also had players
on international duty.
We should bring more.
When we are winning,
I would give the team to complement
for that but then we get a winning
goal and we gave it away
and that's very disappointing.
You can see from this graphic that
Brentford fully deserved
something from the game.
31 shots that they had
today, 81 touches in
the opposition box, Martin.
Nine of those shots from Ivan Toney
and he set up the goal.
How would you have handled him?
It would have been tough,
he has gone to another level.
It would have been a travesty
if they didn't get
something out of this game.
Ivan Toney is the player to go to.
That probably should have been
a chance for him to score.
He creates so much for his team.
A willing runner with the ball.
This one, just a lovely
weighted pass.
It's all there.
Everything is in the locker.
Pace, power, intelligence.
This one is a little bit,
he needs to be more collective,
but he's leaning back as he hits it.
That was maybe a bit
disappointing, but that is
an opportunity from distance.
That is off his left foot.
This, he puts away
and it's disallowed.
Fantastic finish.
Look how he plucks this out
of the sky, wonderful touch,
awareness and transfers it from one
foot to the other.
This is top level striker right now.
No more than they deserve.
Kept putting striker
after striker on the pitch
and they were magnificent.
Manchester United went in the game.
The Manchester United
manager had strong words?
Rightly so, you can't go
from beating Liverpool
and then being poor.
If you are the manager,
correct that on the pitch.
Is he strong enough to do that?
He didn't show it today.
It's been a busy day
for Guy Mowbray.
The Gladiators Grand Final
and a trip to Bramall Lane
for Sheffield United-Fulham.
Fulham is unchanged
after their victory over Spurs
with two goals from Roderigo minis
made it seven.
A moment to cherish
for four-year-old Harriet Mills.
She is suffering from an incurable
brain tumour and coming to a match
is something to take off her list
of memories to be made.
Well here is another one,
Harriet, you are starring
on Match Of The Day.
Only one win in their last dozen
Premier League games.
They have taken some
absolute Something's
at Bramall Lane in recent weeks.
But the absolutely optimistic
manager says there is
so much to play for.
It is a fine save and then
Alex Iwobi was asking
what that was all about.
It is the closest Fulham have come.
The closest either side
have come to scoring.
Up goes Roderigo.
With the goalkeeper helpless,
he is inches away from
giving Fulham the lead.
He used every part of the cross.
I'm very relieved goalkeeper to see
that one bounce back into his clubs.
McBurney.
Sheffield United have numbers up.
Not much reaction from the bus.
They still believe there is life
left in this season yet.
Cheaply gave it away.
What ball it was from Oli McBurnie.
On a plate for his partner.
He will be stewing.
Good looking cross.
A vital cross.
Jack Robinson stayed
airborne just long enough.
An easy equaliser.
Sheffield United ask questions
of themselves as Fulham celebrate.
His fourth goal of the season
and that is as easy as you like.
He just guided it.
Fulham are on the scoresheet
and in business and they will feel
they should and will go on and win
it from here.
Free kick, Sheffield United.
They have taken it quickly.
They have reversed the roles.
Fulham went to sleep
on the free kick.
Cheeky, cheeky goal.
Such a big one for Sheffield
United if they can hold
onto the lead this time.
Three goals in an
incredible ten minutes.
Here come Sheffield United once more
and they are growing in confidence.
Sheffield United find
themselves two goals in front.
Brilliant ball from Gustavo Hamer.
They are looking to see
if there is any violent conduct
in the pushing and shoving that
happened on the goal net.
The message from the video
assistant referee today,
check complete on everything.
Staying in the Premier League this
season is mission improbable,
but not Mission Impossible.
Fulham have only ten
minutes, but there will be
a huge chunk added on.
Oli McBurnie will get
there with time to spare.
Osborne, barged.
Free kick.
That wasn't a shoulder to shoulder.
Not cleared by Fulham.
Oli McBurnie has a shorter
and another one!
And it is 4-1 Sheffield United.
The goal is being checked just
to make sure the goalkeeper's view
wasn't impeded by a player
in an offside position.
Nothing wrong with the second one.
But it is the first one
that is the problem.
The same phase of play.
That will have to be
explained to Sousa.
The score stays at 3-1.
What an impact, he has
only just come on.
Fulham back in business.
Just a moment after if felt
like the game had been
taken away from them.
And an immediate aftermath
after the video review,
three substitutions made
by Marco Silva and one of them has
come up trumps immediately.
De Cordova-Reid with Marreta.
14 minutes to be added on.
The incredulity in the stadium
announcer's voice.
Now there is brewing
around the stadium.
Magnificent, absolutely magnificent.
A world-class finish from a Fulham
forward who is in form.
Sheffield United's
dreams dashed again.
They have lost another
two-goal lead.
Six second-half goals, and this one
is the pick of them all.
That has to be his best.
Fulham are not done yet.
They carried, they rushed to get
the ball to go again.
Sheffield United look bedraggled.
You can only wonder what it
will do to any sort of hope
that they might stay up.
Willian.
Robinson.
Fulham free kick.
Chris Wilder, wouldn't be any great
surprise if he couldn't bring
himself to watch now.
Does he go for goal or try
and deliver for somebody else?
How it goes.
What a chance.
At the goalkeeper made the save.
Straight at him and that will do it.
It takes it out of you,
this football business,
but that was the sort of half that
keeps you coming back for more.
They refused to lose this game.
Sloppy moments, we played with three
defenders in the last 15,
20 minutes of the game.
The players they showed a great
reaction and team spirit and quality
to score two more goals and create
more chances like we did.
That's why we love
football, crazy game.
The boys gave 100%,
we dug deep and I thought
it was a good performance.
What did you make of the 14 minutes
at the time which meant you had
to play for an extra 60 minutes?
I am not going to get
involved in any controversy.
It has already cost me.
I am not prepared, I am
a hard-working Yorkshire lad,
I work hard for my money and I am
not prepared to give it
to the FA or anybody else,
so I will keep those
thoughts locked in.
Keep them locked in, back-to-back
draws for Sheffield United,
still a long way to go
but if they have any chance
of survival they will need more
performances like the one
from Ben Brereton Diaz?
He came in in January,
not your conventional striker,
Oli McBurnie plays that role,
but he has to come in from
the right-hand side.
He does extremely well.
Barrett and Diaz on
the right-hand side.
Doesn't quite come off this time
but it is the intent to go forward.
You see him circled here,
what you've now got to do,
you have got to understand
where things are
moving on the pitch.
He knows nobody is
on the outside of him.
Lovely ball from Oli McBurnie.
Delightful.
He repays the favour to him,
you want a strike partnership to get
that understanding straightaway.
They understand it, he understands
now that he needs to get back over
to the right-hand side
because Oli McBurnie
is the central point, if you like.
If you are in the wide
position you have got
to get to the back post.
That is where you will get goals,
you might get four or five goals
a season stock you have to be brave
and he is brave there, puts his head
in comic comes off his knee.
He doesn't care, he
makes sure he scores.
Really good start for him
for Sheffield United.
Everton had gone 11 games
without a win ahead
of a trip to Bournemouth.
John Roder was at
the Vitality Stadium.
Three weeks since Everton last
played in three months
since their last league victory.
Bournemouth ten points ahead
of never lofty in the six previous
Premier League meetings
between these two
sides at the vitality.
Tyler Adams makes his full
debut for Bournemouth,
having missed most of the season
injured following his
move from Leeds.
Dominic Calvert-Lewin hasn't scored
in his last 22 appearances
in all competitions.
Seamus Colman start at right
back and Ben Godfrey
switches to the left.
Marcus Tavernier.
The chase is on the Justin Kluivert.
The shot blocked by Pickford and
the rebound is over from Lewis Cook.
Semenyo might have felt
he should have done better
when the ball fell to him here.
Always rising.
He was pulled back by Solanke.
Dominic Solanke with the foul.
It was a very awkward fall Onana.
Calvert-Lewin following up.
That is a terrific save.
He can't get the shot
away, but Calvert-Lewin,
desperate for a goal.
Adams, down in the penalty area.
Corner.
This was so close.
Semenyo, the closest
we've come to a goal.
Calvert-Lewin, down in the area.
The referee says play on.
A cheque has been completed
which agrees with the referee's
initial decision.
Neto claimed it and it was
put behind by Mepham.
Alarming for the home supporters.
The option of a short corner to
Harrison which Bournemouth take up.
McNeil trying to squeeze it
in and somehow it stayed out.
Perhaps caught a bit
unawares at the back.
It came off the upright and somehow
Bournemouth have scrambled it away.
Semenyo, options to his left.
Dominic Solanke and
Bournemouth are in front.
His 18th goal of the season,
his 16th in the Premier League.
And it means he equals Josh King's
record of 16 Premier League goals
in one season for the Cherries.
The cross was from Lloyd Kelly who
has only been on for a minute or so.
Placing it perfectly
between the defenders
and Solanke was there.
The first goal of the
afternoon at the Vitality.
Everton haven't won in their last 30
games in the Premier League
when conceding the first goal
of the match.
Beto!
1-1.
The error from Neto,
and Beto took full advantage.
Sean Dyche sent on the substitute
striker, as Everton chased
the equaliser, and they've got one.
Neto comes for it, doesn't claim it
and it was a relatively
simple chance, there,
for Beto to score his fifth
goal of the season.
The fourth official John Busby
is about to show us how much
additional time is to be played.
And it's a minimum of six minutes.
Pickford left it and it's gone
in off Seamus Coleman.
It's an own goal and Everton
were level for just
a couple of minutes.
A calamitous goal at one end
and another at the other.
Keep watching Seamus
Coleman, the number 23.
As it is played in, is he trying
to chest it back to Pickford?
His 358 Premier League
appearance for Everton,
and one that Seamus Coleman
would want to forget.
The way that they got it, you can
lose a game that you almost won.
Unlucky for us.
We continue pushing.
Things change and we were close.
I'm a fan of VAR and it is in
a bizarre place but we can't give
away second goals like that.
Sometimes when you have that feeling
and you are working for a result
and you need a result,
you take the point but you don't get
it and these things go
against you but only us
can change that.
We will come onto the penalty
decision in a moment.
Like Sean Dyche just said.
They were really poor this afternoon
and they're struggling, Everton,
but they are struggling for reasons,
and that is communication
and understanding.
This isn't strong enough
from Harrison in midfield.
Semenyo does very well.
Bournemouth had opportunities
to counterattack and they made
the right decision here.
There's no pressure on Lloyd Kelly.
Too easy.
Look at the numbers
that Everton have back.
Semenyo isn't even
looking at the ball.
That's just far too easy.
Look at Tarkowski saying
to Godfrey, come closer.
I want to deal with the front post
and you deal with Solanke
and that has cost them.
This is the moment where Pickford,
you've got to take everything,
the man and the ball.
Defenders expected.
If you clatter into him, so be it.
You are trying to prevent a goal,
and the hesitation isn't good.
Pickford has his hands on his hips,
he should be on red alert.
I think it creates indecision.
He comes for it and it
just hit Coleman.
Branthwaite goes towards it as well.
No one taking responsibility
and it's in the back
of the net, disaster.
We get back to the penalty decision.
Can you understand Sean
Dyche's frustration?
I absolutely can.
The referee Samuel Barrott
had a decision to make.
He felt there wasn't enough
contact on the ball.
In this position why
would Calvert-Lewin go down?
He has got beyond
Adams who clips him.
That's enough, at the speed
they are moving, it looks different
when it is slow down.
That's a penalty.
He's very unlucky.
Unbelievable decision,
I can't believe it.
That's ridiculous.
Nottingham Forest played
for the first time since being
docked four points for breaching
Premier League financial rules.
They faced Crystal Palace
at the City Ground.
Steve Wilson was watching.
Forest find themselves
in the relegation zone
for the first time this season.
Off the pitch they are appealing
against the points deduction.
On it, not so appealing,
one win in nine.
Nuno Espirito Santo making three
changes to the team who last
played a fortnight ago.
Hudson-Odoi and Felipe comes
in for the injured Boly.
Three weeks since
Palace last played.
Rested or rusty?
We won't see Sam Johnstone until
next season after elbow surgery.
Henderson is putting on the gloves.
On Thursday we learned of the death
of Larry Lloyd, European Cup winner
with Nottingham Forest,
Uefa Cup with Liverpool
and a league champion with both.
Four of the last five meetings
between these two teams
have finished in a draw.
Forest need wins.
Good ball, Lerma.
Mateta, 1-0.
Crystal Palace in front on a ten
minutes, smartly delivered by Mateta
into the corner of the net
and Nottingham Forest
have gone behind.
This is the pass, it's a lovely one,
Eze with the lay-off and Mateta
with the good finish.
It is too easy from
the Forest point of view.
0-1.
A win a draw and a defeat
in his first three games.
Steady but not spectacular.
Really good ball, Wharton.
Can Eze finish?
Easy finish two excellent
finish by Matz Sels.
Wonderful ball from Wharton
into the run of Eze?
That will be a corner.
Skidding off the head of Ryan Yates.
The Crystal Palace fans
behind the goal have only
seen their team winning away three
times this season.
Sheffield United,
Manchester United and Burnley.
Eze, nicely done.
It only needed a touch.
Munoz wasn't 1 million miles away
from providing it and Eze wasn't
1 million miles away from putting
it in himself.
Four wins in 17 in all competitions
since he took over.
Hudson-Odoi.
Wood, can he get a touch?
He can!
Chris Wood equalises
for Nottingham Forest.
Gibbs-White, the little floating
ball into the Palace penalty area
and Chris Wood just nodded it over
the top of Henderson.
Great awareness of Chris Wood
to know exactly where Henderson
was and how far off his line.
That's a really clever header.
1-1.
Good turn, Eze.
Drifting dangerously.
Good save by Matz Sels.
Hitting Mateta more than he hit
the ball and it has gone for a goal
kick but it easily could have fallen
more kindly for Palace.
Lovely stuff from Eze.
Great composure.
A bit of good fortune.
A good save by Matz Sels.
They haven't won an away league game
since Roy Hodgson took them
to Turf Moor in early November.
Reyna!
Stinging the palms of Henderson.
Working it well to his left
but straight at the keeper, really.
The difference between three points
and one point could be absolutely
huge for Nottingham Forest.
Coming off Felipe, Eze was caught.
A bit of a protest from Williams
but really going through the motions
with that because he must have known
that would be a free kick.
Eze might be trying to get
the better of Matz Sels.
He is more than capable.
Palace corner which is a reasonable
return from a free kick which didn't
seem to go according to plan.
A bit nervous for Forest, this.
In goes the corner
and it's off the post.
Hughes, over the top.
I think that Munoz hit
the woodwork and they have
to settle for one point each.
It is 1-1.
At the moment it feels like we have
lost two points but I was told that
a point in the Premier League
is a good one, so we respect it
because Nottingham are very good,
especially at home.
Chris Wood's header is very clever
because he's very aware
of where the goalkeeper is.
Yeah, it's a good finish.
The only solution that he had,
a beautiful header, a good pass.
We need goals.
Amazing player.
A bigger point for
Forest in the end.
Chris Wood is going
to be crucial for them
in the running to relegation.
Without doubt,
it is a clever header.
He seems to relish these situations.
He's got experience
of it with Burnley.
The way that he improvises,
a deft touch.
Seven goals in eight games now.
That's really impressive.
He just twists in the sky.
A really light touch.
That's a difficult skill to do
and he's put it away beautifully.
You can see how important he is.
Yeah, incredible record,
ten goals in each of his seasons.
He's in great company.
I fear a bit for Nottingham Forest,
one win in ten games this year.
Like many teams at the bottom,
they concede too many goals.
Important games coming up for them.
You feel that he has to get
the balance right off making sure
they are tight at the back
but scoring goals.
They are definitely capable but he's
not getting the balance right.
We are just about out
of time, thank you.
Excellent performance from you.
One point is enough
for Nottingham Forest to move out
of the relegation places
at the expense of Luton.
Arsenal midfielder Declan Rice says
we are not bottlers ahead
of the title showdown.
Pep Guardiola is unhappy
that his team must play
seven games in 21 days.
That's it.
What a day as Harvey wins it
for Newcastle in a Barnes-storming
finish at St James' Park.
Good night.