Good evening.
Newcastle, Sheffield
United and Burnley
are our destinations this evening.
Alan Shearer and Micah Richards
bring the northern soul
to proceedings.
We begin at St James' Park.
Just one team did the double over
Newcastle last season
season and you guessedit,
that was Liverpool.
Your commentator, Guy Mowbray.
Fixture that will always rekindle
memories. Isak! Seven minutes of
additional time. Angry scenes down
on the touchline.
on the touchline. Newcastle have
gone 17 league games without defeat.
Darwin Nunez, and the finish wasn't
bad either. It is finished off by
Cody Gakpo. He had to imply that Mac
improvise and he got a hold of it
and he is off, Nick Pope is off. The
only team to beat Newcastle in the
Premier League all season have done
it again. Your commentator, Guy
Mowbray.
Full throttle, heavy metal, whatever
you want to call that this is how
these do like to play. They have
given us great games in the past and
if the spectacle and noise could be
matched today we could be in for
another. It is an unchanged
Newcastle
Newcastle side, 4-3-3. Alexander
Isak gets the centre forward role.
He scored on his debut to put
Newcastle in front away to Liverpool
last August. Their team shows two
changes, Joel Matip comes in at the
back and there is a first start in
midfield for Endo, alongside Alexis
Mac Allister, whose suspension for a
red card against Bournemouth last
week was taken away on appeal. Diogo
Jota is on the bench. Newcastle
planning to be even more firmly in
the midst of the elite with
Liverpool panning to put the
pretenders back in their box for the
day. Alexander-Arnold sent flying.
Nearly ended up in the dugout. As he
threw the ball away showing his
frustration as he got back to his
feet. That is deemed to be not time
wasting what a show of dissent.
Either way, you're going to get a
card for that this season. Lovely
bit of skill from Mo Salah to get
past Burn. Burn is back at it in the
box. Gordon. And Alexander-Arnold
put his arm across. There is a long
way to go in this game and Trent
Alexander-Arnold is already walking
a fine line. John Brooks is going to
have a word. I suppose the question
is, is John Brooks the referee
perhaps showing some leniency
because he has only just book
Alexander-Arnold? He has got to be
careful now, that is for sure. Here
is Bruno Guimares. Well anticipated
by Joel Matip. Szoboszlai with the
clip out to Luis Diaz who is off and
running and he shimmies past
Trippier, the shot, was it going on,
Nick Pope could not be sure and had
to make the save anyway. Superb,
direct attacking play from the
Liverpool number seven. An early
change might have to be made.
Tonali.
Tonali. Scorer of the first goal of
the five metres got on the opening
day against Aston Villa. What a
performance he put in that day.
performance he put in that day. A
mistake by Alexander-Arnold and
Gordon is in! And Newcastle are in
front! He has picked his game.
Anthony Gordon's first goal at St
James' Park is a Newcastle player.
And the former Evertonian has done
it against Liverpool. Not only that
it has come about after a mistake by
a fully fledged red who is having a
difficult day. Alexander-Arnold
missed it. From then on the crowd
held its breath because Gordon
nipped in, they were not going to
catch him, it was about whether he
could keep his composure, Andy
Goode. Newcastle United 1-0
Liverpool. -- and he could.
Joelinton. Gordon. Finding space and
feel, that is a good ball and that
is a push by Van Dijk? He could be
in trouble. Has he just denied a
goal scoring opportunity? John
Brooks think so. Liverpool's
afternoon going from bad to worse.
Newcastle one goal app, Liverpool
one man down, Van Dijk is not
letting this go. -- one goal up.
Refusing to leave the pitch quietly.
Factor in that Alexander-Arnold is
probably one foul away from our lead
card. Stretching times for Jurgen
Klopp and his team.
Klopp and his team. Schar. Guimares
clearing the head of Gakpo. Tonali,
into the box. The result, a
Newcastle United corner.
Newcastle United corner. Almiron,
Trippier.
Trippier. It is not properly away,
and Alisson has somehow kept it out!
What I say that is! Miguel Almiron
got every piece of this. That was
hit hard! Superb control, brilliant
first time shot. That is one of the
saves of the season at this early
stage from Alisson. They have never
lost after going in front at home
under Eddie Howe. Tonali. Joelinton.
Joelinton over and that is over from
Almiron, and it shouldn't have been.
He was perhaps a little surprised to
get the chance. Looking to hit it
just a little bit early.
just a little bit early. There is a
famous name from this fixture past.
Tino Asprilla put Newcastle ahead in
the first of the two 4- three games
between these teams at Anfield.
Liverpool are coming forward, and
that is a really good cycle in the
end from Portman on Sala. It is a
warning to Newcastle that it is not
done yet.
done yet. Almiron still full of
running. Going all the way, it is
medial Almiron! So close to sealing
the points with a beauty. It only
needed just a little bit more bend.
That is up towards Darwin Nunez who
has got it. He has company now as
well. Bodman, and Burn, Joelinton,
Newcastle on the counter, Harvey
Barnes with Wilson waiting. Barnes
cannot do anything with it. Credit
to the ten players of Liverpool that
is still something in this game. It
is still alive. There will be real
frustration at Newcastle if they
don't make sure. Alexander-Arnold.
Salah, to Diogo Jota. Darwin Nunez
is in, a mistake from Botterman,
Andrew Nunez has buried it! You
can't believe that! -- and Nunez has
buried it. One mistake. That is all
that has taken. Nunez, off the bench
to make an almighty difference with
Liverpool. It is one heck of a
finish, not only the way he has
pretty thin but the timing. The way
the game been going. A big goal in
the biggest of moments. Liverpool
rewarded for hanging on and staying
in the contest. It is Liverpool 1-1
Newcastle, somehow. Switch across to
Kieran Almiron Enfield, good strong
running from low staff, trying to
flick it in, we are back to Chaos
theory at both ends! Once more
Alisson tries to get away from
Wilson to launch the ball long.
Guimares against Elliott, Salafi
Daraa Nunez, Nunez and again and
scores again! -- Salah gives it to
Nunez. Liverpool with another famous
last-minute winner against
Newcastle! This is incredible! We
have got one of the Premier League
stories. Darwin Nunez with another
well timed run and the way he put
his first away, you had just got a
feeling he was going to do it again.
There is a sense of disbelief around
Tyneside that Liverpool have done it
again, somehow winning this game.
They could have lost it ages ago.
They will watch this over and over
again long into the week and wonder
how. What again, what drama.
Newcastle United 1-2 Liverpool. I
still don't believe it!
still don't believe it! You have
experienced some highs and lows,
where is this one? It wasn't last
year I had 1000 games as a manager,
roundabout, but one like this, not
in the collection. We thought we
played really well today, up until
the sending off I thought we were
magnificent and from then onwards it
was a difficult -- different game,
may be a little negative with our
passing, may be slowing the game
down a bit too much, but it is a
team that is very strong, we will
have a few bumps on the road, today
is a pump and a disappointment but
we have be strong enough to take it.
The atmosphere was incredible. We
were playing really well. We had
them in a bad space, and we just
could not get the second goal and
when you play against teams at that
level if you don't do that they will
get more chances towards the end of
the game. From the early minutes
were due in difficult circumstances
with the yellow card? I felt that it
was a foul first of all, there was a
push in the back, but then I have
made a mistake and on a different
day I could have seen red. I feel
like today was about who wants to
win more, especially with the
circumstances we were in, we
definitely showed that. It is a very
proud evening for the club.
This one bang on the money and we
are going to talk about time wasting
and dissent later on. Let's go back
to the start because this was tasty
from the very beginning. John
Brooks, the referee, had a really
poor start, the first ten minutes he
got two big decisions wrong. This
was the first. This was a clear foul
from Anthony Gordon on Trent, that
should have been a foul. No doubt
about it. But he gets a yellow card
for time wasting or throwing the
ball away and rightly so, that was
the right decision, that should have
been a foul. And a couple of minutes
later, this happens. He is on a
yellow card and that should have
been another, there is no doubt
about that, and the only thing I can
say for the referee, he probably
thinks it is too early to give
another yellow and that is not
right. It should have been another.
A really tough ten minutes for the
referee. Trent stays on, you are not
getting away with talking about the
full-backs! He stays on. But then
actually, things go from bad to
worse for Liverpool. Van Dijk, that
was strange. When I saw that I
thought, there is no chance that is
a red card. But as the day has gone
on... I have seen more evidence.
Yes, as we play here, it was strange
because we are talking about his
position here a lot of people think
you should only be thinking about
Isak but Robertson, that run that he
can make behind him, too Nally, I
understand why he delays but once
the ball goes, he makes a fraction
too late of a decision and that
costs in the red card. On this angle
you will see that is an obvious
goal-scoring opportunity so I
understand why it has been given, I
really do but from the defender's
point of view, I think that is
sought. If that was in the box, it
probably would have been a penalty
and a yellow because of the double
jeopardy rule but you can see there,
he has taken him out, he has swiped
him, and I think the referee got the
decision right in the end. After I
have watched it about 50 times! It
took me a while to get there. I was
screaming at the TV when I was
watching it. But I think he made the
right decision. I do think there is
any doubt. He has taken the man out
first and then has the ball after
that and he would have been clean
through. Interesting you say about
Van Dijk's position, should he be
calling the full-back? Robinson
should be inside and he has to make
a judgment whether to stay or go. --
Robertson. As a centre-half you only
worry about that one across, Isak,
that should be his focus because of
the position of Robertson, he has
put him in two minds and that is why
he was a little bit late. Liverpool
down to ten men in the green room
recalling it, getting worried. The
momentum is changing. I could see
what was going to happen because it
was a combination of Newcastle being
sloppy, all over the pitch and
missing chances, and also it was
Liverpool sticking together, being
clever, having a fantastic
goalkeeper to make top saves at the
right time. But also Jurgen Klopp
made fantastic substitutions. And
when you have these two guys, they
brought energy and know-how to the
game and they gave Newcastle
different problems. Newcastle were
sloppy, that was the start of it.
Half an hour, they looked lost. But
Liverpool came back because of this,
they offered a threat, threat
running in behind, they then started
to play the passes in and they got
away with that one and Newcastle
lose the first ball and they should
Naughton all of a sudden, again,
they are into the defence of
Newcastle, making runs behind,
balls, fantastic tackle from Botman.
And all of a sudden Liverpool start
to press. They have not really done
that for a lot of the game, they
couldn't, they were prepared to
gamble and Newcastle really
struggled, they could not get the
ball again. They forced the mistake,
they put it out and Liverpool go on
the attack again and bring another
substitute on, who did all of the
damage, Darwin Nunez. Harvey
Elliott. What he does, straight
away, ball in behind and that
because Newcastle all sorts of
problems, they went deeper and
deeper and OK, they get away with
that one. And this is the turning
point. Harvey Barnes gets a really
good performance a couple of weeks
ago and rightly so, for his
substitute appearance, because he
made such a difference but that time
he has cost Newcastle because that
is a simple ball across, 2-0 and the
game is over. Liverpool stick
together, they have the belief, and
they have that. Another mistake. I
would not even call that half a
chance, that is an unbelievable
finish, the pace and power to find
the bottom corner and the goalkeeper
has no chance. They believe they can
actually go and win the game now so
from ten men, really struggling,
they are back in the driving seat.
Look at the men they have committing
forward? Nothing comes of it, that
is them pressing to win the game and
that is what they do. Again, another
mistake from Bruno, they lose at
midfield, Newcastle, and what a ball
from Mo Salah, running behind, Dan
Burns is slow on the turn and that
is an unbelievable finish and no
wonder he gets that from his
manager. He has won that game for
Liverpool. Two shots on target and
two goals. Is this a turning point
for him? It should be because they
are not bad, 17 goals in 26 starts
but look at the number of chances he
missed last season so that has to be
another start for him to get going
again. What about Newcastle? Last
week and then this one? They had a
good start with Aston Villa and
going to Man City was always going
to be tough but today, it was
moments within the game and Alan
showed that with Barnes and Wilson,
if he plays at the game is dead and
buried and you just think of any
high's record, only losing five
games at home, three of them have
been Liverpool. They have the
numbers but there are positive
signs. To get to do the next level,
punish people and see the games at.
You ended on a positive. Go on,
then! There is no panic.
Disappointing, the position you're
in, when you have a team on the
ropes, they have to finish them off
and they had their chances but they
have played two really good teams
with Liverpool and Man City and
another next week against Brighton
so it is back to training tomorrow
and then working for next weekend
but no panic. No panic for now.
Sheffield United had lost both
games since promotion -
not the best preparation for a game
against Manchester City.
But the big clubs don't always get
things their own way.
Black! What a goal! Robbie Blake may
never score a more famous goal!
Somehow it finds its way through.
Ashley Ward! He gets it down!
Ashley Ward! He gets it down! Tommy
Mooney has put Watford ahead! What a
goal for Andros Townsend! An
incredible story is being written in
front of our eyes today.
Martin Fisher was at Bramall Lane.
The 21-year-old striker -- striker
Archer has completed his transfer
from Aston Villa but signed too late
to be
to be involved so Osula leaves the
attack although McBurnie is back
amongst the subs, Bernardo Silva
returns after illness and just days
after agreeing a new deal. Nathan
Ake replaces the unwell Akanji at
the back.
the back. In the absence of Pep
Guardiola at... Just the third
weekend of the season but already,
Man City are the only Premier League
side boasting a 100% record, and
winning here would take them to the
top of the tree. Walker. Looking for
Haaland, trying to turn away from a
Gunn. It might drop for Alvarez.
That was a fine save by Foderingham.
He was out swiftly. To smother the
Argentine. At the moment, his team
have had 14% of possession. But they
are defending excellently. Bernardo
Silva. Lovely ball for Alvarez,
hooked towards Haaland. Kovacic,
will it reach Grealish? Grealish for
Alvarez. Handball. Against Egan.
Penalty. The referee, Gerrard Gelin,
had no hesitation, he was in an
excellent position. It happened
rather quickly, as Alvarez cooks it
across, Egan's left arm is
stretched. But how do you keep your
arms out of the way when you are
sliding in that position? It is so
difficult for defenders to do so.
Earning Haaland with the chance. He
has never missed a penalty in the
Premier League. But he has missed
this one! Against the post and away.
Listen to the roar around Bramall
Lane. That is a collector's item and
Haaland misses from the spot. He is
human after all.
human after all. Walker for Audrey.
They have to get bodies back.
Alvarez has it, Grealish to his
left. Haaland waits in the middle,
City have players on the edge.
Ignored for the time being. Goes for
the cross. Haaland has gone down.
Haaland tumbled in the box. VAR are
checking. The check complete. Very
important half-time address to come
unless he puts the phone on Speaker
and finds Pep Guardiola to take
charge how long until Phil Foden is
introduced? And the possibility of a
first appearance in the Premier
League. Alvarez, were not quite sit
for him. Rodri again, he has Walker
to his right. Haaland! Wide. It is
not his day. The sort of opportunity
he gobbled up throughout last
season. He steers it wide.
Instructions are coming from Spain.
Maybe it is a bad line. Juanma Lillo
cannot hear him! Or does not want
to. Rodri. City moving through the
lines swiftly. This is where it has
come to an end, when they get to
this part of the pitch, Grealish
back for Rodri. It whistles white.
He beat Foderingham with it. A yard
inside and it would have been 1-0,
City. Lofted forward by Kovacic. A
by Egan. Norwood under pressure, a
good drop for Walker. Rodri.
Kovacic. Inevitably City look for
Grealish once more. Which way will
he go? Across towards Haaland and he
scores this time! No great
celebrations, just an expression on
his face that says, boy, am I
relieved to see that going on! In
the 63rd minute, Sheffield United's
stubborn resistance is broken.
Grealish did magnificently. Perfect
cross. And Haaland rises at the back
post. Above Robinson, to power home.
Won by Larouci. Fed by Hamer. Some
defending for Kyle Walker to do. Has
not done much of that today.
Sheffield United throwing somebody's
forward to attack this long throw.
Henderson has come, he has got
something on it, and the shot was
goal bound by Hamer, Ruben Diaz in
the way. That was a poor clearance
by Addison, quickly back by
Ahmedhodzic. What a good effort that
was. He was similar to the
possibilities that fell his way.
Here is the first effort from Hamer,
City have bodies in the way, and
from that terrible clearance,
Ederson was almost embarrassed by
some sharp thinking by Ahmedhodzic.
Hamer. Traore. McBurnie is in the
box, Basham is up there, too.
Careless by Walker, the pass by
Hamer was drilled too firmly, still
a chance. Bogle scores! The
substitute, only on the pitch for a
matter of minutes, capitalises on a
rare bit of complacent defending
from Kyle Walker. And Sheffield
United have an equaliser. Traore had
trouble, Walker did the difficult
bit and then took liberties. And
that pass picked out Bogle, and he
was not closed down quickly enough.
And he thumps it home. Sheffield
United's first shot on target. It
brings in the equaliser.
Walker knows that it was his
mistake, a mistake that has been
punished. This might run out for
Grealish.
Grealish. Foden is with him. Now
Bernardo Silva. Haaland! Another
good opportunity. This time Larouci
has made a mistake and walk arisen
behind and he has found
behind and he has found Foden and
struck home by Rodri, Sheffield
United were not level long. The joy
has turned to detection for those in
stripes. And Walker, here, culpable
in many ways for the Sheffield
United equaliser worked so hard to
regain possession, detach from Foden
and Rodri does the rest. It is a
sumptuous strike from the Spanish
international.
international. And City protecting
their 100% record. Can Sheffield
United come again? Oli McBurnie with
a cross and missed at the back post
by Ahmedhodzic. What a thrilling
climax to this game at Bramall Lane.
TRANSLATION: We had lots of the ball
but we found it hard to find spaces
in behind because there are not any.
In the second half we were able to
get the ball in more continuous
pressure and it was a different
story in the second half. The two
girls, we can do better, with men
behind the ball, Jack Grealish gets
the ball then, we spoke a lot about
that. If he attacks Jackie forces
him to the other defenders. It was
very passive. The second goal be to
deal with but having said that,
99.5% of the time we were getting
things perfect. That is what you
have got to do to get points against
them, because that was a good City
performance and be produced almost
as good a performance. Pep Guardiola
was not around, what was it like
without him on the touchline and
dressing room? We know what he wants
in these situations, the most
important thing is that he recovered
and he stays fit even though
sometimes he is difficult with the
stress, he is calling there and they
are, but very happy and glad and
hopefully, we can have him soon.
India interesting what they are
saying, 99.5% perfect but still not
good enough. They were so good
within the game. The game was really
interesting. They were so compact in
the middle and leaving the space
wide but I thought they were
excellent, I really did against a
Manchester City side that got
frustrated. They dominated. 35
courses, they had, they had 30 shots
as well but only nine of them on
target. -- 35 crosses. Look at the
shape, the five defenders and three
midfielders helping out and Grealish
and Baldock on a one-on-one, we know
that he can go both ways, so if they
do get across in, it is not going to
be a great cross, on that occasion
it goes out. His position is good
but watch Haaland in the box, the
midfielder was coming in to help him
out. If he goes and makes the cross,
look at Haaland in the centre, they
are all over him, smothering him,
just fighting for everything, making
it so difficult, condensing that
space. And again here, happy for it
to go wide, who comes in, no
problem, you can go wide, but look
at this from Haaland, two of them on
him and knows is again, brilliant
defending. Second half, exactly the
same. You can trust and we will deal
with it. They are watching Haaland,
probing, thinking where he's going
to run. Anything that goes on it is
not a problem, we will deal with it.
This time, Baldock has to defend one
against one, accident, really good.
The ball gets circulated again.
Haaland, noticed a within the box.
And they get it out for a corner.
And then the goal. Talking about
that 0.5%, Alan, to get him in here
is great. You can force him wide and
inside is the back post, he is knows
exactly where he is, but look at the
perdition of Baldock, he gives him
too much room, Jack Robinson uses
Haaland and you know what is going
to happen then. If you give him that
amount of space in the box, he is
going to score. People watching that
will be thinking it is not his day.
Missed a penalty and could not hold
it up any time he got it. But that
is what they best strikers do, isn't
it, Alan?
it, Alan? Alan is bailing you out
once again because... Just because
you did not want to do this space,
can I apologise for laughing but I
found this funny only because he
ended up winning the game. I thought
that Sheffield United were superb,
but this was not the finest for Kyle
Walker. I don't even know what he is
trying to do, back killing it in his
own 18-yard box. Then he stays off
the pitch, Sheffield United keep the
ball alive and this is when Baldock
scores, it is a wonderful strike.
Kyle Walker been off the pitch is
keeping Oli McBurnie on. Edison
claims he would have been offside
but for Kyle Walker staying off the
pitch with his hands on his head, he
can see the error, Thommy knows what
is coming and I know what you are
thinking, your absolutely delighted
that Pep is 1000 miles away and not
waiting for him in the dressing
room! But he wants to rectify that
error, and he did so. Only a couple
of minutes left, Alvarez blasted
over the bar, but it is him that
keeps the ball alive in this
position. That should have been out.
She had been out, but he does not
allow him to do that, he did really
well, it keeps the ball alive, these
it to Ferdinand watch the finish
from Rodri. It was a different
couple of minutes, we cannot repeat
what he is saying there, I know
exactly what he is saying!
Manchester City of all, how is there
start? A good start, three out of
three, they are not playing the
sumptuous football that we know what
they are getting over the line, they
are doing a job.
Burnley were back in action
after a week off due to their game
against Luton being postponed.
Aston Villa followed up a four-goal
defeat against Newcastle
with a four-goal victory over
Everton.
Steven Wyeth was at Turf Moor.
COMMENTATOR: 16 days after making
their Premier League return, Burnley
finally play again. Has given
Vincent Kompany time to assess and
recruit since opening night against
Manchester City, Hans Delterra gets
a start, and it was placed on the
bench for Manuel Benson. Villa have
played three times since Burley last
played competitively, Miriam
Martinez Rico is injured against
Hibernian, and Matty Cash returns to
make his 100th Villa appearance.
They have already lost as many
league games this season as they did
in the entirety of last season. Very
impressive
at
home in their Championship winning
campaign and they will need to be so
again. That is if they are to
survive in the Premier League. John
McGinn. Watkins on the move, and
creating the opening goal for Aston
Villa that has been scored by Matty
Cash! Villa in front inside eight
minutes. An exciting break from one
end of the field to the other with
Ollie Watkins at the heart of it,
the ball over the top and Watkins
was away, Trafford did not know
whether to, or stay at home and once
he was off his line it was
relatively easy for Watkins to lift
the over him, and after that a
relatively straightforward job for
Matty Cash to mark his century of
Aston Villa appearances with a goal.
Watkins, Cash, Gyabi, excellent from
Villa, Cash again, incredible!
Villa, Cash again, incredible! --
Diaby. And the team guarantee goals
at the start of the new season have
a pair already for themselves at
Turf Moor. A milestone appears to
remember for Matty Cash who has
scored twice inside the opening 20
minutes to put Villa in control of
the game, he pulled back from Diaby
into the path of Matty Cash so
inviting, he could strike it sweetly
first time inside the near post. And
Burnley, already 2-0 down at home to
Unai Emery's Aston Villa.
Unai Emery's Aston Villa. Moussa
Diaby arriving in support. Watkins
and, beaten away by Trafford, an
important reaction stop from the
Burnley goalkeeper. Watkins getting
decent contact on the ball, he
scored a hat-trick at Hibernian in
midweek. But not on this occasion,
blocked by James Trafford. That is a
wonderful one and it is the very
best we have seen from the home side
so far. Not too far off target from
Zeki Amdouni.
Zeki Amdouni. Burnley, needing a
vast improvement on the opening 45
minutes if they are to apply any
sort of pressure on Aston Villa this
afternoon. Luca Koleosho has
wriggled between two. The shot from
Amdouni, charged down. Berge,
keeping Burley on the front foot.
That is an inviting delivery, from
Roberts, and Gudmundsson scores, and
90 seconds into the second half,
hope for Vincent Kompany and his
team, a first Premier League goal
for Lyle Foster -- the Roberts
delivery helped on towards Kyle
Foster -- Lyle Foster who
outmanoeuvred Powell Torres. It went
beyond the reach of Robin Olsen and
the game is spark back into life.
Whatever was discussed in that
Burley dressing room at half-time,
the message has hit home.
-- Burnley. Sando Berge is in and
they have had to scramble to play
the ball behind. The letter,
disorientated all of a sudden.
Mistakes creeping into a group of
players who were close to flawless
in the first half. A breakdown in
communication has led to the scorer
to be delivered by Gudmundsson. Also
in getting across goal smartly to
turn it aside. Really good headed
back across the face of goal, Olsson
at full stretch.
at full stretch. Unai Emery, in
comparison to Vincent Kompany, is
seething and simmering. Diaby! Two
goal advantage restored. Another
move of high quality from Aston
Villa. And Moussa Diaby has goals in
successive away games in the Premier
League, and that is just what the
visitors required. A goal to bring
about jubilation as well as some
relief. They were on the back foot
and Diaby from the edge of the area
did not need to hit it too hard,
just needed to place it in the
bottom corner and he did so beyond
the reach of James Trafford.
the reach of James Trafford. Diaby,
the return from John McGinn
beautifully weighted. Towards
Watkins! What a stop from James
Trafford! Sensational save. But for
Burnley's young goalkeeper Aston
Villa would be 4-1 up and out of
sight. He is happier than he was at
2-1, you wouldn't necessarily know
it, a manager who says he prefers to
win but accepts defeats when they
come because there are so much to
learn from them. They have got to
get back quickly. Nicolo Zaniolo is
in, and moments after coming on and
he should have had his first Aston
Villa goal. The hard work was all
done. Maybe he had too much time to
consider his options, Nicolo
Zaniolo.
Zaniolo. Lovely work, back from
Watkins. Cash. Not too far away.
There is a burning desire coursing
through the body of Matty Cash that
he is going home with the match
ball, and he thought there was
enough of a top corner to aim at.
Delcroix. A chance to give Burnley
hope! Rodriguez sent an opportunity
clear of the crossbar. Cullen.
Rodriguez! They have had a couple of
presentable opportunities, the
curling delivery from Cullen onto
the head of Jay Rodriguez, who got
there ahead of the goalkeeper,
Olson. It is a contest that Aston
Villa have controlled for the third
time in four troops to Turf Moor,
they are living with maximum points.
Probably the biggest jump in the
biggest gap in world football, from
the Championship to the Premier
League, it has been done before
successfully but the level keeps
improving in the Premier League and
I look at the squad and every
morning I wake up with a smile on my
face because I know they are getting
better and I have seen an up to date
and we will get over moments and our
goals and winds. We just have to
stay away from any type of emotional
coaster. Matty Cash, we have been
encouraging him to shoot more often
and get into goal-scoring positions
and he responded with two, did you
know he had that capability? He
played as a winner when he was
younger and further C can be
important, playing higher and
deeper, the back four and sometimes
full-back and today as a winger.
Today was a strange game, we
normally have a lot of possession
but the game plan before was to let
them have the ball and catch them on
the counter and I played a higher
role and I know I can finish, I
chatted with the gaffer and he likes
the way I attack and get forward and
today it paid off. A bit of
composure in front of goal and it
could have been three! It certainly
paid off Matty Cash. Cash in the
pocket!
LAUGHTER
It has been a long night! What's
going on?! I have to try! We know
Unai Emery, the tactician, and he is
obviously studied Burnley's
weakness. And it worked perfectly,
he said himself that he played Matty
Cash higher up and because Burnley
play high risk football, they commit
so many men forward, on the turnover
of possession you can get at them
and that is exactly what Aston Villa
did today and they punish them,
particularly on the right-hand side.
They got a warning here, Matty Cash
on the right-hand side, that is what
I mean about the high risk, if they
lose the ball in that position, then
this happens to them. All right, the
wrong ball, but that was the
warning. They work it really well
again but it is three on three and
this you have Matty Cash, watch his
determination to get on the end of
this, really good work, really good
cross and he is there, he sticks it
away. And it gives them the
advantage. Similar again, but always
on the right-hand side, sometimes it
was on the left, Digne did really
well as well. That little one, two,
what a finish that is. Unbelievable,
that is exactly why Unai Emery is
playing him in that position, to
offer a threat. I said about Burnley
losing the ball, again, the turnover
of possession, they work it on the
right-hand side and it should have
been in the back of the net from
Ollie Watkins. Matty Cash had more
touches on the box than Watkins, you
can see on the left-hand side, this
time into Diaby and other than 20
minutes after half-time when Burnley
gave it a good effort, I thought
Aston Villa were superb and deserved
the points. Straight after half-time
there was a reaction. They got the
goal back and they got a bit of
energy going and the crowd got
behind them but that is all that
was, for about 20 minutes. I always
felt that because of the way they
play and they commit men forward,
they would always get done in
behind. It has been a struggle for
all three teams that have been
promoted because seven games played,
seven defeats. This is the Premier
League. No one said it would be
easy. A little disappointed with
Burnley in terms of what I saw last
season and the way they approached
the game, they play at a higher
level, Vincent Kompany has brought
in 13 new players and they will take
time to gel but in terms of the way
they press, they only had a 20
minute spell today. And the way
Sheffield United defender, it is
just whether they will get enough
goals. Every single year we come
into this position, the teams that
come up, we always say at this level
you get punished for your mistakes,
whereas in the Championship and
lower it is not so much but this
level you play quality centre
forwards and the quicker they learn
in the quicker they cut out the
errors, the more chance they have
staying up, all three will struggle
but Burnley have the best chance. We
have some news just in. After the
match, the windscreen of the Aston
Villa team bus was hit by a brick
two miles from Turf Moor and Burnley
said we strongly condemn this
behaviour and we will support
Lancashire Police in their efforts
to find whoever was responsible.
Just used to bring you on that one.
Here's the rest of
the weekend action.
Corner. Johnson got the touch to
that. Awoniyi charging and he has
got the better of Rashford and he is
three. And he has scored! He took
his time at he made absolutely sure.
And the game has well and truly
started. A good start for the
visitors. It may be about to become
a great start. And another! 2-0,
Forest. This is a truly incredible
start. Gibbs-White with the ball and
Boly did even have to jump!
Rashford. Good burst of pace and
United have got one back, Christian
Eriksen flicking at home. Eriksson
is there in front of Scott McKenna.
Man United one, Nottingham Forest
two. Rashford. Bruno Fernandes.
Surely... Casemiro, 2-2! That was a
long way around. Manchester United
are behind no longer. Hesitation.
The free kick on the edge of the
box. It might be more than that, it
is a red card for Joe Worrall, the
first skipper. He got a hold of his
shorts, tugging him down. That is a
grimace from Steve Cooper. Rashford,
was he tripped? Penalty given! He
did not time the challenge right.
And he clearly impeded Rashford.
Bruno Fernandes... Hernandez scores.
And there is a lot of feeling in
that. 3-2.
Webster is struggling, Antonio in
possession. Support arriving, James
Ward-Prowse, a great chance! 1-0,
West Ham! And James Ward price
scores his first goal for his new
club, and his 50th in the Premier
League in his career. Blasting his
way towards the edge of the box,
Jarrod Bowen, 2-0, West Ham,
fantastic attacking play.
fantastic attacking play. Here they
come again, West Ham, only won three
matches away last season, three
goals today and three points on
their way and Michail Antonio makes
a 3-0. Pascal Gross. Finally! At
last, but in have a go, for all of
their attacking play, a big win for
West Ham.
Saka. Given away. An early chance.
And Fulham are ahead in 58 seconds.
A mistake by Arsenal, and absolutely
gobbled up for the opening goal by
Pereira. It was a stunner for the
Emirates. A yellow card here. Time
wasting for parsley.
wasting for parsley. Martinelli,
Fiona, the flag stays down. All day
long risky challenge. A big moment,
the crowd goes quiet. He scores
pretty. Into the bottom right
corner. Lovely penalty, 1-1. Saka
winning it back, in the middle, they
have got it! The game has been spun
on its head. Two goals in three
minutes.
minutes. Decordova-Reid, for Fulham.
He is going to
He is going to go here, Bassey, his
second of the game and off he goes.
Raul Jimenez is in there, it is in!
2-2. Great spirit for Fulham. And
Arsenal's 100% start goes in a
topsy-turvy game of such drama. We
said we will talk about time wasting
and dissent later on and here we
are. That red card for Calvin Bassey
was the second this week with the
first yellow card came from time
wasting after Tomiyasu on Monday so
we have seen the Trent yellow card
today so let us look at the stats
for the first three weeks. The ball
in play, that time is up, four
minutes, more yellow cards and a big
increase in dissent and time
wasting. We have seen were cards for
dissent as well, how do you feel at
the moment these changes are playing
out? I get why this was brought in.
Because we all want more minutes on
the pitch, there is a lot of time
wasting going on and it has been for
years. Unless abuse of officials. I
understand why, but I think it is
making it more difficult for the
referees, there is enough pressure
on them anyway, it is a hard enough
job, but to give them extra
decisions to make is putting more
pressure on the referees and I think
that is shown in the games because I
do not think the standards have been
anywhere near where they should be
and could be. I don't think the
comments of Mike Dean have helped at
all. Gone are the days of the Old
Boys club, like Mike Riley was part
of, and Mike Dean, those days have
gone on to be fair to Howard Webb,
he certainly has been more
transparent and he is talking to
more people and trying to educate
people in what he is trying to do so
I think that can only be a good
thing. But I do think certainly at
times, but only last season, but at
the beginning of the season the
standard of refereeing is not good
enough. What needs to be done about
that? Howard is trying to do that
and educate people I know they are
trying to change the laws but it is
not always down to Howard. But I
think there has to be an acceptance
to get what he wants to go it might
take a little bit of time. If you
were still playing, with that have
changed your behaviour? No! I would
be exactly the same! Of course! One
more time... You would not have
changed? Were you ever booked for
dissent or time wasting? Never! I am
100%! Really?! What have you done
here?! Let's take a look! That is
perfectly good... Oh!
LAUGHTER
We will not let you get away with
anything. You went into the
archives! Twice, for time wasting! I
want to change.
want to change. I will give you
something... You did go on to score
in that game. I thought I might!
What about you, Alan? I cannot
remember many times, if ever,
getting booked for dissent. I might
have been booked for not retreating
ten yards for the wall but not for
dissent, it was different, you could
have conversations with referees
back then, they would even give you
something back, which I did not mind
but nowadays you cannot talk to the
referees at all. The worst player I
ever played with was Vincent
Kompany, so cool and collected as a
manager... He was horrible, always
in the ears of the referee! But he
was captain, so he sort of got away
with it. Did you ever get booked for
dissent or time wasting? Not at all,
the referee could speak to me, go
and have a word, Alex! You don't
have anything in the archives! Who
else have you played with do you
think was like Vincent Kompany?
Craig Bellamy, was one of them. The
rest of the weekend action to catch
up on.
COMMENTATOR: Turning away from
Christie, finding Sarr, James
Maddison, 1-0, wonderful Tottenham
goal. James Maddison is off and
running.
running. Udogie did really well and
it is 2-0, Kulusevski arriving and
Tottenham doubled their lead. Udogie
has such a big part to play this
game, and Kulusevski the finishing
touch. Pedro Netto, carrying it
forward for walls. The angled ball,
and it is turned in, the first goal
for Kalazsic, only on the field a
short amount of time but that is
what you want from substitute.
Looking for the angle to get the
ball in, and Schade, that is
sensational from Ken Schade, the
German's first goal for Brentford is
an absolute stunner. Joachim
Andersen, played back to Anderson,
and he has sneaked it in, surely
that went over the line, it is
Joachim Andersen! Only his second
ever Crystal Palace goal.
ever Crystal Palace goal. Raheem
Sterling up against Giles. Fantastic
from Raheem Sterling. He guided that
home.
home. Space for Gusto with the first
time cross and once again it is
Raheem Sterling.
Raheem Sterling. Fernandes, Raheem
Sterling will get to that. The
first-time cross and the first
Chelsea goal for Nicholas Jackson,
who makes it three.
who makes it three. Manchester City
winning their opening three league
games for the first time since Pep
Guardiola's debut season in charge
in 2016.
in 2016. At the bottom, Sheffield
United join Everton in having lost
three from three whilst Burnley have
been beaten in both matches on their
top-flight return. Let's look at
what the papers are seen, the back
pages dominated by Liverpool's
dramatic winner at Newcastle. The
Independent because it smash and
grab, while The Express carries
quotes from Jurgen Klopp who
believes that the victory was better
than their famous Champions League
comeback against Barcelona in 2019.
Time to get into 2 Good 2 Bad.
Time to get into 2 Good 2 Bad. Look
at this.
Even the mascots look
like Kompany men at Burnley.
How cute is this?!
Pervis Estupinan sums up
Brighton's day in a moment.
Not sure the Man City bench
are enjoying their Pep talk.
Now, not having it!
Never get between a cameraman
and his tripod -
even if you're injured.
He's not having any of it!
Roy wasn't enjoying the rain.
Looks like Crystal Palace use the
same coat supplier as Arsene Wenger.
We can't tell you exactly
what Bournemouth fans
were shouting at James Maddison,
but you're not wiping the smile
off his face right now.
Enough mum jokes from me!
This weekend saw Nicolas Jackson,
Kevin Schade, Sasa Kalajdzic
and Lyle Foster all get off the mark
in the Premier League.
Everyone remembers their first
time - right, guys?
We do. Indeed we do. Shearer,
fantastic goal!
fantastic goal! To Klinsmann, who is
the diver? And he has scored.
Fantastic goal. 30 yards out! What a
goal! Wayne Rooney. What a goal!
Micah Richards, and they have
equalised!