Hello,
I just came back from work
and then I simply went to
my neighborhood noodle restaurant
and ate a bowl of noodles
and then I bought some fruit to take home
so now I am in a place
where I can just
take a rest and
washed a little strawberry here.
I'm not particularly busy today, so I'm in
a good mood.
Relaxed and smooth.
In fact
in the past month, my life and work
have begun to get on the right track
so I have tried
my best to keep my life and work
in a relatively stable state,
rather than in a endless tense state.
So in fact
this month, I am not that tired as before
And then, for me
On weekends, I will go outdoors to relax.
There are
several weekends
when I don't have a job at all.
It does not mean
I wanted to do extra work
Also, in Beijing
the spring is coming.
So I like to go out for a walk
with my friends,
and go to the park
especially on sunny days.
So in fact
we often appreciate the flowers in the park
and then chat, so as to relax
Besides, in fact,
I think my favorite way to relax is
to be alone.
I live alone to make me relax.
For example,when I am at home
I may like to listen to podcasts quietly
or listen to podcasts
when I take a shower