Introducing Microsoft 365 Copilot,
your copilot for work.
Copilot combines the power of large language
models with your data in the Microsoft Graph
and the Microsoft 365 apps to turn your words
into the most powerful productivity tool
on the planet.
It’s coming to life in the products
millions of people use and rely on every day.
Let's see how Copilot can use
your customer notes
in OneNote as well as another internal document.
Copilot quickly creates a first draft.
You can turn your Word document into a PowerPoint
presentation that you can hone and polish.
Let's jump into Copilot in Excel.
You start by asking Copilot to analyze the data
and give you three key trends.
Within seconds, you’ve got what you need.
Triage your inbox,
highlighting the most important emails to prioritize.
You can draft a reply
using data from an Excel file
and Copilot will generate a reply for you.
The real magic of Copilot
happens during a live meeting.
You can ask Copilot to
summarize what’s happened so far.
You can see who said what, what points were made.
You can follow a meeting and catch up
to see what you missed, even if you can’t attend.
I want to show you an entirely
new standalone experience.
Business Chat works across all your emails, files,
meetings, chats, documents, calendar,
and more to turn all your data into knowledge.
Now let's imagine you're
working on your business strategy.
You ask Copilot to pull up quarterly projections
and identify related risks.
Copilot gives you key data points and flags
potential issues.
We're deeply committed to
listening, learning, and adapting with speed
to help create a brighter future of work
for everyone with AI.