The project homepage demonstrates the most critical information condensed from analytics conclusions and organized in accordance with requirement of daily property management. A customer will be typically provided with summaries of energy use, operational KPI, equipment health, prioritized faults, and weather conditions, etc.
A fault history and navigation bar on the left guides users to search and query any specific fault and look into its fault curves as a snapshot of historical data. BeOP automatically or manually turns a detected fault into a work order to be dispatched to a predefined responsible person.
An archive analogue to medical records is established on BeOP for each piece of equipment. At a glance, users will grasp equipment health from its diagnosis history.
Besides a variety of utility dashboards, BeOP performs energy performance diagnostics to identify opportunities of energy savings as a result from sequence optimization or fault amendment.
For energy management users can select sub-meters in the navigation bar and query and compare energy data for different historical periods.
BeOP provides users with diagnostics on sub-meter health and its data quality.
Besides its ability to convert raw data into performance indicators for facility management, one of the highlighted features of KPI is its capability of automatically analyzing factors resulting KPI failure in an automatic way enabled by AI.
Daily Operation Report summarizes operational parameters for the last 24 hours.
KPI Report summarizes KPI assessment and factors behind any of their failure.
Data Quality Report is based on diagnostics on raw data lively collected from equipment of properties. It fundamentally guarantees reliability of the basis on which analytics or algorithms are further implemented. Data quality diagnostics is performed in aspects of integrality, effectiveness, and consistency.
Commercial buildings or industrial facilities are often equipped with a large number of utility meters. However, bad meter data due to transmission disruption or else is a serious challenge to effective data-driven management. Therefore, to detect and diagnose abnormal data from metering systems in an automatic way is not only fundamental to energy management but also cost-effective to property maintenance.
By learning features of historical operation, BeOP's AI engine is able to analyze and identify energy saving opportunities thanks to improvement in operation sequence.
Reports are generated by customizable pre-defined period. A weekly diagnostics report summarizes findings and prioritizes detected faults in the last week, while a weekly classification report groups faults by different issues to responsible parties such as a maintenance contractor.
BeOP visualizes temperature distribution of any floor plans by thermal images. Users are free to drag any temperature point to a configurable panel to view its historical data curves. It organizes thermal comfort statistics into views easy for users to browse thermal comfort in different regions.