The Story of Ming Lan
Episode 44
- Please.
- Thank you, Momo.
Thank you, Momo.
Good wine.
Momo,You are too polite.
You are decreasing our blessings.
You are the nurse of Master,
and even a  Momo with high status,
yet you're still  invites us to drink
,I really feel so embarrassed.
Isn't that right?
What position?
Young Master Ye and I have never put any
importance to those seniority rules.
You can say so, but we're still
working for the inner courtyard.
No matter how good
Master is, he can't
really care about us.
Above us is Big Madam.
Big Madam isn't as resolute as Master.
Look at how chaotic that
kitchen has become.
- She doesn't even ask about it.
- Indeed.
Today, Rong'er insisted on eating
the back meat of a swamp eel.
I then went to the kitchen
to ask if there's any.
I haven't entered and I've already
heard Nanny Lai inside talking.
Her words were really unbearable.
Even my mother in the province would
feel embarrassed if she heard it.
And this person even
came from the attending
the Big Madam of
the marquis house.
She claims that she's a person
who has attended to Big
Madam of the marquis house,
but I don't think so.
Those dowry servants that Big Madam
brought with her from Qin Manor
were  mostly gone or dead.
Only Nanny Xiang is left by her side.
I really am puzzled. What
could be the background
of this Nanny Lai?
So barbaric.
I heard that...
...she entered with Nanny Xiang's help.
Because she has served longer than us,
hence, she was able to look so decent.
She kept showing off that she's
a trusted aide of Big Madam.
What's there to be proud about that?
In my opinion, you two
are not worse than her.
Why must you two get stepped by her?
We work for the fourth and
fifth house, who are not
as prestigious as the Big
Madam of the main house.
Talking about that, do you know that
before going to his western expedition,
do you know how Young Master was
able to become a general overnight?
Wasn't it because he was meritorious
for saving the emperor?
The current emperor was still
a submerged dragon then.
Afterwards, there was a palace
siege to usurp the throne.
It was Young Master who risked
his life to escort His Majesty,
and fought all out against the rebels,
hence, he has his current prestige.
If that time, Young Master
was afraid of dying
and just hid in Yuzhou
to preserve his life,
can he have achieved success? Can he have
this enormous wealth and high status now?
Then what Momo means is...
Every time a new emperor ascends,
the subjects are changed.
If you two can unite to
pull down that Nanny Lai,
remove the eye sore of Big Madam,
will she treat you two unfairly?
You two are quite cowardly.
Whether you do it
or not, I'm still the
nanny of our master.
Who in this house can have
a position higher than me?
You won't listen to the good words I say.
When bandits join a group, they first
must show their loyalty and devotion.
Fine. You two are indeed just suitable
to drink wine in this garden,
and unable to enter the main house.
Momo said it right.
Yes, Momo, we will remember your words.
Come, Momo, let me give you a toast.
I caught something!
I've caught it! I've caught it!
Let me do it.
After catching so many, we'll have
something to eat with wines tonight.
Since I came here to the capital with
Older Sister and Brother-in-law,
this is my happiest day.
No need to restrain my face and
consider the opinion of those elders.
I also don't need to keep myself
from moving my head when walking,
or showing my teeth when laughing,
as if I'm some demure lady.
Come here often then.
You're the only one left that doesn't mind
me being wild. In this Bianjing City,
which rich daughter isn't being
courteous with me upfront,
but mocking me as a country
bumpkin behind my back?
Don't even talk about fishing,
just talking a bit louder and
they will already laugh at me.
Sometimes, I didn't even know
that they were laughing at me.
I even laughed with them.
You're also laughing at me?
The two of us can get along well. You and
a cousin of mine in our home province
are of similar age and personality.
She is also wild when she plays and runs.
She can climb trees to get
bird's eggs or dive into
the river to catch toads.
She can do all those.
In our home province, she's the person
that I'm able to get along with the most.
Once she comes to visit me,
I'll tell her to play with you.
This capital is almost
killing me from suffocation.
Don't know if I can still live
until your cousin arrives.
It's indeed a good thing that
brother-in-law of mine became the emperor.
But it feels like shackles
have been placed on me.
If I make any mistake,
I would be bringing trouble
to my whole family.
Aristocratic families are indeed like that.
They are deeply entangled. One committing
a mistake will affect everyone else.
Good thing, you were married
into the Zheng Family.
Your in-laws are all from reputable
families. As days pass by,
everyone will know that
you have a pure and kind
temperament. They will
eventually accept you.
Xiaotao, take these fishes to the kitchen.
Let's stop fishing and just go around.
We haven't been to a huge
half of this garden yet.
Sure!
In this kitchen, I'm the
one in-charge after all.
I'm just getting a few of these
rotten leafy vegetables.
Must you comment so much?
Rotten leafy vegetables?
All these were each raised and cared for
by idle people like us in the garden.
They are for the Miss Rong's soup.
Just for saying that it's a rotten leafy
vegetable, you want to take it away?
Are you more precious than our Miss?
I... Isn't it just a few wild vegetable?
If I ate yours, I'll just
get you some to make it up.
Must you make a big issue out of it?
Say, just for a few leafy vegetables,
just let this matter go.
- Stop fighting.
- Make it up?!
If Big Madam asks, how would I explain it?
You know very clearly that this is not
about just a few wild vegetables.
Since you got in-charge of the kitchen, how
many items have been converted to silver
and entered your pocket. Can
you explain those clearly?!
You...stop using Big Madam to oppress me!
I didn't eat yours or spent your
money, so why are you being hurt?
I think that you're just jealous
because other are getting kickbacks
while you're not.
Getting agitated about it.
You've already gotten advantage
and you still pretend to be nice?!
I'll hit you until you die!
Do you believe that?!
What are you doing?!
You people want to beat me up?! Hit
her until she dies! Get out! Leave!
Stinky brat! Get lost!
You are really so bold! You!
Stop! Stop!
- I'm indeed hitting you!
- Stop!
- Stop pulling me!
- Let go of me!
Did a thief enter your house?
No. It must be the senior
kitchen maids fighting again.
Forget it. Let's look for a
more peaceful place to talk.
No, they are breaking things now.
Sister, you're not intervening?
I'll kill you!
You stinky brat!
Young Master! Young Master!
We have trouble!
The people inside the inner
courtyard kitchen are fighting.
What has happened?
I heard that it's about
some wild vegetables.
Nanny Lai, Nanny Hua, Nanny Tian,
and a few more maidservants
are all fighting in there!
Why are you telling me these?
Must I still meddle with those
trifle matters in the kitchen?
Where's Big Madam? Tell her to
go over there and take a look.
Big Madam doesn't dare to meddle.
She said that those are nannies sent
by the elders of the marquis house.
Then...just forget it.
Is everything still okay?
It's fine, General.
You better just go over and take a look.
What's there to look at?
A few elderly women fighting and I still
have to meddle? Just let them fight.
At most, let them trash the
kitchen and destroy its roof.
I'll just look for people to rebuild it.
Come, come, let's drink. Hey!
You few quickly sound the drum!
Okay! Okay!
Right. Just watching isn't fun.
Sounding a few drums
makes it more exciting.
One more time!
State Uncle Shen and his
little sister left happily.
Aren't you afraid that
Shen lady will gossip
how we are not strict
in managing our house?
That the maidservants
here fight every day?
Making this place more lively
than the southern operas.
I just fear that she
might go defend me and argue with
others because we got along so well.
That's harder to handle.
Why?
She and I are both from low background.
It's only because of
accidental fate that we're
able to climb up a
higher social status.
Those people from illustrious aristocratic
families will surely not believe her words.
They will think that she's being
biased with her same kind.
Don't worry. One day, I will let those
people not dare look down on you.
Since they have come, we
should make them comfortable.
Outside, you've already given
me enough splendor and dignity.
For this small matter inside the house,
just let me deal with with it alone.
To resist foreign
aggression, pacify internal
conflicts first. Once
the house is clean,
our reputation outside
once our house is clean.
The days are long. No need to rush.
On a more serious note,
shouldn't you disperse the
maidservants outside now?
Danju,
go out and spread my word.
Big Madam instructed
that all people involved in the fight can't
be allowed to stay in the manor anymore.
Considering that you all are old
servants of the marquis manor,
it's also not convenient for
us to just expel you all out.
Tomorrow, all are being transferred
to the farmstead outside the city.
Miss Cuiwei, we were seeking
justice for Big Madam
that's why we turned hostile
against that Lai woman!
That's right!
We were seeking justice!
Even if you are, you could
have reasoned out properly.
Why must you become violent?
You all say that you were
seeking justice for Big Madam.
So this matter has become the
mistake of Big Madam then?
Tomorrow, if you kill a person,
will you be claiming that you're
seeking justice for general then?
What should we do?
Nanny, how's your injuries?
Do they still hurt?
With my old skin and face, I'm fine.
I'm just afraid that Big Madam
has gotten so mad about this.
Nanny, don't worry. Big Madam has already
punished the people who have hurt you.
She had them get transferred
to the farmstead
outside the city to
do manual labor.
Those evil whores,
they really dared to cruelly hit me.
Big Madam is right to handle them that way.
But, with so many people leaving,
the manor will surely lack people.
Tomorrow, I must take care
getting some new people in.
Big Madam said that since you're hurt,
don't worry about the
household matters anymore.
Tonight, you'll be transferred to
the farmstead outside the city.
You just need to be at
ease and recuperate.
No need for you to worry
about other things.
No! No! My injuries aren't serious.
When Big Madam gave the instructions,
Master was also there.
He then sent out his two
servants to escort you.
Nanny, stop being courteous.
Whether you leave now or
later, you're still leaving.
You people are all loyal ones.
With Nanny Lai and the others leaving,
the positions emptied is also
making me be at my wits' end.
Everyone, please do your best to do them.
Madam, don't worry. We always give
it our best in doing our tasks.
What marquis manor? We don't
acknowledge it at all.
In our eyes, there's only Big Madam.
We'll only listen to your orders.
I have to rely on everyone then.
You... If you want to do a good
hairstyle on your daughter,
you should at least follow the norms.
Why did you make her look like some lion?
Look. Put on some hair oil,
then turn it like this. Isn't it done?
So pretty.
Wife's fingers are like softstem bulrush,
so fine and long.
My fingers are like ginseng. How could
I beat you in doing a hairstyle?
Not true.
There's an old maidservant in our house
whose 10 fingers are so coarse
and short like carrots.
But it's her who can do
hairstyles the best.
She's able to do the best
and latest hairstyles.
Hence, this has nothing to do with
the coarseness of one's fingers.
If you want to do a great hairstyle,
you should practice more.
Don't blame the fingers.
So pretty.
Okay. Okay. I'll practice more.
I'm preparing to practice
on my wife's hair.
Don't!  Don't! Stop it!
You're not even saving
me and still laughing?!
- Don't save her!
- Save me!
- Get lost.
- Miss.
Stop it already!
That... I'm teaching your Big
Madam some defense moves.
Then...I'll just come back later.
Wait! Wait!
- What is it?
- Big Madam from the marquis manor is here.
She's here to denounce me for my crimes.
Serve her tea first. I'll be right there.
Yes.
You go first. I'll then hide
and listen to what you two are saying.
If they bully you,
I'll come out and give you support.
You better just think about
how to fix her hair.
You decide on where to put those.
Hurry up!
This...how do you do this?
Nanny Lai is old and gravely injured,
I was afraid that she can't
stand staying idle here
in our house and refuse
to focus on recuperating.
Hence, I made the decision to transfer
her to the farmstead outside the city.
They are really so bold to disobey!
Nannies Lai, Diao, Hua, and
Tian are all behaved people
when they were still in the marquis manor.
How come upon coming here to your house,
they ended up this way?
Quickly sit down, my good child.
Maybe because in the marquis
manor, you're there
personally attending to
the household affairs,
they dare not do any mischief.
Upon coming here, seeing how I am young
and have such small might, I'm
unable to control my servants.
They instead went mad.
It's all their fault. How can
it be mother-in-law's fault?
From now on, I still
must learn more
principles of managing
the household from you.
Good thing, among the people I've sent you,
there were still a few that's useful.
I've already asked around
when I've arrived.
That..one named Mingyue
and another one named Ruyue
didn't join the fight.
Especially that Mingyue,
when she learned
that mother did that,
she tried to stop her.
But saying didn't work.
This child, in terms of
looks and needlework,
she's really good. She's
also a very prudent person.
I think that she would be helpful to you.
Mother-in-law is right. This
maidservant is indeed not bad
and I know her background very well.
She surely will be a good help.
I'm at ease for you saying that.
If these maidservants do
anything inappropriate,
just have people tell me.
You are too shy. You aren't bold
enough to be hostile with them.
I'll deal with them for you.
With mother-in-law's
words, I feel so at ease.
- Have caused you to worry, mother-in-law.
- No such thing.
You've just moved in here. There are still a lot of things
that you must handle in this house. You just go back now.
Okay.
- Go back.
- Mother-in-law, take care.
Quickly go back.
Let's go.
That illegitimate daughter
is really formidable.
Ten plus people entered,
and now, only two are left.
It's good too that there were two left.
Although Mingyue and Ruyue
are not that pretty,
that Second grew up in
the alleys of brothels.
He likes having someone new.
Even if he can endure it now,
can he still do in the future?
Too bad, Nanny Lai and those others
who were trusted aides of ours
that we trained for decades
would actually end up in failure.
The future days are long.
This game of chess has
just reached the middle.
Daddy, I want to write
by my own, by my own.
Okay. Okay. Rong'er can
write it by herself.
What are you laughing at?
You can't kick out those two
remaining maidservants?
Yes. That person already left her words.
Even if those two make any
mistakes, I must first inform her.
If I kick them out, that's
turning one's back to my elder.
Turning your back to your elder?
She still has the nerve to
call herself your elder?
Anyway, I've turned my back against her
not just this once. I'll go talk to her!
No need to trouble you.
Wife still has some countermeasures?
As the main madam of this house, you think
it will be hard for me to drive people out?
The only hard part is not to let others
catch any flaws. I must make it reasonable.
Don't you people who fight wars
also pay attention to
winning without fighting?
These next few days, the
weather will be colder.
I'll then tell those two ladies
to go to Heishui (Blackwater)
Farmstead and visit Nanny Lai.
In handling the household, wife
is even using the art of war.
Did I just marry a Zifang (courtesy name
of Zhang Liang, a great strategist) ?
[ Sunset along the long river... ]
It's really too cold here.
There aren't even things that
can warm your hands and feet.
I really can't stay here anymore.
Didn't the marquis house ask
you to relay me a message?
They don't mind me that much now.
They would only sometimes
tell me to do my work well.
Whether I'll be able to get a concubine
position will depend on my ability.
No matter how fierce master is, I must
think of a way to make him like me.
Looks like Big Madam has
completely forgotten about me.
Mother. In the Cheng Garden now,
only me and Ruyue were left
in the group that came
from the marquis house.
We are outnumbered. Those people
who were nice to us before
are afraid of getting implicated and
don't usually socialize with us.
People like us who lacks foundation
can't even get near in front of the Master.
Child, do you want to take a step higher
and become the concubine of master?
I initially liked to,
but that was in the courtyard
of Young Master Wei.
Young Master Wei is easygoing
and easy to amuse.
But the current master...
Master is too fierce. I'm afraid.
Looks like the two of us are not
people who can do great undertakings.
That Big Madam saw that I'm now useless,
so she just threw me on the side
and didn't even show any care.
I've worked hard for her. It's
fine if they were honorable tasks,
but they were shameful deeds.
She will never care about our lives.
Mother, what should we do then?
That one in marquis manor is a
person who keeps her words.
If I don't follow her
instructions to seduce master,
she'll never let me off.
Child, go and beg the current main madam.
I beg Big Madam to give me a path to live.
Don't be afraid. I won't eat you.
If my husband really likes
you, I can't really stop it.
No! No! I don't have such intentions.
It's just that Big Madam
Qin...she forced me to do so!
I don't want to,
but I'm afraid. I'm afraid...
Afraid of what?
I'm afraid that she'll kick me out.
What do you want me to do then?
I want to leave this place.
I want to take my mother, Nanny Lai,
and little sister Ruyue
to leave Bianjing together,
and just go back
to our home province
Qizhou to live our days.
I beg Big Madam to get my slave contract.
You have really thought
about it very clearly.
If there's a survival path, who would
dare charge into the gates of death?
I beg Big Madam to be merciful.
You people are so broad-minded.
How sure are you that I can get
your slave contract back for you?
Big Madam, the three of us were old
servants of the adjacent house.
If the three of us leave,
the remaining ones will also just be a
loose pile of sand. (lose a leader)
Whether Big Madam kicks them out
or be considerate and makes them stay,
they will never be able to
create any trouble anymore.
This is good for our family,
and also to your family.
If you're this clever
from the start, how could
there still be so much
problems afterwards?
Sometimes, if you don't try it first,
you will never know which gate is for
survival and which will lead you to death.
Big Madam.
There are three of us in my family. Our
lives are in someone else's hands.
I was forced to do it.
I'm begging Big Madam to be kind.
Enough. You all can leave.
Thank you, Big Madam.
This meat is delicious too.
Try it now.
Now that the three of them have
left, it clean and peaceful now.
I finally have time to spare in
supervising the house and the farmsteads.
And that farmstead that was
granted to you by the emperor.
After dealing with several crafty old maids
and expelling out two beautiful ones,
in this round, you obtained
a resounding victory.
Just do the inspection of the
farmsteads once you're happy to do it.
If you didn't support me from the back,
I wouldn't have been able to
borrow the courage to do this.
This merit goes to you.
You are a slick person.
You are humoring me to make me feel good
and let me be the evil guy
to help you with the slave contract.
Then...I will go instead.
I was only joking with you.
How could you regard it as real?
I will go. I will go after I'm done eating.
No need to force yourself.
Wait for a few more days.
If they still don't get
someone to deliver it
it's still not too late to go.
No. I'm going later. I will go.
I want to see my stepmother
fuming and can't withstand me.
I...I can't wait for it.
Alright, you go then.
Wife.
I married you so that you
can enjoy happiness.
If you think managing the household
is too much, you can throw it to me.
I want to see you having the freedom
to eat the meat like just now.
No matter what you want
to do, I will agree.
I'm a military man.
I can't totally guess what's on your mind.
You must tell me.
Why are you suddenly saying this?
I'm a man of my word. I surely
will fulfill my promise.
Do you believe me?
I do.
Really?
It's true.
Master, people from
Shitou's family is here.
They said they had something
urgent to report.
I bumped into them when
we were docked on land.
The more I looked at
her, the more I find her
similar to the
illustration you gave me.
I thought of asking them to
settle down there first, then
asked my husband to come back
here and report it to you.
But didn't know how, she
saw through my plan.
When the boat docked, she immediately
took the child and escaped.
My husband immediately went
down the boat to chase after
them, but he lost them
when they turned a corner.
If there will be news about them next
time, be sure to be more careful.
Even if you have to look for 7 to 8
big men to surround and tie her up.
Yes. Brother Bai, we didn't handle
your matter well this time.
Really so sorry.
Not really. This woman is too cunning.
She's even more cruel than a
formidable man. Even I lost to her.
You all were also just being cautious,
fearing that she might hurt the child.
I brought problems onto you.
After removing the sand blocking my eyes,
these accounting books
look more clearly too.
I will be able to sleep soundly tonight.
In the past, everyone
thinks that it's
dangerous for you to marry
into the Gu family.
Looking at how the Lord
protects you, I'm relieved.
Old Madam is extremely relieved too.
No one in this kingdom is reliable.
He is a good man and takes care of me.
This is great
but it's best not to place
too much hopes on him.
Everyone has their predicaments.
Even if you are to put your hopes,
don't make it too much and too deep.
The more hopes you have, the
more disappointed you will be.
Once there are too much disappointments,
you'll develop grudges.
Once you bear these grudges
all your life, you'll develop
hatred and your days will
become unbearable to live.
Big Madam, you don't seem to
be referring to your husband.
It's more like you're
talking of Master Sheng.
I indeed have to treat
my husband like he's
him. I have to be cautious
and conscientious.
Now, we're just newlywed. Of course,
he still find me interesting,
but it's not only for just a few months.
There are still many years to come.
In any case, placing hopes on him,
he might find the burden too heavy one day.
What's up?
My brothers in Canal Gang found
traces of Chang and his mother.
However, they eventually lost them.
It's fine. Since there were traces,
with the broad connections
of the Canal Gang,
they surely will be
able to find them.
If there's news again,
I might leave everything here and
personally go there to look.
You should. By then, I'll
pack up your luggage.
And then go to Yuqing Monastery
to burn you some incense
and pray to the gods.
You talked about inspecting
the farmstead earlier.
Actually, those farmsteads don't really
earn us a lot of money every year.
You don't need to put too much
attention to it. Don't tire yourself.
How could I not? Grandmother instructed me
that the assets of the family
must be supervised regularly,
to prevent those in-charge
in deceiving us with
their reports and oppressing
the people under them.
If someone dies because of
it, this is no child's play.
That urgent?
Why don't I take time off and go with you?
No need. Just be at ease and stay in the
military camp to train your soldiers.
Just leave a few capable soldiers for me.
It will be fine.
Those people in-charge
of the farmsteads are
not really killing
and looting bandits.
They are sufficient.
If I leave everything behind here
and go look for Chang alone,
Will you be unhappy?
In the past, Nanny Zhang asked me too.
I don't know why I should be unhappy.
I think that, in the next life,
I will want to be your child too.
Marrying you is really good karma
that I've accumulated from saving humankind
in the my previous several reincarnations.
You already told me this. I know.
Alright, take a bath now.
Don't let the water get cold.
I'm going to get you a set
of clothes to change into.
What should I do
to make you trust me?
Why are you just here now? Old Commander
Bo has been waiting for you all day.
What has happened? Did my army
fight with other people again?
No. His Majesty made a decree yesterday
that he will inspect the training
of the army these next few days.
The two old generals went to inform
all the different military camps
to organize and prepare.
Inspection? With such a major thing, how
come there were no news from Prince Huan?
Who knows.
I wanted to take a few days off to settle
some personal matters in my family.
I urge you not to bring
that up anymore. This is
serious matter. It can't
be handled sloppily.
Can't you see that even
State Uncle is here?
I, Ba Fu, greets Big Madam.
Big Madam, you must be
tired from your travel.
The house inside has been prepared.
Manager Guan, you have worked hard.
It's getting dark soon and I
still made you wait here.
Big Madam is a noble person.
Having some time to spare in coming
here to visit us is our good fortune.
We so wanted you to come.
Thank you, Manager Ba.
Everyone, you all are tired too.
Quickly go home and rest now.
I'll just examine the
books tomorrow morning.
This...
Go now. I'm tired.
Thank you for understanding, Big Madam.
This Heishan (Black Mountain) Farmstead and
the Guyan (Ancient Stone) Farmstead behind
can't compare to the Xiaoyu (Little
Rain) Farmstead I brought as my dowry.
This is a penal farm set
up by the government.
We're also not familiar
with the people here.
Sister Cuiwei, I'm a bit scared.
Silly girl.
Have you prepared all the items that
Big Madam asked you to prepare?
She indeed was from a scholarly family.
Such bearing.
No matter how imposing her bearing
is, she's still just a young wife.
What can she know?
Tomorrow, we can report directly according
to what we discussed tomorrow.
It's a newlywedr just married
that want to come out
to visit her fields and show off her might.
Just let her show off. This will
be over after some coaxing.