(CIRCUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(ELEPHANT TRUMPETS)
(TIGER ROARS)
(CIRCUS MUSIC STOPS)
Hello?
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen!
Boys and girls!
The Flying Graysons!
(APPLAUSE)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(CROWD CHEERS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(INAUDIBLE SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
Rachel!
The circus again!
The boy...
Take a breath, honey.
Just calm down.
He watched as his parents fell.
Oh, God. It was...
It was so scary, I felt it.
It was just a dream.
Okay. Just...
Just breathe like we practiced, okay?
(BOTH INHALING AND EXHALING)
Good girl.
It's okay.
Everything's gonna be okay.
- Okay?
- (SNIFFLES)
Sweetie, you need to get
a little more rest. Come on.
(VOICE BREAKING)
Everything is gonna be okay.
Mom?
Yeah.
Keep the door locked.
(DOOR LOCKING)
(SIGHS)
(THUNDERCLAP)
(MAN ON RADIO) With the
low pressure coming in,
we will see
the temperatures dropping.
Which means this rain would then turn
to sleet and possible, even snow.
(RADIO CHATTER CONTINUES)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
AMY: Detective Grayson?
Amy Rohrbach.
Transfer from Oakland.
I'm your new partner.
Right. The Captain mentioned.
It's a pleasure.
I read your file.
You seem to know
what you're doing.
You keep doing your thing,
I'll keep doing my thing. We'll be good.
WOLF:
Don't take it personally.
AMY: I need a breath mint
or something?
He's been pushing off getting a
partner since he got here a month ago.
Some shit about his last one
or something.
He's from Gotham.
Likes to work alone.
Gotham?
Jesus...
What happened
to his last partner?
- Gassed by The Joker.
Who knows? -(CHUCKLES)
(ALARM CLOCK BEEPING)
(COUGHS)
(SIGHS)
Did you have breakfast?
You shouldn't drink coffee.
You shouldn't smoke.
MELISSA: I quit.
No, you didn't.
Well, I'm going to.
Darn it.
I forgot to get cream.
You forgot to get everything.
Okay. (SIGHS)
I'm late.
MELISSA: Can you take
the bus to school again today?
Sure.
Okay.
You never sleep anymore.
No, not often.
It's because you're
scared of me.
(CHUCKLES)
I am not scared of you, honey.
I can tell when you're lying.
I can feel it.
You know I can.
(SIGHS)
Pray with me.
No, no. Talk with me.
What's inside of me?
What is it?
Rachel, just please pray
with me. Please!
- Our father who art in...
- No more praying.
No more lying.
Tell me what you're not, Mom!
(SNARLS) Tell me!
I'm sorry, Mama.
It's okay, baby!
- Rachel!
- I'm gonna miss the bus.
Rachel!
MAN: Hey, kid.
You tell your mother
that screaming keeps us up
all hours of the night,
I'm calling the police again.
You hear me? I don't care
about your emotional issues!
Weirdo.
Boo!
Come on.
What are you hiding from?
You don't have to be
shy with me.
I like freaks.
Leave her alone, Kyle.
Don't you have a touchdown
or something to throw, Matt?
Just leave her alone, asshole.
Before I make you.
Maybe you should take a seat.
Take a seat.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
BOY 1: Knock him out!
DRIVER: Sit back down!
Both of you! Now!
BOY 2: Come on.
It was getting good.
(STUDENTS GRUMBLING)
- BOY: Does it hurt?
- MATT: It doesn't hurt.
Slut.
(STUDENTS LAUGHING)
(SNARLS) Slut!
Uh, Matt. Thanks for...
(SIGHS)
(BUS ENGINE REVVING)
(BUS DOORS CLOSE)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Mom?
Mom, I am really sorry
about this morning.
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Rachel. That's what
she calls you.
But that is not who you are.
Let my mom go.
This woman is not your mother.
Tell her.
- (GRUNTS)
- Tell her!
I am not your mother.
But I do love you.
- No.
- You have good inside your heart, sweetheart.
Don't do...
(SCREAMS)
There. Now, that's better.
(SCREAMING)
(SNARLS)
(PANTING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(DOOR SHUTS)
(BEEPING)
(DOG BARKING IN THE DISTANCE)
(GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES)
(FABRIC RIPPING)
Pink?
The kids love it.
(SWOOSHING)
MAN: What was that?
ROBIN: I'm only here
for Tyler Hackett.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Leave the drugs. Leave the guns.
And walk away.
Where's Batman?
MAN 2:
He could be anywhere, man.
He's up there somewhere.
Look up. Look up.
MAN 3: Oh, where's the Bat?!
Where is he?
Hey.
The little birdie's alone.
- (CHUCKLES)
- (GRUNTS)
- (GRUNTING)
- (SCREAMING)
MAN 2: Get him!
- (ROBIN GRUNTING)
- (GAS HISSING)
(ALL GRUNTING AND COUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
(BONES CRACKING)
(SCREAMS)
- (BONES CRACK)
- (SCREAMS)
(GRUNTING)
MAN 4: Tyler!
Where you going, man?
(YELLS)
- (SCREAMING)
- (GLASS BREAKING)
If you ever touch your kid
again, I will find you.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(SIGHS)
Fuck Batman.
♪♪ You know
♪♪ How it feels
♪♪ Alone
♪♪ Fight for your life
♪♪ Pray for the others
♪♪ To die
♪♪ You're waiting
For the others
♪♪ To die ♪♪
CAPTAIN:
Are you guys sure it's him?
COP: Absolutely, Captain.
WOLF: We called Gotham P.D.
He hasn't been seen
for over a year.
Disappeared, they said.
They thought he might be dead.
Why come here?
Why Detroit?
- The weather?
- (CHUCKLING)
Let's just hope to hell
he's just passing through.
You know the problems that
these masks bring with 'em.
Painted freaks.
Psychopaths in drag.
We don't need that shit.
We got enough of our own regular problems here.
Come on, guys.
Back to work.
I need to talk to you
for a second, Eddie.
Sure, Captain.
WOMAN: Where to?
Detroit. One way, please.
(BEEPING)
♪♪ I'm gonna writhe
and shake my body
♪♪ I'll start pulling out
My hair
♪♪ I'm going to cover myself
With the ashes of you
♪♪ And nobody's gonna
Give a damn
♪♪ Son of a bitch
Give me a drink
♪♪ One more night
This can't be me
(SIREN WAILING)
♪♪ Son of a bitch
If I can't get clean
♪♪ I'm gonna
drink my life away ♪♪
(VOCALIZING)
SALLY: I'll give your
compliments to the chef.
My name is Sally.
I work here.
First, I don't need to know
who you are,
or how you got here, okay?
What I really care about is keeping
girls your age off the streets.
Or out of the adult shelters
which aren't much better.
There's a youth shelter,
a few blocks from here.
They'll have a bed for you.
No questions asked.
Shortcut.
SALLY: I grew up here
in the city.
I've lived here
since I was your age.
(MICE SQUEAKING)
On the streets, too.
Shelters saved my life.
(DISTORTED VOICE)
Lies!
She's lying.
Look behind you.
SALLY: Hey, come on.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
I've been where you are.
You feel like
you can't trust anyone.
(CAR ENGINE HUMMING)
What's wrong, sugar?
I was just gonna
give you a ride.
Come on. It's okay.
Run!
SALLY: Rachel!
Rachel!
Wait!
Stop!
(SIREN WAILS)
POLICE OFFICER:
Let's go, kid.
Hey, uh, any luck
on that Robin thing?
Wait, are you talking to me?
Is everybody else dead?
Because I clearly must be the last
person on Earth for that to happen.
(DOOR OPENS)
I guess I haven't been
the most welcoming.
Hey, Grayson.
You got that
thing for helping kids, right?
Hi, there. How you doing?
Word on the street is you like playing
baseball with bricks and cop cars.
I am Detective Dick Grayson.
You wanna talk about
what happened?
It's you.
- I'm not sure if you...
- You're the boy from the circus.
Please.
Can you help me?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(UPBEAT DISCO MUSIC PLAYING)
(EXHALES)
♪♪ Heaven must be
Missin' an angel
♪♪ Missin' one angel child
♪♪ 'Cause you're here
With me right now
♪♪ Your love is heavenly baby
♪♪ Heavenly to me baby
♪♪ Your kiss
Filled with tenderness
♪♪ I want all I can get
♪♪ Of your sexiness
♪♪ Showers
Your love comes in showers
♪♪ And every hour
on the hour... ♪♪
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GUN FIRING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN)
(WATER RUNNING)
(WATER SHUTS OFF)
Kory Anders.
(BELL TOLLING)
(WOMAN SPEAKS IN GERMAN)
(SPEAKS IN GERMAN)
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(ELEVATOR BEEPS)
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Hello?
(LOUD KNOCKING AT DOOR)
(LOUD KNOCKING CONTINUES)
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
(PANTING HEAVILY)
(SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (BONES CRACK)
- (SCREAMS)
(PANTING)
(WHEEZING)
(COUGHS)
Hmm? Hmm?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(COUGHS)
- (BONE CRACKS)
- (GRUNTS)
Who are you?
Is this some kind of
sick practical joke?
I remember.
People were happy that night.
What the hell is this?
You, most of all.
Your parents...
I watched them fall.
You kept wishing it was a dream.
Wishing you would wake up.
Who put you up to this?
Everything led me here.
To you.
It can't be by accident.
You've got to help me.
I don't know how...
You want help? So you throw
a brick at a cop car?
You don't understand...
- Okay, make me understand.
- Someone killed my mom!
Okay. Name, address.
(SNIFFLES)
She was all I had.
The only person in the world
who cared for me.
I am alone now.
DICK: I want to help you.
(GASPS)
- Listen, I'm gonna check this out, okay?
- Don't leave me here.
Rachel, you vandalized
a police car.
- You're not going anywhere.
- You don't understand.
You need to lock me up.
Please.
There is something inside of me.
Something evil.
I can't give you
the kind of help you need.
I will find someone who can.
Don't leave me here.
Look, I'm sorry.
I really am.
Hey, so, she's saying
her mom was killed.
If you could send someone
down there, that'll be great.
OFFICER JONES: Okay,
I'll call you if anything checks out.
Thanks.
It's probably bullshit though.
Kids down there livin'
on the street stealing...
- REPORTER: The Mayor has...
- They'll say anything to get out of trouble.
...released a warrant demanding the crime
fighting vigilante known as Robin...
Yeah, I know.
...to leave Detroit
immediately.
- Quote. "This is a violent sociopath."
End quote. -(SIRENS WAILING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
AMY: Hey, can I
ask you something?
I'm kind of in the middle
of something.
So, what?
You and your sidekick go bad?
I'm sorry?
Your partner at Gotham P.D.
I mean, I'm no mind reader,
it just seems kinda obvious.
I guess we had different ideas
of how to do the job.
How's that? He on the take?
I heard most of Gotham is.
No, not him.
He was a hero
to a lot of people.
Including me.
A stop-at-nothing guy who solved
everything with his fists.
I admired him at first,
what he did...
Or was trying to do.
But eventually,
I had to walk away.
AMY: Why?
Because I was becoming
too much like him.
So, you're not really, huh?
What?
An asshole.
(CHUCKLES)
Don't tell.
It will kill my rep.
(LAUGHS) Yeah. Well,
your secret's safe with me.
OFFICER: Hey, there.
We're gonna transfer you.
We'll be putting you in
with the other kids.
It will be safer for you there.
It's okay. Bring your bag.
OFFICER: Right this way.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Grayson.
This is Officer Jones.
Traverse City P.D.
- Mm-hmm.
- Girl you called in about, Rachel Roth?
We found her mother. Gunshot to the head.
Looks like a homicide.
I'll have our C.S.I. send you
the details as we get them.
Okay, thanks.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Let me kill him!
Let me kill him now!
(GASPING)
(SYRINGE INJECTS)
(SIGHS)
Detective Grayson. Can I get
a 10-20 on the car number 310?
- (DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
- (CROWD CHATTERING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES OUTSIDE)
KONSTANTIN: My dear...
I was worried for you.
Who are you, exactly?
Who am I?
Who the hell are you?
And who do you work for?
Uh, I don't...
I don't know. I...
(CHUCKLES)
(SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN)
You come here,
you sit at my side,
you sleep in my bed!
I trusted you!
And you turn on me?
You betray me?
Because of this girl?
Who is she?
What do you want with her?
I don't know.
I woke up in a car and these
men were trying to kill me...
(SHUSHING)
(CHUCKLES)
I loved you.
Oh...
(CLICKS TONGUE)
I don't think I loved you too.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure
that's a no.
Wait!
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
(BLOWS AIR)
Rachel Roth.
(CHUCKLES)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
ACOLYTE: You've always known
you were different, haven't you?
That you have a destiny.
Please...
I have been looking for you
for so long.
RACHEL: Let me go.
Nothing resembles itself
tonight.
This dirty room is a church.
I appear the villain
but in truth, I am the savior.
You...
You pose as the innocent,
but deep inside...
You know you're fecund
and damned.
You have the skin of the lamb.
The sheath by which he will
penetrate this world,
and seed its destruction.
But alas, you are the doorway
he would walk through upright
to put out our sun, and I...
Cannot allow that to happen.
I have to save us all.
(DOOR OPENS)
(GRUNTING)
I will lay your heart
beside the heart of a beast.
(SHUDDERING)
And beside the heart
of a simpleton.
(CRYING)
And burn them all.
(WHIMPERING)
And the doorway will be
closed forever.
Don't hurt me!
Rachel!
(SCREAMS) Help! Help!
(SCREAMS)
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
DICK: Rachel!
(GAGS)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
Rachel!
Rachel.
Rachel, open the door!
Rachel! Rachel!
- Rachel! Open the door!
- (SCREAMING)
(GAGS)
(VOMITS)
(SCREAMING)
(COUGHING)
- Rachel!
- (CRYING)
What happened?
I don't know!
(CRYING)
Please help me!
(SOBBING)
(GATE OPENS)
This is yours?
Family heirloom.
From the circus?
Not the one you're thinking.
- Come on, let's go.
- (CAR DOOR OPENS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Where are we going?
Somewhere safe.
My mom
says there's no such thing
as monsters.
I think she was wrong.
(SLURPING)
(VIDEO GAME MUSIC PLAYING)
(THUDDING)
(CLANGING)
(NOISES CONTINUE)
(GROWLS)
(ROARS)
(FIRES)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Okay.
(GROWLING SOFTLY)
(GROWLS)
(BONES CRACKING)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
Rad.