[Music]
I'm Carl azuz for CNN 10 where we
explain events happening around the
world thank you for watching on this
second Friday of 2018 a series of
disasters has devastated parts of
Southern California the largest wildfire
in state history flared up in early
December it was named the Thomas fire
because it started near Thomas Aquinas
College it's burned more than 280 1000
acres and it's still not completely
contained or blocked off officials
expect that to happen later this month
but its effects led to another problem
the Thomas fire burned off trees brush
and bushes in the area and when a storm
struck earlier this week dumping rain on
charred hillsides there wasn't enough
living vegetation to help keep mud
boulders and dead trees from flowing
downhill debris covered roads and
swamped buildings mudslides and flooding
destroyed 65 homes and damaged more than
460 others and at least 17 people were
killed though several others are still
missing the rain has stopped and
hundreds of first responders are working
through the debris field searching for
survivors deadly mudslides have struck
this area before its unique landscape
has contributed to both its beauty and
its potential threat from disaster The
Sun has come up and is exposing the
vastness of the devastation look at this
house behind me not only a debris field
of enormity with trees and parts of
other houses and so much other but it
looks like the front windows were blown
straight out of the house because in
some of these instances we had ruptured
gas lines and then looking just over to
the left this house cars sealed off
debris everywhere
trees poles all of that Montecito is
unique in that it goes from about 3,000
feet to sea level in just a few miles
and running up to these first rains they
had warned that this area that is the
Thomas fire burn area so vast the
largest brush fire acreage was in
California history they had feared that
they could get a big slide they had so
much rain here at one point
nearby Carpinteria in just one hour an
inch of rain and once those loose
hillsides were hit by this pinwheeling
storm the ashy mud just came flowing
down jumped over a creek you see yet
another home devastated and it came
right down a main road here there are
people who have been cut off by this
huge boulders trees power lines there in
the Romero Canyon neighborhood just a
little north east of me we saw heist
rescues as they call them yesterday
that's when they literally get the
helicopter and pull people out by
helicopter the US Congress is moving
closer to renewing a controversial law
that allows the government to collect
information about people in other
countries who aren't US citizens this is
part of something called FISA the
Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act
which dates back to 1978
a component of FISA passed more recently
in 2008 lets US intelligence officials
gather email and text messages of
foreigners without a warrant but because
the information of American citizens can
also be caught up in this intelligence
gathering some privacy advocates oppose
the law while its supporters say it's
necessary to keep Americans safe these
divisions aren't strictly along party
lines most Republicans including
President Donald Trump support
reauthorizing the law but dozens don't
most Democrats don't want to reauthorize
the law but dozens do we say reauthorize
because this part of FISA is set to
expire on January 19th unless Congress
renews it and lawmakers move to step
closer to doing that yesterday when the
House of Representatives voted 256 to
164 to renew the law the House votes
considered a victory for the Trump
administration even though the president
appeared to criticize the FISA law on
Thursday morning he tweeted that it
might have been used to inappropriately
collect information on his presidential
campaign later in the morning President
Trump tweeted his support for the law
saying the vote was about quote foreign
surveillance of foreign bad guys on
foreign land
and that the u.s. needed it critics said
the tweets caused confusion on Capitol
Hill the White House denied that saying
President Trump supports the law and was
happy to see it passed in the house now
it goes to the Senate for its
consideration where again support and
opposition is not divided straight down
party lines
ten-second trivia which of these search
engines was founded first Yahoo Google
Bing or Ask Jeeves
Yahoo dates back to 1994 which makes it
the oldest internet search engine on
this list what was the name of
Napoleon's most famous horse what does
it mean when you dream you're being
chased by an elephant is there a book on
how to build with popsicle sticks search
engines could help you find these
answers but in their current form
they've only been around since the mid
1990s the New York Public Library has
been open since 1911 and if you don't
feel like searching through its
collection you can always give him a
phone call for a news reporter in the
field being on the air live with animals
can be a bit unpredictable case in point
Alex Dunlop a reporter from the British
Broadcasting Corporation recently
learned what it was like to be swarmed
by lemurs thankfully he was at a zoo but
these things can still be pretty wild
Dunlop was trying to report on an animal
count he probably wasn't counting on the
highly social animals to be quite so
highly social wonder if he thought to
tell them Lemur alone your lemur 'king
this too difficult I'm a professional
you're only prosimians and we'll never
be primates unless you stop being an
arboreal pain oh yeah
lemur puns it's like they grow on trees
I'm Carl azuz and we'll see you next
Tuesday after the Martin Luther King jr.
holiday have a great weekend
[Music]
when we are here with Martha
the texts are sometimes it our planning
with the patient is Kerry Wood
[Music]
what I can we start I couldn't speak the
language I'm bad weather as well and
then rejection was a nightmare
[Music]
hola Matt they annuity and Angelina's
Mazel Tov and Jameis Winston gray and
Granderson Amana fear the Kulu ahead to
McCain you've been hounding Apollo ahead
you gain mastery from a beautiful
afternoon shoulda never certain routes
where the rock of more hydrophobic named
Ron Allen on foreign soil mousqueton
below but it then
[Music]
but when mr. Brannon proposed them Habra
sorry team Panetta me and they will
evolve and their dynamometer have 11 of
sir when sitting senator Hackbarth
Lesnar going to levitate off the water
with a p-channel Isis ferocity radula
diathermic we're Italian
[Music]