A partial shutdown in the U.S. government.
That’s what officially started on Friday
night, and was still going when we
produced this show.
That’s first today on CNN 10.
Congress and the president have to agree on
funding for the U.S. government for all of
its offices to stay open.
They haven’t.
Their latest deadline
to do this was Friday night.
And though the House of Representatives passed
a measure last week to keep the government
funded temporarily, that
measure failed in the Senate, and Democrats
and Republicans spent the weekend blaming
each other for the roadblock.
Republicans control both chambers of Congress
and the White House.
So, Democrats believe voters will blame Republicans
for the shutdown.
But the Republican majority in the Senate
is slim.
They hold 51 seats to the Democrats’ 49,
and Republicans believe Democrats will be
blamed because
they filibuster.
They moved against legislation that would
have kept the government open, and there weren’t
enough votes in the Senate to overcome
the filibuster.
So, why did Democrats filibuster?
Before they approve the budget, they want
an agreement to be reached on what happens
to 700,000 people who came
or were brought to the U.S. illegally as children.
Republicans don’t want to negotiate on that
until enough Democrats vote to reopen the
government
first.
So, yesterday afternoon, both sides were dug
in.
Most Americans are not directly affected by
a government shutdown, but those who are face
some uncertainty.
(BEGIN VIDEOTAPE)
TOM FOREMAN, CNN CORRESPONDENT (voice-over):
Roughly 1.9 million government workers would
be considered essential and stay on the job.
Air traffic controllers, security officers,
food inspectors, prison guards, Social Security
checks would go out.
The post office would be open.
But
at a steep price to many workers.
MICK MULVANEY, DIRECTOR, OFFICE OF MANAGEMENT
AND BUDGET: The military will still go to
work.
They will not get paid, OK?
The border will still
be patrolled.
They will not get paid.
FOREMAN: Meanwhile many services would be
stopped or delayed.
The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention
would back down its flu tracking program
even as the nation faces the worst outbreak
in years.
Some senior nutrition programs would be paused.
Two hundred thousand passport
applications went unprocessed in 1995.
Congress funds much of the scientific research
done in this country.
In 2013, that meant some
experiments went on hold and suffered costly
losses of data.
And in space same year, that same year, for
more than two weeks, NASA reportedly stopped
monitoring potentially dangerous asteroids.
A big one,
by the way, is expected to brush by Earth
on February 4th.
(END VIDEOTAPE)
AZUZ: Activists and protesters, Hollywood
stars and politicians turned out in cities
worldwide over the weekend for what’s called
the Women’s March.
The first one also a massive event, was held
a year ago, on the weekend when U.S. President
Donald Trump was inaugurated.
And many of this year’s
demonstrators, like those in the first women’s
march protested against the election and the
policies of the U.S. leader.
President Trump tweeted that people should
march to celebrate America’s economic success
over the past year, and the lowest female
unemployment in
18 years.
Other issues of the march included sexual
harassment.
Recently, there’s been a wave of acquisitions
against politicians, entertainers and members
of the media.
Religious freedom, immigration, women’s
rights and equality were also addressed by
hundreds of thousand of men, women and children
who
marched in America.
(BEGIN VIDEO CLIP)
AZUZ (voice-over): Ten-second trivia.
Most cars on the road today have what level
of autonomous technology?
None, partial, conditional, or high automation?
The vast majority of today’s cars are still
at level zero, meaning they have no automation
and that the driver is in ultimate control
at all times.
(END VIDEO CLIP)
AZUZ: And that’s even if they have blind
spot monitoring or emergency breaking systems.
The manufacturers are moving toward making
cars with more autonomy.
And one big argument for that safety.
The U.S. government estimates that 94
percent of deadly car crashes are because
of human error and that driverless cars could
significantly reduce that.
But what if they’re
hacked?
(BEGIN VIDEOTAPE)
REPORTER: We all carry computers in our pockets,
and every day machines like thermostats, refrigerator,
cameras, and even our cars are connected
online.
Experts call this constant connection the
Internet of things.
And just like everything else, it’s susceptible
to security breaches.
The two big
questions that I have: could autonomous vehicles
be hacked to hurt us?
And how can we be sure that the personal data
that we produce in these cars are
protected?
The answers are still not perfectly clear.
BRUCE SCHNEIER, CYBER-SECURITY EXPERT: The
Internet of things is going to have enormous
benefits that I think we can’t even begin
to realize -- the
power of computerizing and networking our
environment.
But there are risks also.
Here we are creating an Internet that senses
things and acts.
What we know about computers and software
is that they
have bugs, they have vulnerabilities.
All computer systems can be hacked.
So, you can easily imagine these attacks being
used against cars to cause
the car computer systems to crash, or cars
being used as the attack vector.
So, as we build autonomous systems that affect
the world, in a direct physical manner we
risk bad actors doing it.
We risk glitches and errors,
causing physical harm.
REPORTER: Using cars as weapons is unfortunately
already a tactic used around the world.
The good news is that perhaps far into the
future,
properly functioning autonomous cars won’t
allow humans to hit people.
It could neutralize this tactic of terrorism.
But if the cars can be
controlled remotely or hacked and programmed
to cause harm, it could bring on a whole new
set of issues.
To see what’s being done to make these systems
more secure, I visited a company that actually
started out in the video game industry.
Nvidia now
also makes the graphic processing chips that
go into driverless cars.
DANNY SHAPIRO, SENIOR DIRECTOR OF AUTOMOTIVE
AT NVIDIA: We’ve developed an artificial
intelligent brain for the car.
REPORTER: And how they build those chips will
have major impacts on the safety of future
driverless cars.
SHAPIRO: What we’re building is a computer
first and then a car is built around it.
We’re essentially building a map of the
world in real time
based on what we sense.
We had cameras, ultrasonic sensors, radars,
Lidar, which is a laser scanner, and each
of those sensors are generating a
massive amount of data.
REPORTER: Data collection is crucial for allowing
these cars to function.
But like security, it also raises questions
about how the information
gathered from our personal lives will be used.
The new technology has the attention of privacy
advocates like Lauren Smith at the Future
of Privacy
Forum in Washington, D.C., a group that explores
issues with all sorts of home gadgets, like
Amazon Echo’s Alexa system, drones, even
smart dolls.
LAUREN SMITH, FUTURE OF PRIVACY FORUM: Alexa,
are you spying on me?
AMAZON ECHO’S ALEXA SYSTEM: I only send
audio back to Amazon when I hear you say wake
word.
REPORTER: And now, autonomous cars.
SMITH: It’s important that people start
to think about their cars in the same way
that they think about their computer or smartphone.
So, if you
use a technology like this that relies on
connectivity, that relies on data inputs and
outputs, you are creating sort of an information
trail.
SCHNEIER: Data has good and bad uses.
There are some very powerful reasons to collect
data about us and our society and put it together
so we
can do research, we can data-deliver services.
Smart government is the wave of the future.
But the same data can be used for surveillance,
for
control.
I don’t really think any government is prepared
for the Internet of things and what it’s
going to do.
These are computers that affect the world
in direct physical manner.
And there are risks to life and property.
Largely, Western governments have taken a
very hands-off view to regulation of Internet.
The United States is special.
And that worked great when it
didn’t matter, when it was data, when it
was a spreadsheet, when it was conversation.
But when it’s a car and it’s a medical
device, when it’s an
appliance, when it can actually do physical
harm, that changes everything.
(END VIDEOTAPE)
AZUZ: OK.
So, let’s pretend a freezer malfunctions
and continues making ice long after the tray
is full.
That might look a bit like what happened
recently in Ohio, except that in this case,
the freezer was the Arctic and the tray was
Lake Erie.
Ice shoves or ice tsunamis formed when winds
blow ice across the lake and into its shores
where it files and forms mountains of ice.
Some hills here
grew to be more than 30 feet high.
If they’re not fans of "Frozen", the locals
better hope it stops or Elsa.
Sure, some fans may find it Arendelightful
but it’s hard to conceal don’t
feel when a lake shore crystallizes like an
icy blast, potentially causing an Olaf of
problems.
Unless, of course, the cold doesn’t bother
you
anyway.
I’m Carl Azuz for CNN 10.