The Story of Ming Lan
Episode 43
Wife,I will take off my clothes.
Look at this long and straight leg of mine.
Stop looking at it.
You can't finish reading today.
Just continue tomorrow.
There are a lot of spies from  the marquis
manor.How can I not be  nervous?
Danju said that a new maidservant today
wanted to enter your inner study to attend
to you, but got scolded away by her.
And this Nanny Lai isn't
that easy to deal with.
When she was not doing
anything, she would go around
the garden and would
enter any door she sees,
would pull any people she
sees and ask around.
I can't really stuff her
mouth to shut her up, right?
It's better to drive her
away as soon as possible.
How come you can't just stuff
her mouth and make her leave?
I'll tell Shitou to lock
that old woman up tomorrow.
Aren't you oppressing the old and weak?
If that gets out, do you still
want you reputation or not?
How about when I go to court tomorrow,
I'll leave some guards here.
In the places that you
think are very important,
I'll leave two people holding
blades to guard there.
Let's see who still dares
to randomly touch things.
Looks like that Big Madam Qin is attacking
me from two angles at the same time.
Sending me some old crafty servants
to add to my trouble on one hand,
and then simultaneously sending
some beautiful ones to
seduce you. She really gave
a lot of thought in this.
Beautiful?
How beautiful?
Of course, they are indeed quite pretty.
How about...tomorrow...
...I'll let them attend to us when we
eat and you'll be able to see them.
I'm just joking with you, but look at you.
You got serious with it.
Either way, you're
going to take in a
concubine in the future,
and I'm not jealous.
I'm just worried that those
people are inappropriate.
Why are you not jealous?
Even that stepmother of mine, who can
really pretend and endure things,
would still argue with my
father about such things.
Why are you not jealous?
That jealous of hers
must be pretentious too!
In my house, there's this
Little Mother Lin of mine.
When she gets jealous,
it's really so colorful.
Isn't it all just to make their
husband think that in their heart,
he is so precious and important?
You little fox! Can't you even pretend?
If you dare take in a concubine,
I'll hit you with a huge
pole and drive you out!
I'll never allow you to enter my room.
Okay! Okay!
That's how my good wife should be!
Being jealous is good!
Come. Come. Let me read that for you.
I...let me help you! Let me help you!
Come...
Thank you, Sister.
- So heavy?
- With such a small box,
this is really heavy.
Is this filled with  gold and silver?
Not only that. There are a
lot of precious gems too.
Outside, there are carts
and carts of fabrics.
We have to transport each one of them
to the stockroom of the inner house.
I will surely be busy this whole day.
With so many good objects,
where did they come from?
Is it Big Madam's dowry?
- Still not done moving them?
- You must be joking.
How is that possible? These are all
gifts given by other people to General.
Not only these, there are still a lot
of outside falling in line and waiting.
They've been placed in a corner.
So many things waiting for us.
Big Madam just accepted all of them?
Maybe so. With so many good items being
delivered right in front of her,
will she still refuse them? Is she dumb?
Sister, hurry up!
Coming! Coming!
Have you settled down the people
sent by the marquis manor?
More or less. I've given
them unimportant tasks.
For the important areas, I've
placed people that I can trust.
Later, I'll tell Eldest Sister
to find me some new ones.
New servants have no foundation.
They will naturally follow my every order.
They won't work for the marquis manor.
Based on my temper, I'll just drive
them all back to the marquis manor.
Just blame it on me that I
hate all those old servants.
My husband, you're just temporarily dealing
with the problem to avert a crisis,
and not completely solving it.
To send them back to the marquis manor
without allowing your aunties and
stepmother to say any criticisms,
you can't use force.
Some people in the imperial
court might report
you as not cultivating
private morality,
and being disrespectful to your elders.
Aren't you satisfied yet with how
you got taken advantage of before?
My wife...
You've become a military
adviser that schemes
while inside the
comfort of your tent.
Stop being talkative.
Okay.
It's okay now.
Okay already. Quickly go.
Take this!
Do you still need me to guard you?
No need. Quickly go.
I'm going.
A palanquin from the marquis manor?
Big Madam Qin has come?
She most likely is bearing evil intentions.
You few, come over here.
Go to the drill area and
inform generals Geng and Duan
that I have some matters in my house and
will be delayed. I'll arrive an hour later.
Yes!
Young Master.
Later, I'll be waiting in
the outer courtyard study.
Don't be loud about it and just
guard in the inner courtyard.
Once Big Madam is unable
to handle it, immediately
tell me and I'll help her
out of the situation.
Okay, Young Master. Let's go.
Greetings, Mother-in-law.
I should be the one
going to the marquis
manor to greet you.
I was too busy moving and
cleaning up these past days.
Mother-in-law, hope you won't mind.
I know that you were busy moving, so
I didn't come for the past few days.
Are the young and old servants
that I've sent you useful?
You are considerate of me, so of course,
you'll choose the most able people.
I thank you for it.
If they are honest and capable,
how come you're still not giving
tasks to Nanny Lai and Nanny Diao?
Could it be because they are old,
so you think they aren't
nimble in doing their tasks?
No such thing.
Nanny Diao has a sickly body. I was
afraid that she'll tire herself out.
Nanny Lai is a well-experienced servant.
I'm thinking that I should give her an
important and honorable job, right?
So I kept weighing things
and still unable to decide.
Since you seem to know
what to do, I'm at ease.
Or else, if other find out, they
might think that I'm a miser.
That what I gave you are old,
weak, and disabled servants.
Mother-in-law, you've always
had a virtuous reputation.
Who in Bianjing City doesn't know that
you have a Bodhisattva-like heart?
Even if anyone will say such
words, no one will believe them.
The reputation of a widow
isn't really that important.
What's important is the
reputation of our Gu Family.
If you lack anything, just
send people to get it from me.
Why must you privately accept gifts
and hide it from your husband?
What are you saying? No such things.
You still want to hide
it from me, is that it?
Since Ye got promoted, people
didn't stop from sending him gifts.
You didn't inquire about them
and just accepted them all.
If His Majesty asks about this,
won't it be your husband and our
Gu Family bearing the brunt?
Although the imposing bearing
of our marquis manor
isn't as great as before,
our reputation has always been clean.
Must it get destroyed
in your hands?
I...really didn't accept any gifts.
General said that the current imperial
court situation isn't that stable.
If I don't accept all of them,
that's being enemies with everyone.
If I nitpick and accept only a few,
that's forming alliances or parties.
It's better to just accept them all,
but not open them. He'll just
inform His Majesty about it.
The items would be placed in the
stock room of the courtyard
and submitted to His Majesty as it is.
This Ye has really grown up.
He actually is this scheming and shrewd.
If I didn't know, I would have thought that
he was just pretending in the past.
Mother-in-law, you mustn't praise him.
If he's really shrewd, he wouldn't have
wandered outside for so many years,
unable to pass the civil examination.
He had to rely on
himself to achieve merit
through his sword and spear.
It's really hard for my husband
to achieve what he has now.
Although as his wife,
I'm indeed a bit dumb,
I do understand the principle of
husband and wife being united,
of sharing blessings and going
through hardships together.
I just say a statement,
and you have ten waiting for me.
Young Master!
- How are things?
- Don't worry. She has left.
- She has left?
- She has left.
- She didn't cause any trouble?
- She didn't.
It's very quiet in the inner courtyard. I
especially hid behind a tree to watch them.
That lady from the marquis
manor has a face that was this
long when she left. It's
almost touching the ground.
My stepmother has finally met her match.
My previous act of directly
punching my fist on them
is really not as good as
employing a soft nail tactic.
- Let's go to the drill field.
- Let's go.
What are you laughing about?
Young Master, your face earlier
really looked like a hen
protecting her chicks.
Get lost!
Don't let me use a small cup.
Quickly change it to a huge bowl.
Miss, Big Madam, that is too inappropriate.
I'll just pour you more.
What's wrong with Big Madam?
That old...thing, Nanny Lai,
kept leisurely touring our
manor and asking people
around, and then she'll report
it to the marquis manor.
Or else, how could she have come this fast?
What can we do?
I can't really tie her up, right? Moreover,
without her, there are still other
young and old maidservants.
All those sent by the marquis
manor are their spies.
I can't really kick all of them out, right?
That Nanny Lai even likes to pretend
to be a good person. Always
dragging a group of old maidservants
for drinks and gambling.
In just a few days, they are
already so close with each other.
Everyone is saying that she's very
generous and straightforward.
They all they her everything.
She has worked in the
marquis manor for decades.
For her to be like that
means she does have skills.
My mother-in-law of mine
is also not stupid.
How could she send
over a useless person?
Since she's here, then
she's a thorny porcupine.
You can't hit, scold,
or drive her away.
Never thought that despite
moving out of the
marquis manor, it will
still be this stuff.
So annoying.
Xiaotao is getting agitated.
Be careful of choking. Big Madam,
there are still a lot of pear soup.
Oh, right. There's still
a pile of books over
there. Big Madam, please
take a look at them too.
Cuiwei,
I really feel that it's better to
just be a miss at Shouan Hall.
My good Miss, good Big Madam,
you now holds great power. The
whole Bianjing are envious of you.
Let's go. Let's go. Quickly go read them.
This manor is so huge.
Just the garden, you won't be
able to completely stroll it
in half a day. Asking just
a few of us to clean it,
is really asking for our life.
Big Madam said
that she's going to pick some reliable
ones. But it's already been half a day
and there are still no one coming.
Could it be that the manor has
not enough money for expenses,
hence, she couldn't buy
any servant anymore?
She can only talk.
Say, among the people here in this manor,
who doesn't have siblings
or nephews and nieces
at home?
Call all those who are not doing anything
to come here for work.
Pick some smart and nimble ones to hire.
Won't that be more reliable than
- those bought from outside? Am I right?
- Right...
It's really better to work
in the marquis manor.
Big Madam is a goddess, a Bodhisattva.
She also doesn't have so many weird rules.
Those that work in the garden are not
allowed to enter the front courtyard,
not allowed to casually move around.
Prisoners sentenced to die might be
having a more relaxed life than us.
You better lower down your voice.
That Big Madam of ours
can really hold grudges.
I just refuted her a few times
when we met her a few days ago.
She immediately punished my daughter.
She had all those first
level female servants
attending to Young
Master plant trees.
Not placing any people in
the room of the Master
isn't the doing of a wife of
a great aristocratic family.
She probably is afraid that if Master
sees how beautiful your daughter is,
he might realize how she pales
in comparison to your daughter.
Indeed.
I can't be sure about that.
But, at the bottom of it all,
she did come from a family of officials.
Although she's an illegitimate daughter,
she shouldn't be this jealous, right?
What are you all saying?!
Are you people even worthy
to be seen by our Master?
Are you even worthy to
gossip about Big Madam?
Dirty shrews. If you get put
together, expelled out, and threw
in the snow, even beggars won't
take a second look at you.
What did I say? Miss Xiaotao,
don't you falsely accuse me.
So, you're the master of this house now?
You can just hire anyone that you like
or let anyone you want to
serve in front of the Master?
If you're that capable, why
still order your daughter?
Why don't you go out, walk around, and in
passing, find yourself a man to marry?
Say, miss, why are you so
rude and unreasonable?
At the very least, I'm old
enough to be your ancestor.
I just made a few jokes
while tending the ground.
How did that offend you?
Exactly. Miss, you might
have heard it wrong.
We didn't say anything.
Don't use this trick to fool me.
If I hear it again, I don't
need to inform Big Madam
and will just get a pole
to drive you all out.
She wouldn't be going to Big
Madam and tell on us, right?
So what? Can that Big Madam
hit us with thorny planks?
Won't she has become being harsh on old
servants and disrespectful to her elders?
As a servant, we shouldn't lower ourselves
and just let our master deal with us
in whatever way she wants, right?
Won't we have become
like pigs or dogs then?
If we don't want to get
bullied, we must stick together
and be like a rope, stay
united and work together.
Only then can we make a
footing in this manor.
That's right. From now on,
we'll listen to you then.
We'll listen to you from now on.
Yesterday, it was the
birthday of Duke Ying of the
State. Rulan and I accompanied
mother to greet him.
You were the most talked about topic there.
They say that you don't
give any importance to your
elders and is unfilial to
your legitimate mother.
Big Madam Qin has a hard
life for being a widow,
yet was able to maintain
such a good temper.
They said that you were late in greeting
them on the first day after your wedding.
That there is clearly a
legitimate mother yet, but
you have to move out and
set up your own manor.
They are all saying that you're heartless.
What else?
There's still a lot. They even said that
you two are being harsh on your servants.
Just willfully hitting and
scolding old servants.
Not putting any importance on the people
that your elders have arranged for you.
That is equivalent to being
supercilious and unfilil to elders.
There are still a lot of bad ones.
I don't want to say them anymore.
When mother and Rulan heard
them, they were really
mad, but they couldn't
really openly argue.
They were so angry that
they left without eating.
It's all my fault?
Doesn't that Big Madam Qin
not have any fault at all?
Of course!
How come everything you said were about me?
Is my husband a perfect person?
Must you two get criticized together
before you will stop?
It's all him who dragged me
into this muddled water.
It shouldn't only be me who
gets talked on, right?
The criticisms about your husband
are still those same words.
Things like being disobedient since he
was a child, a frequenter of brothels,
the god of death in front
of a mountain of corpses.
Those are nothing. Aren't
there anything else?
This Yunhui General of yours saved the
past emperor and the current emperor.
Two imperial decrees have
said that he is loyal
to the emperor, considerate
to the empire,
virtuous, filial, lofty, and unsullied.
Who still dares to say more?
He indeed got himself a protective armor.
This is already great for him.
Or else, don't
know what else those
people could have said.
I was never invited in those banquets.
I've never been this coldly treated even
when I was just a Miss in our house.
The ways of your mother-in-law is
way better than those in our house.
No wonder grandmother initially
wouldn't agree to marry you to here.
It was clearly her who spread the news.
She then had to put out
a being bullied facade.
My husband and I can't really go explain
that to each and every person, right?
Even if we do, no one will believe us.
Sixth, this can't do.
Since I've walked this path,
there's no use no matter how I hated it.
I can't really stop walking it, right?
Even if I don't want to walk, someone
would be pushing me to walk.
Since that's the case, why
not just walk smilingly?
Either way, I'll be walking it forever.
The task of purchasing for the kitchen
is not a job that one can be sloppy at.
Nanny Lai, you are a
well-experienced servant.
You also are doing this
back in the marquis manor.
I'll entrust you this task then.
I surely will do my best!
Nanny Diao, you are sickly, so I
won't give you any more task.
Nanny Hua and Nanny Tian used
to be in-charge of clothes
washing and cleaning of the manor
back in the marquis manor.
We'll do the same here. Since
you are well-experienced
in these tasks, I'm at
ease to hand them to you.
Yes. Yes.
I've already written what job
everyone else will be having.
Cuiwei will be reading them to you later.
And then, everyone, just
follow the task you were given
to get your badge and keys.
I'm young, so my arrangements
may not be that adequate.
Let's just test it for a year.
If you really can't do
it or if there are any
improper assignments,
just go exchange work
or come tell me about it.
Yes.
I've woken early today
and feel a bit tired.
I'll go back and rest now.
You all just go busy with your work.
Okay. Okay.
Let's go. Go.
See that? She's still indeed young.
After being imposing for three days,
she still couldn't continue with it.
So ingenuous.
She only know to eat and sleep.
Easy to deal with.
Aren't you quite happy?
Go. Go. Let's go get our keys.
Go now.
[ Jiaxi Lodge ]
This rain is falling as
if the sky is falling.
Good thing you instructed people to
take the clothes inside this afternoon.
You indeed can predict things well.
I feel that what you said is very right.
Wrong. You should say that
I've lectured you well.
It's all thanks to Big Madam
for teaching me well.
It's all because you have
incredible foresight.
Correct.
I feel that what you said is very right.
Did you predict then that your husband
will get drenched in the rain?
Quickly enter the room.
I've predicted that it would rain
and instructed someone to deliver
you an umbrella. How come...
I rode a horse to attend the
imperial court meeting.
It would be better if you have
just given me a veiled hat.
Why don't you...just ride a carriage
to the palace next time?
Next time, I'll ride a
carriage to fetch you.
I surely won't let you get wet.
Am I angry about that?!
What then?
Forget it.
I'll just patiently wait.
Wait for what?
Wait until you know how to treat
your husband during a rainy day.
A horse carriage still won't do?
Is it because you recently heard
the public discussions about us
that's why, you're a bit upset?
During the birthday of the wife
of Duke Ying of the State,
she invited all illustrious
families in the capital, except us.
She not only didn't invite us,
other than his son-in-law State Uncle Shen,
Little Duan, Old Geng, and all the
others from Yuzhou were not invited too.
You're just going to watch?
He's an old official that
has served three emperors.
Duke Ying of the state and his wife have
very strong personalities, are very
strict in managing their household, and
give too much importance to etiquette.
I had a very bad reputation before,
and is now just a newly favored officer.
An old man like that will never
give men any importance.
I'm just afraid that three
people can turn a gossip into a
tiger. That the more people
doing it can destroy a bone.
No matter how heroic and valiant you are,
if the whole world say
that you are a scoundrel,
as days go by, the whole world
will start to believe it.
Didn't you exactly suffer
because of such trick before?
I'm a scoundrel.
Wife is seeking justice for me?
As a married couple, we are of one body.
Either one
getting glory or destruction
will affect both.
Of course, I must think for your sake.
No need.
I've survived a mountain of
blades and a sea of fire.
Would I still mind these these things?
Are you mad again?
Anyway, you can't run away.
The days are long.
It's broad daylight!
Let's eat together later for dinner.
Dinner later!
He's such a ruffian.
So moody.
One moment, so happy.
One moment, getting mad
for no reason at all.
Even Buddha isn't this hard to attend to.
Have you ironed the clothes?
Who do you think you are?!
I've eaten more salt than
the rice you've eaten!
Is it your turn to meddle in this matter?
You are using your age to take advantage of
us, assigning good tasks to your relatives
and earning kickbacks from it.
And you won't even let people talk? Don't
think that we don't know about it!
Since that's the case, go report me then.
Go! The courtyard of Big Madam is just that
way, as if you don't know the direction.
Go and report on me! Go!
Isn't it because you know that
Big Madam has a good temper,
- So what?
- and that you're from the marquis manor,
so no one can touch you, right? But
don't bully people so intolerably!
These two maidservants are
young and inexperienced.
When things have gone missing,
you just blame it on them.
You're already this old, yet
you still bully a child!
Do you have an conscience?!
These two little kids
clearly have dirty hands.
You are still defending them?
You must be their accomplice.
If I've taken any money
improperly from this manor,
I would then have a tragic death.
There's no use for you to make oaths here.
Let me tell you that the kitchen
purchasing is under my jurisdiction.
I'm also in-charge of the items there.
I can investigate whoever I want.
It's none of your business.
- You...
- What?
You stinky woman!
- You bitch! You say is to beautifully!
- What?!
Each of you are...
That Nanny Lai was still pretentious
before in being so just.
Seeing how everyone can't dare
turn hostile against her,
she started to be imposing.
My guess was right.
No matter how sly a fox is, it will
show its tail sooner or later.
The one fighting with her earlier
is the wife of Wang Wu, right?
In the whole Cheng Garden now, only she
can dare to argue with Nanny Lai.
She's also a very straightforward person.
Big Madam, you have to intervene.
If you still don't, that
straightforward person
will soon get pushed aside
to having no way out.
I'm intervening, but the
right time hasn't come yet.
After lunch, tell that Wang Wu...
- Tell that Wang Wu's wife to come to me.
- Yes.
[ Jiaxi Lodge ]
What task do you do?
Replying to Big Madam, just some manual
labor. Once I'm not doing anything anymore,
I'll go help the gardeners water
the flowers and plow the soil.
I can see the plants in the
garden growing quite well.
It was also very clean.
You are really capable.
I'm a crude person and is
very straightforward. I
only know to do tasks that
requires manual strength.
I dare not be described as being capable.
The eastern side of the garden is quite
barren, hence, not pleasing to the eyes.
I feel that we are lacking
people who can plant.
I can see that you are knowledgeable
in this and is quite an honest person.
I'll leave this matter to you then.
Big Madam, are you serious?
Of course, I am.
What? You're not willing?
No. No.
It's just that planting will
require a lot of expenses.
I...only know to do the manual labor
and has never did such an important task.
I..fear that I might not do it well.
You haven't done it, so how do you
know that you can't do it well?
I fear that I don't know the market.
If I buy too expensive ones,
that's additional expenses.
If I buy poor quality ones, I will
cause our manor to lose face.
As long as you set your
thoughts in an upright manner,
it's fine even if you aren't
able to do this task well.
Whoever dares to criticize you
and not listen to your orders
will not be lightly spared by me.
Since Big Madam is willing to trust me,
I'll surely give it my best
to fulfill this task beautifully!
As long as you remember two things. First,
do this task well and don't
let anyone find any flaws.
Second, Nanny Lai is a well-experienced
servant of the marquis manor.
She has such good temper
and is very amicable.
You must respect her.
Of course, Nanny Lai must be respected.
I understand. I understand everything.
Okay. You go now.
Yes.
Miss, did you deliberately let
everyone outside hear that?
This early morning, that Wang Wu's
wife and Nanny Lai had a fight.
This afternoon, I immediately
granted her a fat task.
Everyone can surely guess where
the wind is blowing, right?
Hope she did understand what you mean.
Big Madam, father said
that it's fine if you can't write well.
You just need to practice more.
Who said that my words are bad?
I just wrote the wrong stroke earlier.
Your stroke isn't wrong. I saw it.
Good child, let's just
continue writing tomorrow.
Let's just read some books for a while.
This...I've already
finished reading that book.
I can recite all of it.
You...at such a young age,
how come you know so many words?
You also know to read poems?
When I used to live on the boat,
my father would have me
memorize a poem every day.
Later on, I went to Second
Aunt-in-law's home academy too.
Who is Second Aunt-in-law?
Sheng House's second aunt-in-law. Aunt Hai.
You don't even know that?
My brother and sister-in-law
left me with no gap.
They've taught you everything and
I've got nothing left to teach you.
Big Madam, I want to play polo.
I can teach you that!
But, but not yet since
you're still too young.
You can't ride the horse.
Let's wait a couple more years
and I'll surely to teach you.
We can learn to fish first.
We can still ride a small horse first.
Look at your look!
Looks like you've made
up your mind already.
Fine. I'll have your father
buy you a small horse then.
We learn to fish first though.
You can learn that, right?
Yes, I will hook a carp
and make chopped fish.
- Take it slow, Nanny Chang.
- Big Madam.
Big Madam.
The miss and you are so fated.
Our Miss Rong still lacks
skills about lady's crafts.
We have to coax her three
days to embroider once.
She holds a needle and says she's
sleepy just at one incense burn.
She's not as steady as Miss Xian next door.
It's alright.
When she's older, she'll be more steady.
When I was little, I was
much more playful than her.
Just that my house wasn't too peaceful,
so I forced myself to be more rule-bound.
But look how great now.
This whole room is full of our own
and she can fuss if she wants.
She keeps playing with Sister Xian
and she'll pick up naturally.
My sister-in-law Shao next
door is so amiable too.
Our grown up matters
aren't the kids' issues.
Actually, Miss Rong is lucky.
My young master is always
worried about Chang.
Big Madam, may you not be offended.
That's his only heartache.
Why would I find offense?
This is how a father should behave.
If I could have had a father
like him when I was young,
many sufferings would have been spared.
You are so understanding, Big Madam.
My young master is so lucky
that he married you.
I also hope everyday that
he can find Chang sooner.
And our courtyard will be
that much more bustling.
Who said I stole?
I thought these were just useless branches.
So I was cleaning them up
to throw them away outside.
You are always bluffing about how you're
a seasoned elder from the marquis manor.
That you've managed everything
before and you know it all.
But you can't even recognize tree roots?
You are seriously! You're trying
to fool us as if we're idiots?
This is a noble specie
transported in from Jiangnan.
Each stem costs a strand of money.
You're trying to take
it to sell it outside!
Which one of your eyes saw me steal?
Let me tell you. Even if you report to
the big madam, I won't acknowledge it.
You think you are worth
something before Big Madam?
She's a lady of a noble house and
she doesn't stoop to your level.
But you turn around and
think you're so mighty!
Mother Lai, there's God three
inches on top of your head.
Stop committing so many evil
deeds or karma will hit you.
You! You!
Stop hitting.
- Don't stop me.
I must teach this whore.
Stop pulling me.
- You'll all get reprimanded.
What are you!
I'm at least from the marquis house.
You? What can you all do to me?
You're from the marquis house.
And you instigated your second
daughter to go and seduce our lord.
Who can't see that through?
If our lady finds out,
you'll be the first to sent out.
I'll kill you.
We're onto you.
You still think you're so mighty?
Stop pulling me.
Forget it.
They're fighting! They're fighting!
Then you don't go out
so you don't get hurt.
I won't. They won't dare to hurt me.
That.
That child. She's like her father.
Just as bold.
Forgive me, Big Madam.
It's not that I want to be meddlesome.
But nowadays, in this marquis manor,
it's always someone fighting here or there.
It's ridiculously chaotic.
Allow me to speak an usurping word.
Back then, in the inner courtyard
of the Bai House in Yangzhou,
even they were more
rule-bound then this lot.
The Bai House lord must
have set a strict code.
Of course.
Such a large manor can't be without rules.
Back then when Ye's maternal
grandmother was alive,
the servants didn't even dare
to talk in a loud voice.
Later, unfortunately she passed away,
and my miss took over things.
She set up iron rules herself.
If someone commits a grave wrong,
they are severely punished
without ever any mercy.
It's true.
In order to punish those petty
troublemakers severely,
I must wait till they
commit a grave wrong first.
Big Madam, I don't understand.
If it's our own servants,
we can handle however
we want if they error.
But these are all sent over by the
elders from the marquis manor.
Small and big fights.
A couple rebukes today and
two slashes tomorrow.
Each and every, and they'll
know it's not such a big deal.
Now, Mother Lei isn't winning
any trusts from anyone.
But without Mother Lei, we still
have Mother Hua and Mother Tian.
When will it all end?
It's better to hit them dead with one
cane for them to never resurrect again.
Big Madam. If there's anything,
I  can perhaps help with . . .
There is a matter that I
really do need your help with.
Great.
I hear that illegitimate
daughter of Sheng House,
as soon as she married over, she
drove Gu Second to move out.
She even scolds an elderly nanny
who's been there over a decade.
That Gu Second is a rogue as well.
He's always running around outside.
Fetching all sorts of
novelties for her to eat.
A great general and being
dispatched like a junior servant.
No propriety whatsoever.
Old Marquis's corpse is still not cold yet.
And that Gu Second already left
the capital to pursue freedom.
I don't know what luck he's got though.
Somehow he's baked himself
into a new noble.
He's made it and turns around
to give the cold shoulder.
And mock the Gu elders like this.
I think he and that one from Sheng House
are perfect match.
I don't know what curse Yuanruo was under.
To be smitten by her kind.
Thanks to Heaven's providence
that she didn't marry here.
Or else, our Qi House.
Who knows what plight we'd be under now.
How are you up?
You've been ill for so long
and you're just recovering.
Don't get chill again.
Sixth Sister only loves to eat a bit.
I imagine Gu Second doting
on her isn't a major issue.
What's there to speak of?
Her temperament is most
prudent and diligent.
She's not someone to ever go
wild over gaining of power.
People are just too talkative
and I imagine it's false.
We don't mention her then.
I came to report to Father and Mother.
My body is fine now.
I was ill before and it
delayed my reporting to duty.
Starting tomorrow, I will head on over.
I'm glad you've thought it through.
We all need to look to ahead to live life.
Yuanruo, Yuanruo, about the,
if you want to again . . .
Don't mention it again.
Then we never mention it?
We'll mention it in a couple of years.
Father. Are you trying to find me a marriage?
Look at you, since you're not that young anymore.
And you've passed the exam
and that Shen House . . .
You're still young so we do not rush.
We'll talk in a couple of years.
Just focus on your official career.
If father and mother feel it is necessary,
please do it.