[MUSIC PLAYING]
- We welcome our viewers
worldwide to this January
31st edition of CNN 10.
I'm Carl Azuz.
And an act required by
the US Constitution played
out in America last night.
Our first topic today
is the president's
State of the Union Address.
The event as we know
it is not spelled out
in the US founding document.
It says the president, quote,
shall, from time to time,
give to the Congress information
of the state of the union
and recommend to
their consideration
such measures as he shall
judge necessary and expedient.
That's from Article II,
section II of the Constitution.
The fact that it's done
in person, the fact
that it's done as
a speech, the fact
that it's done on
television, the fact
that there is an official
response from the opposing
political party--
none of that is required
by the Constitution.
But it is tradition
dating back decades.
And so it continued last night
when US President Donald Trump
entered the House
of Representatives
to give his first official
State of the Union address.
So what topics does he judge
necessary and expedient
for Congress?
- Tonight, I call upon all of
us to set aside our differences,
to seek out common ground,
and to summon the unity we
need to deliver for the people.
This is really the key.
These are the people we
were elected to serve.
So let's begin
tonight by recognizing
that the state of
our union is strong
because our people are strong.
Since the election,
we have created 2.4
million new jobs, including--
[APPLAUSE]
Including 200,000 new jobs
in manufacturing alone.
Tremendous numbers.
[APPLAUSE]
After years and years
of wage stagnation,
we are finally
seeing rising wages.
We have proposed
new legislation that
will fix our immigration
laws and support our ICE
and border patrol agents.
My duty, and the sacred duty
of every elected official
in this chamber, is
to defend Americans,
to protect their
safety, their families,
their communities, and their
right to the American dream.
Because Americans
are dreamers, too.
As part of our defense, we
must modernize and rebuild
our nuclear arsenal, hopefully
never having to use it,
but making it so
strong and so powerful
that it will deter any
acts of aggression.
In the past, we have foolishly
released hundreds and hundreds
of dangerous
terrorists only to meet
them again on the battlefield.
So today, I am keeping
another promise--
to re-examine our
military detention policy
and to keep open the detention
facilities in Guantanamo Bay.
As long as we are
proud of who we are
and what we are
fighting for, there
is nothing we cannot achieve.
As long as we have
confidence in our values,
faith in our citizens, and trust
in our god, we will never fail.
Our families will thrive,
our people will prosper,
and our nation will
forever be safe and strong
and proud and mighty and free.
Thank you, and
God bless America.
- Another State of
the Union tradition
is the opposing political
party's response.
The first televised one of
those took place in 1966
after the State of
the Union address
by President Lyndon B Johnson.
He was a Democrat,
and two Republicans--
Senate Minority Leader
Everitt Dirksen and House
Minority Leader Gerald Ford--
recorded speeches
that were shown
after the president's address.
And so that tradition
continued last night.
After the speech by the
Republican president,
a Democratic US
representative named
Joe Kennedy from Massachusetts
gave his party's response.
He's the grand nephew of
President John F Kennedy,
and he spoke from a high
school in his state.
- We see an economy
that makes stocks soar,
investor portfolios bulge,
and corporate profits climb,
but fails to give workers
their fair share of the reward,
a government that struggles
to keep itself open,
Russia knee deep
in our democracy,
an all-out war on
environmental protection,
a Justice Department rolling
back civil rights by the day,
hatred and supremacy proudly
marching in our streets.
It would be easy to dismiss
this past year as chaos
and partisanship as politics.
But it's far, far
bigger than that.
This administration
isn't just targeting
the laws that protect us.
They're targeting
the very idea that we
are all worthy of protection.
Ladies and gentlemen,
have faith.
Have faith.
The state of our
union is hopeful,
resilient, and enduring.
God bless you.
God bless your families.
And may God bless the
United States of America.
NARRATOR: The 10-second trivia.
Which of these seasons typically
coincides with fall and winter
in the US?
Baseball season,
hurricane season,
flu season, or carnival season?
The only one of the seasons
that starts in the fall
and continues through
winter is the flu season.
- It's closed down schools
in at least 12 states.
It set a record for the number
of cases in New York state.
It's the first time in
15 years that every state
in the continental US has
reported widespread activity
during the same week.
And it's possible
that the current flu
season that's ravaging the
country hasn't even peaked yet.
Part of the reason is that
this year's flu vaccine appears
to be one of the least
effective in recent years,
though doctors say people
should still get it because it
might make the flu less severe.
H3N2 is the specific
strain of the virus that's
making so many people sick.
This strain usually
causes higher rates
of hospitalizations and deaths.
REPORTER: It's
always scary when you
hear of someone dying from
something as common as the flu.
There are four main ways
the flu can turn deadly.
The first and most common
cause is pneumonia.
The influenza virus can
directly cause viral pneumonia.
Once someone has the flu, it
can weaken their immune system
so much that another virus or
bacteria can enter the lungs.
Infected lungs fill with fluid,
making it difficult to breathe,
so oxygen can't get to
the rest of the body,
which can lead to death.
Sepsis is the second
way the flu can
become lethal, especially
in healthy younger
adults and children.
Sepsis occurs when a
person's immune system
goes into overdrive
trying to fight the flu.
This causes
inflammation, which can
lead to a cascade of
symptoms that ultimately
ends in organ failure.
A third way the flu can
kill is by increasing
your risk of heart attack.
Experts say in adults, risk
of heart attack increases
six-fold in the seven days
following a flu diagnosis.
The fourth way the
flu can kill is
by dehydration,
particularly among infants
and young children.
The flu often causes
vomiting and diarrhea,
which can quickly become
life-threatening if fluids
aren't replaced in the body.
So if you get the flu,
when should you be worried?
Some people have a higher
risk for serious complications
from the flu, including the
elderly, children under the age
of five, pregnant
women, and those
with chronic health problems.
If this is you, make
sure you see a doctor.
If you're a healthy
older child or adult,
watch out for sudden dizziness,
severe, persistent vomiting,
difficulty breathing, pain
or pressure in the chest
or abdomen, and flu-like
symptoms that improve,
then return with a
fever or worse cough.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
- A horticulturist says
the average humidity
in a normal office is 30%.
Average humidity here is 60%.
And it kind of needs to be.
What's known as The Spheres
is mostly an office space
for Amazon employees-- that's
Amazon, the internet company,
not the rainforest.
Although by looking at
this, it has 40,000 plants
and 400 different species held
together by millions of pounds
of steel, concrete, and glass--
a place where you could discuss
career and plant growth,
forage for new ideas, solve
problems with good reason,
see how many meetings
you can jungle,
call in tech support
to survey ecosystems,
bring in coworkers
for a "conifer-ence,"
make the tough
"decidu-isions," and foster
strong workplace habitat.
Oh, yeah, forest puns--
they'll grow on you.
I'm Carl Azuz, and
that's "CNN 10."