Tonight at ten,
President Trump stands by his
"America first" policies for trade
but insists the US
is still open for business.
He told his audience
of international finance leaders
that a booming US
would benefit everyone.
America first does not
mean America alone.
When the United States grows,
so does the world.
But a blow tonight
to America first -
US proposals for massive new tariffs
on imported Bombardier planes
part-made in Belfast are blocked.
If the vote had gone the other way,
it would have been devastating.
It would have been devastating
for the 4000 directly
employed workers, for the 20,000
in the supply chain,
and for the
Northern Ireland economy.
We'll be looking at the implications
for Bombardier's Belfast factory.
Also tonight,
charting a new course -
the Brexit Secretary
outlines his vision for the years
immediately after Britain's
departure from the EU.
Six male BBC presenters
agree a salary cut
after a row over unequal pay.
I was earning a lot of money,
and it seemed entirely proper to me
that I shouldn't rather less money,
so I've taken a few pay cuts, yeah.
My daughter Angela was murdered
seven months ago...
And the multiple
Oscar-nominated film
Three Billboards
Outside Ebbing, Missouri -
we speak to the British
writer and director.
And coming up in Sportsday on BBC
News, Yeovil Town take on Manchester
United, hoping for a giant-killing
in the fourth round of the FA Cup.
Find out how they got on.
Good evening.
President Trump has told an audience
of business and political leaders
that his mantra of "America first"
does not mean "America alone".
Speaking at the World Economic Forum
in Davos, Mr Trump said
the US was "open for business",
despite having campaigned
to shield US manufacturers
from foreign competition.
But tonight, US proposals to impose
tariffs of nearly 300% on imports
from the aerospace group
Bombardier were rejected,
in a surprise ruling
by the body which regulates trade.
It means thousands of jobs
in Belfast which were under threat
are now likely to be safe.
More on that in a moment,
but first our North America editor,
Jon Sopel, reports on the day's
events in Davos.
Wherever Donald Trump
has gone in Davos,
the crowds have gone with him.
And wherever the cameras
have been,
the President has
been pleased to oblige.
I hope we're going to
bring back many billions
of dollars into the US.
I think that will happen.
It's already happening.
But billions of dollars
is coming back into the US,
and I think that will just continue.
How much today? How much?
Probably a lot.
And that was
the theme of his speech.
America first, yes,
but an America welcoming the world.
I will always put America first,
just like the leaders
of other countries should
put their country first also.
But America first
does not mean America alone.
When the United States grows,
so does the world.
But at the end of a week
in which the US imposed
extra charges on some imported
goods from China,
he played down talk
of a trade war.
Nevertheless, there was a warning.
We cannot have free and open trade
if some countries exploit the system
at the expense of others.
We support free trade,
but it needs to be fair,
and it needs to be reciprocal.
Because in the end,
unfair trade undermines us all.
Some stood to applaud,
but it wasn't the ovation given
to President Xi of China last year.
This hasn't been
a complete meeting of minds,
but then again
it was never going to be.
That said, Donald Trump
has been more conciliatory
than many would have expected,
and the audience have
reacted more warmly.
It may be that Davos 2018
turns out to be a win-win.
And the President was in
conciliatory, almost repentant mood
over those Britain First
anti-Muslim retweets from last year
that brought him to blows
with the Prime Minister.
Here's what's fair.
If you're telling me
those are horrible people,
horrible, racist people,
I would certainly apologise,
if you'd like me to do that.
I know nothing about them.
So, yes, he would apologise,
he just didn't actually say sorry.
The President has now
left the Swiss Alps,
and if not yet a fully paid-up
member of the Davos set,
he will probably be invited back.
There's a lot they liked
about what Donald Trump said,
and who would disagree
with his central message,
that a booming US economy is good
for the global economy?
Jon Sopel, BBC News, Davos.
As you heard earlier,
President Trump's "America first"
trade policy suffered
a blow tonight,
after US plans to impose
hefty duties on sales
of Canadian airliners
in the States were blocked.
It's a ruling that will be welcomed
by the workers at
the Belfast factory where the wings
of the C Series jets are built.
Our correspondent Danny Savage
is outside the factory
in Belfast tonight.
Reeta, this really has cast a
shadow, this trade dispute, over
thousands of jobs in Belfast,
Bombardier is a goodly one of the
biggest employers here in Northern
Ireland, and most people really
expected this vote do go the other
way, the expected these trade
tariffs to come into force. So there
is jubilation here over the decision
in the United States tonight.
Bombardier say it is a victory for
innovation, competition and the rule
of law. And the Prime Minister,
Theresa May, has tweeted this
evening as well, saying that she
welcomes the decision, which is good
news for British industry. So a
surprise result is that many people
have welcomed.
There will be relief and celebration
on this production line tonight.
A thousand people make wings
for the C Series passenger
jet here in Belfast.
There was deep concern that a big
order for an American airline
would be lost if a huge US import
tariff was imposed.
They don't have to worry any more.
Officials in Washington have tonight
thrown out a plan to impose an
import tariff of nearly 300% on each
of these aircraft after the American
plane-maker Boeing said they were
being sold cheap because of unfair
subsidies. The American giant lost
its case.
You've worked in there for years -
what will they be saying
in there tonight?
I think they'll be pleased,
I'm certainly over the moon
about the decision, it's came
against all expectations.
How bad could it have been
if the vote had gone through?
If the vote had gone the other way,
it would have been devastating.
It would have been devastating
for the thousands of directly
employed workers, for the
20,000 in the supply chain,
and for the Northern
Ireland economy.
At the heart of the dispute
was a claim that Bombardier
received illegal subsidies
from Britain and Canada,
allowing it to undercut its rivals.
In 2016, Bombardier won a big order
for 75 planes from Delta Airlines -
it was a key breakthrough
into the US market,
but Boeing took legal action.
It claimed Bombardier spent more
than $33 million building each plane
but sold them for less
than $20 million.
Today's judgment means
a 292% tariff won't be added
to the aircraft sale price.
Theresa May raised her concerns
over Bombardier with Donald Trump
at their meeting yesterday when
they talked friendship and trade.
Could that and months
of lobbying the US authorities
have influenced this decision?
Well, I don't think the political
pressure has been unhelpful,
whether it is from the
United Kingdom Government
or from the Canadian government.
But you know, the fundamentals
of the C Series
and the fundamental arguments
that Bombardier have made
throughout this have
been vindicated.
And full power to them.
I'm delighted with the news
this evening,
and I wish them every success in
selling what is a magical aircraft.
Boeing may appeal tonight's
decision, but that could take years.
Meanwhile, this factory will be able
to sell its plane parts
tariff-free into the United States.
Danny Savage, BBC News, Belfast.
The Brexit Secretary, David Davis,
has outlined the Government's plans
for the transition period
after Britain leaves the EU
in March next year.
He confirmed that during that time
the UK would be free
to sign new trade agreements.
But Mr Davis played down rifts
within his own party over Europe,
insisting there was "no difference"
between himself, the Chancellor
and Theresa May.
Our political correspondent
Alex Forsyth reports.
In Teesside today,
the Brexit Secretary was trying
to calm troubled waters.
Surrounded by businesses
dependent on EU trade,
he promised certainty and continuity
when we leave.
David Davis set out
the Government's plans
for a transition period
of up to two years after Brexit.
This is a bridge
to a new future partnership,
where crucially the United Kingdom
is outside the single market
and outside of the customs union.
He said for business
there would be no dramatic change,
but the UK would start to talk trade
with other countries,
all to be negotiated with the EU.
But for now it's comments
by his Cabinet colleague
causing problems.
The Chancellor said there could be
very modest changes in EU relations.
If the Cabinet can't
agree on its position,
how can you possibly
negotiate with Brussels?
Look, I'm in politics,
and people debate,
and they have different views.
There's a diversity of views
on this subject, in all parties.
That doesn't mean that we don't
have or can't have a coherent
and forceful view, in the interests
of the United Kingdom.
Ministers don't always
want their divisions laid bare.
Today the Chancellor insisted
he backed the Government's view.
I was speaking about our trade
relationship with the EU,
and it is the Government's policy
that we want to maintain
the maximum possible access
to markets, and the minimum
friction at our borders.
Nonetheless, his comments
angered some Tory MPs,
although they insisted theyre
still behind Theresa May.
Downing Street has made it clear
that the Chancellor did not
represent Government policy,
and Government policy remains
as set out by the Prime Minister.
But the businesses
Brexit will affect
say the political discord
is damaging.
This car-parts manufacturer
in Redcar relies on being able
to import from and export to the EU,
and its boss wants far more clarity
from the Government about
its long-term Brexit plan.
I think it's been
pretty shambolic,
and I just want them
to get on with it.
From the contrary statements
coming out and infighting
that is happening, I don't know
what they're expecting to achieve,
I don't know what their targets are,
because it's just wishy-washy.
Businesses like those here
which rely heavily
on trade with the EU
crave certainty.
The Government says that's what
the transition phase will offer.
The trouble is
the Conservative Party
simply cannot agree
on what should come beyond.
And as talks slowly approach
future trade relations,
what has so far been a fragile truce
among the Tories looks rocky.
Alex Forsyth, BBC News, Teesside.
The UK economy grew faster
than expected
in the last three months of 2017,
according to new figures.
The Office for National Statistics
said it grew by 0.5%
instead of the expected 0.4%.
But economic growth
for the whole of last year
was the slowest since 2012.
Our economics editor,
Kamal Ahmed, reports.
Building a stronger economy.
Global growth in China lifting
businesses like this one
in Oxfordshire, making health
equipment for export.
It's been a challenge.
It took about three or four years
for us to gain approval for us
to sell into in China,
but with a bit of patience
and dedication we've now
got those approvals,
and we are seeing that uplift
in business now that were able
to expand into the market
the size of China.
Speeding around the World Economic
Forum in Davos, the Chancellor,
selling Britain abroad.
Our export markets are growing,
we've seen strong growth
in services in this quarter.
The economy is just resilient -
it has been much more resilient
than people expected.
Also here, the Governor
of the Bank of England.
Yes, the UK economy is growing,
but it is slower than
many of our competitors.
The world economy's accelerating,
and we haven't seen that yet,
but there's prospect, and I think
this is the important point,
there's the prospect this year,
as there is greater clarity
about the relationship with Europe
and subsequently with the rest
of the world, for re-coupling,
if I can use that term,
borrowed from Gwyneth Paltrow,
a conscious re-coupling
of the economy,
with the UK economy
with the global economy.
Gwyneth Paltrow to one side,
let's look at the positives first.
The UK has certainly had
a better end to the year
than many people expected.
Employment is high and growth
is picking up,
but just as the Governor warned,
there is this drag on the economy,
and that at least in part is down
to Brexit uncertainty.
We talk to businesses who tell us
they're waiting for greater clarity
about the future before they invest.
What I'm very clear about is that
as we move forward, and we made
very good progress in December,
as we move forward in this
negotiation, we will be able
to start to deliver that clarity.
It's not all about
Brexit, of course.
Economies are complicated
things, and we haven't
reached full velocity.
That productivity problem,
that income squeeze,
all way down on our performance.
I think we've still got
the same problem -
austerity is rolling on,
the Government hasn't listened,
that's impacting upon people's wages
as well as the demand overall.
A lack of investment.
We've been seeing it for years now.
We need to scale up investment
in our economy to grow our economy
and make it more productive.
The economy is being fixed,
to an extent.
Manufacturers are doing well.
Will that optimism now spread
to the rest of Britain?
Kamal Ahmed, BBC News, Davos.
A 15-year-old boy who
crashed a stolen car,
killing five people,
has been jailed for
four and a half years.
The three children and two adults
were passengers in the car when it
crashed into a tree.
The family of one of the children
expressed their anger,
saying the sentence was too short,
as Phil Bodmer reports
from Leeds Crown Court.
The faces of three children
killed in a car crash
in Leeds last November.
Ellis Thornton-Kimmit
was just 12 years old,
his brother Elliott was 14,
and Darnell Harte 15.
They were killed in a stolen
car alongside friends
Anthony Armour and Robbie Meerun,
who were both 24.
The vehicle hit a tree near houses
in the Meanwood area of Leeds
after the 15-year-old driver,
who can't be named, lost control.
The impact split the car in two.
Today, he was sentenced to four
and a half years in prison.
No words can never describe
the pain that we feel.
Relatives of one of the victims
said it wasn't enough.
He's going to serve two
years in prison, it's
not ever going to be
long enough, ever.
That's what, a couple of months
for each person's life?
You know?
We've lost one of our siblings,
Ellis and Elliot's mum
has lost two of her,
both of her children.
When police arrived here, they say
it was a scene of total carnage.
Today Leeds Crown Court heard how
witnesses saw the stolen
Renault Clio driving erratically
on the wrong side of the road,
running red lights, and travelling
at speeds of up to 88 mph
in a 40 mph zone.
It was a truly horrendous incident,
it really was, to lose three
children and two adults in such
a significant incident
is absolutely horrendous.
Many, many people affected by it.
And what I will say is no sentence
will ever compensate
for the lost that the families
and the communities
of Leeds have felt.
The court heard the boy had shown
remorse, with the judge
telling him his actions that night
will shape his life
every day from now on.
Phil Bodmer, BBC News, Leeds.
The BBC says it is "grateful" to six
male presenters who have agreed
to a pay cut after revelations
of salary inequality
at the Corporation emerged.
The details are still being worked
out, but the six are Huw Edwards,
Nicky Campbell, John Humphrys,
Jon Sopel, Nick Robinson,
and Jeremy Vine.
John Humphrys this evening confirmed
that he'd agreed to a substantial
reduction in his pay.
Our media editor,
Amol Rajan, reports.
So now it's official -
at least six of the BBC's most
high-profile male journalists
will take a pay cut,
though some haven't yet
signed on the dotted line.
Last summer, when the salaries
of those earning over
£150,000 were revealed,
the BBC argued the move
would be inflationary
and a poacher's charter.
But precious little
poaching has taken place,
and if anything, this transparency
is proving deflationary.
On his way into work this morning,
Radio 2's Jeremy Vine said
he applauded the changes.
I think it all needs to be sorted
out, and I support my female
colleagues, who've rightly said
that they should be paid the same
when they're doing the same job.
It's just a no-brainer,
so it wasn't a problem
for me to accept one.
It's Friday morning...
On his breakfast show on Radio
5 live this morning,
Nicky Campbell revealed
that he is one of
those taking a cut.
And I am also on that list.
Radio 4's John Humphrys has taken
a substantial pay cut.
The BBC used to have,
in the good old days,
an awful lot of money.
It no longer has an awful lot
of money - it's having to cut
right, left and centre.
I was earning a lot of money,
and it seemed entirely proper to me
that I should earn rather less
money, so I've taken
a few pay cuts, yeah.
In a statement, the BBC thanked
those taking a pay cut and said...
The pay cuts reveal the changing
economics of broadcasting.
Many of those taking pay cuts got
generous deals in an earlier era,
when the market for talent
was more competitive.
Today, the big money
is in entertainment rather
than news, but some people feel
the BBC shouldn't
enter bidding wars.
The BBC is there, it's financed
by licence-fee payers' money,
it is public money, and it obviously
has to be careful with it.
It develops talent, but if talent
then goes elsewhere because the pay
on offer is greater,
then that is a matter
for those people concerned.
The issue of equal pay is about more
than current disparities
between people doing similar jobs.
It's also about what some see
as historic injustices
and the feeling among some women
at the BBC that they've
accumulated this advantage over
the course of their careers.
Reducing the salaries
of six high-profile male
presenters may be a necessary,
even inevitable first step,
but it doesn't address or solve
the deeper, structural issues.
The BBC faces other
pressing challenges -
from the discrepancy in pay
between on and off-air talent,
to the growing disconnect
with working-class audiences.
These pay cuts are a significant
gesture, but they barely begin
to address the causes of anger felt
throughout the corporation.
Amol Rajan, BBC News.
A brief look at some
of the day's other news stories.
The release of the serial sex
attacker John Worboys from prison
has been temporarily put on hold,
after a legal challenge
by two of his victims.
Their lawyer said the application
for the review had been
made to the High Court,
and is due to take place
early next month.
Families of the Birmingham pub
bombings' victims have welcomed
a court ruling that a coroner
was wrong to exclude
the names of the alleged
suspects in a new inquest.
21 people were killed when two IRA
bombs exploded in 1974.
The families, however, are angry
they had to pay for legal help.
The suspension of non-urgent
operations to ease winter NHS
pressures in England is to be
lifted from February.
Hospitals had originally been
advised to delay non-emergency
surgery until mid-January.
That was then extended, in a bid
to free up hospital beds and staff.
The Food Standards Agency says it's
looking at issues
involving the use by dates on meat
supplied to thousands of pubs,
hotels, and some schools and care
homes by the Derby-based
company Russell Hume.
Its six sites have been
closed since Tuesday.
One of its major customers,
the pub chain Wetherspoons, today
apologised to its customers and said
it had found a new supplier,
as Emma Simpson reports.
No steaks being served here.
There haven't been any
at Wetherspoons since Tuesday.
Thank you, cheers.
Not great for a business which sells
thousands of steaks every week.
It decided to withdraw
them when it discovered
problems with its supplier,
Russell Hume.
We are none the wiser.
We are a big customer.
We serve 10 million
steaks a year in our pub.
That's a lot of steak.
And we've always served them in good
faith and it's been great.
Russell Hume have been
a good supplier to us.
But something has gone
terribly wrong here,
and people really need to know
what the situation is.
We cut the steak between 15 and 20
millimetres in thickness.
Russell Hume prides itself
on selling quality products,
but tonight the Food
Standards Agency said
it was concerned about use by dates.
The company had failed
to demonstrate it complied
with food hygiene rules.
The FSA said so serious
and widespread were the issues,
it called for production to be
stopped at all of Russell Hume's six
sites, and for a withdrawal
of unused meat from its customers.
In a statement, the company
said it was shocked
by the FSA's actions,
adding:
But that hasn't stopped
Wetherspoons from changing supplier.
It's not just Wetherspoons.
A host of household names have
also withdrawn meat,
including Jamie Oliver's
Italian restaurants,
the pub chains Greene King
and Marston's, and Butlins.
Schools and care homes
have also been affected.
It's important for people to be
given information as quickly
as possible so they can make
informed decisions about where
they are eating and indeed
what they are eating,
and knowing that they
are doing so safely.
I think it would have been helpful
if the Food Standards Agency had
given a little earlier
the information that
they provided today.
So the FSA has gone
some way in satisfying
the appetite for answers.
Steaks will be back
on the menu here next week.
This investigation, though,
will take a lot longer.
Emma Simpson, BBC News.
Football, and no giant-killing in
the West Country tonight. Manchester
United beat Yeovil 4-0 in the FA
Cup. Alexis Sanchez made his debut
but was substituted in the second
half as United took control. Lingard
scored the pick of the goals,
running through the Yeovil defence.
It's been nominated for seven
Oscars, including Best Picture.
Three Billboards Outside Ebbing,
Missouri is the story of a grieving
mother's fight for justice
in small town America.
Will Gompertz has been speaking
to the man from London
who wrote and directed
the film, Martin McDonagh.
My daughter Angela was murdered
seven months ago...
Francis McDormand as Mildred Hayes,
the uncompromising, unflinching
and very angry grieving mother...
You drilled a hole in the dentist?
Who rents three billboards
outside Ebbing, Missouri,
a fictional town created
by Martin McDonagh,
the film's London-born Irish
writer and director.
Martin McDonagh has got an Oscar
nomination for his writing
but not for his directing.
I wonder if he's a little
bit disappointed.
No, not really, particularly
because the mates got nominated
in the other categories.
It would have been nice,
but seven's good.
You get over here.
No, you get over here.
All right.
One of the criticisms that
Three Billboards has
is that the Sam Rockwell character,
Dixon the policeman,
who is a racist, is treated
sympathetically by you.
Well, he's definitely
a racist and a bully.
I wouldn't say he's
treated sympathetically.
I was trying to see, I think,
the hope in all of these people.
So if you say that's treating
characters symathetically,
to a degree it is.
But the point of the film,
and I think the thing that I hope
people come away with,
is the possibility
of changing people.
If it was me, I'd start a database.
Every male baby that's born,
stick them on it, and as soon
as he'd done something wrong,
cross-reference it, make 100%
certain it was a correct
match, then kill him.
We've heard many speeches from many
people in the movie industry saying
it is time for a change.
Do you think that's just lip
service, or do you think
something actually quite
fundamental is happening?
It feels like something really
new and really great is happening.
Like, I've been in the rooms
at the last couple of awards things,
and it is palpable, and it does feel
angry, and it does feel like it's
not going to go away,
and I think that's great.
It feels like a change
is properly happening.
I'd do anything to catch
your daughter's killer.
The Oscars ceremony at the beginning
of March might well point
towards that change,
with some surprising winners,
and quite possibly a forthright
acceptance speech from this lady.
Will Gompertz, BBC News.
That's it.
Now on BBC One, it's time
for the news where you are.
Have a very good night.