Mum!
Dad!
Bingo!
- Bluey!
-Home!
Ahhh.
What a day!
Cut us down, kids.
-Yeah!
-Chop, chop, chop!
-Timber!
Five minutes till bed, kids.
And five years till the
next trip to Crazyworld.
Can we play a game?
As long as it's one
where I don't have to move
any part of my body or say anything
with my mouth.
Okay.
Hey, Bingo!
Let's make it that
Mum and Dad are a mountain!
Yeah!
Mount Mumandad!
This episode of
Bluey is called Mount Mumandad.
We can have a race to the top!
Whoever plants their
flag first wins.
Ready?
Go!
Wait!
I'm gonna get climbing stuff.
Bingo, we only have five minutes!
Don't start without me!
All packed.
Ready, set, go!
Wait! I forgot the music box.
Bingo!
That's it, I'm starting.
Ready!
Hey, you didn't wait for me.
You were taking ages!
I was packing important mountain stuff.
Grr!
Ooh!
Aaah!
Eeeh. This is hard!
Your backpack's too heavy,
that's why!
But it's got
all my climbing stuff
and my map
of Mount Mumandad.
Hmm.
Yes, I'm going the right way.
Oh, Bingo.
Oooh! This is a nice view.
Eww!
This bit of the mountain stinks.
I'm gonna win, Bingo!
Click, photo, click, photo...
Bingo, what are you doing?
We're racing!
Click, photo.
Ooh, yeah! Hee hee!
Ooh, this is gonna be a bit tricky.
-Aaah!
-Ohh!
Aaaaaaaah!
Ohh!
Help! I'm slipping!
I can't hold on!
Help, Bingo!
I'm coming!
Don't worry!
I've got some rope in my backpack.
Grab on!
Ooh!
I got you, Bluey! Hold on!
Ohh, ohh!
Phew! Thanks, Bingo.
That's okay.
But I'm still gonna win!
Huh!
Bluey!
-Yaah! Ooof!
Ooh, it's steep here.
Eeek!
So slippery!
Bingo, can I just use your head
to give me a little boost?
-Hey!
- Aah!
Oop! Sorry!
Oof. Bluey!
I'm gonna win, Bingo!
It's not fair, Bluey!
You cheated!
No, I didn't!
Yes... you... did!
No... I... didn't!
No... I...
didn't!
Aah!
-Ehh! Ohh!
Uh-oh.
Aaaah!
Dad, stop it!
Oh, no! It's an avalanche!
Grooowwww!
Grr!
-Grr!
-Aaaah!
Ooof!
Are you okay, Bluey?
I'm fine.
A silly little
avalanche isn't gonna stop me.
Aah! Bluey, there's the storm!
Dad, stop it!
Bluey, come back down.
It's not worth it.
No, I'm almost there!
Aaaah!
Ooof!
Bluey, come in my tent.
No, I have to get to the top!
But the storm is too strong.
Aaaah! Oof!
Dad!
Aaaah!
Aaaaah!
What a cheeky Old Man Mountain.
Ooh, I like your tent, Bingo.
Thanks.
Oh, you'll need this.
Ooh, that's better.
Nice and toasty.
We can play London Snap
till the storm passes.
Okay.
Black cab.
Trafalgar.
Furry hat guy.
Buckingham Palace.
-Snap!
- Ow!
And then rabbit ran off really fast,
leaving behind the slow tortoise.
Hurry up, tortoise!
Yeah, hurry up!
You have to beat that cheeky rabbit!
The storm's still going.
What should we do?
We'll have to stay in the tent longer.
We can watch the ballerina spin around.
I'm sorry I cheated, Bingo.
That's okay.
I'm a cheeky rabbit sometimes.
I think I'm more like the slow tortoise.
Bingo, I think the storm is stopping!
The mountain's quiet.
Come on.
Let's go!
Okay!
Shhh!
We don't want to disturb Old Man Mountain.
You do not climb Mount Mumandad
by trying to race ahead on your own,
or by competing with your comrades.
You do it slowly and carefully by
unselfish teamwork.
That is the mountain way.
- Ow!