Mum!
Dad!
Bingo!
- Bluey!
Ahh! Ohh!
-Almost.
-Ooh!
-Almost!
-Come on, Bluey!
Almost! Got it!
-Yeah!
I reached it!
Alright, bumblenuts,
I'm out of here.
- Nooo!
-Yow!
I've gotta go to work!
No!
No work!
Quick, Bingo, we need a plan.
How are we gonna
get Dad to stay?
Think, Bingo, think.
Um, um...
My brain can't
think of anything.
I know!
But, Dad, you can't leave
without having breakfast!
Huh?
We were gonna make
breakfast for you.
Yeah!
And you always say,
you have to eat breakfast.
That is true.
I am always
saying that.
-Okay.
- Hooray!
This episode of Bluey
is called Trampoline.
I'll just have
some toast.
Hooray, toast!
I'll just get some bread.
Now, just bung these
in the toaster.
Piece of bread one
and piece of bread two.
-Ka-ching!
And now, just peruse
my newspaper
and wait for my toast
to be perfectly --
- Ka-chunk!
What?
Toast is ready!
That wasn't very long.
Ugh!
Nyum nyum nyum nyum!
This toast is raw!
Again, toaster!
No, no, no,
I've really got to go.
No way!
You have to have some...
Um, some...
Argh, I can't think!
-Juice!
-Yeah, juice!
Juice! Juice!
Well, I do like a good juice.
-Hooray!
Mm-mm-mm-mm,
mmm, mmm.
Now, what have we got
in the fridge here for a juice?
Psst!
What are you?
Oh, oh, uh,
pineapple!
No, a blueberry.
Black.
-A blackberry!
-Got it.
What about you?
What fruit do you love?
Banana.
I'm a banana!
Banana and blueberries. Perfect!
-Blackberries!
-Oh, blackberries.
Blackberries.
Perfect!
Okay, let's just get them
in the juicer.
Wait, what fruit
do you hate?
Ooh, rockmelon.
Bleaghh!
Hee hee!
I'm a rockmelon!
Yeah,
and I'm a fly.
-Bzz, bzz!
-Oh, no.
Okay,
let's get the lid on.
Clunk!
Now, switch the juicer on.
Okay, there we go.
Lid off.
Let's have a taste!
Gulp gulp gulp gulp gulp!
Ahh!
Bleaghh!
Rockmelon and flies?!
Yuck!
Again -- juice!
Nah, kids, that's it for me.
I've got to get to work.
No!
You need to have some...
-eggs!
-Yeah!
Well, I am
off the carbs.
-Hee hee! It's working!
-It's working!
Okay.
I'll have some eggs.
Hooray!
Quickly.
Okay, I just need to crack them
in the frying pan.
Boing! Boing!
Ah ha ha!
That was an easy one.
One egg cracked.
Just need to crack the other one.
Ba-boom!
This one has a tough shell.
Must be free range or something.
-Come...on...egg!
I want breakfast!
Ha!
There it goes.
Have us scrambled!
You got it.
Scramble scramble scramble,
scrambleee!
Right.
That's my brecky sorted.
Now I've gotta get
to work, kids.
-No!
Wait!
-Yaah!
-Get off!
You're not leaving!
Yes, I am!
Chilli!
Come on, kiddos.
You have to let Dad
go to work.
-Aw!
Sorry, kids.
I really do have to go.
Dad?
Yes, mate?
I don't want you to leave.
Come here, kid.
I want you to stay
and play with us.
I know you do.
I have to go do my job, though.
And you have to do yours.
What? I don't have a job.
Yeah, you do.
Really? What is it?
Making up games.
Oh!
And making your bed,
doing the dishes,
and setting the table!
But making up games is more
important than you think.
Okay, Dad.
Bye, Dad.
Bluey, I don't know
what to play.
I know.
Come with me!
Ohh!
I'll kink the hose!
Aaaaah!
Good one, Bingo.
What's going to happen?
I don't know.
-Ready?
-Yeah!
Unkink!
I know!
We can be lettuce!
And this is
a big salad spinner!
Yeah, getting washed,
ready to eat!
That looks like a fun game.
Mum, come and have
some salad for lunch!
We know how much you like salad.
-Yeah, alright.
- Yeah!
Whoooaaa!
Whoa!
Who made up this game?
Me!
Nice job, Bluey!