[CLOCK TICKING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
CARL AZUZ: Hi.
I'm Carl Azuz, and for those
of you who are wondering,
Fridays are awesome.
Thank you for watching
CNN 10 on this January 19.
Paris, France is just over
40 square miles in area.
That's also about the size of
an oil spill that's spreading
in the East China Sea.
It started when an
Iranian oil tanker
collided with a
freighter from Hong Kong.
That happened on January 7.
The oil ship caught
fire and stayed afloat,
burning until it
exploded and sank
a week later on January 14.
Officials believe all
of its 32 crew members
died in the accident.
The tanker was carrying
136,000 tons of condensate oil.
It's a type used in jet fuel,
and it's lighter in color
than the thick black
crude oil that's
been seen in other oil spills.
But though environmentalists
say some of the oil on board
the ship probably
burned off in the fire,
they're concerned
that what remained
could still hurt marine
life in the area,
like whales and porpoises.
They're also worried that the
fuel that powered the ship
will leak as well, and that
could make things worse.
It's very toxic.
The oil slicks--
China says there
are four of them--
almost doubled in
size this week.
Other boats are in this
area of the East China Sea
working to clean up the oil.
An environmental
group, Greenpeace,
expects any contamination
to stay relatively
close to the sunken ship,
though winds have pushed
the spill east toward Japan.
There have been some breakneck
swings in the value of Bitcoin.
We reported on this digital
form of currency last month.
It was created in 2009.
People can either buy
Bitcoin units or mine them--
use computers to solve
complicated math puzzles
to create Bitcoin, And huge
amounts of computer energy
are being used to do that.
But there's a lot of
uncertainty about the currency.
It's volatile--
highly changeable,
like all cryptocurrencies,
and an example of that
played out in recent days
when Bitcoin's value took
a nosedive, temporarily
dropping to below $10,000
earlier this week.
A single Bitcoin was valued
at nearly $20,000 in December.
Investors don't know exactly
why the drop happened,
but the Bloomberg financial and
media company reported early
this week that Chinese
officials were taking steps
to limit trading in
cryptocurrencies,
and South Korea also
took steps to regulate
exchanges of digital currency.
CARL AZUZ (VOICEOVER):
10 Second Trivia.
[COUNTDOWN BEEPING]
H1N1 and H3N2 are
examples of what?
Asteroids, flu strains,
chicken breeds, or robots?
With an H4 hemagglutinin
and an N4 neuraminidase,
these are examples of
strains of the flu.
CARL AZUZ: And a flu strain
circulating in the US
this year, like the one that
hit Australia last year,
is a nasty one.
Widespread flu activity
is being reported
in every part of the
continental US at the same time.
This is the first year that's
happened in the 13 years
that the Centers
for Disease Control
has been monitoring the flu.
One reason-- this year's
vaccine doesn't appear
to be very effective
against the actual flu
virus that's spreading.
Experts predict it'll
be about 30% effective.
In recent years, the vaccine's
been between 40% and 50%
effective, though there was
an exception in the 2014
to 2015 season when the
vaccine was only 19%
effective, according to the CDC.
And the New York Times
reports that this season
is looking a lot like that one.
The hopeful news is that experts
think the flu season may be
hitting its worst
point now and that it's
starting to level off.
But it takes weeks for flu
activity to actually slow down.
SANJAY GUPTA: Let me try and
settle this flu shot thing,
although I'm sure it's going to
keep coming up again and again.
You can't get the flu
from the flu shot.
It's a dead virus.
It can't actually cause flu.
Why do people feel sort
of crummy afterward?
It's because the flu vaccine
is actually working and making
your immune system
fire up, get ready,
and recognize if it actually
sees the flu, how to kill it.
No, it's not 100%
fail-safe, but it's still
going to offer a
lot of protection
so that you're not going to be
as sick, as likely to get sick,
or if you do get sick,
have a shorter duration.
OK, so if you're
like me, your mom
probably said don't go outside
in the cold without your hat
on.
You're going to catch the flu.
You can't catch the
flu from just simply
being outside in the cold.
But it does raise the
question, why are there so many
more flu cases in
the winter months?
You're likely to stay indoors
more, so if one person is sick,
more people are
likely to get sick.
The sun is lower in the
sky, and as a result,
you have less vitamin D actually
being produced in your body.
Your immune system starts to
get suppressed a little bit.
You're more likely to
get sick with the flu.
The winter months tend
to be lower humidity.
Viruses like the flu virus,
they like lower humidity.
They're likely to live longer.
So your mom may have been right.
I mean, look-- moms
are always right.
But maybe not for the reasons
you originally thought.
CARL AZUZ: We're bringing
it back to currency
for our next great big story.
Besides Bitcoin as an
alternative form of money,
mobile phone minutes
have been accepted
as payment in some countries.
Shells and stones pass as
cash in some island nations.
And in part of Italy,
a famous type of cheese
isn't just worth money--
it's invested, stored,
and exchanged as currency.
CARL AZUZ (VOICEOVER): Let's
say you're a cheese producer.
You need a loan
because you want to buy
a tractor or food for your cows,
or really just about anything.
There's a bank in Italy
that'll take your cheese
and give you cash.
This is the story of
three men and millions
of dollars worth of cheese.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Meet Mauro.
MAURO ROSSI: Ciao.
CARL AZUZ (VOICEOVER): He's a
cheese producer in the Emiliano
region of Italy.
He produces Parmigiano-Reggiano,
the so-called King of Cheese.
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
[RECORD SCRATCHING]
20,000 wheels?
Holy cow, that's
a lot of cheese.
When Mauro or another cheese
producer in this part of Italy
needs a loan, they go to Credito
Emiliano, a big Italian bank.
And like any bank,
Credito Emiliano needs
collateral for their loan.
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
And to do that, he
talks to Fausto.
FAUSTO FILIPPI: Ciao.
CARL AZUZ (VOICEOVER): He
works for Credito Emiliano.
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
Parmigiano-Reggiano is
a special kind of cheese
because it needs to be
aged for 18 to 36 months,
and a wheel can be worth
thousands of dollars,
making it a safe long-term
investment for the bank.
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
To be clear, the
bank doesn't store
the valuable cheese
in its vaults
next to gold bars
and stacks of cash.
They have a special cheese
warehouse down the road
filled with thousands and
thousands of wheels of cheese.
That's where Roberto comes in.
He's the general director of
the Tagliate general warehouses.
That's where Credito
Emiliano stores their cheese.
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
Roberto and his team
take care for more
than 300,000 wheels of cheese.
That's currently worth more
than 160 million euros.
Without proper care, cheese
could lose its value.
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
Well, Roberto, sounds to
me like the cow, the bank,
and the cheese
are in good hands.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
CARL AZUZ: If you're aquaphobic,
bathophobic, or claustrophobic,
turn away, because we're
diving deep into what
experts believe is the world's
biggest underwater cave.
It was identified
when divers recently
found out that two
flooded caverns in Mexico
were actually connected.
The cave is 216 miles
long and scientists
hope it will help
them learn more
about the ancient
Mayan civilization,
because their
settlements apparently
ran along this cave system.
Of course, if you're more of a
Copernicus than a cavernicus--
if you'd rather be
starry-eyed than watery-eyed,
you'd rather aim
high than dive deep,
and you tend to cave
under water pressure,
you stalag-might want to drift
elsewhere for va-cave-tion.
This kind of dive
is for those who
tank their spelunkey
stars when something
leaves them breathless.
Have a great weekend.
[MUSIC PLAYING]