Tonight at ten, thousands of jobs
at risk following the collapse
of the big construction
and services firm Carillion.
The business is involved in major
public building projects,
as well as cleaning and maintenance
for schools, prisons and hospitals
and employs 20,000 people.
Workers are now facing great
uncertainty. I am due wages that I
would pick up this week in work, and
I don't know if I'm going to get
them. That's my rant, that's my
food. -- rent.
Tonight ministers held an emergency
meeting to discuss plans
for maintaining essential services
in the public sector.
The Government is working very hard
indeed across all Whitehall
departments to ensure
that the liquidation of Carillion
takes place in an orderly
manner that does not
disrupt public services.
We'll be asking how a company
in financial trouble
was nonetheless able to secure major
Government contracts.
Also tonight...
A coroner in Cumbria concludes that
13-month-old Poppi Worthington had
been sexually assaulted before
she died of asphyxia.
In Bangladesh, fears for the safety
of thousands of Rohingya Muslims
facing a return to possible
violence in Myanmar.
They are living in what is now the
world's largest refugee camp, amid
what the United Nations is calling a
children's crisis. What a great
shot!
And many tributes to Cyrille Regis,
the man who led the way for black
footballers in Britain.
He's died at the age of 59.
And coming up on Sportsday on BBC
News, Manchester United go in search
of a win against Stoke tonight,
while the Potters begin
a new era under Paul Lambert.
Good evening.
Ministers have held
an emergency meeting tonight
following the collapse of Carillion,
the major construction
and services company involved
in some of the biggest
public building projects in the UK.
Carillion employs 20,000 people
in the UK and it sub-contracts work
to thousands of small firms.
The company has 450 Government
contracts, from work on the HS2 rail
link to cleaning and maintenance
contracts for schools,
prisons and hospitals.
But Carillion has now gone
into liquidation with debts
of £900 million and a pension
deficit of more than £500 million.
Our business editor Simon Jack
reports now on the collapse
of Carillion and its impact.
This bypass near Aberdeen
is Scotland's biggest construction
project, with a price
tag of £750 million.
Here's another one, around
Lincoln, cost, 100 million.
Just two of 450 contracts Carillion
has been awarded throughout the UK,
but it did a lot more
than build things.
Through contracts to manage schools,
prisons and hospitals,
it touched the lives of millions.
Today, the Government said
it would not support
the company with public money.
This is, however, the failure
of a private sector company
and it is the company's shareholders
and its lenders who will bear
the brunt of the losses.
Taxpayers should not, and will not,
bail out a private sector company
for private sector losses.
This was the scene the Midlands that
are put in hospital in Sandwell. The
cranes came to a standstill over the
£600 million project. Philip Ellis
was one of 500 workers told to
leave. IMG wages I was due to pick
up this week and white, so I don't
know if I'm going to get them. That
is my rent and food, Christmas, I
found out my girlfriend was
pregnant. I am stuck for money,
ringing around and trying to find
jobs. Everybody is in the same boat,
ringing the same people for the same
jobs. It is more than the second
biggest construction firm, it
delivers 32,000 school meals a day.
It maintains NHS buildings,
containing 11,500 hospital beds. It
provides services to 50 prisons and
as recently as November was awarded
a contract to help build the
high-speed rail network.
high-speed rail network. Big
contracts were added after it was
known it was on the ropes, leading
to angry exchanges in the Commons.
Went to the Otman Bakkal realise it
was in trouble? They have three
CEOs, three separate profit warnings
and were already short selling stock
exchange. Where did it go wrong? Big
contracts like this went sour,
profits had to be written off,
blowing a hole in finances. With
banks unwilling to lend any more
money without government support,
its fate was sealed. Company matter
there was a company that until
recently paid big salaries to
bosses, and big dividends to
shareholders, despite owing banks
and its own pension scheme £1.5
billion. The wisdom of awarding
public service contracts to a
company like that will continue.
Today, the urgent concern is for the
thousands of small businesses that
rely on the big businesses like
Carillion for payments to pay their
own bills. These are bills to them
for goods and services we supplied.
Gordon Stone supplies Christmas
lights to a City Council through a
subcontract. I have a dozen invoices
dated back to November, when we
supplied Christmas lighting to
Birmingham City Council, through
Carillion. These have not been paid.
In total, they value about £17,500.
What is the knock-on effect? The
consequences immediately are cash
flow. We have to have a serious look
at cash flow and business going
forward, and potentially it might
mean that we have to reduce staffing
levels by one or two. We are not
sure. Furthermore, we are not sure
if we will get paid any of this
money. Speaking after a meeting of
the Cobra committee, David
Liddington tried to put a positive
spin on the day's events. The
message today was that they want had
gone pretty well. People were
turning up to work. We had not had
reports of any serious disruption to
service delivery. It is unlikely
workers going home today will see
things the same way.
In a moment we'll be talking
to our deputy political editor
John Pienaar at Westminster
but first to Simon Jack
who's outside Carillion's
headquarters in Wolverhampton.
Simon, what have we learned today
about the way this company was
actually being run? Well, the
recriminations here have really
intensified during the day, with
even a leading business group, the
Institute of Directors, joining
Labour and the unions, issuing a
stinging rebuke to the former
managers. The ex-chief executive who
left last year will enjoy his
£665,000 salary until October. Year
after year, dividends were
increased, even as the pension
deficit ballooned. Once again, the
reputational business is taking a
real beating today. This come in a
way, is worse, because it is felt,
rightly or wrongly, the government's
fingerprints were all over this.
They might argue that they tried to
support the company by giving extra
work to reassure its banks. That
didn't work. The banks were not
reassured, and without them on
board, the company's fate was
sealed.
And to John Pienaar at Westminster
What is being said at Westminster
about the reasons why the Government
was still putting business to
Carillion when the financial
problems were known? The Government
anticipated that question from early
on. Ministers are saying if those
contracts had been pulled, it would
have amounted to pulling the plug on
comedy much sooner. We might have
seen ministers taking more of the
kind of heat we have seen today.
Ministers are also keen to get
across that the taxpayer will not be
bailing out a private company or
private shareholders. But that is
about the only thing that they can
agree on. We have seen them opening
up a wider and deeper ideological
chasm that we have seen at any time
since Margaret Thatcher first set
out to roll back the frontiers of
the state in the 1980s. It is now an
enormous argument and a new scale
altogether. Tony Blair, Gordon
Brown, they were happy to see
private involvement in the public
sector. Before Jeremy Corbyn there
was a general acceptance that was
OK. But those days have now gone.
That consensus has pretty much
disappeared. This week, we will see
a Labour spokesman, after Labour
spokesman, attacking private
involvement in public services in
prisons, health, in hospitals,
across the board. It is a glaring
example of the kind of startling
polarisation we are seeing in
British politics. John Pienaar, many
thanks.
In Cumbria, an inquest
into the death of 13-month-old
Poppi Worthington has concluded
that she was sexually assaulted
before she died of asphyxia.
Cumbria's senior coroner
said her father's account
of what had happened at their home
in December 2012 did not
stand up to scrutiny.
Paul Worthington had declined
to answer more than 250 questions
during the inquest,
and has consistently
denied any wrongdoing.
He's never been charged,
as our correspondent
Danny Savage reports.
For five years, the death
of Poppi Worthington
has been unexplained.
Now it is much clearer how she died
and what happened to her beforehand.
This 13-month-old suffocated
after being left in an unsafe
sleeping position by her father.
She died in this bed where a coroner
believes Paul Worthington also
sexually assaulted her.
He had taken her from her cot before
the assault which the coroner ruled,
on the balance of probabilities,
took place hours before she died.
This statement was made today
on behalf of Poppi's mother.
She is disappointed that Poppi's
father chose to rely on his right
not to answer questions
which might incriminate him.
While she understands
he is entitled to do this,
she considers he should have given
the coroner the crucial evidence
of Poppi's last few hours.
The coroner said that
Paul Worthington's accounts
of what happened the night Poppi
died were not complete or truthful
and his evidence did not
stand up to scrutiny.
Mr Worthington was bundled
in and out of the inquest by police
because of concern over his safety.
He lives in hiding.
In court, he refused to answer
questions 252 times.
I don't blame him.
He was advised not to.
He's gone through all this process
over the last four years,
five years with all the case
and that and everything that's
been dumped on him...
No.
Go with the solicitor's advice.
His sister, Tracey Worthington,
has stood by him throughout.
How convinced are you that your
brother is innocent?
I'm not convinced - I know.
I don't have to be convinced
he's done nothing.
I know.
You know, I wouldn't protect him,
trust me, I would not protect him
if he'd done anything wrong.
I'd be the one dragging him down
the cop shop and he wouldn't be
a pretty sight by
the time he got there.
The first inquest into Poppi's death
was quashed by the High Court
after lasting just seven minutes.
The Cumbria Police investigation was
botched and vital evidence was lost.
Two senior officers had cases
to answer for gross misconduct.
Both have since retired.
Poppi and her family deserve
a better standard of investigation
than the one that was conducted
five years ago.
But no-one is ever likely to be
charged over Poppi's death
because of a lack of evidence.
Many people will view this
as an unsatisfactory end
to years of investigations
into Poppi Worthington's short life.
Danny Savage, BBC News, Cumbria.
A brief look at some of the day's
other other news stories.
A court has heard how Khalid Masood
- the man who killed five people
in Westminster last March -
took steroids in the days
and hours before the attack.
He was shot dead in the grounds
of the Palace of Westminster
after driving into four people
on Westminster Bridge and fatally
stabbing a police officer.
Two RAF jets have intercepted a pair
of Russian bombers over
the North Sea which were
approaching UK airspace.
The Ministry of Defence says
the planes were not responding
to air traffic control, making them
a hazard to other aviation.
Part of a floor inside the stock
exchange in the Indonesian capital
Jakarta has collapsed injuring more
than 70 people.
A group of some 40 visiting students
were on a balcony section
as the floor gave way.
Remarkably, nobody was killed.
Police say the collapse was due
to an accident, not an explosion.
The leader of Ukip,
Henry Bolton, says he has no
intention of resigning
in the light of racist remarks
made by his girlfriend
about Meghan Markle,
Prince Harry's fiancee.
Henry Bolton said he had now ended
the relationship with Jo Marney -
who was suspended from Ukip
after saying Meghan Markle
would taint the Royal Family.
Our political correspondent
Vicki Young has the story.
Her report contains some
flash photography.
Forced to choose between his job
and his controversial
new girlfriend, today Henry Bolton
announced his romance
with Jo Marney was off
and he wasn't going anywhere.
I am absolutely not standing down.
The reason is because it's crucially
important that Ukip has a loud voice
in the discussions leading up
to exiting the European Union.
Mr Bolton was Ukip's
fourth leader in a year.
He was supposed to get
the party onto the front foot
and the front pages -
but not like this.
He's been forced to act
after reports of racist text
messages from Miss Marney,
in which she called black people
ugly and said Prince Harry's fiance
Meghan Markle would "taint the Royal
Family".
She's apologised for the remarks,
which she claims were
taken out of context.
And today tweeted that...
"We all make mistakes,
it's how you deal with them
and conduct yourself
in the future that matters."
Henry Bolton's come out fighting,
but ditching his girlfriend may not
be enough to save his leadership.
Irrespective of these texts
that Jo Marney sent,
which are absolutely disgraceful,
people were calling for him
to resign before they came to light.
The fact is, I think he's become
a bit of an embarrassment
to the party now and he really
has to go.
Can our party really survive
an ineffectual, useless leader,
whose only public fame
is for having a scandal?
Quite frankly, we don't need another
leadership election,
we shouldn't have had one,
but the situation is untenable.
He has to go.
Henry Bolton's critics say that
since taking over he's
failed to make an impact,
that his lack of political
experience shows.
He's also surrounded
by colleagues who think
they could do a better job.
But that doesn't, apparently,
include Nigel Farage.
He's having a busy day, Henry.
Very busy indeed.
Who insists, really,
he's not planning another comeback.
Since the Brexit vote, Ukip has
struggled to find a purpose.
The popularity it enjoyed under
Nigel Farage has plummeted,
and this latest fiasco
won't have helped.
But activists deny that their party
is finished as a physical force.
Bitter infighting continues
to plague the party.
Its ruling body will hold
an emergency meeting at the weekend,
and could decide Mr Bolton's time
is up, plunging Ukip into yet
another leadership crisis.
Vicki Young, BBC News, Westminster.
#
A parliamentary committee has
expressed grave concern
about plans to begin repatriating
hundreds of thousands
of Rohingya Muslims
from Bangladesh back to Myanmar -
from where they fled
violence last year.
The International Development
Committee has warned that
rape and sexual violence
are still weapons of war
used by the military in Myanmar.
Around 570,000 Rohingyas are now
living in the world's
largest refugee camp,
Kutupalong, near the port city
of Cox's Bazar in Bangladesh.
My colleague Mishal Husain
is in Kutupalong with the latest.
It was a mass movement of people
unmatched in recent years that
created this camp in the space
of just five months.
Today, the small shelters
dot the landscape here,
stretching right up to the border
with Myanmar a few miles away.
Living conditions
are very difficult.
Nevertheless, the idea of going back
to Myanmar is unthinkable
at the moment for most
of the refugees - many
say their security would need
to be guaranteed first.
In a camp where hundreds of refugees
are still arriving every week,
there is much to be done.
New wells, new shelters,
all part of providing for growing
numbers and preparing the camp
for the monsoon rains.
The more construction and expansion
that takes place at this last camp,
the more permanent it
starts to feel.
But, at the same time,
the talk of repatriating refugees
is causing deep alarm.
After the circumstances
in which they fled Myanmar less
than six months ago,
who really trust that things have
changed enough for them to go home?
That's because the destruction
of their homes and villages
continued even after Myanmar said
military operations
had come to an end.
These pictures were filmed
by the BBC from the Bangladeshi side
of the border on the 10th
of September last year, five days
after the supposed ceasefire.
This was your house?
This is my house.
That was also the day that
Irfan lost everything.
A father of four, he was
the secondary school teacher back
in Myanmar and lived
here with his extended family.
Who is that?
That is my brother.
The authorities told
them they'd be safe,
and then the soldiers came.
TRANSLATION: The military surrounded
the whole area and they had weapons.
They opened fire as people
were trying to leave.
Some escaped, but
others were killed.
My brother was at home that
day, but he went out
to check on his shop.
He never came back.
We don't know if he
was burned alive.
We still haven't heard anything.
Away from the main camp,
another area is home
to Hindus from Myanmar,
who were caught up in the violence.
They have been identified as among
the first to be repatriated.
But even they are not ready to go
without international protection.
TRANSLATION: If the United Nations
goes with us, the Hindus,
we hope we will get security
and be happy.
If they are there, and we face
any problems, the whole
world will know about it.
For now, it seems most likely
that the children of these camps
will grow up here without a country
to call their own.
The UN's access to their old
home, Rakhine state,
is severely restricted.
They too call for change
and for the Rohingya
to be doubly recognised.
At this stage, I think
it is premature to talk
about returns in large numbers
until three conditions exist.
Number one, the issue
of citizenship and legal
identity must be addressed.
Number two, there has to be a safe
and secure environment
for refugees to return to.
Number three, reconstruction
and the re-establishment
of services must occur.
Services here are more organised.
But it's a precarious existence.
A community who have been
marginalised and persecuted are now
entirely dependent on aid,
and on what others
decide for their future.
The aid agency Unicef is calling
this 'a children's crisis'
because of the large numbers
of children who live in these camps.
It's also voicing concern
about the 25,000 refugee babies
who will be born here this year
and will lack any legal papers.
Last September, our correspondent
Justin Rowlatt met one
Rohingya woman who crossed
the border heavily pregnant.
He's been back to see how
she and her new baby are.
Mohammed is three and
a half months old now.
Hello Mohammed.
Hello.
But right from birth,
he's faced discrimination.
The Bangladeshi authorities
won't issue birth
certificates to Rohingya
babies, so officially
Mohammed does not exist.
We first met his mother the day
she escaped from Myanmar.
She was nine months pregnant.
She told me how the
Myanmar army and local
Buddhists had attacked her village.
But their troubles
were far from over.
Guards moved her and her family on.
They said there was
land over the hill.
But not enough for everyone.
Rishida's husband tried to stake out
a plot, but he was driven
off my other refugees.
Her family had to sleep
in the open, despite
the rains.
Finally, they found space
to build a rickety shack.
Her baby was born on
the soggy muddy floor.
TRANSLATION: He was born right here.
There was no midwife,
no medicine, no mat,
no wood to light a fire.
It was so painful, but by God's
grace a girl from next door came and
cut the umbilical chord and then
I picked him up from the mud.
That is how my baby
came into this world.
Luckily, Mohammed
hasn't caught cholera
or diphtheria - two
of the
deadly diseases that have
broken out in the camps.
But not having any official identity
will be a real problem.
It will be hard for him to get
into school, to register for
services and may make getting back
into Myanmar even more difficult
for his family.
So, like the rest of the refugees,
he will have to eke
out an existence here
in Bangladesh - stateless,
with just a shack for
a
home, denied even the dignity
of an official identity.
There were talks between Bangladesh
and Myanmar about beginning the
process of people returning, but
those talks are hard to reconcile
with the fact that the refugees are
still crossing the border and
arriving here in Bangladesh and they
say violence against them is
continuing. Some of those I met are
resigned to spending the rest of
their lives here. But others say if
their rights are guaranteed, they
will will go home. Thank you.
The First Minister of Scotland,
Nicola Sturgeon, has warned
that a hard Brexit could take more
than £12 billion a year out
of Scotland's economy.
She's pledged to make
the case for keeping the UK
in the EU single market,
after publishing the analysis
by the Scottish Government.
The UK Government insists
it is seeking a Brexit deal that
will work for the whole of the UK,
as our Scotland Editor
Sarah Smith reports.
Will Brexit leave us
better off or worse?
The Scottish Government today
published figures they say show what
leaving the EU might cost
each and every Scot.
The Scottish Government analysis
suggests that by 2030
staying in the EU single market
will cost the Scottish
economy £4 billion,
or £688 per person.
A free trade agreement
similar to Canada's deal
with the EU would cost the Scottish
economy £9 billion, or
£1,610 per person.
While reverting to
WTO trading rules if
there is a hard Brexit could cost
nearly £13 billion, or over £2,000
per person.
These figures relate
specifically to the Scottish
economy, but they're very much
intended to persuade people and
politicians across the whole of
the UK that the United Kingdom could
stay in the EU single market once
we've left the European
Union itself.
Staying in the single market
is the only option that makes sense.
Theresa May has been incredibly
clear from the beginning that she
believes the UK has
to leave the single market.
Do you really think
you'll change her mind?
I don't want to be facetious,
who knows whether
Theresa May will even be
Prime Minister by the time these
negotiations conclude?
The House of Commons can
if it chooses to decide
not to allow Theresa May to go down
the road that is in her narrow party
political interest to go down
and instead force a path
that is much more in the interests
of the country overall.
The UK Government
dispute the figures.
Anybody can make end of the
world-type predictions, but
rather than focussing on the most
negative scenario, what we should be
doing is working together to get
the best possible deal.
Cathy and Alistair
Cunningham represent the
great Brexit divide.
She voted to leave, he to remain.
What do they make
of today's figures?
The SNP is making the
case for Scotland and
trying to get as good a deal
as possible for Scotland
and the rest of UK,
but particularly for Scotland.
I don't think it would be a good
deal if you're half in and half out.
In five year's time,
we'll all be laughing
about the fact that we all said
we were going to hell in a
hand cart.
Many Leave voters will share Cathy's
scepticism about any
economic predictions over Brexit,
while Alistair of course disagrees.
And so the debate goes
on in the Cunningham
family and far beyond.
Dolores O'Riordan, lead singer
of the Irish rock band
the Cranberries, has died
suddenly at the age of 46.
She'd been involved in a recording
session in London when she died.
The Cranberries dominated the 1990s
album charts - selling
40 million records around the
world, as our entertainment
correspondent
Lizo Mzimba reports.
# Do you have to let it linger?
Linger was the first
song Dolores O'Riordan
ever wrote with the Cranberries.
It turned her and
the band into stars.
# I just want to be with you.#
Linger was about teenage rejection.
# I'm such a fool for you...
Folks, do me a favour
please welcome and just in
time for thanksgiving -
The Cranberries.
Their rapid success particularly
in America soon saw the
young singer song writer move
on to weightier topics.
# With their tanks and bombs...
Zombie was a powerful
protest song written after
two young children were
killed by an IRA bomb.
# In your head # Zombie #
Zombie
Last year the band were ready
to tour once more, but it was cut
short by health problems.
I have had health
issues a lot in the
last few years, but one
of the worst problems
is I had a disk problem
in
my back and I had
stopped playing guitar.
Today the Irish Prime Minister
said that for anyone who
grew up in Ireland in the nineties,
Dolores O'Riordan was the voice of
a generation.
# You got me wrapped
around your fingers...
A generation tonight
mourning the loss of one of
music's great talents.
# Do you have to let it linger?
#
The singer Dolores O'Riordan - who
passed away suddenly earlier today.
The England cricketer, Ben Stokes,
has been charged with affray,
along with two other men,
after an incident outside a
nightclub in Bristol last September.
The 26-year-old was ruled out
of the Ashes Series in Australia
following his arrest.
He says he's keen to have
an opportunity to clear his name.
The former Manchester United
footballer, Ryan Giggs,
has been unveiled as the new manager
of Wales.
He's signed a four-year deal
and this is his first
permanent job as a manager.
As a player Giggs was capped
64 times by Wales.
Countless tributes have been
paid to Cyrille Regis -
the former West Brom
and England footballer, who's
died at the age of 59.
He was among the first
black players to compete
at the highest level
in England in the late 1970s
and was regularly subjected
to racist abuse from the terraces.
His wife said he'd come
into football the hard way
and never lost his passion
for the game, as our sports
editor, Dan Roan, reports.
COMMENTATOR: Regis taking it well
on the chest and a lovely piece of
control by Regis.
And, oh, what a great shot.
What a goal!
Cyrille Regis didn't just
lead the line, he led
the way.
Known for his pace and power,
he broke through at West Brom
in the 1970s - a time
when there were few black players.
It made the situation
at the Hawthorns all the
more unique, where Regis, Brendan
Batson and Lawrie Cunningham -
together nicknamed the Three Degrees
- were at the heart of
one of the era's
most exciting teams.
At a time of high racial tension,
they were subject to
relentless abuse.
COMMENTATOR: The booing
of the black players...
We were used to 3 or 4,
10,000 people shouting racist
racist abuse at you,
throwing bananas on the pitch and
monkey chants and that stuff.
So I just took it
as if it was somebody
trying to intimidate me.
Just the third black
player to represent
England, not everyone
welcomed his debut.
I got a letter through the post,
which said, you know, "If you
put your feet on that Wembley turf,
you'll get one of those for
you knee."
And it was a bullet.
As a kid, I didn't know what was
going on, but you could hear the
monkey chants... We all knew that...
You just had to get on with it. And
like you know you see the... What
they talk about racist abuse now is
nothing. Compared to... What it was
then.
The tributes laid
here at the Hawthorns
today are testament
to a man who became
a symbol of the fight
against
racism in Britain.
The legacy of Cyrille Regis
felt not just here at
West Brom, but throughout his sport.
A role model for a generation
of black footballers inspired by his
dignity and determination.
He was just a leader.
He was a trail-blazer.
He was - we stood on his shoulders,
that is how strong he was, as black
players.
And it's...
Sad.
Cyrille  Regis was far more
than a mere player -
a pioneer who faced up
to the acceptable side of football
and helped it move forward.
His impact on and off the pitch
cannot be overstated.
Today's tributes to one
of the real pioneers
of English football ,
Cyrille Regis.
Newsnight is coming up on BBC two.
Tonight is the war on sugar paying
off and what impact is it having on
companies? And we ask the Government
why they can'ted continued to give
contract Tosca Rhyl yon.