I'm Duncan mainland and this is
snowboard addiction today we're going to
work on euro carbs
euro carbs are a really fun maneuver to
do on the hill and they're guaranteed to
up your sex appeal by at least 10% no
matter where you go if you do a euro
carve people are going to stop and have
a look at what you're up to
ideally the terrain you're looking for
to Euro carve is smooth evenly groomed
terrain it's really hard to do it in
powder or anywhere that it's lumpy bumpy
or full of little rocks a euro carve is
essentially a toeside carve turn where
your chest is as low to the ground as
you can get it so before you start your
carving you should have a pretty firm
grasp on how to carve on your heel side
and your toe side to start working your
way towards the euro carve start just
getting as low as you can on your normal
everyday carve turn by getting lower and
lower it's going to get you in the
position you need to really lock into
that euro carve as you get lower and
lower start putting your back hand out
and touching the ground it's also a good
idea start pushing your knees forward
and seeing how close you can get your
knees to the ground as you start feeling
comfortable with this lower carve style
see if you can grab on to your heel edge
with your front hand by grabbing on to
your heel edge with your front hand it
puts you right in that position you need
to jump into the euro carve when you're
ready to really lock into that euro car
you're actually going to be throwing
your body weight down the hill learning
how to euro carve you're going to get
covered in snow from head to toe but
that's part of the enjoyment and once
you get really good at them you're going
to love doing them all over the place
and all your friends are going to love
watching them enjoy your euro carves I'm
Duncan mainland
this is snowboard addiction and our goal
is to improve your riding
I hope you guys have been learning from
our snowboard tutorials if you want to
see more of them make sure to subscribe
to our Channel
plus visit our website
snowboardaddiction.com we have a lot
more detailed fully tutorials available
there