^_^字幕制作：春秋风月^_^
Hey    you  grab
dinner yet?
No
Let's  swing  by  Luigi's
Didn't you  hear?  The
old  man  shut the  doors
He  moved  to  Tampa
Oh    damn
Best  pizza
in  the  neighborhood
Luigi's  was
an  institution
Well    l  figured  he  should
get out of the  'hood…
while  he  was  still  alive
Which  is  more
than  l  can  say for you
Hey    these
are  my streets
Somebody's  gotta
watch  over  'em
Unit  1 2    we  have  a  927－－
Denver  on  Carlton
and  Third
Suspicious  circumstances
woman  screaming
We're  on  it
Just another  day
at the  office
You  stupid  ho
You  think you  could
up  and  leave  me?
Huh?
You  think  l'd  just  let
you  walk  away from  me?
Look  at you!
Oh    yeah
But you  take  what  l  give you
and  you  throw  it away
Now    how  does that
make  me feel?
Some  dumb－ass  runaway…
And  l  took you…
molded  you
made you  into  a  goddess
And  you  throw  it
all  away to  become  what?
Nothing
'Cause that's  all
you  are  right  now…nothing
Rigo    Rigo    please
Please  what?
Don't  hurt  me
You  betray  my  love
try to  deny  my  power
No    l  didn't－－
You  disrespected  me!
And  now…
lt's time to  pay
No    no!
Drop the  knife!
Well    well
what  have  we  here?
l  said  put
the  knife  down  now！
Ha  ha  ha.  Will  you
look  at  him  shine?
That's the  light
gleamin'  off  his  armor
Looks  like your  very
own  Sir  Galahad's…
come to  rescue your
sorry  little  ass
This  is your
last warning
You  heard  him
No  need  for  anyone
to  get  hurt
Hurt?
You  can't  hurt  me
Tell  him  why
Please…
Because  l  am  the
power  and  the  glory…
the  darkness
and  the  light
Judge    jury…
and  executioner
－Aah!  Aah!
-Yaah!
No!
This  is  unit  1 2…
Shots fired
Suspect down
Request  back－up
ambulance…
Repeat:  Suspect down
Third  and  Carlton
Hey
You  OK?
Yeah.  Why wouldn't  l  be?
Just another  scumbag
off the  streets
Hey    Dirty  Harry
you  just took  a  life
Stop  pretending  it doesn't
make your  guts turn
Nah    l'm  not  pretending
anything    Angie.  l  mean…
l'm  just doin'  my job
OK
Hello?
Nice  shootin'    Galahad
Who  is this?
Oh    you're  lookin'  at  me
You  didn't think  it'd  be
that easy    did  you?
Hello.  Hello?!
lt's  not over
Eric  Boggs    policeman
These  are  his  streets
his  people
He  sees  himself
as their  guardian  angel…
but  Eric's  sense  of duty
and  his  sanity…
are  about to  be tested  by
a  most  uncommon  criminal…
in  the  Twilight Zone
You're traveling
to  another  dimension…
a  dimension  not only
of sight and  sound…
but of  mind…
A journey
into  a  wondrous  land…
whose  boundaries  are  only
that of the  imagination
You're  entering…
春秋风月字幕工作室
http://gdyfdjg.blog.163.com/
^_^=== 春秋风月 原创翻译 ===^_^
You  sure you  don't
want  us to take you  home?
You're  lookin'  at  it
You  gonna  be  OK?
Yeah.  Don't worry
about  me
Anything's  better
than  working  for  Rigo
Take  care    Galahad
1 7  going  on  40
Feel  like
getting  caffeinated?
Yeah.  Gimme  a  minute
All  right
Hey    Carla
Look    um    officer－－
l  just  have
one  question
Was there  anyone  else  in
the  alley with  you  and  Rigo?
Like  who?
One  of  Rigo's
posse  members    maybe
Rigo  had  no  posse
He  didn't trust  his  ladies
He  didn't trust  nobody
Why are you  asking?
Never  mind
Just a  prank  call    l  guess
You  don't…
remember  me    do you?
l'm  Hector  Arroyo's  sister
Damn.  l  thought
it was you
You  know  Hector's
in  San  Quentin?
Yeah    l  heard
lt doesn't  have to  be
that way    though    you  know?
Look    um    don't  let
that  Sir  Galahad  thing…
go to your  head
l  don't  need
any  more  rescuing
Hey    it doesn't  hurt to  have
someone  lookin'  out for you
lf  l  didn't  have  my  uncle
l'd  probably  be  in  the  cell…
right  next to your
brother  Hector
Well    l  don't
have  no  uncle
lf you  need  to talk
You  be  safe  out  here    OK?
l  said  put
the  knife  down  now！
This  is your  last warning
Yaah!
This  is  Boggs
Hello?
Good－bye
What's  up    Galahad?
The  ho  was  mine
Who the  hell  are you?
She's  a  keeper
A  real  money－machine
Whoever this  is－－
She's  mine!
And  this time  l'm  gonna
finish  what  l  started!
This the  guy?
Officer?  You  with  me?
lt's  him.
Rodrigo  Valentine
l  just  keep  expectin'
him  to  sit  up
8 years  on  the job
hasn't  happened  yet
l'll  be  right  back
What are you  doin'  here?
Johnson  told  me
where you  were
So    the  real  question  ls
what are  we  doin'  here?
l  was just checkin'
somethin'  out
Go  on.  This  should
be  interesting
OK
You're  never  gonna  believe
who's  been  callin'  me  up
The  hooker?
No    her  pimp
How  many  pimps
that girl  have?
Well    as far  as  l  know
she  only  had  one
You  mean  this  guy…
this  guy  right  here…
the  one  with  the  gaping  hole
in  his  chest?
l  know
it sounds  crazy…
but－－but  he  said  he  was
comin'  back for  Carla
Oh    man    that doesn't sound
crazy.  That  is  crazy
Well    Johnson's
tracin' the  calls…
but  l'm  tellin' you
l  know  what  l  heard
Look    Boggs    takin'  a  life
is  a  big  deal
lt will  eat away at you
until  you  talk to  someone
You  think this
is  all  in  my  head?
l've  seen  this  crap  before
You're feelin'  guilty
for  killin' this  creep…
and  this  is
your  subconscious…
tryin' to find  a  way
to  deal  with  it
Nah    l  checked
this  guy's files
This  man  was  into  all
sorts  of twisted  stuff－－
satanic  rituals
the  black  arts
Doesn't  make  him
any  less  dead
You're  right.
You're  absolutely  right
Except for  one thing
And  what's that?
My  phone
won't stop  ringin'
Gimme that
Hello?
Hello?!
There's  nobody there
This  is  Boggs
l'm  comin'
for  her tonight…
Gonna  cut  her  ear to  ear…
And  there  ain't a  thing
you  can  do  about  it
Hello?
ls  anyone there?
This  is  all  in  your  head.
You  know that    don't you?
l  want you
to  promise  me…
you're  gonna  talk
to  somebody.  Soon
What  is  she
your  girlfriend  now?
l  have to talk
to  her    Angie
Carla    we  have to talk
Yeah    well    it's  gonna
cost you  1 00  bucks
Listen  to  me…
You  need  to  get outta  here.
Out of the  city
What for?
l  think you're  in  danger
What  kind  of danger?
Your  life's
been  threatened
lf you're tryin' to  get
me to  quit the  life－－
Look    l'm  tryin'
to  protect you
Well    l  don't  need
your  protection    Eric
What  l  need
is to  pay  my  rent
Come to  my  place
tonight    OK?
ls that what
this  is  about?
You－-you  tryin' to  get
yourself some free tail?
Carla    listen  to  me－－
you're  not saying  anything
worth  listenin' to
Carla    please…
Carla!
Can  you  blame  her?
Let's just circle
the  block  a  few times
Why?!
l  have to  keep
an  eye  on  her
Eric    l  did
some  checking
Rigo's  body was  sent to
a  crematorium  yesterday
He  nothin'  but a  pile
of ashes  by  now
What    are you  gonna  worry
about a  pile  of ashes?
l  don't  know!
l  don't  know
what to think    OK?
Well    l  do.  We  need
to  get  back to  work
Hi.  l'm  not  in.
Leave  a  message…
after the tone    and
l'll  get  right  back to you
Hey    Boggs    it's  Angela.
l  need  to talk to you…
about Carla  Arroyo
Yeah    l'm  here
l  just got the  call
l  don't  know  how
to tell  you  this    but…
But what?
What's  wrong?
lt's  Carla.  She's  dead
They're  still  combin' the
area  for the  murder  weapon
They won't find  one
Boggs    Rigo  had
nothin' to  do  with  this
Just  like
he  said  he  would
No    he  didn't
This  was  a  pissed－off john
or  some  crack－head
Look    he  laid  it out.  He
said  he  was  gonna  come
Eric    listen  to  me
l've  been  listenin'
to you    Angie
And  what did  it get  me
huh?  She's  dead
That's  right…
But you  know  what?  She
wasn't  killed  by some  ghost
There  was  nothin'  supernatural
about this    Eric
That's  easy
for you  to  say
You're  not the  one
gettin' the  calls
Look    this  girl
was  in  danger…
every single time  she
stepped  out onto the  street
What were you  gonna  do
Eric    watch  over  her  24－7?
That's  not your job
Look    Eric    go  home.
Get some  rest
“  My way of  lovin' you
is  like  bullets  in  the  rain  ”
“  Ain't a  single  place to  hide
l'll  always  see you  again  ”
“ You  should  really stop
denyin' yourself ”
“  Of the  sweeter things
in  life  ”
“  That can't  be  bought
with  broken  words  ”
“  Priceless  gifts…  ”
You're that cop    right?
The  one  who  saved  her
from  Rigo?
l  guess  all  you  did…
was just  buy  her
a  little  bit  more time
“  l  feel  like  l'm  hangin'
in  the  coldest  breeze  ”
“  At the  whim  of your  emotion
l'm  apt to  please  ”
“  Here  come the  queen  of  pain
with  the  ice－dusted  throne  ”
“  The  breeze  will  sting
and  a  passion  l  own  ”
“  365  will  equal  360  ”
“  l  hope you  know    'cause
'cause    'cause  ”
“ You  ”
“  And  me  ”
“  Were  meant to  be  ”
“  Destiny ”
“  True  ”
“  Complete  ”
“ You  and  me  ”
“  Destiny ”
What do you  want
you  son  of a  bitch?
Who's there?!
l'm  scared
lt's  so  dark
Carla?
Oh    God.  Here  he  comes!
What?!
He's  here!
Where  are you?!
Help  me    please    help  me!
Help  how?!
Nooo!
－What do  l  do?
－Stop!  No!
Stop    help  me!
Someone    please  help  me!
Noooo!
Oh    God!  Ohhhh…
No!
Eric?
Eric
What are you  doing?
We're  on  duty  in  1 5
You're  on  duty.  l'm
takin' the  night off
What's  up?
l  just  need  some time
to  work this through
Hey    no  shame  in  that
Eric    you're  gonna  be  OK
Yeah
All  right
All  right    you  bastard
listen  to  me－－
Boggs.  lt's  me    Johnson
What do you  want?
That trace  report
you  asked  for?
l  just got  it
You  did?
Those  calls?
They've  all  been  comin'
from  a  pay  phone…
in  the  alley where
you  killed  that  pimp
And  you  know
what's  weird?
That  phone's  been  outta
service for  months
Yeah.  Th-thanks    Johnson
Sure
l'm  here
Where  are you?
Where  are you    Rigo?
Rigo!
Right  behind  you
Galahad
Here  l  am    Galahad
And  here  l  am    Rigo
Tell  him    ho
Tell  him  who  owns you
Rigo
Hear that?
She  knows
This fool  owns  no  one
He's just a  two－bit  pimp
a  nothing
Just a  little  bit closer
l  saved  you  once…
And  l  can  do  it again
Come  on
l'm  waitin' for ya
Aah!
l  should've  never
left you  alone
lt's  a  real  shame    huh?
What do you  got?
Well    it  looks  like…
he  was  shot with  his  own
weapon    close  range
l'm  gonna  run
the  gun  for  prints…
but judging  from
the  angle  of entry…
and  the  powder  residue
it  looks  like  suicide
He  was  in  a  really
bad  place…
but  l  never thought that  he－－
A  real  shame
Hello
Angela
Eric?
Everything's  OK
Carla's  safe  now
l'm  here to  protect  her
Officer  Eric  Boggs
became  a  policeman…
to  protect and  serve
the  innocent…
a  duty  he took
very seriously…
which  is  why  he
is  still  on  patrol
His  new  beat?
The  Twilight Zone