春秋风月字幕站
http://gdyfdjg.blog.163.com/
^_^=== 春秋风月 原创翻译 ===^_^
You've  still  got
a  few  minutes
So?
Well    maybe you  want
to  look  it over...
one  more time?
Ah    l  didn't study
Ben    this test
counts for  a  third...
of your final  grade
l'll  have
to  give you  an  “F.”
Yeah    that's  OK
3  pages  by  Friday    people
Answer
the  immortal  question :
lf they  had  lived...
would  Romeo  and  Juliet
have  stayed  together...
or  were they just
Shakespeare's  version...
of Justin  and  Britney?
Romeo  and  Juliet
killed  themselves...
'cause they were  ass  hats
Smile.  Your  day's
officially over
l'm  not smiling  till
next week    when  my days...
as  a  high  school  teacher
are  officially over
What did  the  little  rat
bastards  do this time?
Please.  They don't
do  anything
They don't work.
They don't  listen
They don't care
And    as  of  next week
neither  do  l
You're  burned  out    that's
all.  You  need  a  break
A  permanent  break
You  take the job  seriously
That's  what  makes you
a  great teacher
Past tense    please
OK.  Fine
That's  what  made  you
a  great teacher
Deep  down    you  love the
little  rat  bastards...
and  they  love you
Uhh!
Oh    yeah.
They  love  me    all  right
They  love  me  so  much
Meet  Rachel  Stark
She  may think  she's  ready
to  quite  her job...
and  leave  her  students
behind    but today...
this teacher's  gonna  learn
a  lesson  in  commitment...
courtesy of
the  Twilight Zone
Hey    geek
Slow  down    Jose
Why don't you
turn  that thing  down?
Do  something  back  here
would  you?!
l  paid  my fare!
l  got  my  rights!
Maybe you  should  calm  down
Call  the  cops!
l  want these  kids
off the  bus    right  now!
Oh    God
You're traveling
to  another  dimension...
a  dimension  not only
of sight and  sound...
but of  mind
A journey  into
a  wondrous  land...
whose  boundaries  are  only
that of the  imagination
You're  entering...
That smells  really good
You're  late
Yes    l  am.
Uh    game  went  into  overtime
And  we  still  lost
Uh...oh    and  then
l  heard  about your  car
That sucks
Yeah
You  all  right?
Something  happened
on  the  way  home
There  was  a  man  on  the  bus
He  had  a  heart attack.
l  tried  to  give  him  CPR...
but...he  died
That  must  have  been  awful
lt was
Have you  ever
seen  anyone  die?
Yeah    my grandfather
when  l  was  1 0
Did  anything...weird  happen?
Weird  how?
Before the  man  died...
l  saw this...
light around  his face
Like  a  halo?
Less  cheesy    but    yeah
That's  weird
The thing  is    l  saw
the  light on  Jose    too
Who?
Jose  Molina
Sophomore.  One  of  my
English  Lit  kids
He  was  riding
his  skateboard
l  thought  it was just
something  in  my eye    but...
What?
Nothing
Hey    Jose  was just fine
l  was  kind  of counting
on  you  to  laugh...
and  tell  me  it
was  all  in  my  head
l'm  sure  it  is
But  l  don't think
it's  a  coincidence...
that you're－-you're
seeing  strange  lights...
right after  giving
notice  at the  school
Meaning?
Meaning    uh...
maybe you're feeling
a  little  guilty
What for?
For  leaving  the  kids...
for  giving  up  on  teaching
Whatever you  say...
you  still  started  out
like the  rest of  us...
wanting  to  make
a  difference
lt's－－it's  gonna
be  hard  to  let that go
Well    here  l  am...
letting  go
Those  kids  will  be
just fine  without  me...
and  l'll  be  more than  fine
without them
l  just  had
a  weird  afternoon
That's  all
So  why does  Mercutio  say...
“A  plague  on  both
your  houses”?
He  wanted  everyone  dead
But  Romeo  was
his friend    right?
Why would  he
want  his friend  to  die?
Arlie?
Um    Mercutio  was  dying
He  was  all  alone
He  didn't
have  any friends
Bet you  know  what
that feels  like    huh?
－Shut  up.
－Brian－－
Ms.  Stark    you  OK?
l'm  sorry to  have
to tell  you  this
Jose  Molina...
was  hit  by a  car...
on  his  way  home
from  school  yesterday
He  died  this  morning
Least  his  parents  got
another  20  bambinos...
running  around
at  home    right?
Go to the  principal's
office    Brian!
That  kind  of talk
is  unacceptable!
What are you
looking  at    Tool?
Hmm
Anyone  who  wants to  see
the  school  counselor－－
the  school  counselor...
there's  a  sign－up  sheet
in  her  office
His  noble  soul
has  climbed  to the  clouds
He  was too young
to  leave this  earth
Romeo and Juliet
Act  3    Scene  one
Hey...you  can't  be  in  here
He's  my  uncle
lt's  almost  midnight.
Where  have you  been?
l  went to the  hospital
Are you  all  right?
l'm  fine
l  went to the  lCU
l  saw the  light
on  a  man  there
He  was  all  alone.
He  didn't  have  any family...
so  l  sat  next to  his  bed
and  held  his  hand
He  died  an  hour  ago
lt could  be
a  coincidence
Did  you  hear  about Jose?
The  lights
are  not  in  my  head
They're  real
Why  is this  happening?
W－what's  it  mean?
lt just  means that...
you  did  the  right thing
quitting  your job
lt's－－it's just a  sign  that
you  need  a  rest.  That's  all
l  wish  l  could  believe that
How  can  l  help?
Can  you  make  it stop?
Ms.  Stark?
What's  wrong?
Mr.  Carr    l  need
to talk to you
What  is  it?
lt's the  students.
They're  in  danger
What  kind  of danger?
Did  you  overhear
something?
We  have to  send  them  home
Get them  out of the  building
and  somewhere  safe
Safe from  what?
All  l  know  is...
something  bad
is  going  to  happen
You  protecting  someone?
A  student  maybe?
No.  lt's  nothing  like that
What then?
Talk to  me    Rachel
Right  before Jose  Molina
was  killed    l  saw...
A  light...
On  his face
A few  hours  later...
he  was  dead
l've  seen  the  same  light
on  2  other  people
They  both  died    too
Today the  light
is  on  the  students
There  were  so  many of them
And  you  think that  means
they're  going  to  die
l  know they are
Ms.  Stark?
l'm  sorry    but...
are you  coming  back
to  class?
Give  us  a  moment
You  have to  believe  me
You  wanted  a  rest.
Clearly    you  need  one
Mr.  Carr!
Tomorrow's your  last day
anyway
lt's  probably a  good  thing
He    uh...
he  asked  me to  make  sure
that you  were  OK
And  to    uh    make  sure that
you  left the  building...
before  he  had  security
escort you  out
l  know  what  l  saw
The  lights  aren't a  sign
l  should  quit  my job
They're  a  sign
l  need  to  do  my job
Protecting  these  kids－－
that's  our job    right?
Yes    yes    but  protect
them  from  what?
From  who?
l  don't  know  but...
why else...
Why  is this  happening?
Look    Principal  Carr
is  serious
He  wants you
off the  grounds
Just go  home    OK?
l  will  keep  an  eye
on  everything  here
l  promise
Ms.  Stark?
Last day    huh?
Apparently
l－－l  heard  about  it...
How you  think that
people  are  going  to  die
And  l  was just wondering...
how  many  people  we  were
talking  about?
We're  not talking
about  it at all
Why  not?
ls  it  because you  see
the  light on  my  face?
No
l  don't
But you  would  tell  me
if you  did    right?
Uh    because
l'd  want to  know
l'd  tell  you
l  like you    Ms.  Stark
You  know    you're
all  about the truth
l  like you    too    Ben
So  what are you
doing  now?
Go  home    l  guess
Yeah    good－－good  idea.  Um...
it's  better
if you're  not  here
Bye    Ms.  Stark
Good－bye    Ben
Kay
l  need  a  favor
Can  you  get  me the  locker
combination  master  list?
You're  kidding    right?
You  leave  me
with  little  choice
Mr.  Carr    it's  Ben
He's  going  to  hurt the  others
but  l  don't  know  how
l  already asked  you
to  leave  once
Now  l'm  calling  the  police
Perfect
This  isn't scheduled?
Of course  not
Please    just  listen
to  me    Mr.  Carr!
Let's  go!
Please    if you'd  just
look  in  his journals!
l  don't  know  what's
going  on  here...
but  if  l  find  out
you're  responsible－－
You  have to find  Ben
Keep  moving    people!
Come  on    buddy
Security    help  out    please
Keep  moving
That's  right
Let's  go.  Go.
Move.  Move.  Move
Come  on
Let's  go.  Rachel!
Hey    Ms.  Stark
Hi    Ben
You're  not  here to    uh...
give  me the  speech    are you?
What speech?
You  know    how    uh...
Killing  is  wrong    Benjamin
You're  a  smart  kid
l  think you
already  know that
You  hate them
as  much  as  l  do!
You  hate  all  of  us.
That's  why you  quit
That's  not true
They slashed  your tires
Brian  and  his  little－－
his  little  maggot friends
Stop  right there!
l'm  not going  to  let you
kill  anyone
How you  gonna  stop  me?
Aah!
Run!  Run!
Ben!
Aah!
Rachel!
Oh    God    Rachel
lt－－it's  all  right  now
They're  all  right
Yeah
You  did  good
lt's  OK.
Help's  on  its  way
Don't  leave  me
lt's  so  beautiful
What do you  see?
A  light
Rachel?
Rachel  Stark  didn't ask
to  be  special
She  didn't want
to  be  a  hero
But sometimes fate
reaches  out a  cold  hand...
to tap your  shoulder...
from  the  Twilight Zone