Tell  me  again
Again?
Once  more
You  gonna  stare
at that  ring  all  night?
l  love  it
[Whispering]
l  love you
Good  thing
since  we're  spending
the  rest of our  lives
together  and  all
Tell  me  again
about the  house
l  drove  by  it  last week
and  it's  still  for  sale
Now    it's  not too  big－－
No
Just enough  room
for you  and  me
For  now
And  it's  on  the  edge
of a  cliff
by the  ocean...
so you  can  wake  up
every  morning
and  see the  sun  rise
over the  water
When  can  l  see  it?
Soon.  [Chuckles]
Does  it  have
a  picket fence?
l've  always  wanted  a  house
with  a  white  picket fence
l'll  put one  up
[Laughs]
And  we'll  paint
the  door  red
My grandmother  says
a  bright  red  front door
is  considered  friendly
and  welcoming
You're  cute
Weird    but cute
Alec!
Damn!
l  got distracted
No!
[Groans]
Hi    Sean
Yeah    l  know.  l'm  late
l'll  see you  soon
For  Edie  Durant
life  as  she  knew  it
ended  over  a  year  ago
on  a  wet country  road
But today she'll  get
a  second  chance  at  happiness...
because  Edie  Durant's future
is  about to  develop
in  a  place  where
the  clearest  picture
isn't always
black  and  white
and  still  life  isn't
quite  so  still...
the  Twilight Zone
Sorry
You  look  a  mess
l  didn't sleep
Nightmares?
The  usual
Edie    we  need  to talk
Are you  breaking  up
with  me?
l'm  serious
Good    because  my  life
isn't serious  enough
Too  much  levity
that's  my  problem
When  is the  last time
you  picked  up  a  camera?
Not since the  accident
You  don't see  any
of our  old  friends  anymore
You  don't work
lt's  been  a  year
and  you're  no  better  off－－
Don't do this to  me    OK?
l  have to
l'm  afraid  for you
l  was  in  a  bad  place
l  won't go  back.  l  promise
Good
So you  don't want
to  go  back there...
and  you  can't stay
where you  are
Your  only option
is to  move forward
What do you  want from  me?
Just go  out and  shoot...
24  pictures  of anything
l  don't  know
Edie    Alec  wouldn't
want you  to  live  like this
A year  of  mourning
is  long  enough
OK
春秋风月字幕站
http://gdyfdjg.blog.163.com/
^_^=== 春秋风月 原创翻译 ===^_^
Hey    baby.  lt's  me
lt's  on  the  edge  of a  cliff
by the  ocean...
so you  can  wake  up
every  morning
and  see the  sun  rise
over the  water
lt's  our  house
Oh    my God
Our  dream  house
You're traveling
to  another  dimension...
a  dimension  not only
of sight and  sound...
but of  mind
A journey
into  a  wondrous  land
whose  boundaries
are  only that
of the  imagination
You're  entering...
Ooh...
these  are  great!
Look
This  is  good
Picture  of a  house
Me  and  Alec
used  to  dream  about
buying  a  cottage
just  like this
Our  last  night together...
he told  me
that  he'd  found  it...
the  perfect  house...
only  he  never  got a  chance
to  show  it to  me
OK    and...
l  didn't take this  picture
l  don't even  know
where this  house  is
But when  l  went
to  develop the  pictures
from  the  graveyard
it was  in  with  them...
right  in  the  middle
of the  roll
Edie    you  haven't  been
in  that darkroom
in  a  year
So  maybe  Alec  took this
picture  of this  house
and  somehow  it got
mixed  in  with  the  stuff
you  shot yesterday
l  checked  the  negative.
lt's  on  there...
but  l  didn't take
this  picture
Sean    it's  in  color
l  only shoot
black  and  white
Well    there's  got to  be
a  logical  explanation
Yeah    it's  a  miracle.
Call  the  Vatican
lt's  not that simple
Hey    Edie
Hey    Phil.  Thanks
Do you  mind?
No    go  ahead
At  least consider
the  possibility
That what?
That Alec  is trying
to  communicate  with  you?
You  know    Sally Maher
booked  a  show  downtown
She'll  be taking  most
of  her  stuff with  her
Do you  want  her  spot?
You  want  me to  hang
my  pictures  here?
Yeah    bring  in  some framed
prints.  We'll  put them  up
l  don't  know
No    no    she'll  do  it.
She'll  do  it
People  will  see your  work
Why can't you  at  least
open  your  mind
to the  idea
that this  is  real?
You're  asking  me
to  believe  something
that  is  impossible
Here  l  thought that was
part of
your job  description
Where  are you  going?
Shoot  more  pictures
see  what develops
“  Every time  it  rains  ”
“  l  listen  to the  sky ”
“  l  wonder  what's  so  great
about sunshine  ”
“  So  everybody  lives  ”
“  And  everybody dies  ”
“  And  no  one's  gonna
love you  like  l  do  ”
“  When  l  misunderstand  ”
“  And  then  misunderstood  ”
“  So  love  me  'cause you  can
and  not  because you  should  ”
You  can  look
“  But every time  it  rains  ”
What's your  name?
“  l  know  it's  good
to  be  alive  ”
“  Every time  it  rains  ”
“  l  know  l'm  trying
to  choose  a  life  ”
“  So take  it as  it comes  ”
“  And  take  me  as  l  am  ”
“  l  never  was
a  good  impostor  ”
“  Well    l  know
how to  dream...  ”
Those  my  photos?
Take them.  Put them
wherever you  want
l  don't  need
them  anymore
No    no    no    no.
What do you  say
we  make  an  occasion
out of  it?
l'll  invite  some
of the  old  gang
Kay and  Erin
and  Zack  and  Ash?
Whatever you  want
l  called  you
last  night
l  was  a  little  worried
l  was  in  the  darkroom.
l  have  something  to  show you
Listen    l  know
that  it was  my  idea
that you  got  back
into taking  pictures...
but  l'm  starting  to think
maybe  it's
a  little too  soon－－
How  did  you  do this?
This  photoshop?
lt's  on  the  negative    Sean
Alec  is  doing  this.
He  has to  be
There's  no  other
explanation
Unless you
want  it so  badly
you're  making
it  happen
That's  impossible
Now  who's  being
close－minded?
lt's  him
[Sighs]
OK    OK
say  it  is  him
What do you  think
he's trying  to  say?
He  wants  me
to  be  with  him
Or  maybe  he's
trying  to tell  you
he's  at  peace
Then  he'd  send  me
a  picture  of  him
lying  on  a  beach
in  Bermuda
He's  at this  house
waiting  for  me
When  l  find  it
we  can  be together
OK    OK    OK
Let's  say this  house
does  exist
lt could've  been  sold
or torn  down
lt's  out there.
l  know  it
l've  been  searching
the  internet
and  the  classifieds
all  night
l  haven't found  it yet
but  l  will
Why can't you
just  be  happy for  us?
Because there  is
no  "us"  anymore
Alec  is  dead
He  can't come
back to  life
There's  no  way
for you  two
to  be together  again
l  mean    really
together  unless you－－
l'll  do  what  l  have to
No    no    no.
You  don't  mean  that
You  promised  me
That was  before
Edie...
Next time
l  might  not get there
in  time to  save you
l  won't  need  you
to  save  me
l'll  be fine
l'll  be  with  Alec
Chances  are you'll  never
find  that  place
l'll  find  it
Alec'll  show  me
Oh    my God
lt's just  like
we  imagined  it
－－Hey.
－－Hey
So    you  ready?
For  what?
The  coffeehouse.
l  left you  a  message
Everyone's  coming
to  see your  pictures
l'm  not going
What?
l  have to  go  back
to the  house
What  house?
l  found  it    Sean
l  found  it.
l  took  pictures
Look
lt even  has  a  nursery
Would  you  listen
to yourself?
lt's there.
lt's  right there
Alec  wants  me to  go there
Alec  doesn't want anything
Alec  is  dead
He's  dead
and  you're  alive...
and  where  he's  gone
you  can't follow
You  know    l  thought you
of all  people    would  have faith
Why do you  want
to  ruin  this for  me?
l'm  not trying
to  ruin  anything
l'm  trying
to  protect you
From  Alec?
From  yourself
Alec  was  my  best friend
l  loved  him
like  a  brother...
and  l  don't  believe
that  he  would  want
you  to  be  with  him
if  it  meant that you  had
to  hurt yourself to  do  it
l  don't want to  hurt  myself
But you  are.
You  are.  Right  now
Edie    this  obsession
is  not  healthy
Now    this  isn't
about the  life
that you  shared  with  Alec
This  is  about death
Now  what  l  want
you  to  do?
l  want you...
to  come  down
to the  coffeehouse...
see your friends...
and  spend  one  hour
among  the  living
OK
One  hour
The  pictures
look  great    kid
Let's take
a  closer  look
at the  installation
l  have to  go
－－What?
－－l'm  sorry
He  wants  me to  go there...
right  now
Edie    you're  changing
these  pictures
l'm  not the  one  doing  it
[Sighs]
Edie    wait
l  have to  go to  him
Alec?
Please  come  out
l'll  follow you
Just tell  me  how
－－Alec.
－－Whoa    whoa
Easy there
You  OK?
Yeah.  You  just
scared  me    that's  all
Looked  like
you  might fall
Thank you
Well    come  on
Storm's  starting
to  pick  up
Let's  get out
of  here    OK?
Come  on
l'm    uh    Matthew  Forsyth
by the  way
l  own  the  little  cabin
up there
lt's  a  beautiful  place
Well    it  needs  some  work
Actually    it's  been
on  the  market for  over  a  year
My  real－estate  agent told  me
that a  woman  called
yesterday asking  about  it...
so  l  came  out
for  one  last  look
And?
Well    l  don't  know
As  soon  as  l  got  here
it's  like...
l  had  this feeling
that  maybe  l  shouldn't
sell  after  all
So    l  came  out for
a  walk to  clear  my  heard
Did  it work?
l  think  l'm  going
to  hold  on  to  it
for  a  little  while  longer...
maybe...fix  it  up  a  bit
Yeah    well
it's  a  great  house
Look    uh    can  l  ask you...
what you're  doing  out  here
dangling  over  cliffs?
l  was...um...
looking  for  someone
ls  he  here?
No.  No    l  think  he's  gone
l'm  sorry
l  thought  he
brought  me  out  here
so  we  could  be together
But  he  didn't?
No
Maybe  he  wanted
to  say good－bye
l  have to  go
l've  got to  get
back  into town
Um...look
l  hope  l'm  not
being  too forward
but you...
you  seem  a  little  lost
ls there  anything  l  can  do?
Yeah.  Yeah
fix the  house  up
Put a  picket fence
around  it
OK    l'll  do that
Um    maybe  l'll  paint
the  door  red
What did  you  say?
Oh    l  just－－
l  know  it sounds  weird
l  just－－l  heard  somewhere
that a  bright  red  front door
is  considered  friendly
and  welcoming
Yeah.
l－－l've  heard  that    too
Uh...
You  know    l  think
the  stove  still  works
Um...
You  want a...
cup  of tea  or  something?
Yeah
That'd  be  nice
OK
Edie  Durant thought
her  life  was  over...
but a  lost  love  gave  her
a  new  path  to follow
Now    Edie  is taking
her first step
back  into the  world...
and  out of
the  Twilight Zone