l'm  telling  you    l'm  sitting
across the table...
from  Trevor  Black
the  casino  owner...
the  guy that  never  loses...
and  l'm  just  lookin'
right  into  his  eyes...
and  l  knew that  l  had  him
And  then  l  blinked
l  just  let  him  bluff  me
l'm  out
Hey    just－-just
out of curiosity    huh?
Sure.  Why  not?
You  had  nothing
House  always  wins    Jonah
Honey    it just  never  ends
l  mean    from  champagne
and  fancy dinners  one  week...
to  not  knowing  if we  can
pay the  phone  bill  the  next
Eighteen  months  of this    Jonah
lt's  gotta  end.
You  gotta  just walk  away
No    no    l  can't walk  away.
Not yet.  Listen    April...
The  house  always  wins
l  just  need  to  beat the  house
one time
Once    and  then  l'm  done    OK?
And  then  we'll  escape to  Florida
and  open  the  restaurant    OK?
l'll  learn  how to  braise.
l'll  learn  how to  sautё
l  promise you
They're  not gonna
hold  that space...
in  the  Promenade forever
Baby    l  can  win.  l  just  need
a  little  money...
from  the  restaurant fund
to  get started
There's  a  reason...
we  decided  to  keep that account
untouchable
April    it's  a  loan
$500
to  be  paid  back  with  interest
Jonah...
my  love...
my sweet  boy...
no
Jonah  Beach  has  a  problem.
All  of  his  adult  life...
he's  been  trying
to  beat the  house...
and  always  comin'  up  short
But Jonah  may  have just found
the  edge  he  needs to  win...
courtesy of the  Twilight Zone
Sir    l  don't suppose
you  could  spare five  bucks...
so  l  could  get  myself a  meal?
Sure  would  appreciate  it
Man    you  hit  me  up
on  the  wrong  night
l  got  $3.00  and  a  bus  pass
to  call  my own
l  wouldn't say  no to  $3.00
Yeah    man
but  if  l  give you  $3.00...
Tomorrow  l'm  gonna  be
hittin' you  up for two
l'll  make you  a  deal.
You  look  like  a  man...
who  likes to  make  a  wager
once  in  a  while
A  wager?
Three  bucks－－
l'll  flip you  for  it
Dude
you  just  hit  me  up for five
What do  l  get  if  l  win    huh?
Bragging  rights
All  right.  All  right
Go  ahead
－Call  it.
－Heads
Oh    sorry    friend
Hey    you  know  what?
Let's  call  it tails.
Go  ahead.  Take  it
You're  a  gambler
and  a  gentleman
For you
Oh    no    no.  Forget  it
No    sir.  Fair trade
Yeah    lucky  me    huh?
Yes    you  are
Whoa!  Whoa!  Wait  up!
Whoa!  Hey!  Wait a  second!
Right over there
l  love you
Testing    one    two    three
l  know
Right over there
l  love you
春秋风月字幕站
http://gdyfdjg.blog.163.com/
^_^=== 春秋风月 原创翻译 ===^_^
You  are traveling
to  another  dimension－－
a  dimension
not only of sight and  sound...
but of  mind
A journey
into  a  wondrous  land...
whose  boundaries  are  only
that of the  imagination
You're  entering...
Watch  where you're  going
－Sorry.
-Jerk
Five    four    three...
Missed  me
Hey.  Hey    wake  up.  Wake  up
Jonah.
Jonah    where  have you  been?
lt's  2: 30
This.  l've  been  testing  this
－A tape  recorder?
－No    no    no
－This  is  my edge.
－Oh    your  edge
Yeah    you  see    some  guys－－
they  read  tells...
some  guys  count cards
but  l  have this    OK?
And  there  is  not a  house
in  the  world  that can  beat this
Wait.  No.  Hold  on.
Hold  on  one  second
l  want to  prove this to you.
See the  clock?
Clock  says  2: 31     right?
l  say that that clock  is  wrong.
l  say  it's  2: 30
Jonah?  Where  have you  been?
lt's－－
Yeah    it's  2: 30.  l  know.
You  see?  See  my edge?
l  can  go  back
up to five  minutes
Up to five  minutes    baby
Right.  You're  drunk
What?  You  mean
you  didn't just see that?
See you  jumping  around  my  bed
like  a  raving  lunatic?
Yeah    l  saw that
The－-the－－
What's the  deal
with  the tape  recorder    anyway?
This  is...
lt's just for  motivation
you  know?
To  record  little  affirmations
and  psych  myself  up
Psyched  up for  what?
Oh    no    no.  Jonah
No.  No!
April    l  have to  get  back
into the  game    OK?
To  get  back  in  the  game
l  have to  win...
and  to  win  l  have to  play
but to  play－－
You  play.  l'm  going  to  sleep
Maybe
l  could  have  said  that  better
Because  l'm  a  winner    baby
And  you  always  gotta
back the  winner
Your  lips    they say
“No    no    no.”
But your  eyes  say
“Yes    yes    yes.”
lt's－－it's  my  mom
She...
She  needs  a  colon  transplant
The thing  is    l  have
to  get  back  in  the  game...
and  it's  not about the  money
Someday
l'm  gonna  have  a  son    OK?
And  l  want to  be  able
to  look  him  in  the  eye...
and  tell  him
that  l  had  the  nerve...
that  l  stayed  in  the  game
and  l  beat the  house
l'm  not gonna  give you  $500
But  l  will  give you  two  hundred
You  do  what you  need  to  do
Then  walk  away
What are you  doing  in  there?
Nothing
Just  psyching  myself  up
“  Dream  away
dream  away    dreamer  ”
“  Fly away    lifetime  screamer  ”
“  Satellite  watchin'
for  my  perfect  love  ”
“  Late  at  night
buzzin' the  street  lights  ”
“  Celebrate
life  in  the firefight ”
“  Every  night
takin'  all  my  love  ”
Call
Well    enjoy  it while you  can.
That ain't gonna  last
What the  hell
you  talkin'  about?
All  those  chips
you  got  in  front of you  there?
Those  are  all  gonna  be  mine
Same  goes for you
And  you    too    love
Why don't you  shut  up
and  play some  cards?
Aren't you  interested
in  how  l'm  gonna  do  it?
Let  me tell  you
Every time  l  wiggle  my toes
the  damnedest thing  happens
l  go  back  in  time
You  believe this  guy?
Hey    pal
l  think your  medication...
is  wearing  off
just a  little  bit
Just telling  you  the facts
－l'm  out.
－No  guts.  No  glory
No  worries
l  got a  feeling
my  luck's  gonna  change
You  think  he's  cheating?
That  kid?  He's  got something
Bring  him  to  me
ls there  a  problem  here?
Mr.  Black
would  like to  see you...
now
58－64    the  score...
3:  42  remaining  in  the  contest
Royals  bringing  the  ball
up the floor
Wiser  across to  Bobby  Daly
He  looks  inside for  Rizen
nothing  there
Over  on  the  left wing
to  Gabrielson
He  squares  up.
Off the  glass－－no  good
Rebound  Priorson
Hey    look
if there's  a  problem...
l  just want you  to  know
that there  is  no  problem
l'm  good  for  it
You  been  havin'  a  good  night
l  think you  got somethin'
Looks  like
you're  back  in  the  game
Tonight.  Be  here
$200 to  put  back
in  the  restaurant fund...
and  while you're  at  it...
why don't you  add
a  little  interest?
Oh    oh    by the  way    there's
more  where that came from
What?
－Fifty thousand.
－What?
Baby    l'm  back  in  the  game
Trevor  said  so
And  this time
l'm  gonna  take  him
This  is just the  beginning    OK?
There  is  no telling  how  long
this  ride  is  gonna  last
Baby    l  deliver food  to those
games.  l  see  what  happens
Trevor  always  wins
Not a  lot of the time
not some  of the time
l've  got an  edge
No    Jonah.  You've  got a  problem
Jonah!
Game's five－card  draw
jacks  or  better to  open...
Ante's  a  thousand
Two  grand  to  open
See that    raise two
See that and  raise three
Raise four
Out
Call
Let's  see  'em
Ballsy  move    Jonah
Can't win  'em  all.
Just testin' the  waters
Two  grand  to  open
See that    raise two
OK
Jonah  Beach
lt's  a  hell  of a  night
you're  havin'
Must  be  my turn
to  dance  with  Lady  Luck    huh?
Listen    looks  like...
you're  kind  of
runnin'  on  empty there
What－－what say
we  bend  the  rules  a  little  bit?
Let  me  increase  my stake?
That's  very generous  of you
－l  can  afford  to  be.
-Yes    you  can
Mr.  Black
there's  a  phone  call  for you
Let's take five.
Stretch  our  legs
That's  a  lot of chips.
You  must  be  up
Oh    hell  of a  lot
Just wish  my dad
could  see  me  now
Well    you  know
what  he'd  say  if  he  was  here?
Cash  in    walk  away a  winner
Can't walk  away.  Not yet
l'm  just settin'  him  up
for the  kill
But you  got what you  wanted.
You  beat the  house
April    honey
if  l  walk  away  right  now...
he's  gonna  think
that  l  lost  my  nerve...
that  l  just got  lucky
What's  wrong  with  lucky?
You  don't  understand
l  want  him  to  look  me  in
the  eye  and  tell  me  l  beat  him
Let  him  crawl  away this time
And  our  restaurant...
where  does that fit  in
to  all  this?
l've  been  waiting
for this  moment  my whole  life
l'm  not gonna  let this
get away from  me
You  know  what?
You're  right.  You're  right
l'm  the  one
who  needs to  walk  away
l  see your twenty-five
l'll  raise you  forty
That's forty grand  to  me
That would  be  accurate
Let's  call  it a  night
That's  it?  You're  done?
You  beat  me
What's  so funny?
l  just－－l  just won  1 85  grand
with  a  pair  of  3s
And  me  with  two  pair
You  bluffed  me
See your twenty-five
And  l'll  raise you  forty
That's forty grand  to  me
That would  be  accurate
Call
One  pair
Jacks  up  7s
Two  pair
You  win  some
and  you  lose  some    right?
Hey!
That's just a  tape  recorder!
You  mean  like this  one?
What?
Jonah    the  house  always  wins
The  house  always  wins
ln  chasing  the  big  score...
Jonah  Beach  forgot the  one
unchanging  rule  of the  game
The  house  always  wins...
especially  in  the  Twilight Zone