Yeah    well    somebody
better take  him  down...
before that skeezer
artist out there...
covers  up
our  whole  damn  sign
Yo    Picasso...
That's your  stuff
he's  pissin'  on    dog
You  going  out?
Screw  it.  l'll  hurt
this  bitch  myself
No.  No    no
l'll  do  it
You  good?
Yeah    l'm  good
l  can  do this
Deuces  wild    baby  boy
Show  him  he  can't
mess  with  the  Deuces
Marcus  Fisher
is  a  tagger...
an  advance  man
if you  will...
for the  “A”  Street  Deuces...
a  gang  armed
with  the  usual  vices...
and  willing  to  do  anything
to  show the  world...
just who  rules
Marcus  is  about
to  get schooled...
in  a  little thing
called  consequence
Because tonight
just down  that alley...
he'll  make  his  own  mark
in  the  Twilight Zone
Yo!
Hey    you!
You're  painting  over
the  Deuces' tag    man
Know  what you  doing?  Huh?
l  come  by this  wall...
seen  it take  a  beating
my whole  life
l  figure  it deserves
a  little  better
Better?  Better
than  what    man?
That
That's  my sign.
l  threw that
Oh    yeah?
lt's  not  bad
You  like  it
better than  this?
l  mean
for  everybody to  see?
Hey
l  need  you  to  stop
You  ready to  die for that?
Come  on
Stop!  Turn  around    man
'Cause that's  what's  coming...
you  put your talent
with  them  killers
Jeez.  Turn  around!
You're  a  big
freakin'  man    huh?
What you  doing?
Give  me that    huh?
春秋风月字幕站
http://gdyfdjg.blog.163.com/
^_^=== 春秋风月 原创翻译 ===^_^
Whoo  whoo!
That's  off the  chain
baby  boy
You  see that  little
punk  drop    Dex?
Boom!  Cleanup
on  aisle  3    dog!
Oh    l  know
he  be  way  past dead!
That was  hard－core.
Give  me  some    Picasso
Hey
Crazy    son
Hey    you  did  good
You  stepped  up
First one's  always
the  hardest    though    you  know?
No  sin
Yeah    yeah.
Come  on  through    man
Just  let  me  know  what time
They all  waitin' for you
right  here
Yo    don't start trippin'
on  us    Picasso
You're traveling
to  another  dimension
A  dimension  not only
of sight and  sound...
but of  mind
A journey  into
a  wondrous  land...
whose  boundaries  are  only
that of the  imagination
You're  entering...
Don't  move!
Yo    what－－
what did  l  do?!
Get down!
Ow!  My arm  don't
go  in  that direction!
Whoa    whoa!
OK    OK    OK!  OK    OK
You're the  good  guys
remember?
l  know this  kid.
l'll  vouch  for  him
He's  all  right.
l  got  him.  Thanks
Thank you
Hey    Marcus
So    where  have you
been    amigo?
You  know    got the  new
girlfriend  and  all
Yeah?  Did  you  forget?
You  owe  me  a  burrito
l  was  gonna
call  you    man
Oh    yeah?  Well    what    she
wants you  all  to  herself?
Heh.  Hey    you  know
how that goes
No    l  don't.
You  kidding  me?
l  been  married
for  1 00 years
The  only thing  my old  lady
wants  all  of...
is  my side  of the  bed
Heh  heh.  No    l  don't
buy that    Rosas
You  a  lover  man
through  and  through
But    yeah
like  l  said    um...
l  was just...jogging－－
Hey    hey.  You  OK?
Todo  tranquilo  contigo？
Are you  good?
Yeah    yeah.  My arm  hurts!
Yeah    well    cops  are  edgy
right  now  because－－
You  heard
what  happened    right?
Nah.  Hear  what?
Last  night
somebody got shot dead
They got  no  witnesses
Ho    oh.  What a  surprise
Yeah?  lt  happened
over there  by the  wall
You  just jogged
right  by  it
You  sure you  didn't
see  nothing?
No    man
His  name  was  Henry  Santos
You  know    he  was
an  artist  like you
Everybody  loved  this  guy
Hey    that sucks
Come  here
Let  me  see－－
look  at you!
You're  still
tagging    Marcus
Writing    writing    man
That's  what  l  do...
and  l'm  not gonna  stop
l  hear that all  the time
l've  been  a  gang
counselor for  1 5 years
You  all  say
the  same thing
You're  right.  Since you
got  it all  down...
l  don't  know
what you  need  me for
l  need  you  not to  wind
up  dead  like  Santos!
That's  a  tonto  way    man...
and  that's
through  and  through
Go  on
Finish  your jog
Stop!  Turn  around    man!
You  ready to  die for that?
That's  my sign
Where'd  you  go  so  early?
You  went  back to the  wall
didn't you?
Look    l  wasn't tripping
Come  on.  Help  me flip  it
l  got  lumps
in  the  mattress...
you've  got  him
in  your  head
The  picture  of  his  body－－
it was  still  there
OK?  l－－l  just wanted  to
cover  it  up    that's  all
Yeah    and  now you're  all
down  and  frown  material
Baby    l  told  you
last  night    OK...
it's  somebody    maybe  one
of the  guy's  people...
but somebody's
trying  to  lay down...
a  guilt trip  on  you
and  play with  your  head
Look    l  didn't want
to  shoot that  man
l  couldn't
He  asked  for trouble...
the  second  he  started
fooling  with  the tags
Look    it was  an  accident!  OK?
String  and  the  brothers...
they treating  me  like
l'm  a  hero  or  something...
and    hell    l－－l  didn't
even  wanna  do  it
Yeah    and  that  is  gonna
stay our  little  secret
You  wanted
to join  the  Deuces－－
now you're  in
You  have
to  stop your  mind...
from  turning  to the
things that can't  be    OK?
OK?
OK
A  Deuces  man.
Now you're  in
First one's  always the
hardest    though    you  know?
Last  night    this  one  here
became the  real  deal
Mad  props    Picasso
To  Marcus    y'all
－Deuces  wild!
－Deuces  wild    boy!
Deuces  wild    baby
Yeah    Marcus
You  the  man
Now you're  a  deuce
Yeah?
lt's  me
Shi...
Yo    hang  on!
How you  doing    Marcus?
Ha.  Look    l'm  all  right
Thought we'd  go
for  a  ride
Ohh.  Yeah    look
lf  l  hear  another
ex－gangbanger  speech  again...
l  might shoot  myself
so  l'm  just gonna...
Oh    no.
l  give you  my word
No    look    maybe
another time    man
l'm  not...
Let's  go
l  wanna  show you  something
You  seen  this?
“Urban Artist's  Digest. ”
What's this?
You  read  that    don't you?
Tsh.  Yeah    once
Just  before  l  got
a  flu  shot.  Why?
Guess  who's  in  that  issue?
Henry  Santos
You  know    the    uh
guy that－－
Yeah    yeah    yeah    man.
l  know  already    all  right?
Did  you  know
how  good  he  was?
Apparently this young
man  had  a  great future
He  was  a－－a  rising
young  street artist
They say all  that
Yeah    all  that    huh?
Now    don't ask  me  what's  art
Victoria's  Secret's
catalogue...
That's  art
Look    man    is this
what you  wanted  to  show  me?
Huh?  OK.  l  seen  it.
Let  me  out
Can  you  let  me  out    please?
Damn
ln  a  sec
Whoa.  Now
that ain't good
So    what  happened
last  night    Marcus?
l  don't  know.  Yesterday
turned  into today?
Tsh.  l  don't  know
all  right?
Are you  sure?
Go  on
Go  ahead.  Take  a  look
You  think  someone's
trying  to  show  me  something?
Marcus
－Marcus－－
－l  destroyed  it
l  destroyed  it...
and  a  minute  later
not even...
lt was  all  back.  Heh
Telling  more
l  saw  it.  l  saw  it
Baby    you're just
feeling  guilty
Feeling?
l  am  guilty
No.  No    no.  See    you  have
to  stop thinking  like that
You  have to!
They saw you  with  Rosas
Yeah?  And?
They think  he  might
try to  get you  to  confess
What?
And  then  start snitching
on  everyone
No.  Don't－－Do  not－－
And  if they think...
that you  are  snitching
to the  cops through  Rosas...
kin  ain't gonna  mean  much...
even  if  my cousin  String
is the  leader  of the  Deuces
l  gave  up  nothing
They will  deal  hard
with  you    Marcus
Yeah!  l  know
Where  are you  going    baby?
Goin' to  mind
my  business
You  tired  of  running?
l  mean    l  see you
taking  the  bus  now
By the  way
the  police  showed  me...
the  coroner's  report
on  Santos'  death
He  had  powder  burns
on  his  right  hand...
and  up  his  right arm
He  probably  had
a  grip  on  the  barrel
Yeah    that takes  brains
Yeah
Or  else  he  was  pretty sure that
the  dude  holding  the  gun...
wasn't gonna  shoot
But then    bang!
The  gun  went off  by accident
ls that
what  happened    Marcus?
How  am  l  supposed  to  know?
'Cause  l  saw the  wall
and  that's you    bro
ls that what  happened?
ls that the  way you're
gonna  tell  everybody...
how  it went down?
'Cause you  know  something...
but you're  afraid  of what
the  Deuces  will  do    huh?
You  are  so  wrong    man
You're  afraid
of the truth    aren't you?
l  ain't afraid  of  nothin'!
Oh    yeah.
You're  proud  of that?
ls that you?
ls that  how
you're  gonna  live?
Snap the freakin'
picture    man
That's  how you're
gonna  die!
That's  not a  tattoo
That's  a  brand
You're their  slave.
They own  you
You  think that  String  and
that  bunch  care  about you?
You're  damn  right they care
Well    they don't.  They
care  about the  wrong  things
The  only  reason  they're
keeping  you  around...
is just to  keep you  down
Because they  know
what  l  know－－
that you  can  be
something  else...
and  they can't
Hey    Rosas
When  you  got out
of the  gang  life    right...
what got good?
First    l  mean
Not  having  to  look
over  my shoulder
l'll  see you  around
He's  a  gang  counselor
Let  me  drop
some  knowledge  on  you
He  ain't counseling  you
on  how to  be  in  a  gang
You  understand  that    huh?
Yeah.  Yeah    man
Then  what the  hell  you  doing
yapping  and  ride－sharing...
with  your  new  best friend...
who  wanna  teach  your  ass
to  be  out of a  gang?
No    he's  dogging  me    man.
You  don't  understand－－
ls that what
you  want?  Huh?!
No    String
To  be  out of a  gang?
Look    it won't...
He  won't  leave  me
alone    all  right?
Yeah?  Askin'
about our  business?
Huh?
What we  got?
Where  we  go?
Who  we  done?
No    man.  L－look.
l  gave  up  nothing
l  swear  it.  Look
l  came  here  on  my own...
to  show you  that  l'm
with  you.  l'm  good  now
Well    you  don't
look  so  good
Hmm?
Mm－mm
He  don't  look  so  good
You  know    man
like that cat...
that shot the  canary
Swallowed    you  fool
You  hiding  something
Picasso?
No    man
Don't  hurt  him!
Shauna?
Please    he's just－－
he's just a  little
messed  up  right  now    and...
He's  gonna  be  better.
He'll  fix  it
What you  saying    girl?
You  all  is  playing  so  much
Fix  what?
The  wall.  l  just saw  it
l  thought you
all  saw the  wall...
and  l  came  here for  Marcus
Let's  go    man
You  gotta  be  kidding  me
No freakin'  way
That takes  balls    Picasso
Yeah.  Cool
You're  a  deuce  now    Picasso
That's  all  there  is to  it
Sweet    baby  boy
Dumb    but sweet
l  don't  know
how you  did  it...
but you  did  it    baby
You're  a  superstar  now.
Can  you  feel  it?
Oh.  No    baby
lt's  all  wrong
Nothing's  wrong    Marcus.
Nothing
l  gotta  fix  it
Just  leave  me  alone
No!
Rosas!
Marcus!
l  shot  him.
l  did  it!  l  shot  him!
Whoa    whoa.
Easy    easy    easy
l  can't get free  of  it    man.
l  did  it    OK?!
OK?  Look    look.
J-just  look!  Look!
l  shot  Santos
l  know
l  didn't－－l  didn't
mean  to  do  it    man
l  know that    too
You're  not a  killer    Marcus
l'm  good  now.
l'm  good  now
A  mark  on  a  wall
ink  under the  skin...
Easy enough  things
to  remove...
with  enough
pain  and  effort
But only
an  act of contrition...
could  erase the tag
on  Marcus  Fisher's  soul...
in  the  Twilight Zone