Javon    l  can't  help  it.
l  have  a  flat tire
Look    listen  to  me    Javon
you  cannot sign  with  C.S.M
Look    who  got you
thirty  million  for four years?
Yeah    that's  right.  Who  got you
a  six  mil  signing  bonus?
Yeah    that's  right    baby－－me!
No－－l  don't care
what they  promised  you!
They said  what?
How  much?
Ohh!  Those  lying  bastards!
Look    Javon    l'm  gonna  be there
in  forty-five  minutes
Don't sign  anything.
You  wait for  me
We're  a  team    right?
Right?
Javon?
Damn  it!  Unh!
Ohh!  Damn  it!
Yeah    is this  Tri－state  Towing?
Look    l  got a  flat tire
on  Columbia  Parkway
Between  48th  and  Lagrange!
l  called  you  guys
forty-five  minutes  ago!
Where  are you?
All  right
you  tell  the  driver...
l  will  give  him
an  extra  fifty  bucks...
lf  he  gets  here  in  ten  minutes
No!  Thank you!
Shut  up    already!
This  is  ridiculous!
Meet  Scott Turner...
a  hotshot sports  agent
who thinks  he  knows the  path...
to  success  and  happiness
But  Scott will  discover
that these two things...
don't  necessarily
go  hand  in  hand...
as  he  makes  a  detour
off the  beaten  path...
and  into the  Twilight Zone
春秋风月字幕站
http://gdyfdjg.blog.163.com/
^_^=== 春秋风月 原创翻译 ===^_^
Hello?
Cell  phones
Anybody  home?
A  little  help  here?
Hello!
Excuse  me
Oh    it's  about time
Can  you  help  me
get  back  onto the  highway?
l  am  so  lost
You  are traveling
to  another  dimension－－
a  dimension  not only
of sight and  sound...
but of  mind
A journey
into  a  wondrous  land...
whose  boundaries  are  only
that of the  imagination
You  are  entering...
You're  asking  me for  directions?
－Well    don't you  live  here?
－No    l－－
l  just stumbled  onto this  place
l  have  been  wandering
around  the  woods for...
Oh!  That's  perfect
Let  me  guess.
Your  watch  doesn't work
Neither  does  mine.
How  about your  cell?
l  can't get a  signal
Neither  can  l
and  there  are  no  phones  here
Well    it's  a  huge  house.
There's  gotta  be  a  phone
No    believe  me    l  have  looked
Not only  isn't there  a  phone...
there's  no  light switches
no  clocks...
no  electric  sockets
l'm  a  real  estate  agent.
l  notice these things
－How  about a  car?
－Car?
There's  not even  a  driveway
So  somebody  likes their  privacy
Well...
it's  not as  simple  as that
Come take  a  look  at this.  Um...
Scott Turner
Marisa  Sanborn
How  well  do you  know the  area
Scott?
Obviously  not very well
l  didn't even  know
there  was  a  forest around  here
This  is  all
supposed  to  be flatland
There  are  no  hills
let alone  mountains
So  what's that out there?
lt's  a  total  mystery
What's that  mean?
This  place  shouldn't  be  here
Hello?
Anybody  here?
l  don't get  it
Somebody's  messin'  with  us
Oh...
Wait a  minute.  Wait a  minute.
l  know  what this  is
This  is  one  of those
silly  reality shows    right?
We're  supposed  to  survive
in  the  wilderness?
l'm  not signin'
any damn  release form!
l  don't think
that's  what this  is  about
So there  l  was
stuck  in  traffic...
on  the  Columbia  Parkway...
in  the  midst of a  horrendous
argument with  my fiancё  Paul
l  just－－
l  couldn't take  it anymore
So you  just got out of the  car?
Well    l  thought
he'd  come  after  me
But  he  didn't
So  l  just  kept walking
There's  supposed  to  be
a  little  park  back  here...
not a  forest
And  l  just wandered  around
until  l  found  this  place...
about an  hour
before you  got  here
All  l  know  is  l  missed
my  meeting  with  Javon  Mercer
The  basketball  player?
He's threatening  to  sign
with  another  agency
He  leaves    l'm  screwed
l'm  juggling  about
a  dozen  real  estate  deals
l've  got  houses  in  escrow...
meetings  with  buyers
meetings  with  sellers...
all  that    and  l'm  trying
to  plan  my wedding
Stress  is  part of the  game
You  ever feel  like
quitting  the  game?
Not an  option
That's  what  l  always thought
Now  l'm  not so  sure
Scott    come  here!
These  are  all  my size
What are the  chances  of that?
lt's your  size    right?
This  is  gettin'
way too freakin'  weird
You're  gonna  throw
what  in  the fire?
My  past
My turn    huh?
When  you're  ready
You  do  know that this  is  crazy
lt's  a  good  kind  of crazy
What  if we find  a  way
outta  here?
ls that what you  want?
Help  me!
Don't get  me  wrong.
l  love  my  bike
But these  old  motorcycles...
They can  get away from  you
like that
l  hit this  oil  slick.
The  next thing  l  know...
l'm  sailing  over the  handlebars
and  l'm  flyin'
Lucky you  weren't  killed
lt's  karma  is  what  it  is.
You  put out good  energy...
the  universe  sends  good  energy
back to you
l  must've  been  walking
around  these  woods for  hours
l  didn't  know
there  was  a  lake  around  here
－Oh...
－Oh.  Easy  now
Here.  Sit  back
Lay  back.  We  can  talk  later
No  problem.  l'm  Rikki
He's  Scott.  l'm  Marisa
Oh    and  phones
don't work  around  here
Hey    Cole    it's  Rikki
Had  a  little  accident
on  Columbia  Parkway
No.  lt's  all  good
Met a  couple  of  nice  people
who  helped  me  out
lf  it's  OK  with  them
l'm  gonna  spend  the  night
Sometime tomorrow
Well    l'm  gonna  hold  you
to that  promise
Did  you  guys  say something
about  phones  not working?
l  don't  understand
what you're  so  upset about
No    l'm  not  upset.  l  just don't
know  what she's  doing  here
Well    she  got  lost  in  the  woods
just  like  we  did
So  what  happens  now?
She's just gonna  stay  here
and  live  with  us?
Where  else  is  she  gonna  go?
All  l  know  is...
this  house  is  set  up
for two  people    not for three
OK    what do you  wanna  do?
You  wanna  throw  her  out?
－No.  l'm  not saying  that.
－What are you  saying?
Just don't  use  her  phone    Scott
Why  not?
Because
if we  let the  world  back  in...
then  we  will  lose
everything  we  have  here
No.  l'm  not stoned.
l'm  freakin'  lost
There's  no  way out
of these  woods
Call  the  police
the fire  department...
the  national  guard    whoever
and  get  me  out of  here
l  need  your  help    Cole
What's  goin'  on?
Oh    l  got stung  by a  wasp
This  is the first time
l've  seen  one  around  here
Oh    you  better
put something  on  that
Yeah
Look    Marisa
Scott's  not  my type...
if that's  what's  bothering  you
l'm  just saying  l've
noticed  a  little  attitude...
and  l  want  us to  be friends
OK
After  all    we're  stuck  out  here
together    right?
Yeah
Poor  Cole.  He's  a  hottie
but  he's  kinda  lost without  me
l'm  sorry to  hear that
What about you?
lsn't there  someone
you'd  like to  call?
No.  l  don't think  so
You're  sure?
No  one's  worrying  about you?
Parents?  Friends?
No.  There's  no  one
l  thought  Scott said
there  was  a  fiancё－－
Paul  something
Scott told  you  that?
－ls  it a  secret?
－Not anymore
You  don't even  want
to  speak to the  guy?
Tell  him  good－bye  at  least?
What's the  number?
l'll  dial  it for you
No.  That's  OK
You're  sure?
l'm  gonna  go
take  care  of this  sting
l'll  say one thing－－
l  hate the  quiet
l  hate the  isolation.
l  hate the  boredom
But  l  love the food
Haven't  had  a  bad  meal  yet
No  matter  how  much  we  eat
there  always  seems to  be  plenty
Let  me  help you  with  those
Don't you  have
better things to  do?
Like  gossip to  Rikki
about  Paul  and  me?
A  scorpion.  Cool
－Hey.
－Oh
lt's  been  three  days
since  l've talked  to  Cole
All  l  get
is  his  answering  machine
l  gotta  get out of  here
back to  my  life
l've  got  my sister's  birthday...
this  party
at Jackie's  and  Rafe's
l  got tickets
to the  basketball  game
-You  like  hoops?
－Are you  kidding?
l  never  miss  a  home  game.
Javon  Mercer  rocks
l  represent  him
－No  way.
-Yeah    way
l'm  a  sports  agent.
He's  my  number  one  client
You  didn't  read  anything
in  the  paper...
about  him  changing
representation    did  you?
l  just  love  watching  him  play
Yeah.  He's  good
lf you're  worried
why don't you  give  him  a  call?
No.  l  don't think  so
What's the  matter?
Marisa  wouldn't approve?
How  do you  know that?
Listen    l  know  Marisa  is  using
this  place  as  an  excuse...
to  hide from
the  rest of the  world...
but you    you  sound  like you
still  have  a  life  out there
l  wonder
who's talking  to Javon  now?
Come  on    Cole    be there for  me
Go    baby!
All  right    your turn
Shoot the  ball!  Shoot  it!
Yahoo!  Three－pointer!
Now  play some  "D."
No    no    don't  kill  it
lt's  a  big  one    huh?
How  did  a  snake  get  in  here?
Are you  sure
you  want to  do this?
Are you  gonna  argue  with  me...
or  are you  gonna  let  me
make  a  call?
l  don't want you
to  get  in  trouble  with  Marisa
You  gonna  give  me the  phone
or  not?
Thank you
Javon!
What's  happenin'    man?  Scott
What do you  mean    Scott who?
lt's  me
No.  l  know    l'm  sorry.  l  just...
You  know    l  should've
called  you  sooner...
but  l've  been  out of town
on  business
What do you  mean?
No.  l'm  just checkin'  in...
to  see  how
my favorite  client's  doin'
You  are  still  my client    right?
－Scott!
-Javon?  Javon?
Javon!
l'll  take that  back
if you  don't  mind
What  have you  done?
l  love technology
lt  makes  my job  so  much  easier
What the  hell
are you  talkin'  about?
This  was your  chance
to  be free...
to  live  in  innocence  again
All  you  had  to  do  was  accept
what you  were  being  given
But you  mortals  always
want  it all    don't you?
l  think  it's time
you  both  were  leaving
How  many times
have  we  been  through  this?
l  don't  understand  why you  keep
treating  me this  way
l  mean  it    Paul    OK?
l  can't take this  anymore
Look    will  you  relax    Marisa?
l  hate to  interrupt...
but do you  have  a  cell  phone
that  l  could  use?
l  seem  to  have  lost  mine
Yeah.  Paul    where's  my  phone?
l  just  had  it  here  a  minute  ago
How  would  l  know?
l'm  sorry
No.  lt's－－it's  OK
Most of  us  dream  of  paradise
at one time  or  another
Scott Turner  actually found  his
Unfortunately    he  was  unable
to  hold  onto  it...
and  found  himself
back  in  the  game  of  modern  life