The  location
and  size  of the tumor...
make  it  impossible
to  operate
How  long  have  l  got?
That's  hard  to  say
How  long?
5  months.  Maybe  6
Wow
l  guess the  good  news  is
l  won't  have to  worry...
about these  headaches
after  l'm  dead
That was  supposed
to  be  a  joke    doctor
So there's  nothing
you  can  do?
No
But we've  got
a  gifted  neurosurgeon...
right  here  in  Memphis
He's found  a  way
to  reduce  cancerous tumors...
with  antigens
and  stem  cell  substitution
So  what's the  catch?
Well    treatment  is  still
considered  experimental
lnsurance  won't cover  it
Well    how  expensive  is  it?
Procedure    meds
and  rehabilitation...
run  over  200  000
Can  you  raise
that  kind  of  money?
l'm  a  law  clerk    doc
l  maxed  out  my credit cards
flying  down  here to  see you
What about your family?
l  don't  have  any family
ls there  anyone?
No    there's  no  one
lt's  a  hell  of a  thing
doctor
Now that  l  know  l'm  dying...
l  realize  l'm  not  leaving
much  of a  life  behind
Ray  Ellison
just got the  kind  of  news...
all  of  us  dread...
but on  the  worst day
of  his  life...
Ray  Ellison's  luck
is  about to  change
He's  going  to  have  a  chance
to  save  his future...
by altering  the  past
l'm  a  nurse.  Comin' through
Who  are you?
My  name's  Adelaide
Are you  in  any  pain?
My  head  hurts
Probably a  concussion
Can  you  tell  me your  name?
lt's  Ray
What's  goin'  on?
You  were  hit  by a  car    Ray
Do you  know  what day  it  is?
Hold  on.  Where  am  l?
Memphis.  Jackson  Street
Yeah    but...
why  is  everybody
dressed  like that?
What year  is  it?
lt's  1 968    mister.
Don't you  even  know that?
This  can't－－
This  can't  be  happening
You're traveling
to  another  dimension...
a  dimension  not only
of sight and  sound...
but of  mind
A journey
into  a  wondrous  land...
whose  boundaries  are  only
that of the  imagination
You're  entering...
You  were  asleep
a  real  long  time
Where  am  l?
My  house
You  staring  at  my  birthmark?
No
What time  is  it?
4: 1 5.  Your  watch  is funny
lt's  a  digital
You've  never  seen  one?
Kid...what year  is this?
Already told  you.  lt's  1 968
That can't  be  right
Aah    damn  it
Ooh    you  said  a  bad  word
Lucas    didn't  l  tell  you
to  go  outside  and  play...
so this  man
can  get some  rest?
l  don't wanna  play
Then  go fetch  the  mail  for  me
Bye.  Go  on
How's your  head?
lt feels  like  l  just did
1 3  rounds  with  Mike  Tyson
Listen    l  appreciate you
taking  me  in  and  everything...
but...
maybe  l  should
be  in  a  hospital
The  colored  hospital's
too far to  go to today
The  what?
The  colored  hospital
But  if you
still  wanna  go tomorrow...
we  can  work  something  out
l  think  it's just
a  concussion  though
No    no    something's  not  right
l'm  not supposed  to  be  here
Listen    mister...
l  know  my  house
is  nothing  fancy    but－－
no    l'm  not talking
about your  house
l  mean    none  of this
makes  sense
This  nonsense
about  it  being  1 968
lt  is  1 968
Look    lady    l'm  not crazy...
and  l'm  not  hallucinating.  Ow
Look    just...
l'll  prove  it
Look...
can  you  hand  me
my jacket    please?
Here
Thank you
Where's  my wallet?
Maybe you  lost  it
when  you  got  hit
Once you  get some  solid  rest...
you'll  start to feel
a  lot  better
Supper  will  be  ready
in  an  hour
春秋风月字幕站
http://gdyfdjg.blog.163.com/
^_^=== 春秋风月 原创翻译 ===^_^
You  certainly eat
like  a  healthy  man
You  should  be fine
in  a  day or two
That depends  on
your  definition  of “fine”
You  have  any Advil?
Uh    aspirin?
Got some  in  my  purse
Time for your  bath    young  man
Oh    mama    it's  still  early
l  don't wanna  take
my  bath  right  now
Lucas    don't－－
Lucas    don't argue  with  me
l'm  gonna  fill  the tub
Excuse  me
Your  mama's  a  nice  lady
Yeah    pretty    too
She's  usually
even  nicer than  this...
but she's  upset
'cause  she  got...
another  one  of those
letters today
What  letter?
Some  people tryin'
to take  our  house
She  keeps  callin' the  lawyer
but  he  won't call  her  back
You  know  where
this  letter  is?
－lt's  over  here.
－Let  me  see  it
Thank you
You  should  be  asleep
Yeah    l  know
You  never  did  ask  me
what  l  do for  a  living
l'm  a  law  clerk
l  mean
that's  what  l  do.  l...
look  at  legal  documents
like these  all  day  long
l  figured
the  least  l  could  do...
to  repay you
for your  kindness...
was to  give you
some free  advice
Where'd  you  get that from?
That  letter's
none  of your  business
l  take  a  stranger
into  my  house...
out of the  goodness
of  my  heart...
and  he  snoops  around
in  my  private  affairs
l'm  of a  mind
to  put you  out  right  now
Even  if  l  can  tell  you
how to  save your  house?
Lucas    how  many times
l  done told  you...
about  bouncing  that  ball
up  against the  house?
Sorry    mama
l'll  be  down  at City  Hall
most of the  day
l  left some  lunch
for you  in  the  icebox...
and  l  want your
math  and  reading  done...
when  l  get  home
-Yes    ma'am.
－Now  come  here  and  gimme  a  kiss
Mama!
Boy    you  better  get your  little
narrow  behind  over  here...
and  give your  mama
a  good－luck  kiss
And  comb your  hair for  me
Yes    ma'am
Give  'em  hell    Adelaide
Hey    Lucas
Hey    Ray
You  think you  could
tell  me  how to  get  back...
to  where  l  had
my accident yesterday?
Sure.  All  you  gotta  do...
is  go to that street
and  keep  walkin'
OK.  Thanks
Uh    listen    Lucas...
there's  a  good  chance
that you  won't see  me  again
Why  not?
Because there's  someplace  else
l'm  supposed  to  be
How  do you  know?  Maybe
you're  supposed  to  be  here
l  don't think  so
Well    can  l  go  with  you?
lf you  do that who's  gonna
take  care  of your  mama?
lf  l  don't come  back...
you  tell  her  l  said
thanks for  everything    OK?
Come to the  rally
tonight    brother
All  right
Can  l  help you?
No    l'm  just  looking
for  something
Well    you  can't  be
messin'  around  in  there...
scarin' folks.
Come  on  out there  now
Well    l  lost－－
l  lost  my wallet
here yesterday
l  was just  looking  for  it
Let  me  see  some  l.D
My  l.D.  would  be
in  my wallet...
which  is  what  l  just
told  you  l  lost
This  is  public  property...
isn't  it?
Are you  questionin'  me    boy?
What did  you  call  me?
Uncle  Ray...
mama  said  the  movie
starts  in  5  minutes
We  gotta  hurry  if we  wanna
get our tickets
Hello    Officer  Bryant
Lucas    you  know  him?
Yes    sir.  He's  my  uncle
from  New York
Officer:  Well...
tell  your  uncle...
he's  in  Memphis  now    ya  hear?
Yes    sir
You're  not  mad  at  me
for following  you?
No.  No
Just wonderin'  if you  figured
out where you're  supposed  to  be
Well    l  know  where
you're  supposed  to  be
Your  mama  comes  home
and  finds you  gone...
she's  gonna  kill  us  both
Come  on
Where  l'm  from
things  are  different
They're  different from
the  way they are  here
You  talk to  people
in  a  different way...
and  police  aren't supposed
to talk to you  like that
You  weren't
scared  of that cop?
When  you  know you're  right
you  don't  need  to  be  scared
Aren't you  supposed
to  be  in  school  or  something?
They sent  me  home yesterday...
'cause  l  got  into  a  fight
What about?
Nothing
Nothing's  a  pretty
empty thing  to fight for
Bobby Wilson  was  makin'
fun  of  my  birthmark...
so  l  punched  him
in  the  stomach
Mama  always
tellin'  me  not to fight...
but she just don't  understand
Can't  be  a  man
without fighting
See    that's  what  l  told  her
Yeah    but the  secret  is...
a  real  man  doesn't
use  his fists to fight
Look    you  fight with  these...
you  can  change things
maybe for  a  few  minutes...
but you  use this  and  this...
change things forever.
You  could  change your  life
You  understand
what  l'm  saying?
Yeah    l  think  so
Wanna  know  a  secret?
What  kind  of secret?
What  l  wanna  be
when  l  grow  up
OK
You  gotta  promise  me
you  won't  laugh
Ok    l  promise
That's  a  pretty  big  dream
l  know
You  ready to fight for  it?
Yes    sir
Hey    mama
What  happened?
They gave you  the  runaround?
l'll  go  back  down  there
in  the  morning  with  you
Runaround
Shoot    those  white folks
didn't  know  what  hit 'em!
l  told  'em  exactly
what you  said
How they can't
foreclose  on  the  house...
while  it's
still  in  litigation
Then  l  whipped  out
a  copy of  my  bank  statement...
to  prove to them
that  l  had  the tax  money
Ha  ha
l  thought  l  was  gonna  have to
nurse them  back to  health...
after  l  was
finished  with  'em
l'm  happy for you    Adelaide
Thank you    Ray
Mama    we  gonna  keep  our  house?
You  better  believe
we  are    baby
Ha  ha  ha!
Now...
l'm  about to  walk
through  my  front door...
and  into  my  kitchen...
and  l'm  gonna  cook y'all
the  best  meal  y'all  ever  had!
Whoo!
He  was  so tired...
he fell  asleep
in  his  clothes
l'll  carry  him
to  his  bed  later
l  appreciate that    Ray
Lucas  really  likes you
Hey    l  really  like  him
He's  a  great  kid    Adelaide
Just  like  his  daddy
You  mind  me  asking  what
happened  to  his father?
Jim  was  a  window  washer
5 years  ago...
he  was  working  on  one  of those
office  buildings  downtown...
and  his  cable  broke
No  one  was  willing  to take  him
to  a  colored  hospital
Died  right there  in  the  street
l'm  sorry to  hear that
l  want a  different
kind  of  life for  Lucas
They say
times  are  changing    but－－
Oh    they are.  They are
l  promise you
So  what about you?
Got somebody
waitin'  at  home for ya?
Nah
Too  busy
playin' the field    huh?
Well
l  guess  it's    uh...
too  late  now
Why do you  say that?
Adelaide    do you
think  it's  possible－－
well...
do you  think  it's  possible...
for  a  person  to  get
a  second  chance?
l  think  if a  person
has  God  in  their  heart...
they get  more
than  a  second  chance
They get a  fresh  start
Fresh  start
l'd  love that
lt's  never too  late
Oh    my God
Ray    what's  wrong?
Tomorrow's  April  4    1 968
And?
Martin  Luther  King's
gonna  be  assassinated...
here  in  Memphis
l  don't  understand
What do you  mean  somebody's
gonna  kill  Dr.  King?
Tonight  he's  speaking  to
the  striking  sanitation  workers
Tomorrow  he's  gonna
be  murdered...
on  the  balcony
of the  Lorraine  Motel
How  do you  know this?
Because  remember
when  l  told  you...
l'm  not supposed  to  be  here?
Adelaide
l'm  not from  this time
l  woke  up yesterday  morning
it was  2003
Now  somehow this  accident－－
Ray    you're  not  makin'
any  kinda  sense－－
No    l－－l  am.  Adelaide
listen  to  me.  Listen  to  me
Now  l－－l've  been  trying
to figure  out why  l'm  here
l  thought  it  had  something
to  do  with  you  and  Lucas
Ray－－
maybe  l  was  supposed
to  help you    but－－
No    l'm  not  in  pain!
Just  list－－
l'm  sorry...
but    Adelaide
l've  gotta  save  King
Now  which  way
to the  Mason  temple?
Ray    you  need  to  rest
No    l  don't
Adelaide...
you  gotta  trust  me
Please
lt's  2  miles from  here
On  Mason  Street
Martin  Luther  King :
Like  anybody...
l  would  like to  live...
a  long  life.  Longevity...
has  its  place...
but  l'm  not
concerned  about that  now
l  just want to  do  God's  will...
and  he's  allowed  me...
to  go  up to the  mountain
And  l've  looked  over...
and  l've  seen...
the  promised  land...
Whoa    there.  We're full  up
This  is  an  emergency
l  just  have to  get  in
for  5  minutes
Yeah    and  l  just told  you
there's  no  room
No    officer
you  don't  understand
Just    please    listen  to  me－－
No    you  don't  understand
All  these  people
wanna  get  in  to  see－－
l  gotta  get  in  here!
You  don't  understand!
Just  listen  to  me!
They're  gonna  kill  him!
They're  gonna  kill  King!
l'm  not crazy!
They're  gonna  kill  him!
No  one's  gonna  kill  anybody!
Listen  to  me!
King :  So  l'm  happy tonight
l'm  not worried...
about anything!
l'm  not fearing  any  man!
My eyes
have  seen  the  glory...
of the  coming  of the  Lord
Thanks for  bailing  me  out
l'll  pay you  back.  l  promise
That's  not  important
Listen    Adelaide
l'm  sorry about all  of this
l  need  you  to  know  something.
l'm  not crazy
l  care  about you  and  Lucas
l  gotta  get to
the  Lorraine  Motel
We're  never  going
to  see you  again    are  we?
l  don't  know
Thank you  for  everything
Adelaide
Lucas    what are
you  doing  here?
l  heard  what you  told  my  mom
last  night.  l  wanna  help
No    you  can't!  Go  back  home!
Ray    you're  supposed
to  be  here  with  us!  l  know  it
Lucas    listen  to  me
Don't forget
what  l  told  you    OK?
You  fight for  what you  want
Don't forget that
Dr.  King!
Go  inside!
Get off the  balcony!
Dr.  King!
Dr.  King    go  inside!
Get off the－－
go  inside!
Ray!
No    Lucas    go  back!
Dr.  King    go  inside!
No!  No!
Wait!  Ray    wait!
No!
Ray!  Ray    are you  all  right?
You  gotta  stop  'em
You  gotta  save  him.
Ya  gotta－－
Oh    my goodness!
They shot  Dr.  King!
l  didn't save  King
But you  saved  me    Ray
Thank you  for  saving  me
Welcome  back to the  living
You  were  in  a  coma  for  3  days
A  coma?
But  l  was－－
l－－l  was－－
How  do you  feel?
My  head  hurts
Yeah
Well    l've  got some  good  news
l  got your  case  reviewed
That specialist
l  told  you  about...
has  agreed
to  underwrite the  cost
What?
lt's  a  new  program
he's  starting...
to  benefit
people  like yourself...
people  who  need  treatment
but can't afford  it
Won't cost you  a  dime
You  better  pinch  me    doctor.
l  think  l'm  still  dreaming
Ha  ha  ha.  Trust  me
you're  wide  awake
Ray    l'd  like you
to  meet your  new  physician :
Dr.  Lucas  Tyler
Nice to  meet you    Ray
Lucas?
Now    l  don't want you
to  worry about anything
The  only thing  you  have to  do...
is fight to  get well
Now    you  fight
from  here  and  from  here...
and  you  can  change your  life
Don't forget that
l  won't forget
Ray  Ellison  was
looking  for  a  fresh  start...
and  he  only  had  to  go  back
35 years to find  one
Sometimes the  key
to  our future...
lies  in  the  past
A  lesson    courtesy of...
the  Twilight Zone