Welcome back.
In this segment we'll briefly described
the latest video
compression standards, the high efficiency
video coding standard, HGVC.
It's a result of the effort by the joint
collaborative
team on video coding and it is therefore
additional names.
It's called H.265 by ITU-T, and MPEG-H
part two by MPEG.
As computers become more powerful, more
involved ideas from
the literature, or new ideas can be
implemented and tested.
So the old idea of breaking a frame
into blocks of various sizes using a
[INAUDIBLE] structure.
To perform motion estimation and
compensation
can now become part of a standard.
Since adequate computational resources are
available.
Similarly, instead of the eight spatial
prediction
modes used in H.264 33 plus 235.
Such prediction modes can be implemented
in H.265.
The overall result is that the latest
standard is a very powerful one.
Especially for large spatial resolutions.
As a matter of fact, it supports
resolution up to 8k UHD, ultra high
definition.
It's really fascinating to watch the
progress the video compression standards
are making.
They bring of course up the important
question of
how much longer can we be push in the
envelope.
By having the rate of the previous
standard
while maintaining the quality of the
constructed video.
Maybe some of you might be the ones to
further push this envelope.
So let us look into some of the details of
this exciting standard.
High efficiency video coding standard is
the latest standard
out of the Joint Collaborative Team on
Video Coding.
That initial objective can be to reduce
the bit rate by 50%
of the same quality when compared to H.264
High Profile.
Since it's a joint def it has various
names; in ITU is referred
to as an H.265 or an H Next Generation
Video Coding.
Whereby the ISO is referred to as MPEG-H
Part 2.
In comparing HEVC to H.264 it provides in
practice better
coding efficiency by more than 35% at the
same quality level.
It supports resolutions up to 8K UHD while
H.264 supporting resolutions up to 4K UHD.
It also supports stereo and multi-view
video encoding and also it
supports increased use of parallel
processing, as we are going to see.
One of the novelties of ATVC is the use of
coding tree units and coding tree blocks.
The CTU contains the lumen and chromacity
B as well as syntax element.
So this is a departure from the standard
16 by 16 microblock used by all standards.
Of course, we saw that H.264 subdivides
this microblock into various sizes.
This CTU however can be as large as 64 by
64 pixels.
And therefore, it's suitable for encoding
high
definition content and results in better
coding efficiency.
The CTU is subdivided into coding blocks,
which can be
as small as four by four, based on their
[UNKNOWN] structure.
And of course some rate control logic.
What we see in this table is how the CTU
maximum size affects
the bit rate, the encoding time and the
decoding time.
So when the largest possible CTU is used,
we are saving bits.
Because there are many more choices in sub
dividing
the CTU and adopting to the content of the
frame.
So with the smaller CTU sizes the bit rate
increased by 2.2 here and 11%.
If we consider the smaller one, which is
concise with the standard size of the
macro blocks.
The encoding time however is higher here,
because
again there are more choices to be made.
The decoding time however is smaller than
the other choices of the CTU's.
Because there are larger now blocks and
not so many blocks to be decoded.
The idea of course of using a quad-32
segment or tesselate the frame is not new.
Here's an old result and we see here the
segmentation for this particular frame.
And those are the associated motion
vectors for each of these specific blocks.
The actually segmentation as well as the
bit allocation
was done in the [UNKNOWN] in this
particular work.
Behind the segmentation I showed you the
previous frame, there's
this multilevel trellis that one hand
shows the [UNKNOWN] structure.
So a 32 by 32 block is potentially broken
down into
four 16 by 16, 16 by 16 and four 8 by 8
and so on.
But this Trellis also allows us to perform
optimal
bit relocation for encoding the
segmentation, the motion vectors.
As well as the texture so that the overall
performance is optimized or the overall
distortion is minimized.
We see here the coding three unit idea
being demonstrated.
Based on this segmentation or tessellation
of the
space or the coding decisions will be
made.
How the bits will be allocated again,
amongst segmentation, motion vectors, as
well as texture.
Here's an example showing that the
tessellation of this
frame from the Foreman sequence by H.264
and H.265.
Clearly seems many more choices available
with H.265, their coding efficiency only
increases.
So here we see that there are large blocks
64 by
64, smaller ones all the way down to 4 by
4.
Their choices again are not as many when
we work with
H.264 we talked about the various choices
in the previous presentation.
When it comes to motion estimation and
compensation,
quarter sample precision is used for
motion estimation.
And this was the case also with H.264.
H.265 however uses 7-tap or 8-tap filters
for this fractional sample interpolation.
While H.264 uses a 6-tap filter to go to
half-sample precision
and then linear interpolation for quarter
[UNKNOWN] precision.
Regarding motion vector signaling.
An advanced motion vector prediction
scheme is used.
According to which candidate motion
vectors
have derived from neighbouring prediction
blocks.
In addition there's the option to merge or
inherit motion vectors from the temporal
or spatial neighbors.
And this compared to HW64 then it's an
improved skip or direct motion mode.
As far as interprediction goes AW65s
supports 33 different directional modes.
As compared to the eight ones that are
supported by AW64.
And this directional modes applied,
they're applied to blocks
from 44 or the way up to 32 by 32.
In addition, there is the planar mode
prediction.
And it's done by assuming an object
service with the
horizontal and vertical slope that is
derived from the boundaries.
And finally there's another mode, the DC
prediction or flat mode prediction.
According to which a flat surface with a
value
matching the min value of the boundary
samples is utilized.
We see here a pictorially the 33
prediction directions, and direction
zero is the planar prediction and one the
DC prediction we just mentioned.
It should be noted here that all these
directions are
not equally spaced and some directions are
more popular than others.
So we see here schematically that
intra-prediction by the direction
of mode 29 as goes numbered in the
previous slide.
When using this intra-angular mode each
block is
predicted directionally from spatially
neighbouring samples that are
reconstructed.
But not get filtered by the in loop
filters.
For a block N by N, a total of four N
plus one spatially neighbouring samples
may be used for this prediction.
When it comes to entropy coding a CABAC
encoder, context adapting binary
arithmetic code that is used to in, in 265
as is the with 264.
The one H.265; however, has undergone
several improvements to improve its
throughput speed.
Especially when its used for parallel
processing, its
compression performance and to reduce its
context memory requirements.
And in 265 no variable length codes are
used as opposed
to [INAUDIBLE] and variable length coding
in H.264.
With respect to the in-loop filters.
They're used in the inter-picture
prediction loop.
It's similar to the one used in H.264
however it's simpler
than the one used in 264 and it better
supports parallel processing.
And also a different filter, this sample
adaptive offset filter is used.
It's applied after the deblocking filter
so that a better reconstruction
of original signal amplitude by using an
offset from a look-up table.
HEVC supports slices and tiles.
Slices are rows of CTUs, as shown here.
This is an example of a slice.
And as mentioned multiple times during
this
week, slices are needed for terminating
error propagation.
Since they're independently decoded,
decodable.
In addition to slices, HDVC supports
tiles.
And tiles are self-contained and
independently
recordable rectangular regions in the
pictures.
So this is one tile here, this is another
tile and so on.
The main purpose of tiles is to enable
the use of parallel processing for
encoding and decoding.
Now the slice is divided into rows of
CTU's.
So the decoding of each row can begin as
soon as some, the decisions are made.
And therefore this supports parallel
processing in
the form of threads as shown here.
So all this threads can be processed at
the same time.
So there are two different mechanisms,
if you will, that support parallel
processing.
The use of tiles and the use of threads.
We show here an experiment of comparison,
of some of the more recent standards.
So HDVC is compared against 264, 263,
MPEG-4, and MPEG-2.
So the rate distortion curves are shown
here for this particular sequence.
So, the bitrate is down here, from 0 to 10
megabits
per second, and the PSNR improvement is
shown on the vertical axis.
So as expected you see kind of
the chronology of a development of these
standards.
The older standard has a registration
curve shown here and
the newest one has the registration curve
shown here in blue.
So there are considerably savings involved
as the newer standards
arrive and the savings are shown on the
plot here on the right.
So what's shown here, is the bitrate
savings with respect to HEVC.
And we say that with respect to the
older standards, there's savings anywhere
between 85% and 70%.
Y with respect to AW64 the savings range
from 55% to around 40% down here.
So in
some sense, we can, we have come to full
circle.
If you recall at the very beginning of
this week's lecture.
I show the similar rate distortion
comparison with
some of the earlier standards with also
smaller sequences.
We use their format, a QCIF image.
At frame rate I believe it was ten frames
per second.
Nevertheless the philosophical question
still remains.
As time goes on these curves keep being
pushed this direction
and we see here that there's not that much
space left.
So the obvious question is will there then
be
a next standard that can push the envelope
even further.
Or in other words, what is really the
limit of compression?
How far can we compress a given video?
This is a question that we can not really
answer.
We have to wait and see.
You know for the reduction of the bit rate
is going
to be with the new standard while keeping
the same quality.
Of course, the objectives change as well.
We have the proliferation of large
displays and
large formats the 4K and And 8K formats.
And clearly, we need new tools and new
approaches to handle these larger formats.
At the same time, the computational speed
and capabilities increase tremendously as
time goes on.
And it's only natural that more
sophisticated
algorithms will be able to be implemented.
That will of course provide the additional
gains that are needed.
So we reached the end of week ten, two
more weeks to go.
During this week the third week out of
three
dedicated to compression we talked about
[UNKNOWN] video compression.
This is probably the most important topic
from an application point
of view since we are surrounded by
application used in video compression.
This is also reflected by the large number
of video compression standards.
We discussed and analyzed the important
topics and covered
some of the intellectually interesting and
practically useful techniques.
We talked about the important concept of
temporal prediction
and also of the concept of intra and inter
prediction.
We described the evolution in video
cooperation standards which represents
a history of the research and development
in this area.
I repeat here a comment I made last week,
that
is, there was nothing really terribly
mathematical in this part.
So I hope everybody feels comfortable with
this material.
You're now knowledgable to also follow the
future development in this exciting film.
Next week we'll talk about a different
topic.
The topic of image and video segmentation.
So, see you next week.