When will be our next race, Ryousuke?
When you beat all the downhill racers
in Gumma
then I'll race you
Off-road?
Downhill
All the downhill roads in Japan
Starting tomorrow, you start
from the South, I the North
We'll compete with different
downhill racers
Let's see who ends up winning more, OK?
You not gonna race in the tracks?
The tracks?
Downhill roads are much more fun
I'm back
What's wrong?
Honey¡­
Help me change my underpants
Son of a bitch, why did you change
my under wear?
Where're you going?
Off to school
School? Isn't it your summer vacation?
You're always out.
Are you a rent boy now?
Lingerie?
You know what's a god?
A god was once human
But he could do
what other humans could not
That's why he became a god
A year ago, that bitch of a principal
expelled me
She said, Itsuki, why don't you¡­
call yourself `Eat Shit' instead?
Then it hit me
I have to tell the world
Itsuki's not a piece of shit
I'll be a racer
Within a year, I've become the racing
god of Mt Akina
The boss of the Speed stars race team
But you didn't get your license
until last year
That's what we called talents
It's simple, just like drifting. How?
Pull the handbrake at a turn
to swing the car sideways
How's that? Cool
Won't it¡­ slow the car down?
How'd you drift then?
Floor the gas pedal
Don't slow for the curve
Then¡­
Then you and your car fly off the cliff
I don't blame you.
We got our licenses together
Yet you still haven't touched the wheel
Why don't you join my team?
I don't have a car
Don't worry, you can wash mine
I drive, you wash.
What a promising career
Come on, bro. Cheers
Milk. What¡¯s so good about it?
Lots of calcium and protein
Also good for your eyes
A good racer needs good eyes
Wanna go to a movie later?
Can't. I got my part-time job
Had an eyeful?
Natsuki from Class 2B
In white today
Having fun?
Why so nervous?
You guys are close, huh?
Not at all
No? I heard that you had a fight over her¡­
with Bulldog from the neighboring class
Time for work
Right, time for my allowance too
Were those your classmates?
Yes
They look like punks. Street racers?
No, they work at the gas station
After school
They work hard
but earn only 100Kyen a month
I bet you've spent all the cash
I gave you last time
Thanks for taking care of me
and my mom
But that's too much
Take it. You deserve it
What kind of dad are you?
I only ask you for a million yen and
you say no?
I'm worried you'll be in solitude
during your last years
I'm sure my last years will be just fine
How so?
What if I leave you
after I become a world champ?
I still have my gas station
Cashier, Boss
After you die,
It will be mine anyway. Get it?
Okay, consider that an advance
from my pay
An advance?
Excluding the money I spent raising you
you have already borrowed 8,635,000 yen
An advance? What have you done,
Mr. World Champ?
I have no idea
Welcome, Sir.
Which gas would you prefer?
Does the racing god of MtAkina
own this station?
Sorry, but I don't know
Look, this is what a car should be
Great body kit, alloy rims.
Wow, sports wheel
What's the price tag on this?
Are you the racing god of MtAkina?
It's actually me
But I was told he's the owner here
Yes, I'll be the owner in a few years
when he dies
You hit your own son.
Beware of divine intervention
We're the Night Kids Team from Myogi
My name is Nakazato
I'd like to race the racing god of MtAkina
There's no racing god in MtAkina
If you're looking for God
there's a temple over there
Anyway, I'll be waiting for you
at MtAkina to night
Wash the car.
We'll go up to MtAkina tonight
How many races have you won?
How¡¯ bout you?
Same here
Who you racin' tonight?
How 'bout we go for a race first?
So crowded. You sure you can manage?
Take it easy. I'll give my best
I have to be home¡­at 3
You know my dad
Don't worry
What? Still nervous?
Look, so many people¡­
Hurry up.
I need to give my assistant a ride home
You gonna take him with you in the race?
Is that for bidden?
Looks like this guy knows nothing at all
Well, in that case, I better sit with you
You guys are gay or what? I better leave
Fatty, we'll start from here.
The first one who¡­
gets to the parking lot wins
Bullshit. Of course the faster wins
Five
Four
Three
Two
He's a real amateur
We'll see at the first corner
The car behind is kissing ours
This guy is clueless
What you gonna do?
Just stay calm
Let's overtake him. It's safer
That's not necessary
Watch out ahead.   What?
Ahead
Look what you've done.
Told you to stay calm
It's all because of you wouldn't stay calm
See, I told you
I would take you home on time
Bastard
What do you mean?
You're the bastard
who puke right after you got out
Looks like it's 'bout time
we have a race here
It's not the right time yet
Why?
You wanna hear the truth?
Go ahead
I noticed something
while I was in your car
You're not smooth each time
you attacked a corner
Although your GTR has big horse power
but the engine is heavy
There're so many corners in MtAkina
Your car was under steered at every turn
Especially the 5 consecutive hairpins
You couldn't cut to the best lane
every time
Unless you can overcome this
you stand no chance with my FC
So glad you're safe
You have to be safe
in order to be a world champ
I wanna buy a GTR
I'll get you a Mercedes instead
And a Rolex
I wanna buy a GTR
But you almost killed yourself last night
It wouldn't happen
if I were driving a GTR
If you were driving a GTR,
you would have died
I wanna buy a GTR
How could I help you?
You can't help me,
I'm here for the fatty racing god
Racing god?
What you up to? Trying to put me down?
I lost to an AE86 last night
He dashed around the corner
with Inertia Drift
I could only catch the tofu shop label on it
You know him?
If you do, just tell him that
I'll be waiting for him
on MtAkina Saturday night
Takumi?
It got nothing to do with me
I was here last night
Whoever beat him last night
is the real racing god
Don't tell me that was you
It's¡­my old pal Banta
What? Say it again
I know it sounds incredible
Like I'm standing here looking at you
But the guy with the GTR did say
you beat him
GTR? Is it very powerful?
350 horse power, a four-wheeler¡­
Fortified body¡­
it's Japan's national treasure
So what?
Just go race with him for fun
It's really hot
I'd kick your ass if you were my dad
I'm leaving, take care
Take care, bye
Takumi¡­
Takumi
Didn't you say hot spring rice bun
is your favorite?
I'm very sorry you were punished
by the principal¡­
for beating up the boy because of me
I've been trying to thank you ever since
But each time I saw you,
you seemed to ignore me
It's because¡­I'm afraid¡­
I'm afraid the school¡­
Others in school would think¡­
Because¡­
You're afraid they would think you
and I are¡­
We've been in the same class
since grade school
We've always talked about anything
But these days it seems that
you're avoiding me
I haven't talked to you for weeks already
How's the bun?
So I can still talk to you in the future?
I have something important to tell you
I bought a very sexy swimsuit
Before the finals, you promised
to take me for as pin to the beach
Have you forgotten?
I bought the swimsuit right
after you told me that
At last I chose the one with the least cloth
Why're you looking like that?
You're choked?
Are you OK?
I'm okay¡­
How're you? Are you OK?
Don'ts care me
I'm okay
Takumi, you'll pick me up
at the station this Sunday
You promised
I gotta go now
Bye-bye.   Bye-bye
You'll pick me up at the station
this Sunday. You promised
Dad
Have you beaten a GTR
in MtAkina recently?
I think so
Was the car real fast?
It's seriously fast on straight roads
But when it entered corners,
it became real slow
You really found it slow?
What's it you wanna know?
Nothing really. Just curious
I bought a very sexy swimsuit
Do you need your car this Sunday?
Yeah
The market union is having a potluck.
Wanna go?
You wanna go?
What a rude brat
Hey, Tofuman
What's up, Gasman?
I'm looking for you
What for?
Got a fun and crowded place to go
Cheers
You're asking me out tonight
So you're not mad
I don't go to your gas station?
No¡­I was mad you asked
everyone not to come
Your gas was indeed more expensive
But my gas was of higher quality
So you asked me out to talk 'b out this?
No
I didn't expect you could still hold up
at your age
You asked these girls to test me out?
I'll show you
I'm referring to you winning the GTR
the other night
That wasn't me
I haven't been delivering in MtAkina
for years
So¡­I saw a ghost that night?
That was my boy Takumi
Takumi?
One night 5 years ago,
my hemorrhoids were hurting bad
It's excruciating.
They were this big. Damn
So I asked my boy to deliver for me
But¡­ he was barely 13 then
What's the big deal? It's MtAkina
There's not a soul at 4 in the morning
I would just let him
He left home at4
and returned at 5:30
A year later
he'd come back at 5:15, or even at 5
Two years later,
he's been back before 4:30
Within a half-hour? Including delivery?
It only takes him four and a half minutes¡­
to go around MtAkina
You telling me he never had an accident?
Not at all
Once he rushed home to sleep
and floored the pedal
All the tofu was crushed
Put this in the car
Don't spill a single drop, or I'll kill you
Go
It took him two hours to get back at first
Then¡­one and a half hour
A month later, it's an hour
Gradually it became half an hour
But I haven't been timing him LateLy
Your boy is so good
why don't you ask him
to race the GTR driver again?
I'll pay for the gas
I was treated as a shitty racer
when I was young
Who knows my boy would be even worse
You know he's the only son
in the whole family
If anything should happen to him¡­
Get another one then
Hey, Tofuman
Tofuman
But what 'b out the GTR?
And tonight's bill?
Tofuman. You bastard
Bring me the scissors
I bought a very sexy swimsuit
Boss, this Sunday¡­I'd like¡­
Let me through
What do you want?
Dad, I've decided not to buy the GTR now
That's my boy
Takumi's dad is right:
a racer should stand up again¡­
after each defeat
Dad
Let me race in your car tonight
My car?
From this moment on,
I'm no longer your dad
So how 's out Mom?
What 's out Mom?
If she knew you went to the night club
last night
what do you think she would do?
Who're you looking for?
Tofuman, you bastard
You sent my son to die,
Itsuki drove off with my car
You have to ask Takumi
to go to MtAkina to night
I'm not free right now
What you mean by that?
This is the first time I begged you,
and you said no?
What 'bout the nightclub bill last night?
What kind a tofu you want?
19 years ago, the fastest racer
in Gumma Province¡­
was Bunta Fujiwara of MtAkina
A gifted racer of that era
Many racers told me that¡­
you could be the first world champ
in Japan
But you chose to get married 19 years ago
You became a tofu man instead of a racer
Sometimes one decision can change
one's whole life
It goes with racing and it goes with life
But not everyone can figure out
the consequence
Like you didn't guess your wife
would leave you
Anger. That's what a racer needs
I wanna race you, just once
Sorry, what you want is not for sale here
Please go to another shop
Sorry to disturb you
Don't answer it. It's some asshole calling
Hey
You wanna use the car tomorrow?
Go up to MtAkina tonight.
If you can win the GTR
I'll let you use my car tomorrow
With a tank of gas
Brim full
Tofuman
If Takumi wins the GTR
at MtAkina tonight
your nightclub bill would¡­
would¡­you know?
We've blocked all the cars going
uphill already
All the roads are clear.
The race can start any time
Hey, racing god, give me a break, OK?
You couldn't even enter a curve.
With this car¡­
I'm afraid you'll die
What Cha doing? This is a public area
You can't block the road
with guys holding walkie-talkies
I'll call the cops
You really won't leave?
After you
What Cha doing?
Don't mess with my car
Don't touch my car
Ryousuke, an AE86 is coming uphill
The real racing god has arrived
Takumi's dad
Itsuki
Takumi, it's you? Where's your dad?
Uncle
Is he hiding?
No, he asked me to come¡­
For what? Delivering tofu?
No, to race the GTR
Stop pulling my leg
You don't even know
how to enter a curve. You'll die
That's ok. I've been delivering tofu here
for 5 years
I know, but you gotcha license last year
I already beat him once
So it was you last time?
Tofuman¡­
Tofuman
If Takumi wins,
is the nightclub bill settled?
Didn't we discuss this two hours ago?
Two hours ago?
The GTR is very fast.
You think Takumi has a chance?
All your cars were dearer and
faster than mine
But did you ever win, you idiot?
That's different, 'coz you're crazy
Did I ever say that my son is normal?
Five, four, three¡­
Go for it Two, one¡­
Go
Don't wag your tail too much
But the AE86 is not picking up speed
It's OK to lose a little at the beginning
There're less straights and
more sharp corners later
That will be the show time for my boy
The mighty GTR is leading all the way
The AE86 is no match for it
on straight roads
He may catch up at the corners
I'm afraid it has no chance
to get near the GTR
They're entering the curves.
The AE86 is gaining
Yet the GTR is extremely accurate
in turning
The AE86 has changed its tactic
and begins to drift
They're getting closer
at the center of the curve
The AE86 attacks the corner very fast
The cars almost touched each other as they drifted out
Your boy is really that good?
A few years ago, my boy told me
he needed glasses
So I took him to an optician
But his eye sight turned out to be 200
I told him: Hey, kid¡­
I'll kick your ass if you're kidding me
And he said, when he drove,
he found everything else
getting slower and slower
I knew then¡­
that he was getting faster and faster
I lost at this corner last time.
It won't happen again
The AE86 is sticking close to the GTR.
Unbelievable
The AE86 tries to overtake,
but the GTR blocks the lane
That's unfair. It's foul play
You like a good licking?
The AE86 fails to pass,
but they're closer at the corner
The AE86 is looking for a chance
at the back
If what you said is true,
then it's sure win for Takumi?
It all depends on¡­
the last 5¡­consecutive¡­.hairpins
The last 5 hairpins.
The AE86 is not slowing down
He can't pass at this speed
The AE86 has overtaken at the inner curve
Can the GTR catch up¡­
at the remaining hairpins?
The GTR is slowing down,
the AE86 has won
It's very funny the way you drove
Weren't you up the hill?
You're down already?
I heard you used the ditch
to enter the corner, right?
I'd like to race you too. You've got time?
I'm sorry. I raced tonight 'coz
my dad asked me to
I don't think there'll be a next time
Maybe you'll change your mind tomorrow
It's done
I've raised you right. You make me proud
Hey, come on
What is it?
Nothing
What's with the towel?
It's the sunlight
Don't be shy
Or you see me in swimsuit and¡­
I'm not
Takumi, why all these wounds?
These wounds are¡­
Inflicted by my dad
After Mom left us,
Dad got drunk all the time
He beat me up when he got drunk.
Disgusting, huh?
I think you look more hunky that way
A real man gotta have a few cars
on his body
I hate those sissies with smooth skin
Especially this one on your back
That's three years ago
This one is last week's
Does it hurt?
And here?
That's a mosquito bite
You fooled me
Here we are
Your driving is really good, Takumi
I always felt car sick on long rides
But I didn't even need to take pills today
That's good
I really had a fantastic time today.
Thanks so much
You're welcome
Bye-bye
You know what's a god?
A god is actually human
But he can do what other humans can't
God, please save me
Please save my car as well
Sit down
Is the World Champ getting cuckoo?
He bought an AE86, that's why
What about him?
That's easy, he's in love
What's with you today?
You won't get it
Of course I will
A man's problem could only be cash
or chicks
What do you want?
You said you'd teach me to drive
When did I say that?
Who cares. I'll drive downhill
at the highest speed
Give me a few tips
Given my talents, things will sink in
after this once
Let's go then, it'll be quick
Have you fastened your seat belt?
Look out for the back
Wow, what a speed,
Can't wait to get laid or what?
Turn on the hazard lights. Let the car pass
Why's it kissing my ass?
What Cha want?
Sorry, I thought it's the tofu shop's AE86
But it's just¡­a piece of junk
Kids
Don't wander around at this hour
Better go home and sleep
He meant you
He must be gay,
wearing a bandanna at night
I think he's up on the hill for¡­
Junk¡­Simply junk
Let me drive
What Cha want? Say something
He was trying to kill us. Didn't you see?
So what?
He said you're a piece of junk
Let him say whatever he likes.
We don't care
Hey, the brake¡­
The brake, yo
The brake
Itsuki, what's wrong with your car?
What 'bout it?
It doesn't brake when it enters a corner
All four wheels are flying off the ground
And it almost over turns every time
it exits a corner
So why you still driving so fast?
I gotta chase that asshole
I wanna go home¡­. Dad
Daddy
Itsuki, are you OK?
Are you sure?
OK?
Takumi, what kind a driver are you?
Sorry for wrecking Itsuki's car.
I'll pay for it
I'm not talking about this. Do you know¡­
the guy last night is a member of
the Emperor Team?
He's a professional racer
You've beaten his EVO
in this piece of junk
Are you crazy or what?
But it's exactly the same as my dad's
How could it be the same?
Your dad has spent so much time
and effort on the car
It took him a month to find
the right suspension
This one over here¡­
Only an idiot like my boy could be
conned to buy this crap
Where's Itsuki?
The World Champ's useless.
Just as pin and he's been puking till now
Who would get car sick?
Takumi, you're different
You'll probably become an ace racer
one day
Keep it up
Hey
What's wrong?
You dropped your money?
The suspension.
It took you one month to fix it?
Why so long?
Not just the suspension
I needed to test the tires, the brake
vertical distance, balance
between front and rear¡­
It took about a month
Is it really fun being a racer?
Why? You wanna be a racer?
I dunno
You dunno?
Then come on in and help me make tofu
Your friend's been helping me
for the whole afternoon
My friend?
You're too kind
It's no trouble
Please have some tea, Uncle
The tofu is done.
I also made some dim sum
Thanks
You're welcome
Takumi, you're back
How come you're here?
Look who's talking
You haven't called me once
since the swim last time
So I came to pay you a visit
Natsuki, where's the dim sum?
Just a second
It's so nice having a woman in the house
Oh¡­and in such a short skirt
If only it's two inches shorter¡­
You should've called me first
I called you several times
Either you're at work or you're sleeping
Lucky that Uncle is a nice guy
He a in't no nice guy
But I've been chatting with him
on the phone for days
He's actually very fond of you,
you know?
You've been chatting with him for days?
What's so strange about it?
What did he say?
Uncle told me you wanna be a racer
I never said that
He also told me, if you try hard enough
you'll become a world class racer
some day
Someone once told me
it's most important to find a world that belongs to us
Life is meaningful only
when we can find this world
Takumi, I think for you,
this world is racing
Who told you that?
It's an uncle who told me that
Uncle?
Since my father died
he's been taking care of me and my mom
I thought it's my dad
I knew he couldn't be that deep
So who is this uncle, Natsuki?
It's most important to find a world
that belongs to us
Life is meaningful only
when we can find this world
If you try hard enough
you'll become a world class racer
some day
Takumi, I think for you,
this world is racing
You deliver tofu so early in the morning?
Something wrong with the car?
Wrong?
I'm tuning it
Remember I told you
I wanna race with you?
I never agreed
If I ask you again now, would you agree?
Co-ordinating the suspension and the tires¡­
really takes a whole month?
You wanna know?   Yeah
It's crucial to increase the barometer of
the turbo charger
But keep an eye on the input air volume
And the exhaust valve should be
accommodated
Suspension must be tuned based on
hardness and absorption
the tire size and its angle formed
on the road
plus the lower arm bar and tower bar
Then fine-tune it based on
the computer data
Your dad is incredible
If I were to retune it,
itwouId take me at least 6 months
The balance has been tuned to
its optimal level
Simply put¡­
It's perfect
So my old man is really that good
However, every car has its limit
You're bound to find it
unsatisfactory one day
Just get another one
But I only like AE86
So how 'b out our race?
3 weeks from now. On Saturday
That long?
You said it took 3 weeks to retune
your car, right?
That's him
Got it
Be careful, He's very fast in the corners
It's just an AE86 after all
Are you OK?
Listen, this junk is for tofu delivery
not for racing with us
It's for your own good, got it?
That's right. You are professional racers
Of course you look down on us
street racers
Professional and street, we're all racers
Right, you beat me once
You remember?
Wanna win again?
OK, call me, you have my team's number
Is the AE87 out already?
Isn't it the AE89 now?
Just talk, don't fight
Hitting your kid in public
will inflict mental damage
Shut up
Tofu man
Let's talk, don't fight
Hitting your kid in public
will inflict mental damage
I'm going home
Still upset about losing?
I asked Kyouichi who beat you
to race again in 3 weeks
You're invited
If you don't have another car, I do
Thanks, but I only wanna drive
my own car
Give me a call if you change your mind
Want some cheese cake? It's delicious
Natsuki bought it for you
When did she come?
She's going home for 2 weeks
but will call you later
What else did she say?
What else she's supposed to say?
Hey. Hey¡­
You eating the whole cake?
You'll be stuffed to death
Tofu man, your AE86 is already
an antique
Might as well change to a new car
Don't tell me you gonna put it
into the AE86?
Isn't this great?
This is for race car only.
You wanna go to jail?
You're nuts
Catching roaches, Itsuki?
No, looking for my old man
He hasn't been back for days,
just like you
Customer
That sucks. He's not young anymore
He's so irresponsible,
leaving his business like this
What's gonna happen to me
if it goes bankrupt?
It's good that I've been living on my own
or else I wouldn't be this chubby
Boss. What are you doing?
Uncle, what're you up to?
We went for as pin at MtAkina
Has he come down yet?
Coming
Sounded like a high rpm
But it wasn't fast enough
as it entered the corner
Hop in
I'll only show you once
Watch carefully.
Pay attention to the new tachometer
Its power won't become obvious
till 11,000 revs
Sit tight. I wanna drive faster
Miya
The Kaiseki dinner was delicious, huh?
Not bad
I'm glad
Thanks so much for taking care of me¡­
when I puked two whole days last time
You were like a goddess who saved me
You're crazy
I mean it
I believe in gods
A god was actually human
but he could do
what other humans could not
So he became a god
But you know¡­
A god also does
what most humans do occasionally
What Cha wanna say?
Most humans would¡­
sometimes go to this neighboring
love hotel and¡­
It's OK since you're in the filling-up
business¡­
Bastard
Natsuki?
What the heck?
I test-drove the car with my dad
yesterday, you know?
This new car had a new tachometer.
I didn't know till yesterday
Just imagine, AE86, 250 horse power
You know how fast is 250 hp?
I tried to make a turn at 150 mph
It took me 3 minutes
through the entire MtAkina
Amazing, huh?
I really wanna tell everyone. You¡­
and Natsuki
No need
No need for what?
No need to tell Natsuki
Takumi
There's something
I wanna tell my best mate
Who?
You
Go ahead
I saw Natsuki¡­
She entered a love hotel with a guy
Love hotel?   Love hotel
There must be a mistake
It only costs 30,000 yen to bang her
What did you say?
30,000 yen to bang her
Your girl is a whore
Come again?
I don't want you get conned,
and you hit me?
Go to hell
Bastard!
Go to hell!
What you guys doing?
come over!
I've known you since 7
Don't!
Stop it!
Come, hit me!
Go ahead, hit me!
Takumi, stop it!
Let's talk!
Why fighting?
Pull him back!
Stop it, boy!
Stop it!
Takumi¡­
Why you hit him, you jerk?
Me a jerk? Yeah, I jerk off too
Hello? It's me
I shouldn't have called your girl a whore.
I'm sorry
You forgot? Today is Saturday
Everyone is waiting for you and
your AE86
Hello
Hello?
It's me
What's up?
I couldn't reach you for days
I've been in my hometown
I'm boarding the train now.
'll be back tonight
I'm racing in MtAkina tonight
Right after I'm done, I'll go see you
No, why don't I go see you
tomorrow instead?
The train is here. Talk to you later
Natsuki, I wanna see you badly
Natsuki
I'm glad you stayed with me
this past holiday
Did I give you enough money last time?
We'd better not see each other anymore
after tonight
I don't wanna be like this anymore
I don't wanna see you again and
remember this
All I want is to be with Takumi
Isn't it too much, broom-head?
I know Ryousuke well
I will never lose to the same guy¡­
twice
Shit, I hope I didn't hurt him bad
Dream on, look who's talking
Your nose' been bleeding for days
See, here you go again
Damn. I hope it won't become
a monthly routine
What're we still waiting for?
Everyone's here already
Are you in a hurry?
Give him 5 more minutes
Who cares if he comes.
The race is between you and me
Block the road.
The race will begin in 5 minutes
Wait, a car is coming up
It's the AE86
There weren't so many girls at the races
in our days
That's right
Uncles, this is a ladies-only zone. Get lost
It's coming up¡­
So you've resurrected this piece of junk?
Way to go, tofu boy
What happened to the car you crashed
into the hill?
Tofu boy, you wanna go first?
No need. Just drive faster,
I got of her things to do
For you
No need
Ryousuke has something to tell you
Listen. Although Kyouichi is
a professional
all professionals have their weaknesses¡­
You don't need to teach me.
I'm gonna win anyway
What about me?
I'll beat you too
The road is clear. We can start anytime
I repeat: We can start anytime
Five
Four
Three
Two
One
Go
All three cars took off at top speed
Kyouichi's E3 is leading,
followed by Ryousuke's FC
The AE86 comes last
They've past the first corner
Both Ryousuke and Takumi
made their best lap time
Everyone's faster in the presence of
a professional
What Cha doing?
That's what we called strategy
The FC suddenly lags behind
before the tunnel
I wonder what's happened to Ryousuke?
The speed is unbelievable
All three cars exceed 100 kph
At the corner just now
The AE86 is waiting for its opportunity
Let's see if it can overtake the E3
in the next corner
Go for it, Takumi
Give it back. What's with you?
What? It's a race
Of course we have to shout. Go ahead
Here we go
Over taken
The E3 doesn't leave much room
Both the FC and AE86 used the ditch
to overtake the E3
Let me explain, little girl
In street racing, a professional's common
weakness¡­
is to leave some open space
when taking a right corner
Go for it, Takumi
Takumi, it's just you and me now
What 'bout the car at the back?
I can block for you
Better watch your own ass
The AE86 and FC both managed
to pass a professional
But the E3 is trying to catch up
Although they use different tactics
the FC and AE86 are way too fast
in entering corners
It's not an easy task catching up
Go for it, Takumi¡­
Attention, everyone
A vehicle has just taken off
from the national park
and is heading up the mountain
A car is coming ahead.
Get ready to slow down
Kyouichi ignores the warning
and tries to overtake
Should we block him?
It's too late
The E3 has crashed
The AE86 and FC passed through.
The race goes on
Is he OK?
Forget him
Kyouichi, are you OK?
The 5 consecutive hair pins.
Can the FC pass it here?
The AE86 is at its limit. Now it's my turn
The FC has overtaken the AE86
There's only 1 km left
I don't think the AE86 can make it
What the heck?
I knew it
You knew again?
Takumi has never taken the leading
position before
Ryousuke's car is powerful but
he still followed Takumi
He wants to learn his move
and then overtake him
So it's a lost case for Takumi?
Not necessarily
You've been driving by yourself
all these years
You've never competed with anyone
Remember
Don't pay attention to the competition itself
Ignore other racers
The one you need to beat is yourself
Almost at the finish line.
The AE86 hasn't given up
It's still right behind the FC
The FC has missed its lane
when entering the corner
Can Ryousuke with stand the pressure
from the AE86?
The pressure is from the tires
It's retuned to 250 hp,
But the FC is still too powerful
As time drags on, the tires won't hold up
and the car can't go all the way in its drift
So the last 2 corners are the most crucial
in this race
It's here
The finish line is up ahead
The mighty FC has the absolute edge
The result is quite clear
The FC seems to be slower entering
the corner
The AE86 is taking the inner lane,
can it overtake?
The AE86 has won
The AE86 is the ultimate racing
god of MtAkina
Great. He did it
He won
Let's hug!
I've lost anyway
So what's your plan now?
Nothing. You?
I'm gonna set up a new race team.
Wanna join?
Dunno. Gottago
Takumi, I really want you on my team
Sleep on it
We¡¯ll see
Takumi
Takumi. Takumi¡­
it's most important to find a world
that belongs to us
Life is meaningful only
when we can find this world
Takumi, I think for you,
this world is racing
So what's up? You lost or what?
Hey. Hey¡­
Let's drink to it
Son of a bitch
Itsuki, I'm sorry
Ryousuke, Takumi here
I'd like¡­
to join your race team