在英国
只有拥有"皇家律师"资格的大律师
更多纪录片网盘下载 请访问夏末秋字幕组论坛 http://www.xmqzmz.org/  本片字幕由夏末秋字幕组制作 仅供试看使用 禁止用于商业行为 并请于下载后24小时内删除 若因私自散布传播造成法律问题 本字幕组概不负责
才能披上丝质的律师袍出庭
"丝袍"是皇家律师的代名词
丝袍加身的大律师
是英国最顶尖的辩护律师
本字幕由 LieseL 子雨夜前 加菲引 南柯一梦 翻译制作 校对 给MP姐姐秒到的懒蘇 此致华年 后期/压制 statm 義經Aizen【夏末秋字幕组】
我们立志翻译各种人文科学纪录片 需要您的知识 充实自己 服务大众 加入我们 联系QQ:1719520679【长期招募】
陪审团做出一致的裁决了吗? 'Has the jury reached a verdict upon which you all of you are agreed?'
有了 'Yes.'
对被告谋杀罪名的指控 成立还是不成立? On count one of the indictment do you find the defendant guilty or not guilty of murder?
不成立 Not guilty.
他的案已经审了一半 Brian 我能做什么? He's part-heard. Brian what can I do?
什么?Brian 等一下 What? Hang on Brian.
我当然已经帮你找到别的人 等等 Of course I've got somebody else for you. Hang on for a second
行吗?Brian will you Brian?
Jake 你猜怎么着? Guess what Jake?
-哈罗 小姐 -我的谋杀案? Hello Miss. My murder?
我还是... I better...
抱歉 喂? Sorry. Hello?
Jake Jake 她搞定了吗? Jake Jake has she finished yet?
-小姐 审完了吗? -是的 -Has your trial finished Miss? -Yes.
-审完了 -好 Brian? -'Yes.' -Good. Brian?
谢谢你 好了 对不起 Thanks Miss. Cheers. Sorry Miss.
你知道他们怎么说的 Brian Well you know what they say Brian.
法务助理守则第一条 把女孩跟精神病归为一类 First rule of clerking. Always put the girls in with the psychopaths.
我再打给你 All right I'll call you back.
Harry 你好吗?听好了 我需要你帮我个大忙 Harry how are you? Yeah listen I need a ginormous favour.
这里是大律师公会 下午好 Chambers good afternoon.
什么叫这回该我帮你? What do you mean it's my turn to do you a favour?
我35岁 是个约会色狼 哈罗 Martha So I'm 35 years old I'm a date rapist. Hello Martha.
我往酒里加料 回到酒店房 她已不省人事 Spike drinks back to my hotel room she's comatosed in I pop.
我丢了婚姻 丢了工作 不只因为我是色狼 I've lost my marriage I lose my job because not only am I a rapist
因为我还是个警察 but I'm also a police officer.
你们有什么看法? So what do you think?
-判我几年? -八年? -What do I get? -Eight?
-给力想啊 -十年? -On a fight. -Ten?
-四年 -四年? -Four. -Four?
-厉害 -厉害 -Brilliant. -Brilliant.
今天上庭了?Marth In court today Marth?
-是 -庭审? -嗯 -Yes. -trial? -Mm-hm.
有什么趣闻吗? Anything interesting?
嗨 妈 是我 Hi mum. It's me.
呃 我有没有跟你说过我在打那个谋杀案? Um did I tell you about the murder trial I was doing?
算了 没事 拜拜 妈 Anyway doesn't matter. Bye mum.
-明天 -什么啊? -Tomorrow. -What?
恶性入室行窃 Aggravated burglary.
-怎么个恶性法? -折磨 -What's the aggravated bit? -Torture.
受害者是个领抚恤金的老人 Of an old-age pensioner.
被绑起来差点给打爆了头  Tied him up and nearly punched his head off.
别告诉我 Oh and don't tell me.
你觉得女人会更容易让陪审团信服 You think a woman would go down better with a jury.
不关我的事 是事务律师点名找你 Got nothing to do with me. Solicitor's asked for you.
-他是怎样的人? -事务律师还是当事人? -And what's he like? -The solicitor or the client?
-当事人 -他 呃.. -The client. -He's um...
你能行的 You'd be fine.
-就一份背书和DVD? -剩下等下找人骑车送过去 -A backsheet and a DVD? -I'll bike the rest over.
你能行的 You'll be fine.
信我 没问题的 Trust me. Fine.
诉讼状呢? Billy Where's the brief Billy?
这辆的士在哪?在哪? Where's this cab? Where's this cab?
-运毒案的犯人打算认罪 -你确定? -The drugs it's going to plead. -You sure?
-你要站到Ladd法官的席前 -太好了 -And you're in front of judge Ladd. -Excellent.
我惦念着你丝袍资格申请的推荐函呢 So reference for your silk application I was thinking sir.
爱死你了 Billy I love it when you think Billy.
-你猜他能拿到丝袍资格吗? -问题来了 -Do you reckon he'll get Silk? -There's a problem.
像我们这种新生律师会提交多过一份的申请 More than one application from a young set of Chambers like us
可不是好事 is not a good idea.
我们有两份申请 We've got two applications.
他的 还有她的 His and hers.
我们也没有什么办法 是吗? Not much we can do about thatis there?
有吗? Is there?
嗨呀 你怎么来了? Hiya. Why are you here?
它们太大份 自行车装不过来 They were too big for a bike.
-它们? -对 -They? -Yeah.
-进来 -上面两尺半厚的是入室行窃案 -Come in. -Top two and a half feet is aggravated burglary
底下六寸厚的是运毒案 and the bottom six inches is a drugs mule.
两个诉讼? Two briefs?
运毒案没什么好担心 五分钟就可以搞定 Don't worry about the drugs it's a five - minute mention and nothing's going to happen.
让法官多见上你几面 I need the judge to see your face
或许他能给你当丝袍申请的推荐人 because he could be a reference for your Silk application.
在你的收件箱看到的 Saw that in your pigeon hole.
两个案件排到同一个庭上? And they're both listed in the same court right?
首先早上10点在9号庭审运毒案 Court nine is first up at 10 for the drugs
接着 10:30在1号庭保释申诉后审入室行窃 and then court one for the burglary trial at 10.30 behind a bail app.
我不要我的被告蒙不白之冤 Billy I don't want my defendant in the burglary short-changed Billy.
15年来你都在坚持 到现在还是 15 years you've been doing this and you still believe don't you?
一日没定罪就是无辜 Innocent until proven guilty.
我一直在留意你 而你从来没有动摇 是吗? I've been watching you all that time and you never waver do you?
没有宗旨 就没有希望 If you don't have that then you're dead.
干杯 Cheers.
晚安 Billy Night Billy.
Reader先生阁下 忘了说... Mr Reader sir? Forgot to mention...
那个运毒案 你跟Marth做同案辩护 The drugs Martha Costello will be co-defending with you.
惨了 惨了 Damn. Damn.
-要帮忙吗? -不用 -Do you want a hand? -No.
请各相关人士到1号庭... Will all parties please go to court one...
抱歉 先生 你口袋里有东西吗? Sorry sir have you got anything in your pockets?
怎样找到带我的大律师? How do I find the barrister who's looking after me?
看法院的清单 看看你分配到哪个庭 Look on the court lists see which court you're in
他们会来找你的 and they'll come and find you there.
对不起 不要跟我说话好吗? Sorry can you not talk to me?
我要百分百的专注 抱歉  I've got to complete focus. Sorry.
-恶性入室行窃?我跟你打诶 -哦 -The aggravated burglary? I'm prosecuting you. -Oh.
你的当事人真行啊 Nice man your client.
每个被你控告的人你都这样说  That's what you say about everyone you prosecute.
他站在被告席上接受审判 If he's here if he's standing trial
就是说皇家检控署和警方 还有我都认为他有罪 that means the CPS the police and me all think he did it.
那对你说明了什么? What does that tell you?
说明他非常需要我帮他辩护 That he very badly needs me fighting his corner.
前科清单 Up-to-date list of previous.
麻烦你帮我叫Mercedes Cordoba案件的事务律师 Yeah sorry yes could you get the solicitor in the case of...
现在过来接待处行吗? Mercedes Cordoba to come to reception right now please?
-最新情况都了解了吧 Marth? -是的 -You up to speed on this Marth? -Yes.
-你是同案辩护律师? -对啊 这个案的法官很好应付 -Are you co-defending? -Yeah big softy this judge.
来吧 我们一起上 好吗? Marth Let's go for it. You and me together eh Marth?
-认罪答辩? -你清楚自己想做什么 -Plead? -You know you want to.
三十分钟后我在1号庭还有个大案 所以... I've got a big trial in court one in half an hour so...
呦 我这边是没辙了 Yeah well I've got no mitigation to speak of
你那边可是可怜又柔弱的准妈妈 and you're poor vulnerable and pregnant.
这案能有多难啊? 我们20分钟就够了 爽 How hard can it be? We'll be 20 minutes tops.
不要再说"爽"了 你正常点吧 Clive Stop saying "tops" like you're someone normal Clive.
你可是上过哈罗的人 You went to Harrow.
-你是Martha Costello -我不是代表你 -You're Martha Costello. -I'm not representing you.
-不 我是你的新学徒 -喔 天啊 抱歉 -No I'm your new pupil. -Oh God. Sorry.
你可别像我一样! Don't ever do this.
-什么? -没有事务律师在场就跟当事人见面 -What's that? -See a client without a solicitor's rep present.
-知道了 但为什么呢? -防范措施 -Right. Why not? -Protection
避免难缠的客户说你错给了意见 in case a difficult client wants to say you've given bad advice.
现在大律师也能当被告 即使你是新手 Barristers can be sued now. Even baby ones.
-这个客户难缠吗? -是的 没错 -Is this client difficult? -Oh yes. Right.
不要说话 一个字也别说 So don't speak don't say a word.
-都让我来 -请讲 -Leave it all to me. -'Cells.'
Gary Rush的律师 Brief for Gary Rush.
我想告诉你 我还没有假发和长袍 Just wanted to say I haven't got a wig and gown yet.
-那有问题吗? -我告诉你一个秘密 -Is that all right? -I'll let you into a secret.
穿上战袍 带上头盔 整装待发 Putting one of these on and one of these on your head so helps.
就像超人变身 It's like Superman coming out of the phone box.
来吧 Gary Rush一案 受害人85岁 这一点让事情... OK Gary Rush. The victim is 85 years old which makes this...
非常糟糕 就是说会影响到对真凶的落网 well a bad bad thing which is why it matters that the right man goes down for it.
一个关键问题 一个85岁的老人在恐慌下 One big question - can a terrified 85-year-old be relied upon
可以正确指认出带着巴拉克拉法帽的袭击者吗? to identify his balaclaved attacker correctly?
-是你来找Gary? -是的 -You here for Gary? -Yes.
Scarrow警司 DS Scarrow.
-这边走 -谢谢 -赠你一言 不要跟他单独相处 -There you go. -Thank you. -Word of advice. Don't be alone with him.
-你别吓唬我了 -我是担心你的安全 仅此而已 -You don't intimidate me. -I'm concerned for your safety that's all.
-我们没时间跟他详谈 来个缓兵之计吧 -啥? -Right we haven't got time to talk to him properly so think like a waitress. -What?
先上餐前小点 然后他们就会乖乖地等上菜 Get the bread on the table the drinks out fast then they're happy to wait for the food.
-你是我代表律师? -对 -Are you for me? -Yes.
-这小子是谁? -这是..是我的学徒 -Who's the boy? -This is...is my pupil.
你能行吗? Are you good?
给我几分钟 我们好好谈一下 Look give me a few minutes and then we'll talk properly.
如果我被判罪了 就要坐蹲牢 而且蹲很久 I'll be going to prison huh for a very long time if I'm convicted of this.
坦白说 我之前从未见过你 Now I've never met you before
而从我这里看出去你有点弱不禁风 but from where I'm standing you look a bit lightweight frankly.
所以你最好马上回答我的问题 So I think you should answer my question. Now.
我能行 I'm good.
-但你不是皇家律师 -还不是 -But you're not a QC. -Not yet.
你不进来跟我谈吗? Are you not going to come in talk to me?
我时间宝贵 Rush先生 I'm short of time Mr Rush.
-这个难缠吗? -不 -Is this one difficult? -No.
是Mercedes Cordoba吗? Mercedes Cordoba?
我是Martha Costello 你的律师 I'm Martha Costello your Brief.
-你吞了12个装满了可卡因的避孕套 -是 -You swallowed 12 condoms filled with cocaine? -Yes.
预产期是什么时候? When's the baby due?
八周以后 Eight weeks.
你知不知道 Do you know
那些避孕套在你体内破开了会有什么后果? what would have happened if the condoms had broken open inside of you?
会死 You die.
-还有你的孩子 -我知道 -And your baby. -I know.
你之前生过孩子? You've got children already?
-是 -多少个? -Yes. -How many?
五个 Five.
你几岁? How old are you?
26岁 26.
-你生第一胎的时候多大了? -17岁 -And how old were you when your first child was born? -17.
关于你的同案被告 你有什么要说的吗? Is there anything you want to say about your co-defendant?
-那么指使你运毒的人呢? -没有 -What about the people who asked you to carry the drugs? -No.
如果你现在认罪 你会得到最大的宽恕 If you plead guilty now you'll get maximum credit
就是说你可以减刑三分一或者四分一 which means about a third or a quarter off your sentence.
无论判刑多少年 对你和你的孩子来说都太长了 You know that whatever sentence you do get will be too long for the baby to stay with you in prison.
你现在不是非要认罪不可 You don't have to plead guilty now
但这个法官挺好的 but this judge is all right
下次审判未必能碰上同一个法官 and you might not get the same judge next time.
我明白 I understand.
好了 好了 OK. OK.
我需要你在我的诉讼状上签字 I need you to sign the front of my brief.
这只是说明我没有给你施加任何压力 你明白吗? This just makes clear that I've not put any pressure on you. Do you understand?
好 OK.
就在那 Just there.
到你了 走吧 You're on. Let's go. OK.
-你多大了? -35岁 -How old are you? -35.
你35岁多久了? How long have you been 35?
几年吧 Couple of years.
是不是很难做到皇家律师? Is it hard to get Silk?
境界都不同了 可以挑案子来做 Everything changes. You get to choose your cases
想休假 就休假 take time off when you want to
提出诱导性提问不被追究 ask leading questions and get away with it.
我是Cant Frogett事务所的 来办Rush的案 I'm from Cant Frogett for the Rush trial.
你死去哪了? Where the hell have you been?
我去试镜了 我不工作的时候我就去当演员 I had a casting. I'm an actor. This is what I do when I'm not working.
-哪里的试镜? -海飞丝 -What was the casting for? -Head and Shoulders.
洗发水巨头? The shampoo giant?
认罪? Pleading?
是的 Yes.
那是谁? Who's that?
公会来了两个实习律师 Two new pupils in Chambers.
-Billy让我先选 我选了那女孩 -你说真的? -Billy gave me first choice so I plumped for the girl. -Did you really?
-看上她哪点? -看上她那个有十分用的脑袋瓜 -On what basis? -On the basis that she's got a really useful brain.
-我是Nick Slade -喔 你是另外一个 -Nick Slade. -Oh right you're the other one.
另外一个? The other one?
抱歉 我说得不太清楚 Sorry that came out a bit wrong.
我是另外一个实习律师 Niamh I'm the other new pupil. Niamh.
我们是不是该...握个手什么的? Shouldn't we...shake hands or something?
大律师不握手的 约定俗成 Barristers don't shake hands. It's kind of a rule.
明白 Right.
-你怎么知道的? -我爸爸是法官 -How do you know that? -My father's a judge.
噢 明白 Oh right.
全体起立 All rise.
Billy说这个法官可能成为我丝袍申请的推荐人 Billy said this judge might be a reference for my Silk application.
-他也那样跟我说过 -不可能我们都找他吧 -He said that to me too. -We can't both ask him.
我们拭目以待 Let's see how we go shall we?
Mercedes Cordoba很穷 Mercedes Cordoba is poor.
她来自波哥大的波利瓦城 就是说她极度贫穷 She comes from the Ciudad Bolivar in Bogota which means her poverty is extreme.
她的弱势让贩毒集团很容易入手 She was classically vulnerable to the approach from the drug cartel
以金钱诱使她毒藏腹内 who exploited her with the offer of money
然后搭上飞往伦敦的班机  for traveling on a hot flight to London with drugs in her belly.
她已提起极大的勇气承认罪行 She has shown great courage in pleading guilty.
她明白那将令她的孩子无所依靠 She knows that she will lose her baby into care.
我们可以想像一个人要有多绝望 We can only imagine how hopeless your situation must be
才会去吞下那些装满可卡因的避孕套 to agree to swallowing condoms filled with cocaine
明知可能危及自身和胎儿的性命 knowing the damage they could cause to you and your baby.
Mercedes Cordoba不是无情 不是邪恶 Mercedes Cordoba is not heartless not evil
她不过是绝望了 she's just desperate.
她要为她的行为付出代价 她知道的 She will pay for what she's done she knows that
但我恳请法官阁下在判罚时 but I ask your Honour to pass a sentence
考虑到她的不幸 给她一个重生的机会 which reflects her sad life and gives her hope for a better one.
你要向我 Do you want to address me
就案中两位被告相对的地位提出见解吗? on the relative status positions of the two defendants?
法官阁下 我认为我要说的都已经说过了 I think it's already there in everything I've said your Honour.
Reader先生 Mr Reader.
我很惊讶我渊博的同行选择了避而不谈 I'm surprised that my learned friend has chosen not to talk about
相对于我的当事人 where her client is in the hierarchy
她的当事人是犯罪集团内的要员  compared with mine.
法官阁下已经看过补充证据通告了吗? Your Honour has seen the Notices of additional evidence?
Mercedes Cordoba是个经验老到的贩毒者 Mercedes Cordoba is an experienced trafficker.
她利用多次的怀孕摆脱海关稽查 She uses her repeated pregnancies to throw off customs.
她没想到 她已经被海关留意多年 What she didn't know was that she was being watched by Customs over a period of years.
每次旅程都在她怀孕期间 She's pregnant every time she travels.
是她防止被截查的手段 It's her protection against being stopped.
修女 女童军和孕妇皆可无障碍通关 Nuns girl guides and pregnant women get waved through.
我的当事人Angel Valera 是司机 Angel Valera my client is the driver.
他在飞机场跟她碰面 He met her at the airport.
没有证据显示他曾经之前参与过类似的事件 There is no evidence that he has ever done anything like this before.
换言之 他不过在贩毒集团最底层 He is at the bottom of the ladder in terms of his position in the hierarchy.
他是这位狡猾的孕妇 即同案被告 手下的一个小人物 A good many rungs below that of his cunning pregnant co-defendant.
Costello小姐 机会是可一不可再 No second bite at the cherry Miss Costello.
你们两位 起立 Stand up both of you.
你们的非法集团给我国带来痛苦和不幸 I have to establish in my own mind
我必须理清思路 where each of you stands
明确你们各自在这个集团里所处的地位 in the ranks of this evil organisation that brings misery into our country.
ercedes Cordoba 我确信你是集团的上层人物 I have no doubt that you Mercedes Cordoba are a good way up it
你的辩护律师怎样力辩也是徒劳 whatever your Counsel says.
你将入狱14年 You will go to prison for 14 years.
Angel Valera 你侥幸地 Angel Valera you have the dubious good fortune
只是身处这个不法集团里的底层 to be a long way down the pecking order in this obscene organization
对你判刑时我会考虑及此 and I have to reflect that in your sentence.
你将入狱8年 带他们两个下去 You will go to prison for eight years. Take them down.
全体起立 All rise.
-午饭时间我过来看你 -谢谢你 谢谢你 -午饭时 -I'll be down at lunchtime to see you. -Thank you thank you. -Lunchtime.
噢! Oh!
-混蛋 你给我下套 -我能怎么做呢? -You set me up you bastard. -What was I supposed to do?
-难道预先通知你? -你就是要打击我 -Tell you in advance? -You knew you were going to cut my throat.
我只是在尽本分 做当事人的代表和解读诉讼状 Doing my job representing my client reading the brief.
你别多想  Don't take it personally.
想那么多 这个律师还当不当阿? Where would we all be if we took things personally?
你别以为高我一等  Don't patronize me.
不是吗? 你像个孩子一样 Why not? You're behaving like a child.
明显是你没有看过补充证据通告 You clearly hadn't read the NAEs.
让我猜猜看 文件还没开封 Let me guess still at home
静躺在你家地板上不知道哪个角落 an unopened file lying on the floor somewhere?
你知道自己没有做好本分工作 You didn't do your job properly you know it
这才是你发火的原因 that's why you're cross.
-天杀的 她给判了14年 -这是谁的错? -She just got 14 years for God's sake. -Whose fault is that?
你要去哪? Where are you going?
-去找法官要推荐信 -没错 是我想太多了 -To ask the judge for a reference. -Of course I don't take things personally.
-请辩护律师Costello小姐... -看啥? 看啥? -'Will Miss Costello of Counsel please...' -What? What?
-喂?Billy 那个运毒案 -'Hello?' Billy the drugs mules
-我这边判8年 她那边14年 -拿到推荐信了? -'I got eight. She got 14.' -Reference sir?
-渴望已久的推荐信 -非常好 -'Reference to die for I'd think.' -Very good sir.
有245名女性披上丝袍 245 women Silks ever.
从成千上万个人中脱颖而出 Ever. Out of tens of thousands.
现在我们不得不敬重这个统计数据 Now boys you've got to respect a statistic like that.
在丝袍界里 一个女人要单挑十二个男人 And it's still 12 male QC's to every Doris.
我就说嘛 这是怎么一个比率啊?Jake 嗯? I mean what are the odds Jake? Hmm?
您尊驾惠临真是我们的荣幸 Costello小姐 Kind of you to grace us with your presence Miss Costello.
抱歉 法官大人 我在别的法庭耽搁了 I'm sorry my Lord I was detained in another court.
重头戏前的空档不忘赚点小钱? Nice little earner before the main act?
收90英镑 减掉给助理的费用 About 90 Pounds minus clerk's fees
办公室租金 交通费用 税金 增值税 大概还剩12.50镑 chambers rent travel tax VAT so that leaves about 12.50 Pounds.
赚钱能力真不咋滴 而且迟到完全是我的错 So not much of an earner really but entirely my fault I'm late.
昨日是一场硬仗 你还是赢了 Good result yesterday against the odds.
陪审团的判断总是明智的 Well the jury's always right.
我们可以开始宣誓了吗? Let's swear one in shall we?
其实 我还没跟被告谈过 Actually I haven't had a chance to speak to the defendant.
-五分钟 -多给一点点? -Five minutes. -A little longer?
四分三十秒 开始计时 Four and a half and counting.
明明白白地告诉我 你不在现场 Just confirm for me 100% you weren't there
你从来没到过那地方 凶手不是你 you've never been there it wasn't you?
说 是还是不是? Look...yes or no?
那不是我 It wasn't me.
你没做过? You didn't do this?
所以说他通过视频指认的时候错认了你? So he was mistaken when he picked you out in a video ID?
我知道你想怎样 Look I know what you're doing.
难倒你了吧 知道自己还不够格 就想哄我认罪 You're up against it you're out of your depth so you're leaning on me to plead guilty.
我不会那样干 I don't do that.
只要你告诉我你是无辜 我就为你拼了 You tell me you didn't do this and I will fight for you.
你什么时候拿到的诉讼状? What time did you get this brief?
昨晚 Late last night.
一起化压力为动力 We all perform better under pressure.
Dodds先生 你可以慢慢说 Take as much time as you need Mr Dodds.
他打了我三次 He hit me three times.
每隔三分钟 他就走向我 Every three minutes he'd just walk over to me
系紧我的椅子 挥拳打我的脸 tied up in my chair and punch me in the face.
不急不忙地 Wasn't in any hurry.
你可以列出被偷的东西吗? Have you been able to establish what was stolen?
我亡妻的珠宝 我的婚戒 My late wife's jewellery my wedding ring.
我带不上了 因为患了关节炎 I can't wear it any more because of this arthritis.
抽屉里的55镑 我的手表 55 Pounds in a drawer my watch.
我的特等军功勋章 My Distinguished Conduct Medal.
他偷了我的勋章 He stole my medal.
-你是怎样获得勋章的? -诺曼底 -How did you win the medal? -Normandy.
在1944年6月4日的晚上 Night of June 4th 1944.
在诺曼底登陆前 我们空降到已被占领的法国 We dropped into occupied France ahead of the beach landings.
我... And I...
我 呃... I er...
救出一个受伤的战友 brought a wounded comrade in.
你有多少时间看着作案者? How much time did you get to look at the intruder?
-13分钟 -为什么如此精确? -13 minutes. -How are you able to be so precise?
墙上挂着钟 There's a clock on the wall.
因为警方 The police
不是就爱问一些时间之类是事情么? like to know about the time of everything don't they? So
我就多看几眼 I thought I should keep an eye on it.
作案者穿着什么衣服? What was the intruder wearing?
他戴着摩托车头盔 He had a motorcycle helmet on.
后来他给摘掉了 Then he took it off.
下面还戴了一个巴拉克拉法帽 He had a sort of balaclava on underneath
就像F1赛车选手在头盔下戴了那个帽子 like the ones Formula 1 drivers wear under their helmets
他一直戴着那帽 and he kept that on.
休庭五分钟 Five minute break.
全体起立 All rise.
-入室盗窃有很多种 -对 -Lots of form for burglary. -Yes.
-那? -Nick 够了 -So? -Yes Nick?
那...不能因为他以前犯过类似的错误 So... just because he's done this kind of thing before
-就说他这次有罪吧 -没定罪 就是清白 -doesn't make him guilty this time. -Innocent until proven guilty.
我就靠这几个字活的 Four words to live by.
但你怎么认为? But what do you think?
-你会明白的 -明白什么? -It'll happen to you. -What will?
如果被告有罪 辩护律师是知道的 Well all defence counsels know when a defendant's guilty.
但审判中途他们经常会忘记 But by halfway through a trial they always forget.
-你视力怎么样? -还行 -How good is your eyesight? -It's fine.
你在警察局进行了疑犯指认程序 You attended an ID procedure at the police station
过程中你要求离屏幕近儿点坐 and during that procedure you made a request to sit nearer to the screen.
我想看清眼睛 I wanted to look at the eyes.
形状和颜色 Their shape their colour.
当他在公寓时 我想 你有两刷子啊 When he was in the flat I thought "You're good
虽然没有留下什么证据 "you're not giving me anything here
但你确让我记住了你的眼睛  but for one thing - your eyes.
我就要靠这个抓住你 "I'm going to get you on that."
你挺为你自己的老而弥坚而自豪 You pride yourself on being sprightly for your age.
你或许不太乐意承认你的身体机能 You might not be very good at admitting that your faculties
已经不如从前了 are working less well now than they were.
一天一天衰退的视力让你感到懊恼吧 You're raging against the dying of the light.
Costello女士 我还没有瞎呢 My light is not dying Miss Costello.
他就是在我公寓的那个男人! 我没有认错! That was the man in my flat and I'm not mistaken about it.
Dodd先生 那你听到他说什么了吗?  How's your hearing Mr Dodd?
他没说过话 一次也没有 He didn't speak. Not once.
您能看一下您的证人供词吗? Will you look at your witness statement?
在第二页的倒数第三行文字 It's three lines from the bottom of the second page.
-上面说了什么? -上面说 -What does it say? -It says
作案者没有特别的口音 "The intruder had no particular accent."
Dodd先生 但你刚才告诉陪审团他没有说话 You've just told this jury that he didn't speak Mr Dodd.
那你怎么知道作案者操什么口音? So how do you know what accent the intruder actually had?
他哼哼唧唧的 He hummed.
他在我公寓的所有时间 The whole time he was in my flat.
他一直在哼哼唧唧 He only stopped humming
除了他打我的时候 when he was hitting me.
那你的证人供词上提及了吗? Is that in your witness statement?
没 No.
证人供词的重点 The whole point of a witness statement
难道不就是告诉警方事实真相么? is to tell the whole truth to the police isn't it?
那你为什么没提及他一直在哼哼唧唧 So why didn't you mention he was humming?
我不想让他看上去像个疯子 I didn't want him to seem like he was mad.
什么意思? I beg your pardon?
我想让他去正规的监狱 I'd like him to go to a proper prison.
噢 我明白了 Oh I see.
你要让你认为的凶手在检察官面前别无选择? No soft option for the man you believe did this to you?
我不想让他被关到住精神病人的地方 I don't want him going into a home for the mentally ill.
警方一逮捕嫌疑人 你就认以为警方抓对了人 The police have made an arrest and you've assumed they've got the right man
而现在你只是想给他定罪并且施以惩罚 and now you want to make sure he's convicted and above all punished.
Costello女士 你是在问问题还是在做演讲 Is this a question or a speech Miss Costello?
那上面坐的不是被告 This defendant wasn't there.
Dodd先生 你认错人了 You've got the wrong man Mr Dodd.
我妻子就是在精神病患之家去死 My wife died in a home for the mentally ill.
她最后是穿着尿布死的 She had to wear nappies at the end.
当她走的时候 她的尿布都3天没有换过了 When she died her nappy hadn't been changed for three days.
我想给她换 但是她不让 I wanted to do it for her but she wouldn't let me.
她总说 你是我的丈夫 "You're my husband" she said.
最后一次我去探望她 The last time I visited her
在他们看电视的房间里有个新的标语 there was a new sign up in the room where they sat to watch the television in.
上面写着 It said
不许跳舞 "No dancing."
我不希望任何人经历这样的痛苦 I wouldn't wish that on anyone.
即使是我最憎恨的敌人 Not even my worst enemy.
午休时间? Lunch?
她来了吗? Is she coming?
-你还好吧? -什么意思? -You OK? -How do you mean?
呃... Um...
心态平和 Emotional detachment.
-任何一个大律师都应能信步闲庭 -像你? -Any barrister worth their salt has it. -Like you?
-这个下午... -我真的很忙 Nick -This afternoon... -I'm really busy Nick.
阁下知道自己头部的大小吗? Does sir know his head size?
-嗯? -我们量一下? -Hmm? -Shall we find out?
好 Yeah.
我们要两个备用领儿? And shall we say two spare collars
六条细带和一打装口子 six bands and a dozen studs?
非常好 多少钱？ Great. How much?
含增值税价1759元 1759 Pounds plus VAT.
-你们做二手货吗? -做 先生 -Do you do second hand? -Yes sir.
已故大律师的假发? Wigs from dead barristers?
是的 先生 Yes sir.
那我能看一下二手的假发吗? Could I look at the second hand then please?
唔唔呼! Whoo hoo!
唔呼! Whoo!
一个戴着巴拉克拉法帽的陌生人大半夜出现在你的公寓 A strange man in your flat in a balaclava in the middle of the night.
你一定被吓坏了 You must have been terrified.
呃 我是吓到了 但是 Well I was scared but
我不想让他看出来 I didn't want him to know that.
-他打了你吗? -对 -And he hit you didn't he? -Yes.
三次 Three times.
我尽量地看着他 I tried very hard to look at him.
每一次他打我时 我都尽量地看着他 Each time he hit me I tried to look at him.
证明我不怕他 Show him he wasn't winning.
你对作案者在你寓所内的动作 You've been incredibly precise
描述细致得让人难以置信  about the actions of the intruder inside your flat.
每隔三分钟打你一次 Three minutes between each time he hit you.
这很有意思 但是 It's funny but
让自己集中注意看他在做什么 我想这很有帮助 making myself focus exactly on what he was doing I think it helped.
我的意思是 这样使我不那么害怕 I mean it stopped me from being quite so frightened.
在战争时期你是伞兵团成员吧? You were in the parachute regiment during the war?
是 Yes.
跟我们讲讲当半夜遭到袭击时 Tell us about jumping out of aeroplanes
从飞机上跳出时的情况 at night under fire.
只要看好了 一变灯跳就是了 You just do it. Wait for the light.
1只短吻鳄 2只短吻鳄 3只短吻鳄 跳 One alligator two alligator three alligator go.
人家数鳄鱼 我就数短吻鳄 Some people do crocodiles I do alligators.
所以你认为在压力面前 反而让你头脑清醒? So you know about thinking straight under pressure?
我觉得是 Well I suppose so.
-他戴手套吗? -戴 -He was wearing gloves? -Yes.
-他咳嗽了吗? -没有 -Did he cough? -No.
-他打喷嚏了吗? -没有 -Sneeze? -No.
-他挖鼻孔了吗? -没有 -Scratch his nose? -No.
Costello女士 和案件有关吗? Relevance Miss Costello?
我不明白 我想陪审团也不理解 I'm struggling I'm sure the jury are.
他打哈欠了 He yawned.
就在他离开的时候 Just as he was leaving.
他站在门口 看着我 打了个哈欠 He stood at the door looking at me and he yawned.
然后他提起手捂住他的嘴 And he put his hand up to cover his mouth.
我在想这个盗贼好奇怪啊 没有情感 I thought how strange a burglar with no emotion
但是却很有礼貌 but very good manners.
然后他把手放在了门把上 Then he put his hand on the door handle
看着我 looked at me
开门 然后走了 opened the door and walked out.
你在想什么? What do you think?
难道那个哈欠能给他再加一年刑期吗? That yawn put about another year on his sentence?
-进展如何? -你应该去买个二手的 -How's it going? -You should have got a second hand one.
一个白花花的新假发让你看上去你很无知 A virgin white wig makes you look like you don't know what you're doing.
呃 事实上 我偷的 Well actually I nicked it.
有意思 Very funny.
我的律师见鬼去了? Where the hell is my barrister?
我的律师在哪? 我马上就要坐牢了 Where's my brief? I'm going to get sent down for this.
-你想先见谁? -我先在Gary Rush那边呆两分钟 -Who do you want first? -Can I do Gary Rush for two minutes
然后见Mercedes Cordoba 行吗? and then Mercedes Cordoba?
我觉得你都不知道自己在做什么 I don't think you know what you're doing.
我会救你出去的 I'm going to get you off.
Mercedes cordoba呢? Mercedes Cordoba?
-囚车走了 -什么? -Van's gone. -What?
我告诉过你 就2分钟 I told you I was going to be two minutes!
大喊大叫已经没意义了 There's no point shouting about it.
她离开了 She's gone.
有14年时间给你跟她慢慢谈 You've got 14 years to talk to her.
找出监狱的电话号码 我要打给他们 Get the number for the prison and I'll call them.
-招揽派对 -招揽? -Touting party. -Touting?
Billy邀请了很多法官和事务律师 Billy invites lots of judges and all the solicitors
他们都是拍马屁的对象 we're supposed to suck up to
我们拍马屁就是 and we do lots of sucking up.
-招揽派对还是戴高帽派对? -第一印象啊 Nick -Touting or tarting party? -First impressions Nick.
让他们喜欢你 Make them like you.
有法定探望的口头命令下来吗? Is there a VO for a legal visit?
Mercedes cordoba Mercedes Cordoba.
为什么没有? 你们应该已经接到一个申请的啊 Why not? You should have received a request for one.
她怀孕了 那么脆弱 She's pregnant she's vulnerableand
还要从今晚开始十四年的刑期 she's about to start a 14 year sentence tonight.
我得去看她 I need to see her.
喂? Hello?
借过 Excuse me.
Brian Frogett是Cant Frogett的高级合伙人 Ah Brian Frogett Senior Partner from Cant Frogett
他打电话来提醒我们 rang to remind us
他这样身份的人不会来这种聚会 he's too important to come to this kind of do
但是听说了你今天的表现后 but he says he's making an exception because he heard about
他就决定破例参与 过来了见见你 your performance today and he'd like to meet you.
那算哪门子的问题? What kind of question was that?
-什么? -什么? -Sorry? -Oh what?
你忘了? You've forgotten?
就是史上那个对证人席最烂的提问 About the worst question asked of anyone in the witness box ever?
我们来看一下那个贼有没有打哈欠? I know let's see if the burglar yawned shall we?
请问 他海扁你的时候 打哈欠了么? Tell me did he yawn at all after beating the crap out of you?
-你不懂的 -加重语气已经不够表达这些了吧? -You don't understand. -Aggravated doesn't cover it does it?
咱们得为这发明一个专有名词 We're going to have to invent a new term for this.
变态贼 怎么样? 贴切吗? How about psychopath burglary? Will that do it?
谁告诉你的?
又是一个烂问题 Another stupid question.
-Peter告诉我的 难道他说错了? -我都说了 -Peter told me. Or was he wrong? -I told you
你不懂的 you don't understand.
还有 谁是Peter? And I'm sorry who's Peter?
那个整天跟你待在一起的跑腿 The outdoor clerk who's been with you all day.
奇闻了 Hardly.
他大部分时间都在试镜 He spent most of his day at a casting
要么就给他的经纪人打电话 or on the phone to his agent.
没准你曾经有过一个懂得观审的跑腿 Maybe if you had an outdoor clerk who knew how to read a trial properly.
谁提这种找死的问题的? Was it him asking the suicidal questions
-还是那个戴假发的笨女人? -你最好离开 -or was that the brainless woman in the wig? -I think you'd better leave.
-你说什么? -没人这样跟她说话过 -What did you just say? -No-one ever talks to her like that.
麻烦了 Excuse me.
借过 Excuse me.
清理掉 赶紧清理掉 哥们 Clear this up clear this up. Get this cleared up boys.
这就叫无条件的爱 It's called unconditional love.
换作是你们 我也会这么做 I'd do the same for any one of you.
这爱没啥好处 It can be a liability love.
-什么意思? -Brian Frogettis是个超级事务律师 -What are you saying? -Brian Frogettis a big big solicitor.
他讨厌我们的话 我们就没活干没钱赚 He hates us we lose work we lose money.
-你还好吧 小姐? -嗯 -抱歉 -You all right Miss? -Yes. -Sorry about that.
谢谢 Thank you.
喂 妈 是我 Hello Mum. It's me.
你不在那 我就... You're not there so I...
你妈妈还好吗? How is she? Your Mum?
-你竟敢 -Martha -你这个伪君子 -How dare you? -Martha. -You hypocrite.
你应该替她去坐十四年的牢 It should be you that goes to prison for 14 years not her.
你为什么就不... Why don't you just get off your...
天呐 Martha Jesus Christ Martha.
就因为有你 在法庭熬过一天后 拿这玩意儿逍遥 That's why people like Mercedes get screwed by everybody so you can
-Mercedes这样的人才会被弄的这么惨 -有错判吗? -stick coke up your nose after a hard day in court. -Was it the wrong result?
你真恶心 You make me sick.
有错判吗? Was it the wrong result?
有时候你可能对案子太投入了 Martha Maybe you get in too close sometimes Martha.
你干嘛? 你到底在干嘛? What are you doing? What the hell are you doing?
-我在报警 -把电话给我 -I'm calling the police. -Give me the phone.
-把电话给我 给我 -怎么了？ -Just give me the phone.Give me the phone. -What's going on?
你是谁? 你是谁? Who are you? Who the hell are you?
把电话还给她 Give her the phone back.
Jake Jake 叫救护车 Jake Jake call an ambulance.
麻烦派救护车来 Ambulance please.
地址是中殿律师学院 Shoe Lane街 Shoe Lane公会 Address is Shoe Lane Chambers Shoe Lane Middle Temple.
你还好吧? You OK?
你真能控制自己的情绪 You do emotional detachment incredibly well.
-你多大了? -快23了 -How old are you? -Nearly 23.
-什么时候? -有几年了吧 -When? -In a couple of years time.
Clive他自己滑倒的 我们都看见的 He slipped Clive. We all saw it.
是啊 但是问题是 Yeah but the question is
还有谁想看见我跟他在同一个公会共事 how is anyone going to want me and him in Chambers together?
-我完了 是吧? -不 -I'm finished aren't I? -No.
我保证 不会的 I promise you you're not.
咱们继续努力 We'll work on it.
拿着 打的回家吧 Here. Take a cab home.
我去看一下那些还没用上的资料 I'm going to look at the unused.
嗯 这才像样 Now you're impressing me.
谢谢 Thank you.
-有事么? -我刚刚在工作 -What do you want? -I was just working.
现在 我要走了 And now I'm going.
我是Martha Costello的新学徒 I'm Martha Costello's new pupil.
据说你是她那位穿着闪亮盔甲的骑士 You're her knight in shining armour by all accounts.
她很厉害 是吧? She's great isn't she?
嗯 Yes.
-你还好吧? -我很好 -Are you all right? -I'm fine.
-我能问你个问题吗? -嗯哼 -Can I ask you a question? -Mmhmm.
你觉得她会穿上丝袍吗? Do you think she'll get Silk?
会的 Yes.
再见 See you.
1只短吻鳄 2只短吻鳄 3只短吻鳄 4 One alligator two alligator three alligator four.
1只短吻鳄 2只短吻鳄 One alligator two alligator
3只短吻鳄 4只短吻鳄 5只短吻鳄 three alligator four alligator five alligator.
-喂? -过来一下 -Hello? -Get over here.
不 这边没别人 No there is no-one else.
必须是你来 It must be you.
好吧 你这儿有什么新发现? Right what have you got for me?
-你没见过Gary Rush吧? -没有 -You've never met Gary Rush? -No.
看一下这个 Watch this.
-那我该怎么... -就看着 -Well how am I suppose... -Just watch it.
被告有可能在你看的DVD里面 也有可能不在 The defendant may or may not be present in the DVD you are watching.
哪个是他? Which one is he?
第四 第四个 Four. It's number four.
-为什么? -我不知道 -Why? -I don't know.
我每天过去三次 I come in three times a day.
早上帮Dodd先生穿衣服 I help Mr Dodd to get dressed in the morning
帮他准备午饭 晚上侍候他就寝 I give him his lunch and then I help him get to bed at night.
那晚他在床上之后 And when you left him that evening he was in bed
你离开的时候是不是一切如常? and everything was as it should be?
是的 Yes.
无需提问 No questions.
不不 对不起 就一个问题 Oh actually sorry just one sorry.
你离开的时候关门了吗? Did you close the door behind you?
嗯 肯定关了 Yes of course.
谢谢 Thank you.
被告住的地方离犯罪现场很近 The defendant lives a short distance away from the scene of the crime.
你逮捕他是不是因为 And you arrested him because
闭路电视录像出现一个骑着摩托车的男人 there is CCTV footage of a man on a Vespa
在抢劫案发生后 leaving from outside Mr Dodd's home address
从Dodd先生家离开 just after the burglary took place?
被告有一辆摩托车 The defendant owns a Vespa.
这个录像不能完全证明事实 但是... The footage isn't good enough for us to identify it 100% but...
是怀疑的理由 也是逮捕的根据? Grounds for suspicion. Grounds for arrest?
是的 Yes.
在被告公寓里有无发现任何被盗财物? Was any of the stolen property recovered from the defendant's flat?
-没有 -任何与盗窃案相关的东西呢? -No. -Any paraphernalia associated with burglary?
这些东西很容易处理掉 These things are easily disposed of.
请根据证据说话 警官 不要假设 Stick to the evidence officer not supposition.
这个假设是根据我25年的经验 It's supposition based on 25 years of experience.
接下来是疑犯的展示 关键一击 Then came the ID parade. Slam dunk.
在此之前你还都没出席过庭审 You haven't been in the court until now
所以你不会知道Dodd先生在证人席上说的 so you won't know what Mr Dodd said in the witness box
但是你可能听说过打哈欠这回事了 but you will have heard about the...yawn moment?
这...太恐怖了 It's...chilling.
殴打了老人之后再打哈欠 Torture an old man and then yawn.
他这是厌倦了? 累了? Was he bored? Tired?
你早已认为被告会有这种行为? And this is the kind of behaviour you'd expect from this defendant?
Costello女士 请搞清楚你在做什么 Do you have any idea what you're doing Miss Costello?
被告是否有前科? Is it right that this defendant has previous convictions?
其中包括三次盗窃行为? Including three previous convictions for burglary?
是的 Yes.
能说一下Rush先生在那些犯罪中获得的判刑吗? Can you tell us about the sentences Mr Rush received for those offences?
第一次缓刑 第二次社区服务80个小时 Probation the first time 80 hours community service the second time
第三次是六个月监禁 followed by six months in prison.
根据你25年的经验 In 25 years of experience
-你对那些判决有什么看法? -太短了 -how do you feel about those sentences? -Too short.
要是一个人打哈欠 并用戴着手套的手  if a man yawns and puts his gloved hand
捂住嘴 之后又用同一只手 up to his mouth and then with the same hand
通过门的把手开门 我们会在把手上发现什么呢 opens the door using the handle what will we find on the handle?
DNA 在哪? DNA. Where is it?
-谁是第一个到达犯罪现场的警官? -是我 -Who was the first officer to arrive on the scene of the crime? -I was.
那是在犯罪现场调查员和法医人员到达公寓前 This was before the SOCOs long before forensics had got to the flat.
检测门把手的时候 有没有发现指纹? When the door handle was tested were any fingerprints found?
-没有 -一个也没有? -No. -None?
一个门把手却没有任何指纹？ A door handle with nobody's prints on it?
没有Dodd先生的指纹? 没有社工一小时前留下的指纹? Not Mr Dodd's? Not the Social Worker from an hour before?
Dodd先生很明确地说 入侵者打哈欠了 Mr Dodd couldn't have been clearer. The intruder yawned.
他在打哈欠时抬起戴着手套的手捂住了嘴 He put his gloved hand up to his face to cover his yawn.
又用同一只手拧着门把开了门 He opened the door with the same hand using the handle.
凭借你多年来丰富的经验 警官 Gather up all your experience Officer
平息怒气冷静地推敲一下这个细节 bring it to the front of your mind and park it next to your anger
告诉陪审团这个门把 在检验前被清理过 and tell this jury that someone didn't wipe the handle clean before it was tested.
你诬陷被告 因为你对他本没有好感 You've fitted up this defendant because you don't like him.
他累积的犯罪记录 He's got form and
在你们警察的眼中便意味着 in your policeman's mind
他应该受到更严厉的惩罚 he hasn't been properly punished.
那Dodd先生为何指认他呢? 嗯? So how did Mr Dodd pick him out? Hey?
如果你说不是他? If it wasn't him?
1只短吻鳄 2只短吻鳄 3只短吻鳄 4只短吻鳄 One alligator two alligator three alligator four alligator.
1只短吻鳄 2只短吻鳄 3只短吻鳄 4只短吻鳄 One alligator two alligator three alligator four alligator
5只短吻鳄 6只... five alligator six...
非常精彩 That was something.
实在是精彩之极 That was really something.
你们已经看到了用于指认程序的DVD You've seen the DVD of the ID procedure.
你们也听到了受害人以他自己 You've heard the victim count in his very own
独特而精确的方式来计算 very particular very precise way
Gary Rush出现在屏幕上的时间比别人多出了两秒 the fact that Gary Rush is on that screen for two seconds
或者说多数了2只短吻鳄 比其他人的时间都长 or alligators longer than everyone else.
你们都看到屏幕上每一次只显示一张照片 You've seen the black screen either side of only one image on that video.
控方所依靠的唯一证据 The only evidence this prosecution relies on
是Dodd先生在嫌疑人照片中指认了被告 is Mr Dodd picking out the defendant on an ID parade.
不仅缺少法医证据 Not only is there no forensic evidence
而且原来提出的法医证据 已失去说服力 there is evidence of there being no forensic evidence
坦白说 这令人难以信服 which frankly is impossible.
如果Gary Rush当时的确在公寓里打了哈欠 If Gary Rush was in that flat and he yawned
他的DNA就会遗留在门把上 then his DNA would be on that door handle.
仅凭这点证据能够证明 Is it safe to convict this man
这个人有罪吗? on this evidence?
作为陪审团你们担负着神圣的使命 You as a jury have a sacred task.
你们的工作就是运用整个司法体系 It is your job to apply the one basic principle
赖以运作的一条基本原则 on which everything in our justice system turns.
控方必须拿出真凭实据 The prosecution have to prove
消除一切合理怀疑来证明被告有罪 beyond all reasonable doubt that a defendant is guilty.
回到你们的仲裁室 Go back to your jury room
将此原则应用于这些事实之中 and apply that principle to these facts
然后回来作出唯一公正的裁决 and come back with the only proper verdict.
Gary Rush无罪 Gary Rush is not guilty.
-三次因盗窃罪被判刑 -我们已经讨论过这个了 -Three convictions for burglary. -We've had this conversation.
显然 去年他另一桩盗窃案被判无罪 But obviously his acquittal last year for another burglary
不在犯罪前科的单子上 你没有提到这一点 isn't on the list of previous. But it is in the unused.
那是因为他被判无罪了 Nick That's because it's an acquittal Nick.
也或许是因为受害人的头部遭受了三次重击 Or because the victim was punched three times in the head
直至最后也没能作证 and bottled out of giving evidence at the last minute.
你怎么看待这个呢?  What does that tell you?
Scarrow警司有明显的动机要诬陷Gary Rush That D.S. Scarrow has a classic motive for fitting up Gary Rush.
他擅入犯罪现场 That he walked into this crime
还主观地排除了Rush或许不是真凶的可能性 and removed any possibility from his mind that Rush might not be the right man.
这事关司法公正 Nick It's about integrity of justice Nick.
为了人们得到公正的审判 就是这样 这非常重要 It's about people getting a fair trial and that's all there is and it matters so much.
-Costello小姐? -有裁决了? -Miss Costello? -Verdict?
被告人请起立 Will the defendant please stand.
陪审团团长请起立 Will the foreman please stand.
-你们作出一致的裁决了吗? -是的 -Have you reached a verdict upon which all of you are agreed? -Yes.
你们裁定被告人犯有恶性盗窃罪吗? Do you find the defendant guilty or not guilty of aggravated burglary?
-无罪 -太好了! -Not guilty. -Yes!
有两件事是真的 These two things are true.
Gary Rush令人生厌 而他免于处罚也是正确的 Gary Rush is a horrible man and it's right that he gets off.
两者之间并不矛盾 They are not mutually exclusive.
我们去看看Mercedes Cordoba Let's go and see Mercedes Cordoba.
出来 Come on.
他们轮奸我 They raped me.
每一次 Every time.
七个男人 Seven men.
他们总是一起来 当我怀孕以后 Always all of them so that when I was pregnant
他们都不知道谁是孩子的父亲 they wouldn't know who the father was.
等到我肚子越来越大 When my belly grew bigger
他们就让我吞下毒品 they made me swallow the drugs
然后飞去伦敦 and I flew to London.
你的孩子们现在在哪? Where are your children?
每次孩子出生后 Every time the baby was born
他们就把婴儿带走 they took the baby away.
三个男孩 Three boys.
两个女孩 Two girls.
然后他们再次开始轮奸我 And then they raped me again.
我不知道我的孩子们在哪 I don't know where my babies are.
你之前为什么不告诉我呢? Why didn't you tell me this?
我本可以用这点来帮你 I could have used it.
我想要一个长时间的判刑 I wanted a long sentence.
在这里我是安全的 Here I am safe.
我摆脱了他们 I am away from them.
我们有上诉的理由 There is a ground of appeal.
你怎么还不明白呢? Why can't you hear me?
我不想上诉 I do not want an appeal.
谢谢你 Thank you.
上诉的理由是什么? What was the ground of appeal?
我 我的不作为 Me. Me being hopeless.
Gary Rush可不认为你不作为 Gary Rush doesn't think you're hopeless.
-这是谁送来的? -一个骑自行车的 -Who delivered this? -Bike.
他有脱掉头盔吗? Did he take his helmet off?
没 怎么了? No. Why Miss?
我已经20年没亲自给人递过诉讼状了 20 years since I delivered a brief by hand.
明天在中央刑事法院审理的绑架案 Kidnapping at the Bailey tomorrow.
干得好 小姐 Here you go Miss.
Gary rush重获自由 你成功地阻止了一次误判 Gary rush is a free man you've prevented a miscarriage of justice
Cant Frogett欣赏你 Cant Frogett love you.
Martha Costello大放异彩 A day in the life of Martha Costello.
不要去想审判 证据法规 定罪率或别的什么 forget trials and rules of evidence and conviction rates and whatever.
重点是从来没有女人会捏造强奸案 Women do invent rapes that never happened.
在东南部的巡回法庭里当着最权威法官的面 Win a rape trial in front of the most influential judge in
打赢一场强奸案的官司 the South Eastern circuit
丝袍资格你就手到拿来 好好把握机会 and you go straight to Silk do not pass go.
你凭何以为可以打赢这场官司? What makes you think it's winnable?
-我有几成胜算? -五成 -What are my chances? -50-50.
如果要找人盘问你 我会选择Martha Costello If I chose anyone to cross examine you it would be Martha Costello.
她不会偏袒你 她没这个心思 She won't go for you. Her heart isn't in it.
替我向Martha Costello问声好 Say hello to Martha Costello.
就说她是最适合我的女人 Tell her she's the girl for me.
这枚勋章和Gary Rush一点关系也没有 你别胡思乱想了 There will be nothing on that medal to link Gary Rush to it so you do nothing.
喂? 'Hello?'
我们需要新人 但是Billy we need to modernize. But Billy
我们还不确定他能否胜任 we're not sure how he fits in.
别以为我不知道 John Never underestimate what I know John.
我是你的当事人 我需要你竭尽全力来帮助我 I'm your client I need more from you than you're giving.
我说的是事实 I'm telling the truth.
说谎的人是你 不是我 You're the liar here not me.