pervious on EIl stone
??
???
Wow
-??
-???
???
??
-???
-??
??
???
I WON'T HAVE ANYTHING LEFT
TO LIVE FOR ANYWAY.
THERE'S GOTTA BE
A LESS HUMILIATING OUTFIT--
SOMETHING THAT CLOSES
IN THE BACK, AT LEAST.
I OVERHEARD
ONE OF THE NURSES SAYING
SHE THOUGHT
YOUR BUTT WAS CUTE.
COME ON.
DON'T BE NERVOUS.
ALL WE'RE DOING IS TALKING
ABOUT SURGERY ON MY BRAIN.
WHAT'S THERE
TO BE NERVOUS ABOUT?
-BLINDNESS.
-COMA.
LONG-TERM MEMORY LOSS.
SURE, I CAN REMOVE IT.
IT'S NO BIGGIE.
YOU'VE FOUND YOUR MAN.
REALLY?
-THAT'S FANTASTIC
-TOLD YOU.
JUST OUT OF CUOSITY,
HOW ATTACHED ARE YOU
TO YOUR ABILITY TO SPEAK?
SO I'D BE A VEGETABLE.
I WOULDN'T USE
THE WORD "VEGETABLE."
WELL, I WAS COMBINING
BLINDNESS, PARALYSIS
AND PERMANENT BRAIN DAMAGE INTO
ONE EASY-TO-REMEMBER CATEGORY.
DIDN'T YOU MENTION SOME HOSPITAL
IN CHINA? TIN-TIN PUMA?
TIANTAN PUHUA.
AND THE NEWS WON'T SOUND
ANY BETTER IN MANDARIN.
LOOK, ELI,
ARE YOU SURE THIS
IS SOMETHING YOU REALLY WANT?
IF THE SOMETHING IS ENDING UP
A DROOLING IDIOT, THEN NO.
BUT IF IT MEANS GETTING
THE BRAIN DEFECT REMOVED FROM MY HEAD
THAT'S MAKING
MY LIFE A LIVING HELL, THEN YES.
WELL, THE GOOD NEWS IS YOU'RE ????
SO THE ONLY THING
LEFT TO DO
IS PICK A SURGEON
FOR THE OTHER THING.
OUT OF THOSE GUYS?
THEY DIDN'T SEEM LIKE THEY
COULD REMOVE A CAP FROM A PEN.
THEY'RE THE BEST NEUROSURGEONS ???
WELL, NOW LET'S TRY THE ONES
THAT YOU COULDN'T GET ME IN WITH.
ALL RIGHT, THERE'S ONE--
???
BUT HE DOESN'T TAKE WALK-INS.
HE ONLY HANDLES CASES ORIGINATING
FROM HIS OWN HOSPITAL.
OR HE DID,
UNTIL YOU APPLIED YOUR
COPIOUS POWERS OF PERSUASION.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
??
YOU'RE THE BEST.
THANK YOU.
MM, doN'T THANK ME.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO SPEND THE REST OF MY LIFE
WIPING DROOL OFF YOUR CHIN.
BETH?
ELI!
HI!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
AT THE HOSPITAL?
I, UM... I'M SORRY.
I JUST DIDN'T
EXPECT TO SEE YOU.
OH. BEN.
I'M BRINGING BEN
TO THE DOCTOR.
YOU KNOW
HE'S NOT WITH YOU, RIGHT?
YES, HE'S...
AT THE PSYCHOLOGIST.
THEY WORK ONE-ON-ONE FOR
AN HOUR, INDIVIDUAL COUNSELING.
SO HOW ARE YOU?
I SAW YOU ON THE NEWS.
I WAS GONNA CALL,
BUT I FIGURED, YOU KNOW,
YOU HAVE ENOUGH
ON YOUR PLATE.
YEAH, I'VE BEEN BETTER.
I, UH... I GOT DEMOTED.
I LOST MY OFFICE.
I HAD A FIGHT WITH MY
ACUPUNCTURIST/SPIRITUAL GUIDE.
I ALIENATED THE ONE PERSON
AT WORK WHO MISTAKENLY ADMIRED ME
AND MADE A SERIOUS ETHICAL BREACH
WHICH HELPED GET SEVERAL HUNDRED PEOPLE
KICKED OUT
OF THEIR HOMES...
AND I-I BROKE UP
WITH TAYLOR.
OH, WOW.
THAT'S...
OH, ELI.
IF YOU EVER NEED TO TALK,
YOU STILL HAVE MY NUMBER,
RIGHT?
YEAH.
I MIGHT JUST GIVE YOU
A CALL.
OKAY.
BYE.
www.1000fr.com present
Capture:FRM@优雅的冰
Sync:FRM@爱笑的眼睛 花~
YOU'LL NEVER GUESS
WHO I RAN INTO.
COME ON, PATTI,
GUESS.
YOU'RE NOT PATTI.
NO, UM, I'M BRADLEY KITSIS.
I'M YOUR TEMP.
WHERE'S PATTI?
SHE'S NOT HERE.
I NOTICED. I CAN SEE, BRADLEY,
AT LEAST FOR NOW.
OH, SHE LEFT ME THIS NOTE
TO READ TO YOU.
UH, "ELI, I'M TAKING
A PERSONAL WEEK..."
PERSONAL WEEK?
"TO LOOK AFTER MY FRIENDS
AND RELATIVES IN SILVER TERRACE
WHO THANKS TO YOU,
NOW HAVE NO HOMES."
"NO HOMES" IS IN CAPITAL
LETTERS, WHICH IS WHY I...
THANKS, BRAD.
I GOT IT.
OUR BILLABLES
ARE UP BY 10% THIS QUARTER--
AN INCREASE ALMOST ENTIRELY DUE TO
OUR SUCCESS IN THE SOLINSKY CASE.
I CAN'T HELP BUT SWELL
WITH FATHERLY PRIDE.
I HAD A LOT OF HELP.
PERHAPS YOU'D BE WILLING
TO APPLY YOUR DEFT TOUCH TO JUDGE DOYLE.
-THIS BEING DOYLE "THE IL."
-GOOD LUCK.
JUDGE DOYLE
HAS JUST RETAINED W.P.K.
IN CONNECTION
WITH A PERSONAL MEDICAL CRISIS.
IS HE FINALLY GETTING THE POLE
REMOVED FROM HIS RECTUM?
I HEAR THAT CAN BE
A PAINFUL PROCEDURE.
NOT NEARLY AS PAINFUL
AS LEUKEMIA, MR. DOWD.
JUDGE DOYLE NEEDS A BONE MARROW
TRANSPLANT TO TREAT HIS CANCER,
BUT HIS ONLY DONOR MATCH BACKED
OUT OF THE DONATION AGREEMENT YESTERDAY.
AND NOW THAT WE'VE ESTABLISHED
YOUR SENSITIVITY
TO THE JUDGE'S PLIGHT,
YOU CAN ASSIST TAYLOR.
SIR, DOYLE THE--
UH, JUDGE DOYLE HATES ME.
I'M SURE YOU'RE FAMILIAR WITH MY
"I COULD CARE LESS" FACE.
MOVING ON TO OTHER
OUTSTANDING BUSINESS...
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN--
MR. GEORGE MICHAEL!
OH, NO.
IT'S NOT.
OH, NO,
IT'S NOT WHAT?
ARE YOU ELI STONE?
I'M GEORGE MICHAEL.
WOULD--WOULD YOU MIND
NOT POKING ME, PLEASE?
WELL, I'M SORRY,
IT'S JUST, YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE VERY SOLID
FOR A VISION.
AND YOU'RE A VERY ODD MAN.
WELL, AT LEAST
I'M NOT A HALLUCINATION.
WELL, HE CAN SEE ME.
ADLEY, DO YOU SEE ME
TALKING TO ANYONE?
REAL LIFE?
ACTUAL PERSON?
OF COURSE I DO, SIR.
THAT'S BONO.
YEAH, IT HAPPENS
ALL THE TIME.
I HAD THE GLASSES FIRST,
BY THE WAY.
MIND YOU, BONO AND I DO
HAVE SOMETHING IN COMMON
IN THAT WE ARE BOTH
PERFECTLY VISIBLE.
I'M SORRY. I THINK I'VE BEEN
WASTING YOUR TIME, MR. STONE.
NO, NO, NO. PLEASE, PLEASE,
PLEASE, UH, STAY.
I... I'M SORRY.
I JUST DON'T--
I DON'T TYPICALLY
GET VISITS LIKE THIS ONE.
UM...
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU,
MR. MICHAEL?
CALL ME GEORGE. UM, WELL, I WANT
YOU TO TAKE A CASE FOR ME.
??
IT'S ABOUT A YOUNG GIRL WHO WAS
THROWN OUT OF HER HIGH SCHOOL
FOR PLAYING ONE OF MY SONGS AT
A SCHOOL "ABSTINENCE" ASSEMBLY.
OF COURSE.
THIS WAS ALL OVER THE NEWS.
WHAT WAS THE SONG AGAIN?
UH, "I WANT YOUR SEX."
SORRY, YOU'RE NOT MY TYPE.
IT WAS A JOKE.
ANYWAY, UH, I WANT TO HIRE YOU
TO HELP HER GET BACK IN.
NOW OBVIOUSLY I'LL COVER
ALL THE LEGAL FEES, MR. STONE.
CALL ME ELI,
AND THIS IS ???
OBVIOUSLY, I WOULDN'T, UH...
I COULDN'T SAY NO TO YOU.
SO...
IF YOU DON'T MIND ME ASKING...
MM-HMM?
WHY ME?
WHY DID YOU COME TO ME?
WELL, YOU MIGHT THINK
I'M THE ODD ONE NOW.
BUT THE OTHER NIGHT
I HAD A DREAM,
AND, UM, IN THE DREAM,
I WAS COMPLETELY LOST,
UH, WHEN SOMEONE TOLD ME
I NEEDED TO FIND A LAWYER
NAMED ELI STONE.
Eli Stone
S01 Ep09
MR. WETHERSBY?
YOU WERE LOOKING FOR ME,
SIR?
THAT WOULD BE INCONSISTENT
WITH THE TERMINATION
OF OUR RELATIONSHIP,
NOW WOULDN'T IT?
I JU HEARD THAT YOU WANTED
TO SEE ME, SIR.
MAYBE BRADLEY
MEANT MR. POSNER.
NO, HE MEANT ME.
I JUST
DIDN'T WANT YOU INFERRING
THAT I ACTUALLY CRAVED
THIS CONVERSATION.
NEVERTHELESS, I UNDERSTAND
THAT YOU'VE BEEN RETAINED
BY--WHO WAS IT AGAIN?
GEORGE MICHAEL,
THE POP SUPERSTAR?
YES, SIR, UNLESS THERE'S
A PROBLEM WITH THAT.
THERE IS, ACTUALLY--
TWO PROBLEMS, IN FACT.
FOR ONE THING,
YOU'RE STILL ON PROBATION.
SECONDLY, SECTION 6.3 PARAGRAPH
"J" OF THE PARTNERSHIP AGREEMENT
OBLIGATES A PARTNER
TO OVERSEE ANY CASE
WHERE THE CLIENT HAS
A HIGH PUBLIC PROFILE.
WELL, I GUESS IT'S GOOD THEN
THAT GEORGE
ISN'T TECHNICALLY THE CLIENT.
HER NAME IS MOLLY FOSTER.
SHS 17
AND MUCH LESS FAMOUS, SIR.
I DON'T HAVE ALL DAY
TO WASTE ON SEMANTICS.
IF SOMEONE OF MR. MICHAEL'S
ESTEEM IS INVOLVED IN THIS CASE,
THEN OBVIOUSLY THE REQUIREMENT
TO OVERSEE APPLIES.
INCLUDING APPEARING IN COURT?
AND MANAGING
CLIENT RELATIONS, YES.
OKAY, THEN.
WELCOME TO THE CASE.
I'M SURE MR. MICHAEL WILL APPRECIATE
HAVING A SENIOR PARTNER ON HIS TEAM.
AS WILL MOLLY, SIR.
WHO?
OUR CLIENT,
MOLLY FOSTER.
RIGHT. MM.
RIGHT.
I DIDN'T EXPECT THIS
FROM JORDAN WETHERSBY.
I ASK HIM TO SEND ME
HIS BEST LAWYERS.
HE SENDS ME A GIRL.
WELL, LET ME INTRODUCE YOU TO
MR. WETHERSBY'S DAUGHTER, SIR.
I WASN'T TALKING ABOUT HER,
DOWD.
GOOD TO SEE YOU, TAYLOR.
SO LET'S GET TO IT.
SO YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT THE, UH,
LACK OF LEGAL PRECEDENT?
NO, I'M WORRIED ABOUT THE LACK
OF PRECEDENT IN OUR FAVOR.
WELL, THAT'S WHY I PAY
THE 2 OF YOU $550 AN HOUR.
I KNOW THIS IS A LONG SHOT,
BUT I HAVE NO CHOICE. I'M DYING.
LEUKEMIA PROESSED
TO STAGE FOUR.
NOWHERE TO GO BUT DOWN.
DID YOU TELL
THE WOULD-BE DONOR?
NO, MR. DOWD.
I WANT HIM TO THINK I NEED
THE PAINFUL EXTRACTIONS
OF HIS BONE MARROW
FOR MY PERSONAL COLLECTION.
USUALLY ONLY FAMILY MEMBERS
ARE AN EXACT MATCH.
THE WOULD-BE DONOR
IS A RELATIVE, ISN'T HE?
MY SON.
AND HE KNOWS YOU'RE DYING,
AND HE STILL WON'T HELP YOU?
WE AREN'T EXACTLY CLOSE.
HE WAS 2 WHEN
HIS MOTHER AND I DIVORCED,
AND I HAVEN'T SEEN SCOTT
SINCE THEN.
SO THE SETTLEMENT CONFERENCE
WE'RE SCHEDULED TO HAVE IN AN HOUR
IS THE FIRST TIMEYOU'RE SEEG
YOUR SON IN 19 YEARS?
MM.
OKAY!
I'LL HAVE ALL THE SHARP OBJECTS
REMOVED FROM THE CONFERENCE ROOM.
THIS IS
A CRITICAL MEETING, OBVIOUSLY.
IT'S IMPORTANT THAT YOU
LET ME DO THE TALKING,
GET US OFF
ON THE RIGHT FOOT WITH MARY.
-MOLLY, SIR.
-UNDERSTANDABLY, SHE'LL BE
RELUCTANT TO DIVE...
-INTO THE LEGAL WATERS, BUT--
-ELI!
GEORGE, HELLO AGAIN.
I'M SORRY.
I'M NOT TOO LATE, AM I?
YOU'RE JUST OFF TO SEE MOLLY?
EXACTLY.
NO, YOU'RE JUST IN TIME.
COOL.
THIS IS THE FIRM'S SENIOR
PARTNER, JORDAN WETHERSBY.
HE'S GONNA BE TTING US OFF
ON THE RIGHT FOO
GOOD TO MEET YOU,???
YES, IT'S, UM...
AN HONOR,
MR. MICHAEL.
YEAH.
CALL ME GEORGE.
GEORGE.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
YOU MAKE IT SOUND LIKE WE JUST
SAW EACH OTHER LAST WEEK.
WHY DON'T WE
ALL SIT DOWN?
HAVE YOU HAD A CHANCE
TO REVIEW OUR PROPOSAL?
YES.
SCOTT?
THIS ISN'T...
I DON'T CARE
ABOUT THE MONEY.
WELL, UNLESS I'M MISTAKEN,
JUDGE DOYLE ALREADY PREVAILED
UPON YOUR MORE
NOBLE INSTINCTS.
I TOOK THE TEST.
DOCTORS STARTED TO DESCRIBE
THE PROCEDURE TO ME,
AND I GUESS
I HAD SECOND THOUGHTS, OKAY?
I'M SORRY.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE
I EVEN KNOW YOU OR ANYTHING.
I KNOW. I KNOW,
AND I'M SORRY. I TRULY AM.
BUT I'M ASKING
FOR YOUR HELP HERE.
AND BELIEVE ME
WHEN I TELL YA,
THAT'S NOT SOMETHING
THAT COMES EASY FOR ME.
I WENT THROUGH THIS PHASE
WHERE I'D SEND YOU THINGS LETTERS,REPORT CARDS.
WHAT DID YOU EVER DO
WITH THOSE THINGS ANYWAY?
I THOUGHT...
I THOUGHT I SHOULDN'T PROMISE
A RELATIONSHIP I COULDN'T DELIVER ON.
YEAH.
YEAH, WELL, I GUESS
I CAN'T DELIVER NOW.
SORRY.
I DON'T THINK
WE'LL BE SETTLING.
YOU ARE A DEAD RINGER.
IT'S AMAZING.
MOM, YOU HAVE TO SEE THIS
GEORGE MICHAEL IMPERSONATOR CHLOE HIRED!
IT'S HILARIOUS.
HI, MOLLY.
IT'S GREAT TO MEET YOU.
I'VE READ ABOUT YOUR EXPULSION
FROM SCHOOL,
AND I'VE HIRED THESE ATTORNEYS
TO HELP YOU GET BACK IN.
SHUT UP.
NO WAY.
PLEASE COME IN.
OH, CAN I GET YOU GENTLEMEN
ANYTHING? COFFEE?
MAYBE SOMETHING BRITISH SOME CRUMPETS
OR A PINT OF BITTERS?
NO, THANK YOU.
SIR, YOU'RE UNUSUALLY QUIET.
ARE YOU FEELING OKAY?
I FEEL FINE.
DON'T EVER TOUCH ME AGAIN.
SO YOU TOTALLY READ
ABOUT ME?
YEP.
THAT IS SO COOL.
WHY DON'T YOU TELL US EXACTLY
WHAT HAPPENED AT SCHOOL?
THERE WAS THIS, UM,
LAME-ASS ASSEMBLY--
THE "ABSTINENCE ONLY"???
TWICE A SEMESTER, SOME EXPERT
IN NEVER, EVER HAVING SEX
TELLS US ALL ABOUT IT.
AFTER TWO YEARS
OF THIS, UM, BULL,
I DECIDED TO TAKE A STAND.
I SNUCK
INTO THE PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE
AND PLAYED "I WANT YOUR SEX"
ER THE P.A.
THE CHALLENGE HERE
WILL BE CIRCUMVENTING
THE SUPREME COURT'S DECISION
IN MORSE vs. FREDERICK,
WHICH LIMITS THE RIGHT TO
FREE SPEECH ON SCHOOL GROUNDS.
SO YOU'RE SAYING
I COULD LOSE?
ALWAYS A POSSIBILITY
IN LITIGATION, MS. FOSTER,
BUT...
YOU GOTTA HAVE "FAITH."
ANOTHER ONE
OF YOUR SONGS, I THINK.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT,
YEAH.
EXCUSE ME.
Hey, it's me.
I just got off the phone
with Rajapaksa.
YOU REMEMBER?
SUPER NEUROSURGEON?
Well, uh,
it took a lot of begging
and a new set of
golf clubs,
BUT...
HE'S AGREED TO SEE YOU.
OBVIOUSLY, IT'S A RISK
EITHER WAY YOU SLICE IT.
ACTUALLY, THERE WON'T BE
ANY SLICING INVOLVED.
WE BURN IT OUT OF YOU.
THAT'S JUST
WHAT I ALWAYS WANTED.
SO YOU GUYS WILL TALK
AND LET ME KNOW?
YEAH, WE'LL CALL YOU LATER.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, DR. RAJAPAKSA.
ANYTIME.
AWESOME.
OKAY, THERE IS AN O.R. FREE WEEK
AFTER NEXT WITH YOUR NAME ON IT.
YOU SURE THAT'S THE GUY?
WELL, HE'S COMPETENT, CONFIDENT,
EXPERT IN THE LATEST TECHNIQUES.
ELI, IF HE WERE ANY MORE QUALIFIED,
HE'D BE A FICTIONAL TV CHARACTER.
I'M NOT ASKING ???
I'M ASKING IF YOU THINK
THAT'S THE GUY.
I CAN'T MAKE
THAT CHOICE FOR YOU, ELI.
I...
IT'S TOO BIG. I...
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN DO THAT.
YOU WANT THIS THING OUT
OR NOT
I WANT IT OUT.
I JUST--I'M NOT SURE THAT
THIS IS THE RIGHT TIME.
I'M HAVING A STRANGE WEEK.
WELL, COMING FROM YOU,
THAT'S SAYING SOMETHING
GEORGE MICHAEL SHOWED UP
AT MY OFFICE--
FOR REAL THIS TIME--
DON'T JOKE--THE SAME DAY
I HAPPENED TO BUMP INTO BETH,
AND SHE HAS KIND OF
A CONNECTION WITH HIM.
BETH? BETH... KELLER?
YEAH. HER SON SEES
A DOCTOR AT THIS HOSPITAL.
I WAS THINKING
OF GIVING HER A CALL.
A-A CALL LIKE--
-LIKE A DATE, YES.
-YEAH.
WHY NOT? I'M NEWLY SINGLE,
ABOUT TO BE ANEURYSM-FREE.
WELL, YEAH, BUT...
BUT WHAT?
NOTHING.
I JUST, YOU KNOW,
BE CAREFUL, ALL RIGHT?
I KNOW I'M NOT THE REASON
MY PARENTS SPLIT UP AND MY FATHER LEFT,
BUT WHEN YOU'RE A KID,
THAT'S HOW IT FEELS,
YOU KNOW,
LIKE IT'S YOUR FAULT.
BUT NOW YOU HAVE A CHANCE AT--
AT RECONCILING WITH YOUR FATHER.
IF I GIVE HIM
MY BONE MARROW.
WHAT KIND OF RELATIONSHIP
DO WE STAND TO HAVE
WITH THOSE KINDS
OF STRINGS ATTACHED?
I'M CURIOUS.
HOW DO YOU EVEN KNOW WHETHER
YOU'RE A COMPATIBLE DONOR?
I GOT TESTED.
THREE MONTHS AGO,
HE CALLED ME UP.
NO "HOW ARE YOU?"
NO "SORRY I WROTE YOU OFF."
JUST, "I'VE GOT CANC. WOULD
YOU GET YOUR BLOOD TESTED?"
I TAKE IT
THE TEST DETERMINED
THAT YOU ARE INDEED
A COMPATIBLE DONOR?
YES, I'M A MATCH.
HOPING THE FAMILY SIMILARITIES
END THERE.
WHY GO THROUGH THE STEPS
OF HAVING YOURSELF TESTED
IF YOU'RE NOT PREPARED TO GO
THROUGH WITH THE DONATION?
IS IT BECAUSE MAYBE YOU HAVE
AN OBLIGATION TO YOUR FATHER,
HOWEVER ESTRANGED
HE MAY BE?
I GOT TESTED BECAUSE...
I WANTED TO SEE
IF I WAS A MATCH.
IF I COULD SAVE YOUR LIFE...
SO I COULD TELL YOU
TO GO CHOKE ON IT.
MY REASONS WERE JUST.
I KNEW I'D GET IN TROUBLE.
I JUST DIDN'T THINK
I'D BE EXPELLED.
DID YOU NOT KNOW THAT SCHOOL
POLICY GIVES THE PRINCIPAL
DISCRETION TO EXPEL ANYONE
WHOSE--WHOSE BEHAVIOR
"MATERIALLY INTERFERES WITH
THE LEARNING OF OTHER STUDENTS
OR DISRUPTS
THE OVERALL EDUCATION PROCESS"?
YES, BUT THAT ASSUMES
WHAT WAS HAPPENING
AT THE ASSEMBLY WAS LEARNING.
THE ABSTINENCE-ONLY LADY
TELLS US CONDOMS DON'T WORK,
THAT GIRLS WHO HAVE ABORTIONS
ARE MORE PRONE TO SUICIDE.
AND BECAUSE OF ALL
OF THOSE MISCONCEPTIONS,
STUDENTS IN
ABSTINENCE-ONLY PROGRAMS
ARE LESS LIKELY
TO USE CONTRACEPTION.
OBJECTION.
ARE WE TO ACCEPT MISS FOSTER
AS AN EXPERT WITNESS?
THE PLAINTIFF'S KNOWLEDGE--
OR, I SUBMIT, LACK THEREOF--
GOES TO THE MERITS--
OR LACK THEREOF
OF THE VERY PEDAGOGY MISS FOSTER'S
PROTEST WAS TAKING ISSUE WITH.
MISS FOSTER,
PLEASE LIMIT YOUR ANSWERS
TO YOUR DIRECT EXPERIENCES.
MOLLY, HOW HAS THE SCHOOL'S
POLICY AFFECTED YOU?
FIRST, MY LAB PARTNER
GOT PREGNANT.
THEN, UM, A FRIEND--I DON'T
WANT TO TELL HER NAME,
'CAUSE HER MOM
WOULD TOTALLY KILL HER--
SHE GOT GONORRHEA...
IN HER THROAT.
I DECIDED
I HAD TO DO SOMETHING.
THANK YOU, MOLLY.
VERY DESCRIPTIVE.
AND THE "SOMETHING"
YOU DECIDED TO DO
WAS TO PLAY THE SONG
"I WANT YOUR SEX"
AT A SCHOOL ASSEMBLY?
THAT'S A VERY MATURE FORM
OF POLITICAL PROTEST.
THE EXECUTION OF MS. FOSTER'S
PROTEST ISN'T AT ISSUE HERE,
ONLY WHETHER IT'S PROTECTED UNDER
OUR COUNTRY'S MOST CHERISHED CONSTITUTIONAL PRINCIPLES.
-IS THAT AN OBJECTION?
-A STRENUOUS ONE, YOUR HONOR.
SUSTAINED.
THERE WAS
NO OTHER COURSE OF ACTION?
YOU COULDN'T HAVE
ORGANIZED A PETITION?
I WANTED TO EXPOSE
THE HYPOCRISY.
AND WHEN YOU DID, DO YOU THINK
YOU WERE BEING DISRUPTIVE?
I HOPE SO.
THK YOU.
NO FURTHER QUESTIONS.
THAT WAS INVIGORATING.
IT REMINDED ME
OF MY SALAD DAYS STANDING UP,
MAKING A COMPELLING OBJECTION...
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
OF MY DIRECT EXAMINATION.
ON AN ISSUE
OF REAL SIGNIFICANCE--
NOT JUST FREEDOM OF SPEECH,
BUT THE APPLICATION OF THAT RIGHT
TO OUR NATION'S YOUNGEST,
ONES WHO ARE TRULY DISENFRANCHISED--
NOT HAVING THE RIGHT
TO VOTE OR...
SOMETHING ON YOUR MIND,
MR. STONE?
I WAS JUST WONDERING
IF IT WAS POSSIBLE
THAT YOU WERE A... FANBOY
OF A CERTAIN
CELEBRITY CLIENT.
MR. STONE, DID YOU
JUST CHARACTERIZE ME,
JORDAN WETHERSBY II,
SENIOR PARTNER
OF ONE OF THIS COUNTRY'S
MOST PRESTIGIOUS FIRMS,
A "FANBOY"?
OF COURSE NOT, SIR, BUT--
I DIDN'T THINK SO.
AND FOR THE RECORD,
MY MUSICAL TASTES
ARE NONE OF YOUR CONCERN.
IN THE NAME OF ALL
THAT'S GOOD AND HOLY, WHAT NOW?
-"I GOT YOU, BABE"?
-YEAH.
I HATE THAT SONG. I WOULD NEVER
SING IT UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES,
EVEN HALLUCINATORY ONES.
JUST LIKE YOU WOULD NEVER GO OUT
WITH ONE OF OUR CO-WORKERS.
ELI, IS THERE SOMETHING
YOU WANT TO ASK ME?
NO, 'CAUSE I DON'T LISTEN
TO MY VISIONS ANYMORE, SO...
WELL, CONSIDERING LAST WEEK,
A.K.A. BRIBING A JUDGE,
IT'S PROBABLY FOR THE BEST.
WELL, WITHOUT ADMITTING
OR DENYING ANYTHING,
THERE WON'T BE ANY MORE
OF THAT STUFF,
CAUSE I'M--
I'M HAVING IT TAKEN OUT...
THE ANEURYSM.
I THOUGHT
IT WAS TOO DANGEROUS.
NAH. THE ABILITY
TO SWALLOW'S OVERRATED.
JUST TELL ME. IS THERE SOMETHING
GOING ON WITH YOU AND MATT?
NO. YOU KNOW, IF YOU HADN'T
DUMPED ME REPEATEDLY, I MIGHT ADD--
I WOULD SAY YOU WERE JEALOUS.
I'M NOT JEALOUS. I'M NOT.
IT'S JUST BEEN
A ROUGH WEEK, OKAY?
YOU WOULDN'T HAPPEN TO HAVE
ANY TIME LATER, WOULD YOU?
I'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT IT.
LOOK, I GET THE FEELING
YOU'RE ALONE RIGHT NOW.
SO AM I.
BUT I'M TRYING TO MOVE ON.
SO I CAN'T BE THAT SHOULDER
FOR YOU TO CRY ON.
I'M SORRY.
I JUST--I CAN'T.
THAT'S OKAY.
HEY, BETH?
IT'S ELI.
YEAH, WELL, I WAS THINKING ABOUT
WHAT YOU SAID THE OTHER DAY ABOUT,
UH, NEEDING
TO TALK TO SOMEONE,
AND, UH, I KINDA DO.
L ACKERMAN,
YOU SAID THAT MOLLY WAS
EXPELLED BECAUSE HER ACTIONS
WERE A VIOLATION
OF SCHOOL POLICY, CORRECT?
STUDENTS HAVE TO LEARN
ABOUT CONSEQUENCES.
THAT'S WHY THE SCHOOL HAS
A STRICT ZERO TOLERANCE POLICY
IN THOSE CIRCUMSTANCES.
ZERO TOLERANCE? SO YOU EXPEL
EVERY KID WHO PULLS A PRANK?
WH THOSE PRANKS
ARE DISRUPTIVE.
SO LAST FALL,
WHEN THE FOOTBALL TEAM
KIDNAPPED THE MASCOT
FROM A RIVAL HIGH SCHOOL,
DID YOU EXPEL THE WHOLE TEAM?
I DIDN'T DEEMTHAT PRANK DISRUPTIVE
TO THE OTHER STUDENTS' EDUCATIONS.
WHAT ABOUT WHEN MEMBERS
OF THE SENIOR CLASS
SUPERGLUED
THE TEACHER'S LOUNGE DOOR SHUT?
THOSE STUDENTS WERE SUSPENDED.
BUT NOT EXPELLED?
IT SOUNDS LIKE YOUR ZERO TOLERANCE
POLICY IS MORE LIKE A...
SIX TOLERANCE POLICY.
OBJECTION.
PASS THE WITNESS.
PRINCIPAL ACKERMAN,
WHY DOES YOUR SCHOOL HAVE
AN ABSTINENCE-ONLY PROGRAM?
BECAUSE IT'S
THE ONLY SEX EDUCATION
THAT THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT
WILL GIVE US MONEY FOR.
AND IF WORD GOT OUT
THAT A STUDENT PLAYED
A SEXUALLY EXPLICIT SONG
DURING ONE
OF YOUR ASSEMBLIES--
I'D LOSE THE FUNDING,
AND THE SCHOOL WOULD HAVE
NO SEX ED PROGRAM.
IS THAT RIGHT?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT I DO KNOW IS THAT A GIRL
PLAYING A SONG
THAT PROMOTES PROMISCUOUS SEX
DURING A LECTURE ON ABSTINENCE
RISKS THE PROGRAM FOR EVERYONE.
YOUR HONOR, THE PLAINTIFF
WOULD LIKE TO CALL A REBUTTAL WITNESS--
GEORGIOS KYRIACOS PANAYIOTOU.
IT'S THE LEGAL NAME
OF THE ARTIST
WHO WROTE THE OFFENDING SONG,
YOUR HONOR.
MR. GEORGE MICHAEL.
FINE. COURT WILL RECESS
UNTIL TOMORROW.
YOU'RE A JUDGE.
THE CASE COMES BEFORE YOU.
DO YOU ORDER ONE HUMAN BEING
TO UNDERGO
A PAINFUL MEDICAL PROCEDURE
TO BENEFIT ANOTHER?
BOTTOM LINE--
IF I WERE A JURIST ON THIS,
I COULD FIND PRECEDENT
TO SUPPORT SAVING MY LIFE.
MY SON CAN BE AS ANGRY
AS HE WANTS AT ME,
BUT THE LAST TIME I CHECKED,
BEING A LOUSY DAD
DIDN'T CARRY
THE DEATH PENALTY.
YOU KNOW, I HAD A DAD.
HE LEFT MY MOTHER
WHEN I WAS... 6...
FOR HER BEST FRIEND.
I SAW HIM SUMMERS
AND EVERY OTHER CHRISTMAS.
I'M SORRY. AT WHAT POINT
DID MR. DOWD BECOME A WITNESS?
AT THE POINT
WHEN YOU LET ME FINISH.
MY DAD DIED THREE YEARS AGO.
AND IF I HAD A CHANCE
TO SAVE HIS LIFE,
I THINK THE FIRST THING I'D WANT
TO KNOW IS WHY I SHOULD.
BECAUSE REGRET'S A LOUSY THING
TO LIVE WITH.
WELL, THAT'S SWEET.
THEY SHOULD
PUT THAT IN A POEM OR SOMETHING.
WE'RE ALL HERE WONDERI WHY
SCOTT SHOULD FEEL
ANY REGRET AT ALL.
YOU ARE AS MUCH A STRANGER
TO HIM AS MY FATHER WAS TO ME.
MORE SO.
WE'RE FAMILY,
HOWEVER ESTRANGED WE MAY BE.
NOTHING CHANGES THAT.
NO, YOU CHANGED IT.
YOU WALKED OUT THAT DOOR
TWO DECADES AGO,
AND YOU NEVER LOOK BACK.
AND SO I SHOULD DIE
FOR THAT?
SCOTT DIDN'T
GIVE YOU CANCER, JUDGE.
YOU WANT HIM TO SAVE YOU?
YES.
TELL US.
TELL US WHY HE SHOULD.
BECAUSE HE'S MY SON.
HE HAS AN OBLIGATION--
NO, HE DOESN'T.
YOU PISSED AWAY
ANY OBLIGATION HE HAD TO YOU.
NOW TELL US WHY
HE SHOULD HELP YOU NOW.
BECAUSE I WANT TO LIVE!
I WANT TO LIVE.
THE ONLY CHANCE I HAVE
OF THAT IS HIM.
BETH? TAYLOR.
-WE MET AT--
-OH, YOUR ENGAGEMENT PARTY,
OF COURSE.
IT'S SO NICE TO SEE YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE? IS--
IS EVERYTHING OKAY? YOUR SON?
OH, HE'S GREAT, THANKS.
NO, I'M, UM,
I'M NOT HERE ON BUSINESS.
I'M HAVING DINNER.
- WITH ELI?
- YEAH.
THAT'S GREAT.
OLD FRIENDS CATCHING UP.
- HAVE FUN.
- THANKS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
'CAUSE I DESPERATELY,
DESPERATELY NEED A MARGARITA.
AND YOU WANT ME
TO COME WITH YOU?
RIGHT! GREAT.
WELL, LET ME JUST...
OR NOT.
-NO, SHE DIDN'T.
-YES. YES, SHE DID.
MELANIE BOSE TOTALLY
HAD THE HOTS FOR YOU.
SO THAT'S WHY YOU WERE
TALKING TO ME AT THAT PARTY?
YOU WERE PLAYING WINGWOMAN
FOR THE GIRL WITH THE HEADGEAR?
WHEN SHE FOUND OUT
THAT WE SLEPT TOGEER,
SHE NEVER TALKED TO ME
AGAIN.
THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU WERE A COLLEGE WHORE.
I KNOW.
-WOW.
-WHAT?
I JUST THINK--AND THIS IS
A GOOD WEEK, YOU KNOW?
GEORGE MICHAEL'S HERE,
MY CASE IS INTERESTING,
AND... AND I HAVEN'T LAUGHED
LIKE THIS IN A LONG TIME.
THANKS FOR GOING OUT
WITH ME TONIGHT.
IT'S MY PLEASURE. YOU KNOW,
ALL THAT'S GOING ON WITH YOU,
I'M REALLY GLAD
THAT I CAN BE HERE.
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW NICE IT IS
TO HEAR THAT.
LATELY I'VE BEEN LESS POPULAR
THAN... MELANIE BOSE.
WELL, YOU'RE JUST GOING
THROUGH A ROUGH TIME.
BUT THINK OF ALL THE PEOPLE
THAT YOU'VE HELPED--
OKAY, ME AND BEN FOR TWO.
WINNING THAT BEUTEL TRIAL
TOTALLY CHANGED OUR LIVES.
I MEAN, YOU HAVE TO KNOW THAT.
I DO KNOW THAT.
I JUST--IT JUST DOESN'T
CHANGE THE FACT THAT...
THAT I'M ALONE.
I'M SO SORRY, ELI.
GOD.
I JUST BROKE
THE RULE NUMBER ONE, YOU KNOW?
YOU DON'T TELL A GIRL YOU'RE ON A
DATE WITH THAT YOU'RE LONELY.
OH, GOD.
WHAT? ARE YOU OKAY?
UH, YEAH. NO.
NATE TOLD ME, UM,
HE SAID THAT HE WAS
GONNA TELL YOU TODAY.
TELL ME WHAT?
-ABOUT YOU GUYS DATING?
-YEAH.
OH, NO. OF COURSE
HE TOLD ME THAT.
OH! THANK GOD!
OH, MY GOD. FOR A SECOND THERE
I THOUGHT MAYBE YOU DIDN'T KNOW.
OH, NO. WELL, THAT WOULD
BE AWKWARD.
TO LOSERS.
NATIONAL ORDER OF TOTAL LOSERS,
SAN FRANCISCO CHAPTER,
IN SESSION.
WHAT--DON'T LOOK
AT ME LIKE THAT.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE ANY PLANS
TONIGHT EITHER,LOSER.
BELIEVE ME,
I COULD HAVE HAD PLANS--
PLENTY OF PLANS
WITH PLENTY OF LADIES.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
I'M THE ONLY LOSER, THEN.
TO ME.
NO, YOU'RE NOT A LOSER,
TAYLOR.
YOU'RE SMART. YOU'RE HOT.
YOU'RE FUNNY...
YOU'RE HOT...
AND AN EXCELLENT DRINKER.
HE'S GETTING IT OUT.
WHO'S GETTING WHAT OUT?
- ELI.
- ANEURYSM.
OUT. BYE-BYE, ANEURYSM.
TURNS OUT THAT'S NOT
WHY HE DUMPED ME ANYWAY.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKIN' ABOUT?
I THOUGHT HE WANTED
TO PROTECT ME.
I THOUGHT HE DIDN'T WANT ME
TO SEE HIM SUFFER.
TURNS OUT THE ANEURYSM
WAS JUST AN EXCUSE.
ELI DUMPED ME BECAUSE
HE JUST DIDN'T LOVE ME ENOUGH.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT ANEURYSMS,
BUT SOMETHING'S GOTTA BE WRONG
IF HEDUMPED YOU.
THAT'S SWEET.
WHAT YOU SAID IN COURT TODAY
ABOUT UR DAD--
NOW I KNOW WHY YOU HAVE TO BE
SO DAMN COCKY ALL THE TIME,
WHY YOU ONLY DATE
THESE VAPID BIMBOS.
YOU'RE SCARED THAT
YOU'RE GONNA BE ABANDONED
BY SOMEONE
YOU ACTUALLY CARE ABOUT.
SOMETIMES
IT'S JUST SO HARD...
TO BE THE REAL ME.
LOVE IS ALL THE THINGS
YOU DIDN'T SAY
SHE TOLD YOU.
HAVE YOU ANY IDEA HOW
HUMILIATING THAT WAS FOR ME?
-THIS ISN'T HOW I WANTED
YOU TO FIND OUT.
-THAT FINALLY
AFTER MONTHS OF--
OF MISERY AND LONELINESS
AND--AND VISIONS,
I FINALLY ASK SOMEONE OUT,
AND I THINK
WE'RE MAKING A CONNECTION,
ONLY TO FIND OUT SHE'S
ALREADY DATING MY BROTHER.
I-I WAS GONNA TELL YOU YESTERDAY.
YEAH, I COULD TELL
FROM THE WAY YOU DIDN'T.
WE HAD JUST COME FROM THE DOCTOR.
YOU HAVE ALL OF THESE HUGE,
LIFE-ALTERING DECISIONS
ON YOUR PLATE.
I DIDN'T WANT
TO MAKE THINGS WORSE.
BY TELLING ME YOU WERE HAPPY?
I WAS TRYING TO PROTECT YOU.
WELL, I'M A BIG BOY, NATE.
YOU DATING BETH WOULDN'T
HAVE EVEN REGISTERED
IF YOU'D HAVE TOLD ME BEFORE
I'D MADE AN ASS OUT OF MYSELF!
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
SO YOU WOULD HAVE SAID,
"HEY, TH'S GREAT.
YOU KNOW, MY LIFE IS TANKING
"WORSE THAN THE LATEST
BEN STILLER MOVIE,
BUT I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE HAPPY."
MAYBE I WOULD HAVE, YEAH.
WHO KNOWS?
I'VE BEEN
AN--AN IDIOT LATELY.
I PUSHED TAYLOR AWAY.
I PUSHED MAGGIE AWAY,
PATTI, CHEN.
I JUST--I JUST THOUGHT THAT
NO MATTER HOW MUCH OF AN IDIOT I WAS,
I WOULDN'T PUSH
MY OWN BROTHER AWAY.
YOU HAVEN'T PUSHED ME AWAY.
YOU'VE BEEN DATING THE GIRL
I LOST MY VIRGINITY TO
FOR TWO MONTHS,
AND YOU HAVEN'T MENTIONED IT.
I SAID I WAS SORRY.
YOU CALL THE DOCTORS.
YOU MAKE ALL THE APPOINTMENTS.
BUT YOU DON'T WANT TO GO
ANYWHERE NEAR THIS DECISION,
'CAUSE YOU'RE AFRAID
OF HOW YOU'RE GONNA FEEL
IF IT DOESN'T WORK--
IF I END UP PARALYZED
OR WORSE.
YOU'RE A DOCTOR,
BUT YOU'RE MY BIG BROTHER, MAN.
AND I NEED YOU NOW
MORE THAN EVER.
BUT IF THIS IS
YOUR IDEA OF HELPING ME,
THANKS BUT NO, THANKS.
ELI, WAIT.
- JUST WAIT!
- AH!
COME ON, KITTY, MOVE.
YOU'RE ON MY JACKET!
GIVE HIM A PET.
SONNY BONO LOVES TO BE TOUCHED.
YOUR CAT'S NAME
IS SONNY BONO?
THAT'S SO WEIRD.
IT WAS BETWEEN THAT
AND "JASON BOURNE."
YOU'RE TRYING TO SNEAK
OUT OF HERE, AREN'T YOU?
WOW.
I'M NOT SURE I'VE EVER
BEEN SNUCK OUT ON BEFORE.
NO, WAIT, I HAVE.
I'M NOT SNEAKING OUT.
???
?????
I KNOW... WITH ME.
PLEASE BE SEATED.
IT IS PROFOUNDLY
DISTURBING TO ME
THAT ONE HUMAN BEING
COULD WILLFULLY DENY ANOTHER
THEIR LAST HOPE FOR LIFE.
BUT THAT DOESN'T CHANGE
THE VERY REAL FACT
THAT THERE IS NO LEGAL PRECEDENT
TO SUPPORT JUDGE DOYLE'S CLAIM.
THE PLAINTIFF'S SUIT
FOR BREACH OF CONTRACT
AND SPECIFIC REMEDY
OF PERFORMANCE IS HEREBY DENIED
AND JUDGMENT GRANTED
TO THE DEFENDANT.
THANK YOU.
SCOTT?
SCOTT, I KNOW I DON'T DESERVE
WHAT I'M ASKING FOR.
BUT PLEASE DON'T
DO ANYTHING THAT YOU...
MR. MICHAEL,
TELL ME, WHAT INSPIRED
YOUR SONG, "I WANT YOUR SEX"?
A SONG, BY THE WAY,
WHICH ROSE TO NUMBER ONE
ON THE WORLD CHARTS--
A SONG THAT HELPED YOU
WIN A GRAMMY
FOR BEST ALBUM OF THE YEAR.
WELL, IT WAS INSPIRED
BY A RELATIONSHIP.
LIKE MOST OF MY WORK,
IT WAS AUTOBIOGRAPHICAL.
YOU HEARD PRINCIPAL ACKERMAN
DESCRIBE THE SONG
AS ENCOURAGING PROMISCUITY.
BUT IT'S JUST THE OPPOSITE.
IRONICALLY ENOUGH, I WROTE
THE SONG ABOUT ABSTINENCE,
AND I WAS VERY MUCH IN LOVE
WITH SOMEONE AT THE TIME.
SO HOW DO YOU FEEL
ABOUT YOUR SONG BEING USED
TOPROTEST AN ABSTINENCE-ONLY
SEX EDUCATION PROGRAM?
WELL, I APPLAUD IT,
OBVIOUSLY.
WHEN I WROTE IT,
WE WERE IN YEAR SIX
OF THE A.I.D.S. CRISIS,
A CRISIS THAT RONALD REAGAN
DID NOT EVEN ADDRESS PUBLICLY
UNTIL THERE WERE
OVER 21,000 PEOPLE DEAD.
AND WHAT THE GOVERNMENT
IS DOING RIGHT NOW--
FUNDING FEDERAL PROGRAMS
THAT TELL CHILDREN
THAT CONDOMS DON'T WORK--
IS KILLING PEOPLE
ALL OVER AGAIN.
THANK YOU, MR. MICHAEL.
THESE ARE THE LYRICS
TO "I WANT YOUR SEX."
WOULD YOU PLEASE READ
THE HIGHLIGHTED PORTION?
"SEX IS NATURAL.
SEX IS GOOD.
NOT EVERYBODY DOES IT,
BUT EVERYBODY SHOULD."
DO YOU NOT THINK?
DO YOU DENY THAT THESE LYRICS
COULD BE UNDERSTOOD
TO PROMOTE SEXUAL ACTIVITY?
NO, TO DENY THAT
WOULD BE RIDICULOUS.
NOTHING FURTHER, YOUR HONOR.
BUT WOULD MS. ABRAMS'
INTERPRETATION OF THE LYRICS
BE APPROPRIATE IN THE CONTEXT
OF AN ABSTINENCE-ONLY
SEX EDUCATION PROGRAM?
WELL, I DON'T THINK
I CAN ANSWER THAT,
BECAUSE AN ABSTINENCE-ONLY
"SEX EDUCATION PROGRAM"
IS AN OXYMORON.
ABSTINENCE CAN ONLY BE A CHOICE
IF YOU HAVE ALL THE FACTS.
I LOVE THIS COUNTRY.
I LOVE THE FACT THAT
YOU GUYS HAVE A CONSTITUTION,
THAT YOU PRACTICE SEPARATION
OF CHURCH AND STATE.
BUT I DON'T THINK
I'M ALONE IN WONDERING
WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH ALL THAT RIGHT NOW,
AND, UM, IN MY OPINION,
RIGHT NOW
AMERICA COULD USE
A LOT MORE PEOPLE LIKE MOLLY.
THE WHOLE WORLD COULD.
???
JUDGE TATE'S
DECISION IS IMMINENT.
MY RECOMMENDATION WOULD BE
TO SETTLE THIS NOW.
GET OUT WHILE YOU CAN.
WE DON'T WANT OUT.
JUDGE TATE IS NOT GOING TO
INSERT HERSELF INTO WHAT
IS CLEARLY A SCHOOL MATTER.
CONSIDER
MR. MICHAEL'S TESTIMONY.
JUDGE TATE CERTAINLY WILL.
NOT TO MENTION, ALL THE NEGATIVE
MEDIA ATTENTION HAS TO BE GETTING TO YOU.
JUST WAIT UNTIL GEORGE
DOES HIS PRESS CONFERENCE.
THAT'S A GOOD POINT, SIR.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THIS ISN'T WORTH IT.
ENOUGH IS ENOUGH. WE'LL
REINSTATE MOLLY, ALL RIGHT?
NO!
I DID THIS TO MAKE A POINT.
I WANT THE SCHOOL TO HAVE
A REAL SEX EDUCATION PROGRAM.
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH THIS.
THERE'S NO WAY.
I'M SORRY, MOLLY, BUT THE SCHOOL
CAN'T HAVE A SEX ED PROGRAM
THAT DOESN'T RECEIVE
FEDERAL FUNDING.
WELL, ACTUALLY, I THINK
I KNOW HOW WE CAN RAISE
THAT KIND OF MONEY
IN ONE NIGHT.
A HERO ARISES.
LLY, HOW FAST
CAN YOU GET A MESSAGE OUT?
SIX SECONDS.
THERE ARE OTHER AVENUES
WE CAN PURSUE--
OTHER ANGLES, MORE MONEY.
EVERYONE HAS A PRICE.
WE COULD APPEAL TO HIS MOTHER.
SHE MAY SEE THINGS OUR WAY.
NO, I...
I THINK WE ALL KNOW
I'M GETTING EXACTLY
WHAT I DESERVE.
JUDGE... USE WHAT TIME
YOU HAVE LEFT.
REACH OUT.
MAKE CONTACT WITH YOUR SON.
NO, I'M... I'M DONE USING
OTHER PEOPLE FOR MY BENEFIT.
THEN DO IT FOR HIS.
HIS TESTIMONY WAS PROOF.
HE NEEDS TO LET GO
OF SOME OF THAT ANGER.
OTHERWISE, HE'LL END UP...
JUST LIKE "THE BOIL"?
YOU MAKE A PERSUASIVE ARGUMENT,
TAYLOR.
AND THANK YOU BOTH
FOR EVERYTHING.
NICE PICTURE, MR. DOWD.
WHEN WAS
THIS PICTURE TAKEN?
UH, THIS SUMMER.
AND THIS MAN WITHTHE FAMILIAL
RESEMBLANCE WOULD BE YOUR...
UNCLE?
YOUR MUCH OLDER BROTHER?
BECAUSE I KNOW THERE'S NO WAY
IT'S YOUR DECEASED FATHER.
TAYLOR...
???
BUT YOU ARE A PIG.
OKAY, I LIED.
IN COURT!
OH, COME ON.
I WASN'T UNDER OATH.
I WAS TRYING TO WIN A CASE.
ANYWAY, HOW RELEVANT IS IT
WHETHER OR NOT
MY FATHER'S ALIVE?
IT'S EXTREMELY RELEVANT,
BECAUSE THAT IS WHY
I SLEPT WITH YOU!
OH, COME ON. YOU DIDN'T HAVE
SUCH A BAD TIME LAST NIGHT.
THE QUALITY OF THE TIME
IS IRRELEVANT,
BECAUSE LAST NIGHT WAS
A DRUNKEN, STUPID MISTAKE.
ANY CHANCE WE CAN MAKE THE SAME
DRUNKEN MISTAKE AGAIN TONIGHT?
NOT EVEN THE SLIGHTEST.
OKAY.
IF YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND--
I WON'T.
INTERESTING.
YOUR NEW "OFFICE."
WELL, SQUARE FOOTAGE-WISE,
IT'S AN IMPROVEMENT.
EVERYTHING READY FOR TONIGHT--
INSURANCE, SECURITY,
LIGHTING RENTALS?
YEAH, ONE OF THE PERKS
OF HAVING A CLIENT ROSTER
AS BIG AS THE PHONE BOOK.
CAN I HELP YOU
WITH SOMETHING, SIR?
I CAME BY TO...
APOLOGIES ARE DIFFICULT
FOR A MAN LIKE ME.
BUT GRATITUDE--
YOU HELPED ME, SIR.
WHAT I MEAN IS...
IT'S BEEN SOME TIME
SINCE A CASE
HAS MADE ME, WELL,
FEEL SOMETHING.
I CAN SEE WHY
YOU'VE BEEN FINDING
YOUR NEW CALLING SO FULFLING.
PLUS YOU GOT
TO MEET GEORGE MICHAEL.
YOU DON'T THINK
HE NOTICED, DO YOU?
IT WAS BARELY OBVIOUS, SIR.
I DISCOVERED HIS MUSIC BACK
IN THE EARLY YEARS OF THIS FIRM.
I WAS STUCK ON THIS HELLACIOUS
DOCUMENT PRODUCTION--
JUST ME
AND A ROOMFUL OF FILES
WORKING PAST MIDNIGHT
FOR THREE WEEKS.
I'D STAY SO LATE, IT WAS JUST
ME AND THE CLEANING CREW.
AND... ONE OF
THEM HAD A BOOM BOX,
AND ALL HE PLAYED WAS...
GEORGE MICHAEL.
MOST NIGHTS,
THAT WAS MUSIC WAS
THE ONLY THING
THAT KEPT ME GOING.
I STILL ASSOCIATE IT
WITH MY BETTER DAYS.
I DOUBT THOSE DAYS
REALLY WERE BETTER.
THEY WERE.
AND NOW AS I ENTER
THE WANING SIDE OF MY LIFE...
LOSING EVERYTHING...
"IS LIKE THE SUN
GOING DOWN ON ME."
MM, SORRY.
THANK YOU, ELI.
THIS HAS BEEN THE BEST WEEK
I'VE HAD IN A LONG TIME.
- HEY.
YOU L RIGHT?
I MAY BE GETTING THERE.
LOOK, I SHOULD HAVE
TOLD YOU ABOUT BETH.
AND, UM, I SHOULD'VE--
NATE, SHUT UP.
YOU DIDN'T DO ANYTHING...
EXCEPT THE GIRL
I LOST MY VIRGINITY TO.
YEAH. UM...
IS IT GONNA BE WEIRD
BETWEEN US?
NO.
I'M USED TO WEIRD BY NOW.
AND YOU'RE MY BROTHER,
AND EVEN WHEN I WANT
TO POKE OUT YOUR EYEBALLS...
I STILL LOVE YOU.
SO...
I'VE BEEN THINKIN'...
?????JAPAKSA. HE'S OUR GUY.
SURE ABOUT THAT?
IF YOU ARE.
YOU'RE THE DOCTOR,
AND I TRUST YOU.
THEN HE'S THE ONE
WE'RE PICKING.
AND I'M STICKING AROUND TO MAKE
SURE HE'S THE RIGHT CHOICE.
ARE YOU, UH, SURE
YOU WANT TO DO THIS?
I HAVE NEVER BEEN MORE SURE
OF ANYTHING IN MY LIFE.
IS HE GONNA BE OKAY?
JORDAN?
HE'S GONNA BE ST FINE.
WELL, YOU DID A GOOD THING
THIS WEEK, ELI.
YOU'RE THE ONE DNG
THE GOOD THING, GEORGE.
A HIGH SCHOOL FOOTBALL STADIUM'S
KIND OF A STEP DOWN
FROM THE STAPLES CENTER, BUT IT
MEANS THE WORLD TO THESE KIDS.
WELL, YOU KNOW, THESE DAYS YOU
JUST HAVE TO DO WHAT YOU CAN
TO TRY AND MAKE
A DIFFERENCE, DON'T YOU?
YEAH.
CAN I GIVE YOU A BIT OF ADVICE?
IF ANYONE COULD.
I KNOW I'VE HAD
MY SHARE OF HITS,
BUT I'VE TAKEN
A FEW HITS, TOO.
AND, UH, IF THERE'S
ANYTHING I'VE LEARNED,
IT'S THAT NO MATTER WHAT,
YOU JUST HAVE TO KEEP GOING.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I THINK I DO.
GOOD. WELL,
THAT'S SETTLED, THEN.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN--
MR. GEORGE MICHAEL!
* DA-DA-DA  DA-DA-DA *
* DA-DA-DA-DA-DA *
* DA-DA-DA *
* DA-DA-DA-DA *
* I WAS MIXED UP *
* WHEN YOU CAME TO ME *
* TO BROKE TO FIX SAID *
* DADDY GET YOU GONE *
* I'M MISSING MY BABY *
* STILL MISSING MY BABY *
* I WAS STITCHED UP  *
* BY THE HANDS OF FATE *
* SAID, "HOW YOU GONNA *
* MAKE IT ON YOUR OWN *
* IF LUCK IS A LADY *
welcome to www.1000fr.com