Nice to meet you.
I'm Bong Sang-pil, a lawyer.
Do you know me?
How could I know you from the get-go?
Lawyer Bong Sang-pil.
I'll take the case from now on.
Why don't you switch lawyers?
Are trials a business nowadays?
It must be tough to get by.
I was pretty famous in Seoul too.
Well,
I have a pretty solid lawyer.
Did you see that man
kill your mom?
Yes, I saw him. I saw him.
Hyung-man, hold onto the kid.
I have something to take out.
Let go of me.
Let go.
Detective Wu Hyung-man.
I'll help you get out of here.
Do you know who my lawyer is?
Of course, I do.
Lawyer Koh In-du.
The best lawyer in Ki Seong.
A former district-exclusive judge
of 25 years,
the epitome of legal prestige
and past glories,
the current corporate lawyer
of Ohju Group.
You're well-informed.
He guaranteed that
he'll win 100 percent.
One hundred percent.
But a trial is not a game of probability.
Don't talk to me with those fancy words.
This is a trade secret.
A lawyer who guarantees a win
always loses.
You should've filtered it out.
That old man is lying.
-Get up.
-Hey.
Is she running the business with you?
-You two look good together.
-I told you to get up.
Oh, she's our paralegal.
-She's good, so give us a chance.
-What are you doing?
Where's your pride as a lawyer?
It's not enough for lawyers
to only stand in court.
-Don't you think?
-Do you have
two jobs or something?
I'm closer to a problem solver.
The best problem solver
with a lawyer's license.
I'm here to take care of a lawyer.
Bong Sang-pil.
"I'll turn the tears that you shed
all into money."
He sounds like someone
who can get the job done.
But why is someone like you,
who's a complete outlaw,
interested in a lawyer?
I have my reasons.
No matter how I think about it,
I can't help but be suspicious
of how he suddenly crawled into Ki Seong
after making a name for himself in Seoul.
Ki Seong.
"Ki" means silk, "Seong" means castle.
A castle made out of silk. Ki Seong.
Don't you smell the money?
Silk what?
Ki Seong here,
is a paradise for lawyers.
For people like you and me,
Ki Seong is a playground.
What do you think Ki Seong is
to the lawyers who serve us?
It's the best gold mine.
You're right.
I went out to Seoul
to make a big name for myself,
but you're a bigger success.
Maybe I should've stayed here too.
You and I are
now in different leagues.
I have a favor to ask of you.
Let me join you for old times' sake, sir.
Look at him. What is he saying?
Chairman Ahn is no longer
a gangster like you.
He's a businessman,
an entrepreneur.
Well, you never know
how things are going to turn out.
Please call me
if you need any roughhousing.
I'll be going now, then.
Detective Wu is due for his first trial
for charges of murdering
Mayor Lee Young-su.
Ki Seong will also vote for a new mayor
in the upcoming by-elections
due to the absence of its mayor.
The mayoral election is more…
You're stealing a clearly guilty case?
Yes.
The amount of evidence is suspicious.
And nothing
to back up Detective Wu's innocence.
I know that too.
Wu Hyung-man is obviously the murderer.
Be honest with me.
What's the real reason
you're trying to take on this case?
-The real reason?
-Yes.
I'm so hungry.
Let's eat something.
Thank you.
I'm starving.
See me at my office.
Here, have some.
To be honest,
clients like Wu Hyung-man are
the most cost-efficient.
Let's say he was found innocent.
It'll be a matter of time
until everyone in Ki Seong finds out.
And if that happens,
richer and guiltier clients are
going to swarm in with bags of cash.
So it's for promotion?
What?
In other words,
it's a jackpot if we win the case,
but if we don't,
we still get the lawyer's fee.
You're worse than I had imagined.
Hey. This suit is expensive!
A court must be
where you scratch lottery tickets,
and clients must be bags of cash to you.
I wonder who's worse.
The heinous detective
who killed the mayor of Ki Seong
or the vile lawyer
who wants to get him off the hook
just for money?
What about the ex-lawyer
who judges the defendant on her own terms
before the trial is over?
Darn it, come on.
Hey, Jae-yi!
The vacancy of the mayor position
bothers me.
It's a role someone plays
to aid Ki Seong and you.
Shouldn't you choose someone
after you weigh all the options?
It's not like
I haven't thought about it.
Do you have someone in mind
as the mayoral candidate?
Who do you think it is?
Chief Prosecutor Jang Sang-ik, no?
No.
Then is it Han Tae-gyung,
the chief editor of Ki Seong Daily?
If it's not him either, it's--
Let's see. Is it someone
from outside of Ki Seong?
Nonsense.
Could it be
me?
Were you talking about me?
I'm sure you can handle it.
As the mayor of Ki Seong.
Are you serious?
My goodness. This is--
I can't believe you chose me.
It's a great honor!
You tried living as a businessman
for the last 15 years,
but you're still the same gangster.
From now on, engage in politics.
It suits you, Chairman Ahn.
I understand exactly what you mean.
I'll give it my best, Judge Cha.
Leave it to me.
Does Chairman Ahn have any idea
who actually killed Mayor Lee Young-su?
How would he know that,
even if all of Ki Seong is
in the palm of his hands?
If he did, he would've
wiped out whoever did it.
I mean, his friend is suffering.
Of course, he would.
You get the picture.
By any chance,
do you have any special requests
or a message for Chairman Ahn? No?
PLAQUE OF APPRECIATION
Jae-yi.
-Help me out.
-Yes, ma'am.
Gosh.
There can't be any other clothes
as uncomfortable
and heavy as this one.
There's no one else who looks so good
in a judge's robe.
You talk like everyone else.
This robe is too heavy for me.
About that lawyer.
So he's stealing a case?
Yes.
Sang-pil is rough around the edges,
but I keep thinking of him.
Also, you'll be the judge
for Wu Hyung-man's case.
Did you read the case file?
There is so much evidence
proving Wu Hyung-man's guilt.
Except for one.
It's a murder,
but there's no motive.
There are a lot of cases without a motive.
Wanton murders are common too.
I know that.
But something bothers me.
What is it?
I think
I'll find that out
once I meet Wu Hyung-man.
All right. You're a girl
who can't suppress your curiosity.
Jae-yi.
Your birthday was not long ago, right?
Should we hang out?
Judge Cha, I love this.
It's pretty. How about this one?
-It's pretty.
-Try it on.
How do you know my taste so well?
Can't you at least call me mom
when you're in Ki Seong, like you used to?
Mom.
I like it when you call me that.
I missed it.
I thought you'd go to the Supreme Court.
I honestly didn't think
you'd remain in Ki Seong.
This is my cradle and my grave.
I'm not leaving.
Someone from a family
of district-exclusive judges is different.
My father.
I have a long way to go
to catch up to him.
Judge Cha, let's go.
Goodness.
Look who's here!
Is that you, Jae-yi?
My goodness.
It has been so long.
How many years has it been?
Oh, hello.
Hey.
You've played a big part.
You're the biggest reason
why Yeon-hee became a prosecutor.
-I am?
-People who thrive
need rivals around them,
even if they are no match.
Ms. Nam, don't say that.
Judge Cha, it seems to me
that you favor Jae-yi more than Yeon-hee.
You and your jealousy.
Right.
People like me and Yeon-hee
really need average people like you.
So, you should be
proud of yourself.
Does anyone know what comes
after "however?"
How dare you try and ruin Yeon-hee's life?
Is it that tough
to give her a perfect score?
I'm blaming you if she doesn't
get into Seoul National University.
Ms. Nam!
We're in the middle of class!
Jae-yi, it's fine.
Why do you let her do this?
How dare you talk like that, you brat.
You little--
You disrespectful girl.
-We've never met, yet you curse at me?
-I get it.
You must be Ha Jae-yi,
the girl who has been competing
with Yeon-hee?
I'm going to call the police.
The police?
Goodness. Listen to this girl.
Do you know who I am?
Get out, please.
You.
I'm going to remember you.
Ha Jae-yi.
You're on my blacklist.
What are you looking at?
I'm going.
So you're a lawyer?
You've outdone yourself.
Dragons that rise from stale water
can never reach the sky.
Good luck.
Judge Cha, it's time.
I'll see you again.
Yes, ma'am.
Goodbye.
-Judge Cha!
Young-chul.
Have you been well?
Yes.
This is In-ho.
Na-ri.
And he is
Yoon-su, a good student.
This is
a gift from the judge.
-Thank you so much.
-Goodness. Don't mention it.
I'll be back again.
-Okay.
-Goodbye.
Judge Cha, that was a great interview.
The reporter was pleased.
I'm glad.
HAND SANITIZER
Anyway,
what's going to happen
in the mayoral election?
There are rumors that
you have your eyes on someone.
Who told you that?
People have big mouths.
Whoever you point out is
guaranteed to be elected.
That's why everyone wants your attention.
Mr. Han.
Let the people figure out the election.
Judge Cha, you must be exhausted.
I've been looking
for a great acupressurist.
Take care.
Goodbye.
Foreign press made a report
on the ten years of support
Judge Cha Moon-sook has shown
for an orphanage in Ki Seong.
Judge Cha was voted
as the most respected woman,
and she outmatched her rival
on a survey for a future leader
and has maintained the top for years.
Some call her Mother Teresa of Ki Seong.
Three hundred twenty-three euros.
What’s this about?
-You want 453 euros?
-Yes?
My suit, which you smothered with ketchup.
-So?
-Not only was it limited-edition,
I waited six months to receive it.
It can only be washed
in the headquarters in Italy.
So that's for the laundry and shipping.
I charged you for all that.
It'll be taken from your wage
for the next two months.
As soon as my suspension is over,
I'll pay it back at once.
Great.
Also, my principles have never changed
whether it is for Detective Wu's trial
-or for anything else.
-Hey.
The Attorney-at-Law Act,
Article 1, Clause 1.
"The mission of an attorney-at-law
shall be to defend
basic human rights
and realize social justice."
Even lawyers like you know
the Attorney-at-Law Act.
Goodness.
Lawyers are proprietors.
We don't get public insurance
like doctors do,
but they have a law to make us
realize social justice.
Isn't that funny?
Don't you have
the slightest bit of pride as a lawyer?
Of course, I do.
Lawless Lawyer.
That's perfect. Lawless as in "empty."
No way. It doesn't mean "empty."
Boys.
It means "to fight."
We fight with the law
and win cases for clients,
Lawless Lawyer.
ALWAYS GO STRAIGHT
You are awfully optimistic.
Good work.
We did it. Yes!
Lawyers fight by using the law.
Remember, Ms. Ha.
Let's go and investigate.
Why? We didn't get the case.
We can accept the case if we investigate.
-Chief Tae.
-Yes, sir.
Get the doggy.
-Doggy?
What's a doggy?
It's floating.
Doggy, go fetch.
It's going.
My gosh.
I've only seen this on TV.
You're always a step ahead.
About Lawyer Bong.
I'm dying to know about him.
Our boss, Bong Sang-pil.
May 13, 2013.
At 9:32 p.m.
That's when I got my new life,
thanks to Sang-pil's grace.
You'd be dead if it weren't for me.
Sang-pil, am I still alive?
Something just…
Sir.
Go home if you're going to be scared
-of a simple knife.
-I'm sorry, Sang-pil.
If I see you again from this moment on,
I'm going to kill you.
Bring it.
I only stayed in the gang
because Sang-pil is there.
If Sang-pil is there,
I'm going to follow him
even to hell.
I'm going to start…
following you two from today.
Gwang-su!
It hurts. You're bending it.
This is where Wu Hyung-man
supposedly murdered the mayor.
What are you doing?
Do you think it makes sense
that he was stabbed to death
in a freezer where people come and go?
This is a crime scene.
We came here knowing what this place is.
But who are you?
If you touch anything,
you'll be arrested for obstruction.
Why are you here?
Me?
I'm…
-Are you two acquainted?
-Who let you in?
Prosecutor Kang Yeon-hee.
Sorry, I believe
we weren’t properly introduced.
I'm
Lawyer Bong Sang-pil.
You must be bored.
Investigating a case
that you're not even a part of.
I've never failed to get a case
that I was determined to take.
Whether that was a trial
or a person.
Does Detective Wu
really not have an alibi?
If he did,
why would we go through all this trouble?
I see.
We'll be off, then.
You must not be able to find a case.
Should I find you a good paralegal?
You'll end up
fighting me on this trial.
And I don't need a paralegal.
This is a crime scene,
so please take good care
of the prosecutor.
Let's go, Ms. Ha.
-Why are we here?
-There he is.
You're Lawyer Koh In-du, right?
-Go talk to him.
-Oh, I'm Lawyer Bong Sang-pil.
I don't recognize you. What do you want?
Why don't you hand over
Detective Wu Hyung-man's case to me?
What?
I know that it's not very ethical,
but I have to take that case at all costs.
I've heard that most lawyers
are having it tough,
but seeing you go this far makes me sad.
I'm embarrassed for you.
Romans have their laws
and we have our own laws in Ki Seong.
Get lost when I ask nicely
unless you want trouble.
Yes, begin.
I have a long way to go
to catch up to you, Chairman Ahn.
You paid for his wife's hospital fee
and you hired an esteemed lawyer like me.
If you promise me
that you'll make him rot in prison,
I'll promise to give you a hefty sum.
I have one thing that I want to ask.
Does Wu Hyung-man
have something that will
get you in trouble?
I looked everywhere to make sure,
but found nothing.
By the way, I heard someone
who can confirm his alibi
will be in the trial.
How will you take care of that?
Don't worry. There's no chance.
He'll never vouch for Wu Hyung-man.
There must be…
Make sure you deliver my message.
"If you have something to say,
tell it to my face."
Is this your son?
Look at him.
Which school do you go to?
Ki Seong Elementary School?
Take your hands off the child.
That'll depend
on what you can do for me.
If the mother cooperates,
we wouldn't hurt the child.
Let's go.
Are you awake?
Yes.
Weren't those men scary?
I'm not scared of bad people at all.
I must take after you.
You're brave, Sang-pil.
What did you pray for, mom?
That you would
become a good lawyer.
You should go home.
Tomorrow morning is the first hearing,
so I'll go straight to the court.
You’re really working hard, aren't you?
How did you know that Wu Hyung-man
didn't trust his lawyer?
I'm the one who's curious
how you figured that out.
I was suspicious when I first met him,
then was convinced when we met again.
-Again?
-I visited him.
I knew you were a good lawyer,
but you exceed my expectations.
There's no reason for Wu Hyung-man
to kill Mayor Lee Young-su.
You don't think
that Wu Hyung-man is the murderer, right?
I'm sure you could figure that out too.
The trial will begin.
MAYOR LEE'S MURDER CASE, 1ST HEARING
Your Honor, we'll submit
the analysis report from the NFS
that the blood found on the knife
matches with Mayor Lee's blood.
Moreover, the defendant,
Wu Hyung-man's fingerprints were found
on the knife.
I'm a prosecution investigation officer,
Min Young-jae.
Witness, you found the evidence
covered with the victim's blood.
Where was it?
It was inside Detective Wu's cabinet.
We found Mayor Lee Young-su's bloodstains
on his pants.
Also,
the shoe prints found on the scene
matched Detective Wu's shoes.
First,
the defendant's fingerprints on the knife.
Second,
the victim's bloodstains found
on the defendant's clothes.
Third,
the defendant’s shoe prints
found on the murder scene.
All evidence points to Detective Wu
as the culprit.
Defense Counsel,
start your cross-examination.
I don't have anything.
Next witness, please come forward.
Witness, Defendant Wu Hyung-man claims
he was with you at the time of the murder.
But you testified that you never saw
Detective Wu on the day of the murder
on the police report.
Am I correct?
Yes, you are.
I rest my case.
Defense Counsel, your cross-examination.
Nothing at the moment.
What are you doing?
I'm convincing him right now.
I'm going to make him tell your alibi
before the trial ends.
Don't worry.
Can I really trust you?
Keep quiet, Attorney Koh.
I'm leaving.
Wasn't Kang Ho-il
a witness that you summoned?
Yes, that's right.
Why did you summon him
if you weren't going to ask questions?
You didn't summon
any other witnesses, right?
Also, your evidence list is very lacking.
Your attitude in court is half-hearted.
I'm gathering evidence at the moment.
I'll submit it as soon as I procure it.
The next hearing
will be held in three days.
Have some.
Once its scent latches onto your clothes,
it's supposed to last for 100 years.
It has a delightful scent.
I prefer the smell of money
more than the scent of tea.
Prosecutor Kang.
Who do you get your hardiness from?
Sorry?
Is that a compliment?
I was trying to boost
our rookie prosecutor's confidence today.
Why would
a former district-exclusive judge
with 25 years of experience
go easy on anyone?
You're too modest.
Please finish your conversation.
Thank you for the tea, Judge Cha.
I'll look forward to the next hearing.
You can do it.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Is the trial a joke?
I did it so that you can make
an easy ruling.
Head on the ground.
Okay.
Get up.
You should've at least
pretended to do something.
What if he switches lawyers
because of your sloppy work?
I'm sorry.
You know how I kept this court in order.
So?
Did you forget everything
once your life got better?
Not at all.
Let me keep my pride as a judge.
Don't make me look so pitiful.
I'll do my best.
Please believe me.
What is it?
Why did you come again?
Didn't I say I won't switch lawyers?
That was an entertaining trial.
How are you still saying that?
One defendant received
a five-year sentence
for stealing five bottles of sesame oil.
One defendant got off with probation,
a CEO of an investment company,
after making 27 people commit suicide
by manipulating
12.3 billion won worth of stocks.
-What's your point?
-Here's a question.
In these two trials, is the judge evil
or is the lawyer just incompetent?
Or--
did he plan on making himself
look incompetent?
A plan?
Now, look.
It's according to plan.
He won't notice.
I'm just going to pretend
to defend him.
If he gets a sentence,
he'll fall for my lies if I tell him
we can lodge an appeal
we can overturn the results.
You don't have to worry, Chairman Ahn.
What's the use of having
a perfect-win-rate lawyer
if he has no plans to win?
Koh In-du.
That bastard.
You look like you knew it to an extent.
What?
You.
Who are you?
I can postulate that
Chairman Ahn is Ahn Oh-ju
of Oh-ju Group.
This is what I'm curious about.
Why on earth would Chairman Ahn send you
to prison instead of killing you?
There must be a reason
why he's keeping you alive.
I'll tell you one thing.
An enemy's enemy is my ally.
Here.
Why don't you sign this
and hire me?
Are you part of the plan?
You're not doing this
for the money, are you?
What else would a lawyer work for?
How much research did you do
before jumping into this?
How much?
You're more suspicious.
What's your motive?
My goodness.
I don't trust you.
Get lost.
Hey. Get lost.
That's cold.
What's going on?
-Are you okay?
-Guard!
-Are you all right?
Detective Wu. Look at me.
It's written like so and so,
so there must be a meaning behind it.
Isn't that right?
What letter is it?
Don't you know? It's Chinese.
-You idiot.
-This is Chinese?
I guess so, but it's one letter.
What are you saying? This is Korean.
Lawyers fight by using the law.
Remember, Ms. Ha.
You don't trust your lawyer.
What?
Why don't you trust your top-notch lawyer?
Why do you care whether
I trust my lawyer or not?
Get lost.
You applied for retirement
as a detective, right?
To look after
your sick wife.
Am I right?
What does this mean?
Mu, which means "to fight."
-A date with mom.
-Does it mean to fight?
As in Lawless.
-Lawyer!
Jae-yi.
Once you became a lawyer,
you said you'll buy this house back.
The prices rocketed.
We shouldn't have sold it.
This area is due for redevelopment.
It won't go up much more.
You sold the house saying that
it reminds you of mom.
Take care of the photo studio.
It looks like it'll rain a lot.
It rained a lot back then too.
Jae-yi.
Where are you going?
To buy a harmonica.
I need to take it to school tomorrow.
I'll go and get one.
It's raining cats and dogs.
Let me go too.
The stationery store is too far away.
I'll go by myself.
Dad's going to come out soon
from the shower.
-All right.
-Give me a kiss.
Mom, come back soon.
I'll make it quick.
That was the last time I saw her.
I thought I could find her
if I became a lawyer
or a judicial officer of any sort.
I wonder if she's alive.
Miraculously alive somewhere.
I wish we could at least
get her remains back.
Something to remember her by.
I heard the story.
You almost died.
Do you have any guesses
who might be behind it?
Who are you hearing this from?
This is where I make my deals.
Also, this is a society.
He was arrested.
Don't come to see me again.
Aren't you going to change your lawyer?
I told you to get lost.
Your wife.
I heard she's
on the brink of death in the ICU.
You have to get out of here
as soon as possible.
Why you little--
You.
Who are you?
Who sent you here?
The scar on your arm.
Do you remember the kid who did this?
What?
A detective shouldn't
forget faces so easily.
Or
maybe you don't want to remember.
What should I do with the woman?
Bury her with him.
Let go.
The lawyer that you killed.
I'm her son.
You're that lawyer's son?
As you can see.
You said you wanted to know
why I wanted to take on the case.
I will
kill you after I take you out of prison.
I can't get my revenge on a dead body.
You lunatic.
I will
end your life.
Not here,
but outside.
You.
Guard. Guard--
HA FAMILY'S PHOTO STUDIO
Stay there.
I'll get an umbrella.
Open the door.
Sang-pil.
Did you make a decision?
I can't die in here,
so let's talk outside.
Take my case.
Good choice.
I'm going to do things my way from now on.
Can you get me out of here for sure?
Don't worry.
I'll use everything I have to get you out.
You realize that
I'm a detective outside, right?
You're right.
You'd better keep your promise.
I have to leave this place.
The fee
will be paid with your life.
LAWLESS LAW FIRM
Mom.
How are you?
Don't be afraid.
Be brave.
Live bravely.
Do you understand?
Is this your office?
And where Jin-ae died?
Wu Hyung-man's trial.
I just took on the case.
I see.
Are you okay with only Chief Tae?
I'll get you more men--
No, it's okay.
Has it finally begun?
No.
It began 18 years ago.
I'm going to…
I'm going to punish them
with my own hands.
-Sang-pil.
-All those men who killed my mom.
All of them.
All of them, with no exception.
I'm going to take the ones in prison out.
I'm going to put
the ones outside in prison.
With my hands.
With my hands!
I'm going to show them living hell.
Why are you here at this hour?
Wu Hyung-man switched lawyers.
I think Bong Sang-pil will be in court
for the next hearing.
People who are destined for failure
plot their own demise.
I can't let the rat in the corner
bite the cat.
Am I wrong?
Hey.
Gwan-dong.
I need you to do a job with me.
I got Wu Hyung-man's case.
Come to the court.
He got the case? How--
Lady, let me ask you something.
What?
LAWYER BONG SANG-PIL
You're Bong Sang-pil's girlfriend, right?
-What?
-Why would you
date a guy like him
and get yourself into this mess?
What?
Who are you? Let me go.
Let go! Who are you?
I'm telling you to let me go.
Let go.
LAWYER BONG SANG-PIL
I'm nervous being at court.
He's here.
-Hello, Lawyer Bong!
I don't like this scenery.
I'm sorry, sir.
They wanted to see
your first trial in Ki Seong.
By the way, where's Ms. Ha?
It's 20 minutes before the trial.
-Audience, please enter.
-My gosh.
-Where is she?
-Look at that.
-Fancy.
-It's so fancy.
When are you coming?
The trial will begin now.
Sang-pil.
You can't hear me?
Turn off the music.
Hear me now?
Your voice sounds familiar.
After losing my accountant,
my business was badly damaged.
Why did you come to Ki Seong?
And why do you have Ms. Ha's phone?
I wonder.
Why is your girl's phone in my hand?
Speak, lady.
Tell him you're alive.
You disgusting thugs.
I'm going to--
I'm going to charge you for danger pay.
You better prepare it.
That's my paralegal, all right.
Come here right away.
Your girl is going to lose an organ
for every 10 minutes that you're late.
Do as you wish.
-What?
-She's not my girl.
She's just my paralegal.
You chose the wrong hostage.
The trial's about to begin.
I'm hanging up.
Hey.
-Aren't you Sang-pil's girl?
-What?
Why would I be his girl?
You stupid gangsters.
You should've done some research
before you kidnapped me.
So,
he won't rescue me?
He told me to do whatever.
Darn it, Sang-pil, you traitor.
LAWYER BONG
You decided to be a man and call back.
I changed my mind.
I have to go to court,
but you ruined my mood.
Where are you?
What's your plan?
Don't let them start the trial
before I get Ms. Ha back, okay?
We'll make sure to do that.
Hey.
Sang-pil is heading there?
Yes.
Tell him to choose one.
Either give up the trial
or give up breathing.
I'll make him give up both.
Gwan-dong, it sounds like you're bitter.
Right?
I have your back.
Do what you want.
Everyone knows
if you scratch an imported car,
you're in deep trouble.
But some people lack the common sense
that you shouldn't hit or kidnap a person.
You look better than the last time we met.
Who’s your stylist? You look super fancy.
Is your stylist your mother?
What did you say?
No lawyer would come all this way
to teach you a lesson.
She doesn't look so bad yet.
Did you forfeit the trial?
What else can I do when my employee
and precious debtor is in trouble?
Also…
I didn't forfeit the trial.
Judge Cha Moon-sook is entering.
All rise!
Please take your seats.
I heard that you swapped your lawyer.
That's right.
Are you Lawyer Bong Sang-pil?
That's not him.
Lawyer Bong Sang-pil
left the court before the trial.
Did the prosecution see him?
Where did he go?
He must have been nervous about the trial.
Where did Lawyer Bong Sang-pil go?
Well, about that--
Explain to us why you're sitting there.
I'm his associate lawyer.
I was caught off guard last time.
This time, I'm thoroughly prepared.
You'd better prepare yourself today.
Well, Mike Tyson once said this.
"Everyone has a plausible plan.
Until their heads are
planted on the ground
after they take my punch."
Stop!
An associate lawyer?
Isn't Lawyer Bong Sang-pil
defending this case on his own?
Well, about that,
-a little while ago, the lawyer--
-Defendant.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Is what he just said true?
I mean, that is--
The Attorney-at-Law Act,
Article 112, Clause three.
Do you know that impersonating
a lawyer is a serious crime?
Yes, I know.
This is the body of a gangster,
not a lawyer.
Are you really a lawyer?
Do we have an unidentified man
impersonating a lawyer?
Guards, arrest him immediately.
Defendant.
-Yes.
-What are you doing?
Do you want this to be your last hearing?
No, Your Honor.
Since the defendant is absent,
-today's hearing--
-Come here!
Where is he?
Where is that con artist?
-Me?
-Who else other than you?
Cough up the money, you con artist.
Judge, I will
kill him and go to jail.
You con artist.
You.
Silence.
Can't you hear me?
-You jerk!
-Wait!
You thug!
Order, please!
Are you okay?
Is this real? Are you Sang-pil?
Yes, I'm a lawyer.
Sang-pil!
Damn it.
Let's go.
How could you--
I'm coming soon. Hold out a little longer.
What are you doing?
Please be silent in my court.
If you don't be quiet,
I'll detain all of you.
Listen!
What are you doing? Move.
-It's going to be over soon.
-Are you a gangster?
Take a seat, Judge Cha.
Come here. Come!
How dare you? You jerk!
No need to thank me.
It's only because work would be
troublesome without you.
I was kidnapped because of you.
Of course, you had to come.
You don't need to feel sorry.
Well, you saved me after all.
And even if you hadn't come,
do you think I would've let them harm me?
The defendant was also stabbed.
She was just trying to defend herself.
Security. Take her away.
It's not because I’m a woman.
You made a wrong ruling.
She looks like she was fired.
A partnership is out of the question.
Should I hire her as a paralegal?
Collect money
from all delinquent debtors today.
Right now?
Yes.
Especially here.
Ha Family's Photo Studio.
Ha Family's Photo Studio?
I understand.
That brat.
I'm going to kill you.
Run away! Quickly!
Come back here! Let go!
-My leg!
-Go, quickly!
What happened to my mother
also happened to your mother.
What are you looking at?
This fight
will be our fight from now on, Jae-yi.
A fight?
The trial, you mean?
Yes.
Step on it before we're even more late.
Hey, you thugs!
What on earth are you doing
at the sacred court?
Where are you?
We found it.
What should we do
with the lawyer and her son?
Kill them both.
I don't trust the living.
Who are you?
I'm Lawyer Bong Sang-pil.
The trial starts now.
Judge Cha Moon-sook.
Be careful of those
who exploit your trust.
I trust you.
Jae-yi.
In my opinion, lawyers are people
who fight against prejudices.
Ahn Oh-ju is involved
in Mayor Lee Young-su's death, right?
Have you heard of the Golden City?
Doesn't it stink of crime already?
Oh, gosh. I'm sorry.
Where do I begin?
Jae-yi.
Subtitle translation by: Hae-Lim Lee