Based on novel by MATSUMOTO Seicho
Crossing Mt. Amagi
Numazu, Shizuoka Prefecture
December 1953
The handbills are done.
Thanks.
Amagi...
Amagi is a mountain
on the Izu Peninsula.
Yasunari Kawabata's novel,
The Izu Dancer is set there.
That novel was
written in 1926.
I recall climbing
Amagi that very year.
I was 15 at the time.
I remember meeting
a woman along the way.
It's been nearly 30 years...
I can't help feeling fate
has played a trick on me.
Crossing Mt. Amagi
June 28, 1926
Mt. Amagi, Shizuoka Pref.
I was thrilled to be
climbing this mountain
that I had seen every day
from afar, in Shimoda.
Surely, beyond it was a land
where I could be free.
I'd never come
this far before.
What are you doing?
You gotta put
your back into it.
Do a good job
or it won't sell!
Takichi!
I could only get
three days' worth.
Thanks!
Some candy...
Why're you late? One delivery
shouldna taken so long.
Where were you?
Gimme sake!
With Pa like he is,
I'm depending on you.
But you keep slacking out.
Give the bottle a rest, Pa.
We ain't got no money!
Git some work done...
...'stead of waiting for
handouts from your brother.
Ma...
Can we subscribe
to the paper?
I want to learn more
about the world.
I want to read
some books, too.
Don't make me laugh!
Can I go to
middle school, then?
You think we can afford that?
You wanna drink so bad,
we gotta sell Yoshie off.
I tell you,
there's no sake!
Come on, Hisae...!
Why don't you read
when it's light?
What is it?
You're always looking
at me like that lately.
Why?
Tell me!
Yugashima   8km
Shuzenji   16km
Hey, Sonny!
Where you headed?
Shizuoka City.
On foot?
Is it far?
Sure!
Did you think it was
just over the hill?
You could take a
train from Mishima,
but even that's far —
a good 40 kilometers.
How far are you going?
Shuzenji.
Can I go with you?
Sure, why not?
I gotta air these out
for a while.
You're selling them?
I could sell you some.
Bean cake!
5 sen for two.
Why Shizuoka?
My brother's learning
to be a printer there.
You're going all alone?
Or... did you
run away from home?
I guess all boys go
through that stage.
Water?
Won't your visit
be a problem
if your brother's
still in graining?
Even if you are
his brother...
I just remembered...
I gotta go this way.
What about Shuzenji?
Sorry... See ya.
I was alone again.
And soon beginning to feel
sorry I had left home.
Where are you going?
Shuzenji.
Me, too.
You're from Shimoda?
You have a thirst for
knowledge?
If they had the money,
your folks would send you
to school, I'd bet.
You don't like the work
of a smithy?
It's boring.
Life's not easy, you know.
I've learned that
from my peddling.
Strangers are scary.
That means the
world is scary.
Know anything
about the world?
It's scary.
Just like a woman.
You been with a woman?
How old are you?
Fifteen.
You'll learn
how scary they are.
Remember that tunnel?
Weren't you scared
before you entered it?
It's a woman,
that's why it's scary.
Women and the world...
they're like endless tunnels.
Can't see an inch
in front of your nose.
Can't tell if there's an
exit beyond the darkness.
You may get out,
but what awaits you?
It may be Heaven...
then again, it may be Hell.
That's why it's
so complicated.
Want to take a break?
Just allow us to rest awhile.
How much for rice cake?
5 sen.
Can I go with you
to Shuzenji?
Two rice cakes, please.
There's a navvy.
Guys like him drift
from place to place
looking for
construction jobs.
They're troublemakers.
Be wary of them.
For me, too?
Thanks, kid.
How about this? I'll
make it cheap for you.
Kimono peddlers deal
mainly with women.
"How about a pretty kimono
for your daughter?"
"How about a kimono
for New Year's Day?"
"Add a kimono to your dowry."
I go from door to door
and visit the same homes,
so I learn a lot
about the families.
That gives me an advantage.
Actually, I'm pretty
popular with women.
When I tell them stories of
places like Tokyo or Kyoto,
they practically swoon.
You've been to Tokyo?
I just make believe I've been.
Saki's back? Did she
leave her husband?
I'm gonna make a stop here.
See you around.
She's an old friend...
Where are you going?
Back to Shimoda.
Shimoda...?
Perfect. I'll join you.
I wonder how far
it is to Shimoda.
About 40 kilometers.
Guess we can't
get there by tonight.
Try taking off your sandals.
It's easier walking barefoot.
Just wear them
over rocky ground.
Well?
Feels good!
Nice and cool.
Come over there!
I'll do it.
It smells nice.
I'm sorry.
It's my powder.
In the glow of evening,
red dragonflies
How long since I saw them
from my mother's back?
The mulberries in
the mountain fields
Did really pick them
on so long ago?
You learned that in school?
Yes.
They even teach you
songs there!?
What about you?
Never went to school.
And you...
Why are you alone?
You live in Shimoda?
What does your father do?
He's a blacksmith.
You're taking over?
No.
Any brothers and sisters?
Two older brothers
and two younger sisters.
Then, your brother will
take over the business.
They've both left home.
I just visited my brother
in Shizuoka City.
That leaves only you.
I hate being a smithy.
I want to continue
my education.
And become some great person?
I don't want to be great.
I just want to see the world.
I want to work.
To do that, I need to study.
And one day you'll be
king of your own castle.
A man's gotta dream big.
I wish you success.
You can do it!
My pa won't let me.
What about your mother?
Our home is Hell!
I want to leave it
as soon as I can.
Hell...?
Your only choice is
to escape from Hell.
Of course, there may be
another Hell awaiting you.
But, it's better
than just waiting.
Where are you from?
Me...?
I've been moving
from place to place...
...from one dangerous
rock to another.
Who knows when I might fall?
This might be the
end of the road for me.
The branch got you.
Can't let germs get in.
Is this edible?
Not till autumn.
You sure are smart.
Where are you
spending the night?
Maybe in Yugano.
Oh? How nice.
What about you?
Under the stars, I guess.
Then I'll join you.
Who's that, I wonder.
A drifting navvy.
I was warned to be wary
of drifters like him.
Why?
Guys like him cause trouble.
What sort of trouble,
I wonder.
If he dares,
I'll protect you.
How sweet!
Listen...
I want you to go on ahead.
I have to talk to that guy.
What about Shimoda?
I might be a little delayed.
I'll wait here.
No. Go on!
I have to talk to that guy.
Go on ahead.
I'll catch up to you
when I'm done.
Then, the next day, I returned
to my home in Shimoda.
And now, it's nearly
30 years later.
What a shock!
Among these pages,
I discovered references
to the drifter and the
beautiful woman I met
when I crossed Mt. Amagi
almost 30 years ago.
Even my name was mentioned.
Sir! A visitor.
I'm Tajima. I ordered
a print job.
I was about to send it
to you for proofing.
I was in the neighborhood.
I'm sure there were
larger printers in Shizuoka.
They were busy, it being
the end of the year.
A friend of mine
recommended you.
You're with the police?
I retired last year, but
I help out part-time now.
Since I have time
in my hands,
I decided to write up
some of my old cases.
I suppose you read this.
I glanced through it.
Did anything catch
your interest?
All of them...
I thought the Amagi case
especially interesting.
That murder on Mt. Amagi has
weighed heavily on my mind.
Whys that?
The case began with a report
from the Yugashima police.
It was June 29, 1926.
The site was on the Yugashima
side of the Amagi tunnel,
near the Shirahashi bridge.
We discovered some
personal belongings,
but here was no one in sight.
There was a struggle here.
The plants are crushed.
It looked like the owner
of these belongings
had gotten into trouble.
We searched the area
the next day.
Nice and cool
in this ice shed.
The owner...
These footprints...
They yours?
They ain't mine.
You're sure?
Covered the ice with
a nice layer of sawdust
day before yesterday,
the 28th.
Ain't been in since.
Get someone to check
the footprints.
Shimoda Police
From the type of clothing
and other belongings,
the victim was
probably a navvy.
Check it out.
Now, this vest...
A coin purse with money and
tobacco were in the pocket.
All but the bottom
button are missing,
and these shorts were
inside-out when found.
They were probably removed
forcibly by someone else.
Judging from this slit, the
victim is probably injured.
Why would a robber
leave the coin purse?
June 28, about 8:00 AM,
a man who looked like a navvy
was seen headed toward Amagi.
He was seen near Yugashima
about 3:00 PM the same day.
Witnesses describe him as...
5'7", short-cropped hair,
about 45 years old.
He was headed toward Amagi.
The body was discovered
on July 10.
It was located at Namesawa,
downstream of Wasabizawa.
Do that somewhere
else, will you?
What did you find?
It's summer and the body
was in the water so long
it was badly decomposed.
He been dead about 10 days.
I'd say he was
35-50 years old.
Cause of death?
There is a knife wound
in his back, here.
The wounds about
2-1/2 inches deep.
He probably bled to death.
I have a feeling
it was murder.
He couldn't have
stabbed himself!
Thank you very much.
Sir...
The wound in his back and
the slash in the vest match.
So, that victim was the navvy.
On June 27 and 28,
the victim progressed toward
Amagi on the Shimoda Road.
On the 29th, we found
his belongings here.
On July 10, his body
was found here.
From all this,
we can surmise
that he was killed here
and thrown into the river.
It rained heavily In the hills
on the night of June 28.
The raging river probably
carried his body downstream
where it was discovered
on July 10.
Thus, the time of the crime
has been narrowed
to the night of June 28.
We concentrated on discovering
was on Mt. Amagi
around the time
the victim was there.
Two people came to light.
A priest in Yugashima saw
a barefoot woman of 26-27,
wearing a flashy kimono
walking toward Amagi.
Three hours later, at a
tea shop on the mountain,
the owner and a customer
saw a woman who looked
like a prostitute
and a boy of about 15
heading toward Amagi tunnel.
The two were seen descending
toward Shimoda the next day.
About 7 AM on the 29th,
a woman who looked
like a prostitute
was seen walking
toward Shimoda.
A little later, a young boy
was seen headed for Shimoda.
We later discovered
that the only people
on Mt. Amagi after dark
on the night of the crime
were that woman
and the young boy.
It took the two of them
the whole night
to get to the other side.
We searched for
the two people.
We soon found out
who the boy was.
Takichi, the cops
wanna see you.
What happened?
Did he do something?
We just want to hear
about Mt. Amagi.
You crossed Mt. Amagi
on June 28, didn't you?
He left early in the morning.
I was real worried, but
he came home the next day.
Did you meet anyone on
the mountain on the 28th?
A cake dealer and
kimono peddler.
Anyone else?
When I turned back
at Yugashima,
I came across a woman.
How far did you
accompany her?
Till the entrance
to the Amagi tunnel.
The woman was alone?
No one will be upset with you
for telling the truth.
She told me she wanted to
talk to a laborer there.
Nothing to worry about.
We've got to find
that woman.
Get an ID on her.
Judging from the fact
that she was on foot,
and she looked like
a prostitute,
I'd say she works at one of
the spas in the area.
She's probably somewhere
near Shimoda.
She may have headed for
Kawazu or Ito.
Shimoda Precinct.
Shimoda!
Er... yes, sir.
Shuzenji teahouse...
a prostitute?
Come visit again, honey.
Welcome, sirs.
You're here about Hana?
Behave yourselves in front
of the detectives?
Get to the back.
Clear outa here!
She ran away on the
28th of last month?
That's right.
Hear you had men looking
for her. Any luck?
Not a trace.
That woman's a pain!
She still owes me 300 yen!
What's she like?
Well...
She's a mean one.
Wouldn't surprise me if
she killed somebody.
She tried to get me
with iron tongs once.
She almost killed me!
Shimoda Precinct...
We've ID'd the woman
we put the APB out on.
Date of birth: June 1899
Place: Kuji, Ibaraki Pref.
Name: Hana Otsuka (27)
July 15
Oshima Island
Welcome...
What will it be?
You're Hana Otsuka?
You were once at Teahouse
Ikoma in Shuzenji?
Who're you?
The police.
Let me go!
We took Hana to Shimoda
the next day.
Takichi!
That woman's been caught.
They're bringing her
from Oshima by ship.
Murderer!
But Hana didn't admit
to the crime.
No way! I never
killed nobody!
Why are you doing this to me?
Hana Otsuka!
Your permanent address...?
Tell me!
4218 Oriashi
Kuji, Ibaraki Pref.
Right?
Why would I kill a navvy?
For his money!
You met the laborer on
Mt. Amagi on June 28.
The boy who was with you
told us you sent him ahead
because you wanted
to talk to the navvy.
You had run away
from your brothel
without any money
that day.
And yet, the night of the 28th,
you stayed at inn in Yugano
and paid them 60 sen
the next morning.
What's more, you signed in
as Mitsu Moriyama.
You did it cause
you killed the man!
He gave me that money.
Two 50-sen coins.
He agreed to pay it.
Who'd give you money just
to talk on the roadside?
What's the laugh for?
You know what it's about.
I sold him my body.
For 1 yen!
There was a nice grassy spot
near the tunnel entrance.
I lay down like this.
I could see the sky.
I saw the evening sky
beyond the man's face.
Let me out!
What did I do?
Hot, isn't it?
You bribing me?
Nothing like that.
What's so funny?
I'm laughing?
My folks told me
to always smile,
'cause I look like
a criminal if I don't.
You look worse
when you smile.
Drink up.
You're from Ibaraki?
Why'd you come to Shuzenji?
I didn't come straight there.
You've been through a lot?
I was sent to work at
an inn when I was 14.
There were too many
kids at home.
Guess my folks sold me off.
I see.
My contract ended
when turned 20.
I went on to Atami.
Your folks...?
I never wanted
to see them again.
Atami was better.
Why?
I heard it was warm there.
It's by the sea, there're
lots of hot sprigs
and it's warm in winter.
You like it warm?
It was always cold
when I was little.
I wanted to go
somewhere warm.
What did you do in Atami?
Worked at an inn.
Hooked up with a cook.
Found out he had
another woman.
I didn't mind,
but I guess she did.
That cook got
stabbed by her.
He died?
No, but I didn't want
to stay there any longer.
I spent only
one year in Atami.
I moved to Mishima,
then Numazu...
...to Ito, then Shuzenji.
And this is Shimoda.
You've circled the peninsula!
Everywhere I went...
it was hell.
Why'd you run away from
that teahouse in Shuzenji?
Teahouse...?
It's just brothel.
That's why...
I wanted to find myself
a different life.
I was losing myself!
Damn you!
What is it?
You stole my john!
Who?
Shin!
He was yours?
Damn you!
You sneaky bitch!
You shoulda put
a leash on him!
You gonna kill me?
Don't think I won't.
Hana, must you always
cause trouble?
I don't mean to.
Then don't go stealing
customers.
She's too old to get
her own johns.
If you didn't owe me money,
I'd toss an old bag
like you out!
You get no customers, so
you drink all day.
You're just getting older
and deeper in debt.
More wrinkled, too!
What're you gonna do?
Nobody'd wanna marry you.
What you gonna do?
Maybe there's some old geezer
out there who'll take her.
That might be
your only choice.
Go sweet talk some bugger
out of his savings.
Pay off your debt to me
and get lost.
That would make me
very happy.
Make up your mind!
You better eat!
How long are you
keeping me here?
Let me out!
What did I do?
Why'd you head for Mt. Amagi?
How many times
do I have to tell you?
I figured they'd be looking
for me in Ohito or Nagaoka.
I see.
It wouldn't occur to them
that I'd cross Mt. Amagi.
That's what I told you!
Where did you meet up
with the laborer?
I told you that already!
Where did you meet him?
Shall I repeat that?
The tunnel entrance.
Weren't you with a boy?
I sent him ahead.
We agreed on a price so
I led him into the bushes.
And you had sex.
Listen... you wanna hear
all the details?
I want to hear
what happened after.
He gave me the money
and I split!
Didn't you kill him?
Then you went to the ice shed.
Ice shed?
You planned to sleep there
but there was ice,
so it was too cold.
Instead, you walked to Yugano
and stayed at an inn. Right?
What's an ice shed?
Where ice made in winter
is stored.
We found some footprints in
the sawdust covering the ice.
Size 6 barefoot prints.
Barefoot...
We know you walked
the roads barefoot.
And your feet are size 6!
You left the man behind
as soon as your
business was done?
Yes...
When'd he pay you?
Just before I left.
He didn't hold back?
We'd agreed on 50 sen,
but I begged him
for another 50.
He agreed?
He complained at first.
I don't know
what happened after!
He was clumsily packing
his things, so I left.
Then, he was killed.
It wasn't me!
You were the only people
on the mountain that night!
It was about 9 PM when you
arrived at the inn in Yugano.
If you had sex,
then killed the guy and
stripped off his clothes,
you would have reached
the inn just about 9:00.
Bet you fought
over the money.
As you were arguing, your
violent nature took over.
No telling what you'll do
when you lose your head.
You attacked that whore at
the teahouse with iron tongs!
Isn't that what
happened on Amagi?
You got mad and stabbed him
with a knife or something.
It wasn't me!
Then who?
I don't know!
You sent that boy ahead
so you were the only one
on the mountain that night.
You were seen leaving
the Yugano inn
on the morning of the 29th.
A little later, the boy
headed for Shimoda.
Where'd he spend the night?
He spent the night outside
a temple near Yugano.
Why don't you confess?
This is the end of
the line for you.
You'll either end up
back at the same brothel,
or dead by some roadside.
If he causes any trouble,
I'll protect you.
How sweet!
I...
...I killed him.
Good girl!
In the glow of evening
red dragonflies
How long since saw them
from my mother's back?
The mulberries in
the mountain fields
Did I really pick them
oh so long ago?
You're not cold?
I've got to let air in
from time to time.
But, Hana Otsuka
was found innocent.
After she confessed,
she seemed to not care
what happened to her.
She said she threw the
weapon into the river,
but it was never found.
Her story was ambiguous and
there was no conclusive proof,
in December of that year,
the charges were dropped
and she was set free.
It's been nearly 30 years...
The statute of limitations
ran out 15 years ago.
Looking back, there were
many things we did wrong.
We couldn't get any
footprints at the scene
during our initial
investigation.
Unfortunately, a downpour that
night obliterated any prints.
We never uncovered what
the weapon was, exactly.
To this day?
Yes.
Then... there are the footprints
we found in the ice shed.
I think we were
wrong to decide
the footprints were
those of a woman.
But I feel that someone
spent the night
in that ice shed that night.
But...
Wouldn't it be too cold
to sleep on the ice?
The sawdust must have
been damp, too.
I talked to a man who harvests
natural ice for a living.
He says he naps in the shed
during the summer.
There's a ladder in the shed.
If you lay the ladder
down over the ice
and place a plank over it,
you get a simple bed.
You don't get any sawdust
on you, and it isn't cold.
I've a feeling there was a
ladder in the shed that night.
A young boy accompanied Hana
partway over the mountain.
He told us that he descended
the mountain ahead of Hana,
after parting with her.
But, it wasn't till the
afternoon of the 29th
that he reached his home.
Where did he spend
the night of the 28th?
A size 6 footprint need not
belong to a woman.
It could belong to young boy.
Don't you agree?
Mr. Tajima...
You don't think
Hana killed him?
Not anymore.
We should've probed more deeply
into the actions of the boy.
He was a child of 15, so
we never suspected him.
I wonder why Hana said
she killed the man?
I've been puzzling over that.
I wondered about the song...
Why did she sing that song?
As she murmured the song,
she seemed like a little girl.
Like she was trying to protect
something pure and innocent.
While working on this book,
I took a trip to Shimoda.
The boys home is now
a garage for tour buses.
The boy left Shimoda
over 20 years ago.
It wasn't long after
that Japan went to war.
Who knows what became of him?
Sorry to take so much
of your time.
When will this be ready?
I'd like to have it by
the end of the month.
I'll rush it.
Hana Otsuka
How about another 50 sen?
You said 50.
Listen, I made it
real cheap for you!
You were watching?
I was in such a panic,
I don't remember how
I stripped his clothes off.
I couldn't find
any money on him.
But, I wasn't really
after his money.
I've never told anyone
about what happened.
After awhile, the incident
faded from my memory.
There was a long war, and so
much confusion afterwards,
the incident became hidden
in the recesses of my mind.
Until I heard the
detective's story today.
I can no longer be tried
for what I did that night,
but the shock running through
me now will never fade away.
Your records room...?
3rd floor.
Come in.
I've brought your books.
I had to come
this way, anyway.
Thank you for coming.
So, you've come....
I thought I should.
It must have been
a heavy burden.
No...
...Yes.
Thanks for your trouble.
I still can't figure out
why he was killed.
It wasn't written there.
It probably had to do with
feelings for the woman.
I guess only those
involved would know.
Yes?
...What become of
Hana Otsuka?
She moved from town to town.
Seems she's in Noto now.
She's alive?
She sells seafoods at
the morning market there.
Where's the morning market?
You're leaving, Hana?
You want something?
Won't you sell me some fish?
I only carry seaweed.
I'd like some.
Your home...?
It's not far.
You live with someone?
No. But no use
sweet-talking me!
You're not from
here, are you?
I'm a traveler.
From where?
The Tokyo area.
I'm originally from Ibaraki.
How'd you end up here?
In the old days...
I preferred a warmer
climate. The south.
I lived down there awhile, but
too many things went wrong.
Many things...
there was the war, and
so many other things.
And I liked it better
in a new place.
This isn't Paradise,
but it's a good place.
What did you want?
Seaweed.
40 yen.
Never mind... they're
just leftovers.
Your fingers...
I'm a printer.
The president?
You're king of
your own castle.
Thanks.
Hope you make a fortune!