Ron is down.
He needs a medical evac.
Where is it? Is it there?
- Oh, the drive is gone.
- Are you sure?
It's gone.
Give me a minute.
They must have it.
Get off to them.
- I'm stabilizing Ronson.
- We don't have the time.
- I have to stop the bleeding.
- Leave him!
Have you got him?
He is in the black Audi.
- What about Ronson.
- He's been hit.
I'm sending an emergency
evacuation squad.
Well, that'll be too bloody late.
Have they seen us?
Medical Evac for Ronson,
five minutes way.
It's allright?
You'll wait using it.
I wasn't using that one either.
Keep your head down!
Just get clear!
Tanner, which way?
Keep going.
I can direct you from here.
We both know
what's at stake here.
We can not afford
to lose that list.
Yes, ma'am.
Where are they now?
They're on the top roof
of the grand bazaar.
Take the left, there's a bridge.
You can cut him off.
- What happened?
- They're on the train, ma' am.
What do you mean
on the train?
I mean they're on the top
of the train.
Well, get off to them,
for God's sake.
He's going out of range.
We've lost tracking.
We are blind here.
- What's going on?
- I'm still with them.
There is CCTV satellite,
end of it.
What was that?
VW Beetles, I think.
He's uncapping the cars.
- 007, are you alright?
- Just changing carriages.
What's going on?
Report!
It's rather hard
to explain, ma'am.
007 is saying proceed.
This side here isn't much more road.
I do not think I can go any further.
I may have a shot.
It's not clean.
Repeat.
I did not have a clean shot.
There's a tunnel ahead.
I'm gonna lose them.
- Can you get into a better position?
- Negative. There's no time.
Take the shot.
I said, "Take the shot!"
Well, I can't.
I may get Bond.
Take the bloody shot.
Agent down.
It's like going
into the headmaster study.
It's new chairman's
just a standard procedure.
Bloody waste of my time,
that's what I'd call it.
I'm sorry to have
to deal with such...
a delicate subject
at our first encounter...
But...
I have to be frank with you.
And it would be a good idea.
The Prime Minister
is concerned.
You can tell him my operatives
are pursuing every avenue.
Have you considered
pulling up the agents?
I've considered every option.
Forgive me,
but that sounds like an evasion.
but why am I here?
Three months ago
you lost the computer drive
containing the identity
of almost every NATO agent
embedded in terrorist organizations
across the globe.
A list which,
in the eyes of our allies,
never existed.
So, if you'll forgive me,
I think you know why you're here.
How you should call it,
a civilian oversight?
No, what we call this is...
a retirement planning.
Your country has only
the highest respect for you
and your many years
of service.
When your current posting
is completed,
you'll be awarded to JCMG
with full honors.
Congratulations.
You are firing me?
No, ma'am, I'm here to oversee
the transition period...
leading to your voluntary retirement
in two months' time.
Your successor has yet to be appointed,
so we'll be asking you--
I'm not an idiot, Mallory.
I know I can't do this job
forever.
But I'll be damned if I'm going
to leave the department
in worst shape than I found it.
M... you've had a great run.
- You should leave with dignity.
- Go to hell with dignity.
I'll leave when the job's done.
Yes?
Now?
Main alert from Q Robson,
trying to decrypt
the stolen hard drive.
We are tracing
the encryption signal.
Localizing now.
It's sent here in the UK.
London.
Get to inspect the basis
as soon as possible.
- It's coming from MI6.
- What?
The data back,
it is linking to our network.
Corrupted.
This is behind our firewall.
- We should shut down.
- No, track it.
We have to know
where it's coming from.
Strip the head
and try the source.
How the hell
it entered in our system?
Get in trace right now.
- It is your computer, ma'am.
- Shut it down.
What is this?
For God's sake!
Just get out of the way.
- Don't you recognize the car?
- Madam...
I'm gonna find
who ever did this.
Where the hell
have you been?
Enjoying death.
007, reporting for duty.
Why didn't you call?
Didn't you get the postcard?
You should try it sometimes.
Get away from it all,
it really lends perspective.
Run out of drink.
Were you awarded, eh?
What it was you said?
Take the bloody shot.
I made a judgement call.
You should have trusted me
to finish the job.
It was the possibility
of losing you...
or the certainty of losing
all those other agents.
I made the only decision I could
and you know it.
I think you've lost your nerve.
What do you expect,
a bloody apology?
You know the rules of the game.
You've been playing it long enough.
- We both have.
- Maybe too long.
Speak for yourself.
Ronson didn't make it, did he?
No.
So, this is it.
We are both played out.
Well, if you believed that,
why did you come back?
Good question.
Because we are
under attack...
and you know
we need you.
Well, I'm here.
You'll have to be debriefed...
and declared fit
for active service.
You're gonna return to duty
when you've passed the tests.
So take them seriously.
The shower
might be an order.
I'm going home
and change.
Oh, we sold your flat.
Put your things
into storage.
Standard procedure...
on the death of an unmarried
employee with no next of kin.
You should have called.
I'll find a hotel.
Well, you're bloody
will not sleep in here.
They attacked into the
environmental control system
locked out the safety protocols
and have turned on the gas.
Well, that should
have been impossible.
I was told that they have hacked
into our files.
They knew her appointments.
They knew she would be
out of the building.
They weren't targeting her.
They wanted us to see it.
- Where are we, lieutenent?
- New digs.
The old building was declared
strategically vulnerable.
That's putting it marvelly.
Their aim is to breach the most secured
computer system in Britain.
So we are at war
with them now.
This is part of Churchill's bunker.
Some of these tunnels
are dating back to the 18th century.
Quite fascinating,
if it wasn't for the rats.
- When do I see M?
- Tomorrow, you'll see M...
and Mallory too
if you're lucky.
Who is Mallory?
The new chairman of the
Intelligence and Security Committee.
A charming man, I think.
You and him will really gonna hit it off.
Welcome to the new MI6.
We've have attempted to trace
the computer message, but...
it was sent by an asymmetrical
security algorithm...
with the chance to signal
all over the globe
through thousands
of different servers.
And now that they've accessed
M's code,
it's only a matter of time before
they are able to decrypt the list.
Q branch has been analyzing pictures.,
But so far, nothing.
General feeling it's probably
something from her past
Perhaps when she was
running things in Hong Kong.
- It is no idea what it all means?
- And you believe that?
The truth is we don't have
a clue of what's on the list...
or what they are trying
to do with it.
We can always do this later.
You know what?
Let's.
I'd like to start with some
simple words' sensations.
Just tell me the first word
that punch into your head.
For example I might day,
and you might say...
Wasted.
All right.
Gun.
Shot.
- Agent.
- Provocative.
- Woman.
- Provocatrix.
- Heart.
- Target.
- Bird.
- Sky.
- M.
- Bitch.
- Sunlight.
- Swim.
- Moonlight.
- Dance.
- Murder.
- Employment.
- Country.
- England.
Skyfall.
Done.
This is going well.
Get these analyzed.
When arrives, on me.
She's ready for you.
I'm sorry.
Have we met before?
I am the one
who sould say "sorry".
It was only four ribs.
There's nonetheless
vital organs.
Nothing major.
No enough excitment
in Istambul?
I've been reassigned.
Temporary suspension
from field work.
- Really?
- Something to do with killing 007.
- Well, you gave it your best shot.
- It was hardly my best shot.
I'm sure
I can survive your best.
Time you'll get the chance.
Would you do me a favor,
will you?
If they'll do let you back
out there...
Warn me first.
I'm assisting Gareth Mallory
in the transition...
and then I'll be back
in the field.
- That's what you want?
- Yes, of course.
- This is not for everyone.
- Ah, 007...
It's this way.
In your defense...
a moving target
is much harder to hit.
Then you better
keep moving.
The whole office goes off in smoke
and that bloody thing survives.
Your interior decorating tips
have always been appreciated, 007.
007, Gareth Mallory.
I hope I haven't miss anything
that P.M. does prattle in line of a crisis.
- Bond.
- Mallory.
I have just been reviewing
Bond's tests.
Seems you passed.
Mind the scheme of your tiff?
You're back
on active service.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- I'll be outside.
- I may have one question.
Why not stay dead?
You have
the perfect way out.
Go and live quietly
somewhere.
Not many field agents
get to live this cleanly.
Do you get out
in the field much?
You don't need to be an operative
to see the obvious.
It's a young men's game.
Look, you've been
seriously injured.
There's no shame in saying
you have lost a step.
The only shame, it would be
not admitting until it's too late.
I'm in, or fire me.
Entirely up to you.
If he says he is ready,
he is ready.
Perhaps
you can't see at all.
Maybe you will.
What exactly
are you implying?
You are sentimental
about him.
As long as I am the head
of this department,
I'll choose my own
operatives.
Fair enough.
Good luck, 007.
Don't cock it out.
We've analyzed
these shrapnel fragments.
You're lucky it wasn't a direct hit.
It would have cutted you in half.
It's a depleted uranium shell.
A military grade.
Hard to get,
extremely expensive
and only used by select few.
You recognize anyone?
Him.
Okay, the name is Patrice.
He's a ghost.
An unknown resident
without country of origin.
How do we find him?
Well, luckily I used to have one
or two friends left in the CIA.
They're after him for the Yemeni
ambassador's murder.
And they're getting close.
Intel is he's gonna be in Shanghai
in two days time. Probably a new job.
You have to go there
and wait further instructions.
If he turns up, it's yours.
Find out who he worked for
and who has the list.
- Then, terminate him for Ronson.
- With pleasure.
Is there anything else
you want to tell me?
No.
Report to the new quarter master
for a few documentation.
He hasn't set up sharp yet, but
Tanner will put you two together.
Good luck.
Thank you.
007...
You are ready for this?
Yes, ma'am.
I didn't know
Bond passed the tests.
He didn't.
Always makes me feel
a little melancholy.
A grand whole warship being
ignominiously hold the way to scrap.
Inevitabilty of time,
don't you think?
What do you see?
A bloody big ship.
Excuse me.
007...
I'm your new
Quarter master.
You must be joking.
Why, because I'm not wearing
a lab coat?
Because you still have spots.
My complexion
is hardly relevant.
And your confidence is.
Age is no guarantee
of efficiency.
And youth is no guarantee
of innovation.
Oh, how's it I can do more damage
on my laptop
sitting in my pyjamas before
my first cup of Old Grey
than you could do
in a year in the field.
So why do you need me?
Every now and then
a trigger has to be pulled.
Or not pulled.
It is hard to know which
in your pyjamas.
- Q...
- 007.
Ticket to Shanghai.
- Documentation and passport.
- Thank you.
And this.
Walter PPK, it's 9mm short.
There's a microdermal sensor
in the grip...
encoded to your palm print,
so only you can fire it.
That's a random killing machine
more than a personal statement.
And this?
Standard as your
radio transmitter.
Activated and broadcast
your own location.
Distress it.
And that's it.
A gun, and a radio.
Not exactly Christmas, isn't it?
Were you expecting
an exploding pen?
We don't really go in
for that anymore.
Good luck out there
on the field.
And please return
the equipment in one piece.
Brave new world.
Who got the list.
Tell me, who you working for.
Tanner, he has posted
the first five names.
Their cover is blown.
They're in danger.
Get them out now.
Room service.
I didn't order anything.
Not even you.
I have got some
new information.
Are not you a little too qualified
to be delivering messages?
It's all part
of the learning curve.
And Q is afraid of flying.
So, whoever stole the list
has already decrypted it.
They posted the first five names
on the web.
- It was only a matter of time.
- That should be the start.
They're posting five more
next week and the week after.
It's some kind of
sadistic game.
Cut through razor.
How very traditional.
Well, I'm going to do some things
the old-fashion way.
Sometimes the old ways
are the best.
Are you putting your life
in my hands again?
Tans, already briefed me
on the list...
raising the tantalizing question
of what you are really doing here.
The official directive
was to help...
in anyway I can.
Like spying for Mallory.
You know, Mallory
is not as bad as you think.
He is a bureaucrat.
You should do
your homework.
Gareth Mallory
was Lieutenant Colonel...
Lieutenant Colonel in Northern
Ireland Herford regiment.
He spent three months
at the hands of the IRA.
So there's more to him
that meets the eye.
We'll see.
Keep still.
This is the tricky part.
That's better.
- You know the part now.
- Mmh, mmh.
And what part is that?
Old dog...
new tricks.
Good evening.
Don't you touch your ear.
There are three exits.
And lots of blind spots.
I've got them covered.
You look beautiful
in that dress.
You could scrub out
about yourself.
It's amazing what one could do
with an extra pair of hands.
You're telling mean.
You gamble?
Don't like you a little flatten
now and then?
He doesn't like
to take chances.
Good evening, sir.
How may I help you?
I'd like to cash thes in,
please.
One moment, sir.
Good fortune tonight, sir.
Let's hope so.
With compliments
of the house.
Thank you.
Now you can afford
to buy me a drink?
Maybe I could give
a stretch or two.
I guess I got good
4 million euros in here.
Not bad.
- I like this game.
- Why don't we play another?
I don't gamble.
I'm not very lucky.
With lucky old friend
in Shanghai.
I've been waiting to see
who'll redeem the chip.
You made such a gold entrance
into our little drama.
Do I have
a complicated plot?
Who doesnt't appreciate
the occasion of twists?
- Mr...
- Bond. James Bond.
Severing,
so Mr. Bond...
shall we discuss your next
performance with all that drink?
Not bad.
Are your friends
be joining us?
I'm afraid... it's inevitable.
- She's pretty.
- No, no.
Do you like that ass,
don't you think?
Well, I'll keep you posted.
Perfect.
Would you mind if I ask you
a business question?
Depends on the question.
It has to do with... death.
A subject in which
you're well versed.
How would you know that?
Only a certain kind of woman
wears a backless dress
with a Beretta .70
strapped to her thigh.
One could never be
too careful when...
a handsome man in tuxedos
carry Walters...
I'm correct in assuming
you'll killed Patrice?
Yes.
Might I ask why?
I want to meet
your employer.
Be careful
what you wish for.
You are scared.
Thank you
for the drink...
Mr. Bond.
You put on a good show.
But ever since
we sat down here
you haven't stop looking
at your bodyguards.
The three of them
have been excessive.
They're controlling you.
They're not protecting you.
Tattoo on your wrist...
is Macao's sex trade..
You belonged to one of the houses
when were you, 12?
13?
I can see images
of a way out.
I hope she told
you were in love.
but that was a long time ago.
You know nothing about it.
Right, when a woman is afraid
and pretending not to be.
How much do you know
about fear?
All there is.
Not like this.
And... not like him.
I can help you.
- I don't think so.
- Let me try.
How?
Bring me to him.
- Can you kill him?
- Yes.
- Will you?
- Someone usually dies.
Perhaps you can.
When I leave,
they're going to kill you.
If you survive,
I'm on the Kimera.
North Harbour...
Berth 7.
We cast off in an hour.
Very nice to have met you,
Mr. Bond.
Good luck.