(Tale of The Nine Tailed)
Does it not hurt anymore?
Look at me.
Long time no see, Yeon.
She's mine.
How does it feel?
After a whole 600 years,
you face your enemy through the body of the woman you love.
Ji A...
Where is she?
Right here. She lies inside me.
She screams in agony...
while resenting her inevitable fate.
Let me ask you this, then.
Who was the other guy...
and what exactly are you?
This is all your doing.
If you had let her be sacrificed in the island's well,
we would've stayed as one, not be split into two.
Though when the times comes, we'll unite.
And when exactly will that happen?
When we jump into your body instead.
What's with your obsession over my body?
Why can't you unite in another's and live happily ever after?
Are you not aware of the speed it grows?
Could it be...
that you not only grow,
but also age as fast?
That's the curse laid on you.
I came across one opportunity to change my fate.
By becoming a dragon?
If I had,
I'd have been the spirit of Baekdudaegan, not you.
So what you want is revenge.
That's why out of all the immortal bodies,
you're after mine.
Just so you know, now that I'm finally dominant,
she'll soon fade away.
- I'll kill you. - If you do,
she'll die too.
And saving her will lead to your death.
Will you save her or save yourself?
I hate to tell you this,
but none of the above is what we want.
Yap all you want.
I won't let you touch this body.
You're weak.
What?
Does it weaken you to be dominant in her body?
Most of the Imoogi's strength and abilities lie with him.
You're only the heart, so to speak.
That's why you need Ji A as your shield...
to prevent me from knowing how weak you are.
You two can't change the inevitable.
With you gone, it'll be over. Just you.
And you're the only one I need, Ji A.
Please.
Just give up that body of yours and die.
Ji A,
I know you can hear me.
I know you're there.
Shut it.
Come back to me.
I'll always be waiting for you,
so come back to me.
I'll always be waiting for you.
I've been waiting for you too.
When it comes to waiting, no one can do it better.
24 hours? I could sit there even for 24 years.
I had a feeling that I could meet you here.
I'll always be by your side.
I'm yours till death do us part.
Yeon...
Yes, it's me. I'm right here.
Help me, Yeon.
Just kill me instead.
So that I never hurt you.
Ji A, it's all right.
It'll all be all right.
(Chapter 13: The Other Imoogi)
Dr. Koo, thank you for today. You saved us.
Thank Mr. Lee Yeon, not me.
Take care then, guys.
Mr. Lee!
I'll be right there.
Yeon or the Imoogi, none of them matter to me.
All I need are the ground cherries.
Just the ground cherries!
Hey, there.
One shouldn't be so rough in the driver's seat.
- Who are you? - The name's Hyeonuiong.
I'm here to retrieve the ground cherries.
Who sent you? Imoogi? Lee Yeon?
How's that of importance?
What matters is that this doesn't belong to you.
Stop talking nonsense.
The ground cherries are mine. They're mine!
Gosh, that hurt so much.
I hate the smell of gunpowder.
Listen to me. You shouldn't fight against fate.
What? Are you also a monster?
My goodness.
It looks like we'll meet again pretty soon.
Mr. Lee.
(Shin Ju's Animal Hospital)
So right now, she's Director Nam, right?
But who knows when she might turn into Imoogi and attack you again?
I let him hurt me.
What?
I wanted to check.
The fact that Imoogi split into two could be his strength,
but it could also be a fatal weakness.
What do you mean?
The Imoogi inside Ji A's body...
is a little different from the one I've seen until now.
They're both the same Imoogi but a little different?
This one is a lot more similar to the Imoogi from my past life.
What can I do to help?
Go meet the Snail Bride and ask her about the fortune teller.
The guy who took the fox bead?
Should I turn them back into humans?
Check the list and turn only those who still have lives left to live.
It'll be tiring to turn them all into humans at once.
Okay, got it. But let's eat first.
Honey, should I buy you tteokbokki?
How about I add some fritters and sundae as well?
I also want extra cheese.
Okay, I'll add extra mozzarella cheese.
And as for spiciness, I'll order level three for you,
and I'll get myself a level one.
(The list: A record of each person's lifespan)
There will be chaos...
if I don't stop him now.
(Name: Nam Ji A, Date of Birth: March 3, 1991)
(Date of Death: 2020...)
Even so,
I'd still choose her.
(Name: Nam Ji A, Date of Birth: March 3, 1991)
(Date of Death: 2020...)
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
With my own hands...
I stabbed you with my own hands...
and hurt you.
I know better than anyone that it wasn't you.
Look at me.
How do you feel? Are you okay?
How could you possibly be worried about me...
when you were the one who got hurt?
Want some coffee?
Or how about chicken feet?
No.
Do you want me to take you home?
I don't think I can go home.
What if I change like I did earlier...
and hurt my parents?
Then I might really go crazy.
Then should we go somewhere instead?
Yes, let's go somewhere.
Let's go to a place where it'll just be the two of us.
Don't worry too much about your parents.
I told Shin Ju to keep an eye on them.
Thank you.
Where are we going?
Wherever.
Do you remember when we first met?
When you were a little kid?
No.
Of course, I remember.
All my life, my job was to chase after people.
You were the first person to chase after me instead.
I should've just asked you out then.
Then we would've been able to enjoy our time together...
for a lot longer.
Darn it!
Were you going somewhere?
Forgive me. I must've been crazy.
I was blinded by the ground cherries. I was out of my mind!
Look at me.
You were born as a servant in a filthy thatched house.
And you've come a long way since then.
It's... It's all thanks to you.
I saved you right before you were about to get executed for treason.
Yes, how will I ever forget?
Then...
why did you help Lee Yeon?
I heard you told him a lot of stuff.
Please... Please show me mercy and give me another chance.
No, there's no need.
I no longer need...
anything or anyone.
There's been a change of plans.
Pardon?
I want you to become miserable.
And I mean, every single person who's alive right now.
Go and turn yourself in.
You're better off living as a criminal.
Should we play a game?
What game?
Like you said earlier, let's pretend like we don't know anything.
How exactly?
You're just an average person who's bored of your dull...
and ordinary life.
And as for me,
let's say I'm not a nine-tailed fox.
Do we know each other?
We're...
married. We're a married couple.
We're just an average couple.
Let's say you went to work as usual,
and I'm waiting for you to come home as I cook dinner.
- What do you think? - So I'm the breadwinner?
I own tons of buildings and have a lot of cash.
I just want to be a house husband who gets paid rent every month.
Don't laugh. Try being serious.
What do you want me to do?
Just a second.
Wait here for a moment.
Okay, now come home from work.
Go on. Come home from work.
Gosh, this feels stupid.
I'm home.
Honey.
"Honey, I'm home"?
Is my little puppy mad?
Why are you mad?
Look at the time.
You always say it's normal for a woman to come home late...
because you're out there working.
Did you or did you not promise to be home by midnight?
Did you promise me or not?
- Do I have a curfew? - Yes.
You broke curfew twice last month too.
Are promises to me unimportant?
I did, didn't I? Can you forgive me just this once?
This just won't do. Take a seat.
Sit. Let's talk.
Honey. You finally got sober not long ago.
Me?
You're creating the background story too.
Darling, you've changed.
Do you even love me?
I love you.
Me too.
Are we making up now?
Of course. Our fights never last...
more than five minutes.
It's not fair.
Why can't we even have an ordinary life like this?
It's so unfair.
It would've been so nice...
if you were human...
and we were really married...
If Imoogi never existed...
If we lived in a world like that...
If I had met you like that...
I'll protect you.
No matter what happens...
when this fight ends, you must stay alive.
That's good enough for me.
Regardless of how many times I am reborn,
the world is filled with darkness.
Yeon, I'll show you...
what the world I live in looks like at the end.
(Terry)
Hello?
A party will begin.
I don't plan to be nice to you anymore.
Just wait.
I pity you.
You've never learned how to give or receive love.
All you know how to do is threaten people like this.
As you say, I am threatening you.
Because your body will be a ticking time bomb.
Look at yourself.
Soon, that will take full control over your body.
When that time comes, you will kill Yeon with your own hands.
Have you lost your mind?
Why are you going through my computer?
What are you thinking? Why are you messing with when she dies?
She's the real thing.
The real Imoogi.
What do you mean?
The real Imoogi is within her body.
We must get rid of that in order to get rid of the one running rampant.
You plan to sacrifice an innocent child to catch Imoogi?
Knowing what she means to Yeon?
I do. I know better than anyone.
- So how could you? - That's why I'm doing it.
Yeon can never let her die.
Imoogi knows that as well.
What do you think will happen...
if it takes over Yeon's body?
You'll kill a person because of something that didn't happen yet?
What are you trying to protect by doing that?
This is my job!
Because of that same reason,
our son lost his wife, and we lost our son.
You added her name to the list of the dead then too.
Thanks to that,
our son took his own life,
and we couldn't save his soul yet.
Thanks to that, we prevented a pandemic.
Bok Gil can't even be reincarnated!
That was...
his fate.
You know, I thought you had changed a little...
after losing your child like that.
But I was wrong. You haven't changed at all.
A much greater calamity will come.
- If we don't stop it now... - Fine.
You stop the calamity.
I'll stop you.
What are you trying to do?
The moment you change the date that she dies,
it's over between us.
I write this as I watch you sleep.
I've decided to return to Seoul.
The conclusion I made after spending a night here is this.
No matter how far we run,
we can't escape.
I'm on the beach.
Let's walk together.
Let's walk to the end of the beach and go back together.
I'm small and powerless.
The weight of my destiny is too much to bear.
I feel like I'll sink to the bottom of that ocean.
But Yeon, you push me up like a buoy.
You make me float.
You make sure I don't sink.
I vowed to give her...
the gift of a boring...
and warm life...
that normal people live,
but down by the beach,
this is how she replied.
"Not alone."
She wishes to die together...
and live together.
However,
that seems to be a promise...
I can't make.
Save Mr. Lee.
I tried everything, but to no avail.
Why should I?
Why must I help you?
Because I stabbed him on your command.
This is your responsibility too.
What do you think I even am?
The owner of the ground cherry tree.
You don't scare me.
And you mean that.
Still, shouldn't a deal be beneficial to me too?
You don't seem to have anything to offer,
and this half-breed is useless to me now.
Take my life in exchange for his.
Are you sure?
Just a second.
Mr. Lee, I'll no longer be with you now,
but I wish you a long life.
Don't skip your meals and put on some weight.
Stop chasing after your brother too.
Just a little.
I hope you find a little more happiness.
Kill me.
Don't stall. That's even more annoying!
Open your eyes.
Consider your request granted.
However,
you're coming with me.
When the Imoogi in her calls for you,
you will become my soldier.
Stay in places like that for too long...
and the darkness will swallow you whole.
How may I help you?
I'm here to turn myself in.
Sorry?
I killed her.
Killed whom?
The mummified victim you found.
Are you for real?
There are four more.
Search my car's GPS history,
and you'll find the burial sites for all victims.
- Check it out. - Sure.
What's your motive?
Why would the head of a broadcasting station...
All I wanted was longevity.
If you had been in my shoes,
you would've made the same choice.
Want me to go in with you?
No.
I want to properly draw a picture of my parents' faces inside my head.
- If anything happens to me... - That'll never happen.
Still, go ahead, if that's how you feel.
Don't worry though.
It only surfaces when it senses danger.
Or when it detects blood.
Come to think of it...
Long time no see, Yeon.
The scales are slowly replacing my skin.
It might not be long before...
I lose myself completely.
Well, I'm off to see the Snail Bride.
Bring my part-timers over to my place later.
Sae Rom and Jae Hwan?
Yu Ri... Where's Yu Ri?
She left with that scary man.
She won't ever be back.
What did the fortune teller say? Did you look into it?
I've been asking my contacts.
He didn't seem like some lowly spirit.
Who is this geezer?
Well,
this seems to be a groundless rumor,
but one of the Afterlife judges...
is said to leave his post once in a while.
That's interesting.
Anyway, let me know if you find out anything about him.
- Here. - What is this?
What is all this?
I was never able to buy you anything with the money I earned.
It's been eating away at me.
When did you find the time...
out of your busy schedule to buy this?
Gosh, it's pretty.
How nice.
Try it on.
I don't want to wear it out.
Our daughter bought this...
with the money she worked hard to earn.
Wearing it out is how we thank her.
Go ahead and try it on.
Should I?
This isn't the way home.
Give me five minutes.
Is it that good? Is it?
Yu Ri!
What brings you by at this hour?
That was unexpected.
It's my goodbye.
We're breaking up.
- What do you mean? - Shin Ju, you were just dumped.
So don't wait for me any longer...
and don't come looking for me.
Did I do something wrong?
No, I'm just tired of you.
- I get bored easily, you see. - No.
That's not who you are.
Though it takes a while,
you offer up your heart once the road to it opens.
Though you act cold, you are the kindest of them all.
- As if you know me well. - I do.
- How you treat Rang and the dog... - Enough with Mr. Nice Guy.
I hate how you patronize me...
about needing friends and family.
Your dowdy looks and that constant smile?
I hate them all.
I won't patronize you.
I'll buy and wear whatever you tell me to wear.
I won't smile if you don't want me to.
Will you please stop?
I hate you, okay? I don't like you!
You're lying.
I don't want you clinging onto me either.
I'll be off now.
I can't break up with you.
- Let me go. - No, I'll never let go.
I won't let go until you take back what you just said.
Shin Ju.
You're making me get sick of you by acting like this.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for whatever it is that made you feel this way...
Don't follow me.
Will you please just disappear from my life?
She told me I act too nice.
She doesn't like how I look or the way I dress.
I think I kind of understand what she means.
The ground cherry thief is a real brat.
Why would she play with your heart like this?
Don't speak ill of Yu Ri!
Please.
Stop crying.
She's my first and last love.
I was even going to propose to her.
Yesterday, I went to Jongno and bought her a gold ring.
But I can't believe...
There must be a reason why she suddenly broke up with you.
I don't know why.
It's Imoogi. Imoogi took her.
Mr. Lee.
Rang.
What are you doing?
You're awake. You're back.
Stop acting so unusual. You're making me want to die again.
- How did you wake up? - What do you mean by that?
What do you mean Imoogi took her?
He saved my life, and she went with him in return.
Soo Ho saw them leave together.
No, we need to find her.
- Not like this. - What if he kills her?
Let me go.
Are you dumb or what? Are you trying to die with her?
I figured you wouldn't be able to punch him, so I did it instead.
I promise you this.
I'll save your girlfriend and bring her back.
I'll kill Imoogi.
Leave that to me.
He tried to kill me twice.
What about Soo Ho?
Is he home all by himself?
Yes, of course.
You can't leave a kid home alone!
He won't leave the house even if you try to drag him out.
You're all here.
Although, I can't say I'm glad to see everyone.
Who are they?
They're my part-timers.
- What are you looking at? - You also look like a sculpture,
so I can already tell.
You're not human, are you?
Don't talk to me or I'll bite you.
No wonder.
So there are 3 humans and 2 foxes.
What are you, Dr. Koo?
There are 3 humans and 3 foxes.
Now that we're done introducing ourselves, let's begin.
We're here to discuss our plan, so why are you here?
Because I've dealt with Imoogi a lot more than you.
And you also have one inside your body.
Leave her out. What if he hears everything from inside her body?
No, we need her for this.
Whoever disagrees with that can leave.
We've all encountered Imoogi at least once.
And we almost got killed by him one way or another.
He's even holding someone hostage.
On top of that, he lives in two bodies, not one.
We need to catch them both in order for this fight to end.
And what's even worse...
What's even worse is...
that the main spirit lives inside my body.
Hey, Imoogi's friend.
Why don't you just kill yourself and make this easy for all of us?
You should've just stayed in bed.
Living as Sleeping Beauty suits you a lot better.
We can't kill Imoogi by hurting him physically.
He can even manipulate people's thoughts,
and Ji A and I are the only ones who are free from his powers.
It won't be easy, but try your best...
not to face him one on one.
But how can we fight him without encountering him?
You won't be able to do much even if you do encounter him.
You'd probably just call for help.
- I'm warning you. - "I'm warning you."
What does Terry eventually want by doing all this?
He told me he's going to kill everyone.
And then...
Soon after, a virus will spread.
No one will ever be happy again.
"A virus"?
Will you stop playing games?
I'm listening. Just get to the point.
Up until now, I was worried Ji A might get hurt.
So I kept trying to fight the Imoogi we all know.
But now,
we're going to change our target.
How are you going to kill what's inside her body?
You've found a way, right?
Yes, I have.
(Traditional Korean Cuisine: The Snail Bride)
Do you remember the fortune teller we met at the Korean Folk Village?
Yes, of course.
Thanks to someone, I lost my fox bead.
I heard he's actually pretty powerful. Is that true?
He's one of the afterlife judges.
- What? - He even has...
the Sin Slayer.
No way.
What's a Sin Slayer?
It's a dagger that slays sins.
It slays sins?
I heard King Hades made it himself a long time ago with the branch...
of the tree that weighs our sins.
But didn't it disappear thousands of years ago?
Snail Bride just picked it up.
But wouldn't that dagger hurt Director Nam?
No, she won't get hurt.
The Sin Slayer is a wooden dagger.
It slays things that cannot be slain.
In other words, it'll only slay Imoogi's spirit.
Thank goodness, Ji A.
When are we going to do this?
Tomorrow.
How does it feel to be born again?
I don't know if it's because I came back from the dead,
but this coffee tastes amazing.
You should live a long life.
If you die early, you won't be able to drink coffee anymore.
It'd be no fun.
Were you scared I might die?
Yes, I was scared.
What's yours? Let me have a sip.
It's good.
Why are you so nice to me?
We've never really been to a cafe like this together.
All I needed to do was just reach out.
I don't get why I never thought of doing that.
What's with you? You're acting like you're about to die soon.
It's really delicious.
It is, isn't it? Let me try a sip of yours too.
- No, you can't have mine. - You ungrateful punk.
Hey, don't drink mine.
What happened?
Nothing.
Was it her?
It wasn't like that.
You're defending her, so I guess I'm right.
Will that sin-slaying dagger really work on Imoogi?
It has been over 600 years.
I plan to end this fight once and for all.
What if you fail?
What happens to me then?
Rang.
That's why I need you.
I worked so hard all my life.
I was so close to becoming the most powerful man in the nation.
Darn it.
But I'm stuck in this tiny cell.
At least I'm alive.
I'm alive.
(Two Meals)
This too.
How could you want tteokbokki right now?
Even if the world ends tomorrow, I'd want tteokbokki.
Give me that. Fill that up.
- You want a cheese ball, right? - Yes.
- One cheeseball, please. - Okay.
This is so good.
- This is really good. - This?
How does this taste good even in the midst of everything?
Right?
Don't come to me for the time being.
Your lives may be in danger if you're with me.
That's up to me.
You guys almost died.
Do you remember...
when my mom came to Seoul to get back surgery?
She cried because she couldn't go to the hospital because of her show.
You went to the hospital in my place.
You were there for my mom.
If she were all alone that day,
I would've blamed myself forever after she died.
- Let us help too. - She's right.
We're ordinary humans, so we're powerless,
but I want to do anything I can if it will save your life.
Right now, going back to work...
is how you can help me.
Mr. Choi will throw a hissy fit if all three of us are out.
He isn't in.
What?
He turned himself in?
Imoogi wouldn't just let him live like that.
Find out what's happening at the police station.
Okay.
The person you have reached...
Mr. Choi isn't answering his phone.
- Call an ambulance! - Okay.
This is Geumran Police Station.
- We need... - Let... Let me. I'll help.
- Please hold his head up. - Okay.
Snail Bride, we have to pull up our plan.
(Traditional Korean Cuisine: The Snail Bride)
He's making his move.
We don't have much time.
We'll catch the Imoogi in Ji A's body today.
Everything must go exactly as planned.
We get it, so say it.
It's simple.
Ji A will draw her blood...
and lure Imoogi out.
Once he comes out, I'll stab him with the Sin Slayer.
Shin Ju. Once Ji A and I go in,
lock the door from the outside.
No one can come near us until I give the signal.
Why not?
By chance if he escapes from Ji A,
you guys will be in danger.
He may enter one of your bodies.
That's why I made a border with horse blood.
He's different from the Imoogi we've known until now.
We don't know what he looks like or how and where he'd move.
We don't know anything right now.
We cannot make a single mistake.
What if he goes into you?
That won't happen as long as I'm conscious.
Shin Ju.
It's a snake. I got one that is a perfect fit for him.
So, the best is if you can slay it in one go.
Even if he gets away,
that snake is the only body he can go into.
Let's go. I want to get rid of it as soon as possible.
Here's the dagger.
Thank you. You should go.
Please be careful.
Okay, then.
Shall we begin?
But first,
tie me to the chair with this.
What if I hurt you again?
That's unncessary.
Do as I say. Okay?
Why do you keep trying to protect me?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Don't say that. You'll jinx it.
Okay, then. I'll tie you up.
Okay. Yeon.
Will you give me a hug?
Don't hesitate because of me, okay?
There's nothing to be nervous about.
It's only a blunt wooden dagger.
I'm prepared for any unwanted injuries.
As if I'd let you get hurt.
Besides, this dagger can only slay the unslayable,
like Imoogi's soul.
Does that mean, it can also slay...
your soul too?
Don't hesitate because of me, okay?
There's nothing to be nervous about.
It's only a blunt wooden dagger.
I'm prepared for any unwanted injuries.
As if I'd let you get hurt.
Besides, this dagger can only slay the unslayable,
like Imoogi's soul.
Does that mean, it can also slay...
your soul too?
Of course, it can.
- But... - Yes?
I've been meaning to ask.
Who are you?
What's dying...
is your soul.
- You can't. - Move.
I'll kill her if anything happens to Yeon.
Do so, but only over my dead body.
You think that can stop me?
How pathetic.
Who knew you'd actually come in possession of the Sin Slayer?
Hey. Are you pretending to be asleep?
Wait.
Did that really kill his soul?
This was inevitable anyway.
So how about it? An old home for a new one.
Don't you know how pricey houses are these days?
You little thief.
- What on earth? - Isn't it obvious?
This is what I needed to confirm.
So this is how you jump from body to body.
The fortune teller has been untraceable since the folk village.
Even the Gatekeeper of Samdo River hasn't been able to spot him.
Darn it.
What now?
Go out and find me a random wooden dagger.
A wooden dagger?
What use do you have for a blunt dagger?
To slay the unslayable.
How about we change the game a bit?
Stop the car.
So this dagger was never...
It cost 10 dollars at a flea market.
The fortune teller only pops up...
wherever it wants to whenever it wants to.
Darn rat.
Right back at you.
What was with the silly Ji A act?
Did you know it was me?
I could smell the metallic scent of blood.
As you know, I have a heightened sense of smell.
Anyway, I thank you for the donation.
Knowing my secret...
doesn't automatically give you the upper hand.
Even if you bury it elsewhere, I'll still find a way back to her.
I will keep doing so until you hand over your body.
So what you're saying is that I can plant your soul elsewhere...
by burying this.
For instance... How about that rat snake?
I dare you to try.
Don't tell me...
you're expecting me...
to be gently dragged out of this body.
Right. If I'm being honest,
I like this piece of Imoogi better than the other one.
A villain should at least be this crazy.
Romance, my foot.
This woman is and will always be my hostage.
The other piece of Imoogi is more interested in Ji A...
than being united with you.
He is nothing but a bunch of fragments.
Not according to him though.
You think you can pit us against each other?
Dream on.
Do you even know what he's up to right now?
You see, he's...
Irritating imbeciles.
(Name: Nam Ji A, Date of Birth: March 3, 1991)
(Date of Death:)
(Date of Death: Today)
Innocent lives are being sacrificed.
It won't be long before chaos sweeps the world.
No, you're wrong.
All along, you're the one who's been chaos itself.
- Honey. - Don't call me that.
For I...
just decided to give up that title.
Don't be ridiculous. On whose authority?
Stop right there.
You heard me!
The moment you step past those doors,
you'll lose everything.
I'll make sure of it!
Are you okay?
Yeon.
Yes, it's me.
Let's hurry.
At least so I can be myself...
right before it all ends.
I want to be there beside you.
Let's end this.
Let's put an end...
to this exhausting fight.
(The List)
(Name: Nam Ji A, Date of Birth: March 3, 1991)
(Date of Death: Today)
(Name: Nam Ji A)
(Tale of The Nine Tailed)
Just give me three more days.
I can catch him! I can catch Imoogi!
It's too late.
You'll regret this.
If it weren't for me, Yeon would still be...
living as a mountain spirit.
Yeon will never forgive me for this.
Don't make me regret liking you, Yu Ri.
I have the power to destroy everything you care for.
Let's join hands and kill the gatekeeper of Samdo River.
And what's the condition?
Give me Ji A.