--==本字幕由 美剧台词网 逐行精校==--
详细台词讲解 请访问 fluensay.net
Here's little Ben nodding off.
Look at Aunt Monica's little boy!
- Oh, look, he's got Ross haircut. - Oh, let me see.
Oh, God! Is he just the sweetest thing?
You must just wanna kiss him all over.
That would be nice.
- Pardon? - Nothing.
Just a little extra air in my mouth.
Hey, Chan, can you help me out here?
I promise I'll pay you back.
Yeah, right, okay. Including the waffles last week, you now owe me...
... 17 jillion dollars.
I will, really, I'll pay you back this time.
Now, where's this money coming from?
I'm helping out at the NYU Med School with some research.
What kind of research?
Uh, just, you know, science.
Science.
Yeah, I think I've heard of that.
It's a fertility study.
Joey, please tell me you're only donating your time.
All right, come on, you guys, it's not that big a deal, really.
I mean, I just go down there every other day...
...and make my contribution to the project.
Hey, hey. But at the end of two weeks, I get $700!
Wow, you're gonna be making money hand over fist.
老友记
第一季第二十四集
没人告诉你生活会是这样
So no one told you life was gonna be this way
你滑稽的工作  你的差劲
your jobs a joke, you're broke,
你半途而废的爱情
your love life's D.O.A.
就像开车卡在二档
It's like you're always stuck in second gear,
每日每周每月
And it hasn't been your day, your week, your month,
甚至每年都是如此
or even your year, but
大雨倾盆时
I'll be there for you,
我会陪伴你
when the rain starts to pour.
I'll be there for you,
像我以前那样
like I've been there before.
我会陪伴你
I'll be there for you,
因为你也陪伴着我
'cause you're there for me too.
Okay, we got the coleslaw, we got the buns.
We got the ground-up flesh of formerly cute cows and turkeys.
Men are here!
We make fire.
Cook meat.
Then put out fire by peeing, no get invited back.
Cute.
- Oh Joey, Melanie called, said she's gonna be late. - Oh, okay.
So how are things going with you two?
Is she becoming your "special someone"?
I don't know. She's pretty great.
Yeah? What does she think of your little science project?
What, you think I'm gonna tell a girl I like that
I'm also seeing a cup?
Man's got a point.
The tough thing is, she really wants to have sex with me..
Crazy bitch.
Yeah, well, I still got a week left to go in the program,
and according to the rules, if I want to get the money
I'm not allowed to conduct any...personal experiments,
if you know what I mean.
Joey, we always know what you mean.
How long did you think this barbecue was gonna last?
- I'm going to China. - Jeez, you say one thing, and....
- You are going to China? - Yeah. It's, it's for the museum.
Someone found a bone.
We want the bone, but they don't want us to have the bone.
So I'm going over there to try to persuade them to give us the bo...
It's, it's a whole big bone thing.
Anyway, I'm gonna be gone for like...like a week.
So, uh, if you want to reach me, you can't.
So here's my itinerary.
- Um, here's a picture of me. - Oh, let me see.
Could you take it to Carol's every now and then and show it to Ben
- just so he doesn't forget me? - Yeah.
"Hi, Ben. I'm your father."
"I am the head!"
All right, this barbecue's gonna be very fun.
Hey, is Rachel here? Um, I wanted to wish her a happy birthday before I uh, I left.
- Oh, no. She's out having drinks with Carl. - Oh, hey, who's Carl?
- You knew that guy she met at the coffeehouse. - No.
- You see, there's this guy she met at... - The coffeehouse? Right.
So you do know who he is.
Okay, I'm gonna go say goodbye to the guys.
Okay, hey, you know what? Tell them that bone story.
- I have to go to China. - The country?
china在英语中还有瓷器的意思
No, this big pile of dishes in my mom's breakfront.
Do you know who Carl is?
Let's see. Alvin, Simon, Theodore.... No.
Well, Rachel's having drinks with him tonight.
Oh no! How can she do that
when she's never shown any interest in you?!?
- Forget about her. - He's right, man.
Please. Move on. Go to China. Eat Chinese food.
Of course, there they just call it "food."
Yeah, I guess. I don't, I don't know.
All right, just, just give her this for me, okay?
- Listen, buddy, We're just looking out for you. - I know.
We want you to be happy.
And I may only have a couple beers in me,
but I love you, man.
I'm still on my first.
I just think you're nice.
Anyway, that's when me and my friends started
this whole fruit basket business.
We call ourselves "The Three Basketeers."
Like "The Three Musketeers," only with fruit.
OK, how does everybody like their burgers?
No, presents first! Food later.
Hey, hold on there, tiger. How's it going? How you holding up?
Well, not so good. She definitely thinks
that tonight is the night we're gonna...
...complete the transaction, if you know what
And you do.
So, uh, have you ever thought about being there for her?
What do you mean?
You know, just be there for her.
Not following you.
Think about it.
Okay. I'm guessing this is from....
- Thank you, Melanie. - Ok, this one right here is from me.
Okay. It's light. It rattles.
It's...
...Travel Scrabble!
Thank you.
This one's from Joey.
It feels like a book, I think it's a book. And it's a book!
美国童话作家
It's Dr. Seuss!
That book got me through some tough times.
There's a little child inside this man.
Yes, the doctors say if they remove it, he'll die.
- Who's this from? - That's Ross'.
Oh,my God! He remembered!
- Remembered what? - lt was like months ago.
We were walking by this antique store.
And I saw this pin in the window.
And I told him that it was just like one my grandma had when I was a little girl.
I can't believe he remembered!
Well, sure, but can you play it on a plane?
It's so pretty! This must've cost him a fortune.
I can't believe he did this.
Come on, Ross, remember back in collage,
when he fell in love with Carol...
...and bought her that ridiculous expensive crystal duck?
What did you just say?
Crystal duck.
No, no, no.
The "love" part?
Oh, my God!
Oh, no, no, no.
That's good. Just keep rubbing your head. That'll turn back time.
This is unbelievable. I mean, this is unbelievable!
I know. This is really, really huge.
No, it's not. It's small. It's tiny. It's petite. It's wee.
I don't think any of our lives are ever gonna be the same ever again.
Hey, is there a mute button on this woman?
I think this is so great. I mean, you and Ross!
- Did you have any idea? - No, none!
I mean, my first night in the city,
he mentioned something about asking me out,
but nothing ever happened so I just...
What, what else did he say? I mean, does he, like, want to go out with me?
Well, given that he's desperately in love with you,
he probably wouldn't mind getting a cup of coffee or something.
Ross? All this time?
I've gotta talk to him.
- He's in China! - The country.
Wait, his flight doesn't leave for another 45 more minutes.
- What about time difference? - From here to the airport?
Yes!
- You're never gonna make it! - Well, I've gotta try.
Rachel, what're you gonna say to him?
- I don't know. - Well, then maybe you shouldn't go.
He's right. Cause if you're just gonna like break his heart,
that's the kind of thing that you can wait.
Yeah, but if it's good news, you should tell him now.
I don't know, maybe I'll know when I see him.
Here, look, all right, does this help?
No. Look, all I know is that I cannot wait a week until I see him.
I mean, this is just too big.
You know, I've just gotta talk to him. I gotta... okay, I'll see you later.
Rachel, I love you! Deal with me first!
再见  我的房间要窗子
All right.
你笑什么
- Ross! Excuse me, pardon me. - May I see your boarding pass?
Oh, no, no, I don't have one. I just need to talk to my friend.
Oh, oooh. I'm sorry. You are not allowed on the jetway
unless you have a boarding pass
No, I know, but I... he just went on. He's right there,
he's got the blue jacket on, I... can I j-just...
No, no. Federal regulations!
Okay, all right, okay. Then could you please uh,  just give him a message for me? Please.
- This is very important. - All right. What's the message?
I don't know.
Excuse me, sir! Excuse me, sir?
- Uh, I have a message for you. - What?
It's from Rachel, she said that she loved the present,
- and she'll see you when you get back. - What?
Toby... Oh, for God's sake, I don't know what she's talking about!
There's no Rachel. Don't give me that deep freeze.
Oh, Joey, Joey, Joey!
I think I blacked out there for a minute.
It was nothing.
Well, now we gotta find something fun for you.
You know what?
Forget about me. Let's uh, let's give you another turn.
- Me, again? - Sure. Why not?
Boy, somebody's gonna get a big fruit basket tomorrow!
Oh, I gotta tell you, Joey, you are nothing like I thought you'd be.
How do you mean?
I don't know, I-I guess I just had you pegged
as one of those guys who're always 'me, me, me.'
But you... you're a giver.
You're like the most generous man I ever met.
I mean, you're practically a woman.
Uh, so, uh, Rach, uh... you wanna save this wrapping paper,
I mean, it's only a little bit torn...
So you are gonna go for it with Ross or should I throw it out?
Don't know. Don't know.
Thought about it all the way there,
and I thought about it all the way back. And uh, you guys, you know, it's Ross!
You know what I mean? I mean, it's Ross.
- Sure! - Sure.
I don't know. I mean, this is just my initial gut feeling, this is...
but I'm thinking, oh, I'm thinking it'd be really great.
Oh, my God, me too! We'd be like friends-in-law!
You know what the best part is?
The best part is that you already know everything about him.
It's like you start on the 15th date.
Yeah, but you know, it would be like starting on the 15th date.
Another good point.
No, no, I mean, when you're on the 15th date, you know, you're already in a very...
..."relationship-y" place. You know, you're committed.
Well, I mean, the what happens if it doesn't work out?
- Why isn't it working out? - I don't know. Sometimes it doesn't.
Is he not cute enough for you? Does he not make enough money?
- No, I'm just... - Maybe there's someone else.
Is there? ls there someone else?
No, there is no one else.
Then why the hell are you dumping my brother?
Hey, big Spender!
She's still asleep.
- So how'd it go? - Oh, it was amazing.
You know how you always think you're great in bed?
The fact that you'd even ask that question
shows how little you know me.
Well, it's like, last night I couldn't do the thing that usually makes me great.
So I had to do all this other stuff.
And the response I got! Man, oh, man!
It was like a ticker-tape parade!
Yes, I know. As it happens, my room's very, very close to the parade route.
It was amazing,
and not just for her. For me too!
It's like, all of a sudden I'm blind...
... but all my other senses are heightened, you know.
It's like I was able to appreciate it...
...on another level.
I didn't know you had another level.
I know. Neither did l!
- Hey, great skirt. Birthday present? -Yeah.
- Well, from who? - From you.
I exchanged the blouse you got me.
Well, it's the thought.
Hey, doesn't Ross' flight get in in a couple hours?
At gate 27B?
Uh, yeah, um. Monica, you know, I've been thinking about it.
And I've decided this whole Ross thing,
it's just not a good idea.
Why?
Because I feel like I wouldn't just be going out with him.
I'd be going out with all of you.
and there would just be all this pressure, and I don't wanna...
No, no, no, no, no, no pressure, no pressure!
Monica, nothing has even happened yet, and you're already so...
I'm not "so." Okay, I was a teensy bit weird at first...
... but I'll be good. I promise.
- Who is it? - It's me, Carl.
- Come on up. - Behind my brother's back?
is exactly the kind of crazy thing you won't be hearing from me.
- Seven hundred bucks! - All right, you did it!
Do we have any fruit?
Man, hell of a two weeks.
You know what, though? I really feel like I learned something.
Really? See, you're gonna stick with this "all for her" thing?
What are you, crazy?
When a blind man gets his sight back,
does he walk around like this?
I'm just saying, if I see one more picture of Ed Begley Jr...
演员  环保主义者领袖
...in that stupid electric car, I'm gonna shoot myself!
I mean, don't get me wrong...
I'm not against environmental issues, per se...
...it's just that guy!
I can't believe you'd rather go out with him than me.
Excuse me, please, I'm trying to have a date here.
Fine. Just stop thinking about me.
Can't do it, can you?
So, I'm thinking about you. So what?
I don't get it. What do you see in this guy anyway??
Well, he seems to be a very nice guy.
I mean, come on, buddy! Get a real car!
Rachel, come on. Give us a chance.
Ross, it's too hard.
No, no, why, because it might get weird for everyone else?
Who cares about them. This is about us.
Look, I've been in love with you since like the ninth grade.
Ross, You're like my best friend.
If we broke up, and I lost you...
What makes you think we're gonna break up?
Well, have you been involved with someone where you haven't broken up?
No.
But it only has to happen once.
Look, you and I both know we are perfect for each other. Right?
I mean, so the only question is: Are you attracted to me?
I don't know.
I mean, I've never looked at you that way before.
Well, start looking.
Exactly!
And you just know that I'm gonna be the guy...
...caught behind this hammerhead in traffic!
You're right. You're right.
- You know what? - What?
I forgot. I'm supposed to pick up a friend at the airport.
I am so sorry!
if you want to stay and finish your drinks, please do.
- I'm sorry, I gotta go. I'm sorry. - But....
Excuse me! Pardon me. Excuse me. Sorry.
Toby, for God's sake, will you let it go?
There's no Rachel!
Oh, hey, hey! I got that.
-Thanks, sweetie. - No problem.
I can not wait for you to meet my friends.
-Really? - Yeah.
You don't think they'll judge and ridicule me?
- No, they will. I just.... - Can't wait!
Come on, they're gonna love you.