(Tale of The Nine Tailed)
(Chapter 15: The Destiny That Is You)
I'd like to know one thing.
What made you decide...
to team up with me?
Probably the same reason you decided to team up with me.
What are you doing here?
You must die for me to live.
I'll end this all myself.
Don't do this. If you do...
Farewell.
See? Ji A warned you...
not to do this.
What? You're not...
You're not Ji A.
How could you fail to recognize your own master?
You darn insect.
How dare you? I let you live longer than you deserved.
"Insect"?
I wouldn't have stayed by your side...
if it weren't for the ground cherries.
I'll be honest with you. You make me sick.
You're just a guy with an inferiority complex...
who's neither a deity nor human.
You talk too much.
You've lived for way too long.
Just go to the Underworld.
I bet your family's waiting for you.
- Dad. - I don't even remember when.
But there was a time when I had something I wanted to protect...
with all my life.
Dad, where are you coming from?
- What did you buy, Dad? - My kids,
- wife, and mother. - Dad.
But I barely even remember their faces.
Darn it.
Did you see that?
This feels unfamiliar.
Those who poured me wine...
were always those who begged me for more time.
They begged me to help them stay alive.
For 1 more day. For 1 more year.
There's no need to brag about not having any friends.
It's because I don't trust anyone.
It sounds like you failed to gain people's trust.
It means I have nothing to protect.
That's what makes me stronger than you.
I'm stronger than you...
because I have someone to protect.
Are you sure?
It looks like Ji A's going through something.
My other half has just woken up.
What?
Sit down.
If you leave before I finish this glass of wine,
our deal will no longer be valid.
This is my only chance to take him to the Samdo River.
Should I give up and go to Ji A? Or...
Don't worry.
He shows up when he senses danger.
For example, when I bleed.
He's very protective of himself.
I'm sure everything will be fine.
At least Ji A will be.
This is how we're different.
I'm not sure about that. You also have something...
you must protect at all costs.
For example, your other half that lives in Ji A's body.
I heard you'll become pretty insignificant once that dies.
It looks like you tried to play smart,
but why did you have to hide something so precious...
inside the woman I love and cause such a nasty mess?
I noticed you took a scale.
- Do you want it back? - Will you give it back?
If you give me back Ji A.
The gatekeeper of the Samdo River comes first.
Don't come near me.
Please don't come.
I'm already here.
What will you do?
Will you kill me?
If I die, Ji A will die as well.
- Would you like to shoot me? - Do you think...
I won't be able to?
Like you saw earlier, you only get one shot.
If you fail, I'll be the one killing you.
Okay then. I'm going to count to three.
You have until then to decide.
- One. - Do you think the three of us...
met by coincidence?
No, I think it was fate.
- Two. - The guy who's after me...
is a lot closer to us than we think.
I'd like to protect you guys...
just like how you both protected me in our past lives.
Three.
Darn it. I knew it.
Ji A!
Come to your senses, you brat.
Why do you have so much blood on your hands?
There's blood all over your nice clothes.
Sae Rom?
Yes, it's me. Do you recognize us?
Jae Hwan.
I'm okay.
I didn't get hurt at all.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay. We're all fine. That's what matters.
It's okay.
What am I going to do?
- What am I going to do? - You'll be fine.
How do you plan to attack that old woman who guards the Samdo River?
How much do you know about her?
I know she can easily turn...
a mountain spirit into a rock with the blink of an eye.
And I heard she can see miles ahead of her.
About that power she has to see miles ahead...
How far do you think she can see?
For example, do you think she knows how I look?
It's not a surveillance camera.
She's just able to catch the overall flow of how things go.
For example, she may not be able to hear our conversation.
But she's probably able to tell that we're together right now.
So she doesn't know everything in detail?
If we block her sight, we might be able to win.
How?
This is what you used to make me fall asleep.
Rang only took a small sip, but it worked pretty well.
Do you think she'll drink this?
She might.
That is, if we use the one person she trusts.
Who's that?
Hyeonuiong.
I heard he does everything his wife tells him to do.
Not anymore.
He disobeyed her and saved Ji A. That's good enough to prove that.
So he's going to put her to sleep before we get there?
Once she falls asleep,
you can take care of her.
- When are we going to do this? - Tomorrow.
Meet me there at noon.
Once it's all done,
you gain control over the Samdo River as we promised,
and your ill-fated relationship with me and Ji A will end there.
Okay.
I wonder why I'm so worried.
Things are going a lot smoother than I thought.
No, what matters is that he took the bait.
I just need to take him to the Samdo River.
Didn't they once have a son?
How do you know that?
I just know.
How do you think this story will end?
It's going to be a happy ending no matter what.
Our station president came.
He had the same disease as Sae Rom.
He said he could live if he killed me.
Where is he?
He's dead.
I shot him.
I turned into Imoogi, and...
He defied death and lived for centuries.
He wouldn't have made it past today even if you hadn't shot him.
I almost killed Jae Hwan too.
I finally came to my senses, but...
You did well. You did.
I'm so scared.
It's almost over.
It'll be over tomorrow.
Don't you need to urinate?
I don't do things like that much.
You're lying in bed in my place of business.
Why are you being shy?
Why are you so good to me?
You even closed the restaurant because of me.
People come and go in your life. That's how it is.
You said you lost your husband a long time ago, right?
What was your husband like?
Even if we shared one small fish together,
he'd debone it and give me some first.
Once, it was the middle of winter.
I said I wanted honey-filled rice cakes,
and he climbed over a snowy hill just to get them for me.
He could've just called a delivery service.
Why did he do that? He's a bit over the top.
What about you?
Why do you keep coming to me?
Whenever I eat your food,
my heart...
gets all tickly.
It feels very familiar, and it feels like it's something...
I've missed.
How many souls crossed over the river last night because of Imoogi?
903?
Call in the emergency staff, and tell them to hang on one more night.
Honey!
For when my honey's eyes are tired.
To soothe my honey's temper.
It's good for when my honey has a stomachache.
Is something wrong?
Granny's arthritis medicine...
has probably run out now.
Whatever. I don't care. Whatever.
Go home.
You've rebelled long enough.
- Forget it. - You know you'll regret it.
I'm already regretting it.
Why did I think I could change her?
Why couldn't I leave her when I lost my son?
- Because you loved her... - I did.
I thought it was love.
Our personalities, preferences... We had nothing in common.
We couldn't even share a plate of tteokbokki together.
I always got mild, and she got the spiciest.
Couldn't you split a medium spicy?
That's married life.
We were just too different.
So? Will you just watch?
You said Yeon may die...
in that lady's place.
There's no other reason for Granny to keep her alive.
- Stop him. - If he would listen to me,
things wouldn't have come this far.
But we can't...
lose Yeon like this.
(Yeon)
Hey, what's up?
Let's meet.
Say it over the phone. I'm ready to hear it.
It's too long to say it over the phone.
I just met with Imoogi.
You did?
Okay.
What's with that reaction?
Is that girl dead or alive?
What do you mean?
Why would you swallow his scale?
Because if I do, Imoogi, who's inside of Ji A,
will transfer over to me.
- And then? - I'll take him with me...
and jump into the Samdo River.
No. Definitely not.
I'm sure there's another way.
It isn't...
just Ji A.
Countless lives being lost...
because of this plague are at stake as well.
I thought about every possibility available,
and this is the only way to catch him.
Then I'll do it.
I'll swallow his scale and jump into the Samdo River.
You can't handle Imoogi.
Don't do it.
Please, don't do it. You can't even save your soul then.
You can't be reincarnated or anything.
- I know. - Then please!
Can you not say you're going to die?
Shin Ju.
You must...
understand me.
I'm telling you everything because it's you.
You're so mean.
You're so mean to me.
What brings you here?
Thanks for the gift.
- The gift? - You sent our president to me.
Why didn't you tell Yeon if you knew?
Because I would've done the same.
If I were you, I would've told Yeon long ago.
I did not, and I don't plan to.
Why not?
Because Yeon cherishes you.
Because he'll be sad if he loses you.
Do you even know what it means...
for Yeon to team up with Imoogi?
- What does it mean? - He plans to save you and die.
Because of you,
Yeon will die.
Yeon is planning to die in order to save me?
Isn't it obvious?
Which gets me to my point...
Give me one reason why I shouldn't kill you...
here and now.
If it's your wish, I won't stop you.
But I don't want to encourage it.
You'll either die or get hurt.
Someone else just tried it.
I'll be straightforward with you.
I don't intend to die.
At least not yet.
"Not yet"?
If by chance, I hurt Yeon,
I will kill myself.
If by chance, I fail,
you kill me.
Yeon won't be able to kill me.
Do you mean it?
Unfortunately, we share a common goal.
Protecting Yeon.
If you want to save your brother, we need a truce for now.
Okay?
Deal.
What do you need me to do then?
Don't get caught up in this battle,
stay alive,
and protect Ji A.
In my place,
you'll look after her.
I will.
And if Rang...
suffers a heartbreak and acts out again,
you'll give him an earful.
Tell him to get his act together.
I will do that until his ears fall off.
Start a family with the necklace thief.
Consider this as a pre-wedding gift.
It's a new apartment in your name.
Thank you for putting up with my temper.
Mr. Lee...
Thanking you for all your troubles...
That I won't do.
I made up for it by paying for your expenses.
Mr. Lee,
may I ask you one thing?
When I was being chased by the mountain spirit I served,
why did you save me?
For payback.
I had bibim noodles with your mountain spirit once...
and he had the audacity to steal my boiled egg.
That's why you saved me?
It wasn't for nothing, you know. You see,
I always save my boiled egg to enjoy it at the very end.
What's the meaning of this?
Why should a bowl of naengmyeon carry meaning?
Why are you treating me to this all of a sudden?
You're buying, actually. I skipped lunch today.
As if I don't know how you think.
Can we just eat without this giving me indigestion?
It's true that you only add mustard and no vinegar.
What?
Ki Yu Ri. That's what she said.
You only add mustard in your naengmyeon.
Did she say that?
One needs to be attentive to know that, you know.
Well, I saved her life.
If I hadn't saved her, she would've starved...
or been beaten to death at the zoo.
What's with that kid at your house though?
It's Geomdoong, my dog from my past life.
I don't care if he was your dog back then.
You can't take him away from his current parents like that.
His stepfather has been beating him, and that made me angry.
- Why are you laughing? - It's funny, that's all.
For someone who's been causing mayhem like the Joker,
it's funny to know that you've been doing good deeds too.
- Shut it. - Look at you all grown up now.
Bedwetter.
I'll kill you, you know.
Give me your egg if you're not going to eat it.
You don't have to look overtly unhappy, you know.
I hate being here with you.
I want to go home.
Home?
As if you have a home to go back to.
You attacked Lee Rang with your own hands...
and Shin Ju ended the relationship with you yesterday.
No one will want you back.
You're wrong. Mr. Lee will be waiting for me.
Shin Ju too.
Actually, this is where you belong.
You've been beaten by a human, haven't you?
For a long time too until your soul ended up ragged.
I see the darkness in you.
Don't read people like that.
It's what makes you freakier.
A thing like you...
will only spread misfortune to Lee Rang or Shin Ju.
Like me.
So don't bother with the wishful thinking.
No one will come to save you.
I speak from experience.
Is that naengmyeon that good?
At least it tastes good.
I still don't get what you see in that girl.
For what reason are you willing to give up your life for her?
She saved me in my past life.
She died for me.
If I don't stop her,
she'll give up her own life...
to save mine again.
She always keeps her promises, you see.
Then let her save you.
That's what she wants.
No way.
My pride can't handle her saving me twice.
Crazy jerk.
So? You'll die instead of her?
Rang, join me tomorrow.
- Where? - To Samdo River.
To end Imoogi.
I need you there to prevent...
any unexpected things from happening.
What are you planning?
There's no need to know the details.
Just be there to help things go as planned.
I'll think about it.
Hey, I saved your life twice, you know.
- There's no need to be calculative. - I'm glad you said that.
Is that all the reaction you can give to your brother?
Shouldn't you shed a tear when I could actually die?
You won't though.
It's not like you're mortal.
A nine-tailed fox can't die so easily.
The clear sky sure is nice.
It won't be a bad day for the world to end.
What are you and Mr. Lee planning to do?
Didn't you hear everything...
that we discussed?
So you'll really end up being an almighty?
What comes afterwards, then?
I'll rule the world...
and take Ji A for myself.
That's not what you promised!
What he requested can't be granted.
I'm sure Lee Yeon feels the same way.
That's why you should accompany me to Samdo River.
Why should I go there?
Just in case he doesn't come alone. I'll need you to keep them occupied.
- What if I don't want to? - I wasn't asking for your opinion.
Maybe I should call Lee Rang and Shin Ju.
It'll be over if I suggest suicide.
You know you can't disobey me.
Just kill me instead, darn it!
That's not how things work.
If I kill you,
they won't get to see you in despair.
What brings you here?
I may only be a mere cook,
but I can't sit back and watch Mr. Lee Yeon die.
Just sit back...
and watch.
This isn't something you can prevent.
But I can't.
What?
Snail Bride,
where are you right now?
The bridge between the Afterlife and the Living Realm.
Tell me who I am.
The Lady of Samdo River.
Then,
you must be aware that you just crossed the line.
I'm aware of that.
However, you're not just the Lady of Samdo River.
You're also one's wife,
one's mother, and one's friend.
You're not Bok Gil's mother or my wife.
Just the watchwoman of Samdo River.
You're wrong.
Never have I been...
someone's wife, son, or friend.
Will you be okay...
even after Yeon dies?
- What? - Forget about fate.
I'm asking about how you'll feel.
For a very long time,
Yeon trusted and relied on you.
It's probably because you cared for him that much.
And that's because...
he reminded you of your late son.
Did my husband tell you that?
Then he must've also told you what I did...
to my one and only son.
My son...
also stood there and begged me just like Yeon.
He asked me to let his wife live.
However, I refused to help my son.
And that's why...
you've been beating yourself up all these years.
How dare you?
I'm sorry if I crossed the line. But...
Say one more word,
and I'll make sure you'll never be able to cook again.
(Glucosamine)
I was told to give you this.
Please...
don't give up on Yeon or your husband.
(Glucosamine)
Where are we off to this time?
You don't need to come.
I'll tell you what you need to do once I'm back.
What? You said that to Yu Ri?
She used you?
It was a mistake.
Yu Ri told me she didn't care whether those people died or not.
They're Ji A's parents, so why would she care?
You crazy punk. How dare you treat Yu Ri that way?
She's already risking her life because of me.
I regret what I said to her.
But I don't know how to reach her, and there's no way to apologize.
You're doomed now.
She holds a really bad grudge.
Can you talk to her...
The same goes for me.
I will never approve of you and Yu Ri.
Do you think she'll be able to come back safely?
We must do something. Let's go.
Where?
Yu Ri, it's me.
Your car's outside, so I'm guessing you're there.
I don't care if he's with you, so just listen.
You're in for some trouble once you return home.
Who said you could go live with him?
Things are so uncomfortable without you.
No one's around to buy me naengmyeon.
And the little kid put stickers all over me. He drives me nuts.
You came all the way here to say that?
What if she's not listening?
- Should we just barge in? - No.
Yeon will get furious if he finds out.
Then let me say something as well.
Yu Ri, don't ever forgive him.
Yu Ri.
I'll save my apology for later.
I hope you return safely.
Don't listen to a word he says.
Just make sure you stay safe.
You see, I was...
planning on proposing to you...
- once you returned. - Stop it.
What?
Yu Ri.
I'll save you.
Just hang in there until tomorrow.
- I'll also protect... - That's enough. Let's go.
No, wait.
Guess who.
I can tell who you are just by looking at these hands.
What if it's someone else pretending to be me?
Then my heart wouldn't be beating so fast like right now.
I'm impressed by your lines.
Are you sure you stayed single for 600 years?
Yes, of course.
I only have eyes for you.
You're all I see.
What are we doing today?
Today, we're going to go on a date just like a normal couple.
You can look forward to it.
This is what normal couples do. I'll walk by the road.
Why a claw crane?
I've always wanted to do this.
I know I'm rich enough to buy this entire arcade.
But I want to give you something that shows my effort.
Watch.
Don't fight the machine. You need to go along with it.
Like this.
This is so cute.
- Let's try one more time. - Try it again.
Help.
Like this. There.
Should I press the button?
It's working.
Ta-da.
It's not going in.
No, no. Wait.
- Hold the ball like this. - Let go.
This is a fight between me and this machine.
Move. Move.
How do you like your mint chocolate?
It's nice and fresh.
It's as if I have an entire forest in my mouth.
How do you like your vanilla?
It's sweet.
This tastes like honey too.
Why don't we switch?
How about we mix it instead?
I think I love you a lot.
I've lived for so long.
And I have a vague memory of all the people I've met.
But I remember every single moment I spent with you.
Don't forget me.
Ever.
How could I forget this face?
I love you, Yeon.
Was that it?
Did you not leave me?
Did I abandon you?
Is that why I ended up this way?
I swore over and over that I wouldn't forgive you.
But it turns out...
I couldn't forgive myself.
What kind...
of mom was I?
What did you wish?
That you'll be safe.
That you won't get hurt, sick...
or cry.
How selfish.
And that you could forget everything...
if something beyond our control happens.
No. I'll wait for you.
Just as you waited for me.
No, don't.
A human being's life is too short.
What did you wish?
I wished that a very kind deity exists...
somewhere in this world,
and prayed for something like a miracle.
And I wished...
the deity to save us both.
Hi, Granny.
What? Now?
What did you mean?
I've been smoking for very long.
There were only two people who nagged me to quit.
- You, and... - And the other was your son.
He was the kindest kid.
But...
when his wife died, he never spoke again.
I wish he would've just resented me openly.
And then he jumped into the Samdo River?
He left the shoes I made him nicely on the riverbank.
That jerk.
As if he wanted me to see them.
As if to say he wouldn't forgive me even after he died.
You're wrong.
He was so sad when he was going to meet his dead wife,
but he didn't want the shoes to get wet.
I'm an expert in that field.
I'm planning to quit smoking.
Do you mean it this time?
I've lived long enough. I want to try something different.
What do you mean?
I'm saying there's a way to put an end to this...
without either you or that girl dying.
What is it?
Good work everyone.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Get home safely.
- Good night - Good night.
Let's go.
(Staff Only Admittance)
When Imoogi comes here tomorrow,
stab Ji A with this sword.
Stab her enough to kill her.
- What? - When she's almost dead,
Imoogi's other half in Ji A's body will try to escape her body...
before she dies.
- What about the scale? - Don't use it.
Let him transfer into Imoogi's body.
Once the divided Imoogi becomes one,
I'll turn it into stone.
But what if Ji A ends up really dying?
I'll save her.
I'll be punished as well for breaking a taboo.
Granny.
Don't say anything sappy, and bring them here on time.
Both her and Imoogi.
You know, I knew from the start that you weren't all bad.
Get off of me, kid.
I enjoyed the performance.
Thank you.
I see you're not human either.
You've got a sharp eye.
Human or not, the park is closed now.
I'm looking for something.
If you've lost something, check Lost and Found.
There's no need.
I've just found it.
What is it?
The mirror of the moon.
After my mom passed away,
I felt like I was left all alone in this world.
But I wasn't lonely at all...
because I had you and Jae Hwan.
Thanks.
Hang in there.
Please.
Ms. Nam.
Yes?
You need to take this.
Is someone close to dying?
Where are you?
Very close to where you are.
Finally, you're here to see me.
- Where's the antidote? - Why are you worried about others?
You're day to day yourself.
Where is the antidote?
There is no such thing.
I was born from the plague, so I know how to kill people,
but I never learned how to save them.
You scumbag.
You'll die soon.
I want you to die and rot in the Underworld.
This is why I like you.
Even though you can barely keep your own soul dominant,
you still won't give in.
- You'll be mine in the end. - As if.
I'd rather die than let you have me.
From this moment on, you'll truly wish you were dead.
Show yourself.
Don't join forces with Lee Yeon.
Those imbeciles are plotting something.
It doesn't matter.
Besides, you have a job to do.
What are you doing here?
The governor was attacked.
What?
What are you talking about?
Who attacked him?
Imoogi.
He survived,
but he lost something important.
You're him, aren't you?
Now comes the quiz.
What exactly was taken from the governor?
The mirror of the moon.
How...
How is it that you have his face?
It's the face you missed, isn't it?
The poor child you killed.
Your one and only son.
My Bok Gil...
When being reincarnated,
I selected the shell that'd stir something in you.
I had a feeling this day would come.
How can you know about my son?
Here comes the next question.
Why do you think my other half went after the mirror of the moon?
No... Granny!
- You're staying here with me. - No...
Shin Ju.
- Why... - Because I was summoned.
Someday, when the Imoogi in her calls for you...
You'll become my soldier.
Bok Gil was a sweet kid, you know.
Others found me repulsive,
but he came up to me to talk.
I felt like I had a friend for the first time.
Did you know this though?
I was the one...
who planted the plague in his wife.
Why...
Why did you do such a thing?
Because he seemed so happy.
Darn you!
Let's go. We need Granny.
- It's too late. - Snap out of it, Ji A!
We can both survive this. For the first time, there's hope.
Darn, my head.
- Mr. Lee! - Shin Ju, stay out of this.
Rang, come with me.
- I'm sorry, we... - Later!
You were only compelled by him, that's all.
Take Ji A with you.
Just a second.
Let go. I can get there myself.
Where's Granny?
Where is she?
Did you get her?
It truly is a treasure of a mountain spirit.
Showing up with her son's face...
made her lose her reason.
You can call her the spirit of spirits all you want.
As long as she harbors a human's heart,
she'll always have a weak spot.
This was your plan all along.
It's all your fault, Yeon.
Because you didn't give up,
innocent people had to die as well as the old lady.
And now, Ji A is dying too.
Ji A...
Please.
Even in this state, you can't lay a finger on me.
So just give up your body and die.
You're out of options now.
This is the only way to save Ji A.
That's enough.
Let Ji A go.
I'll...
let you have my body.
What are you doing here?
Rang, you can't go inside. I won't let you.
Yu Ri.
I'm here to save you and Yeon.
But if anything happens to Yeon,
I swear I'll kill you.
Don't.
- Ji A. - Don't move.
You're still hanging in there?
No, don't.
Put that gun down. Please.
I'll protect you, Yeon.
No, let me do it.
Goodbye.
No, don't. No!
Come out from that body.
Forgive me. I'm doing this to protect you, Rang.
Yeon.
Don't come near me.
- Yeon! - Stay away!
No!
The Yeon you know is dead.
I won.
What's going on?
I look hideous, don't I?
I wanted to look nice...
before I say goodbye.
But still,
we won.
This is my gift.
When your other half becomes weak,
you become weak as well.
It's the evening primrose from a burial ground.
Yeon!
Darn it.
Rang.
Rang!
It hurts, doesn't it?
You and I are one now.
If you kill me, you'll die as well.
That's exactly what I want.
Rang.
No, I can't.
Pretty soon,
I'll turn into Imoogi.
Let me stay as myself.
Rang.
No.
Save me.
I will be born again.
I will be born again,
and I will find her again.
You don't know what you're talking about.
Once you fall into the Samdo River,
you'll never be able to come back.
No.
I love you.
No!
He smiled.
As if he was relieved...
that he had saved me.
As if this was his happy ending.
I feel like...
I may have heard...
Yeon!
the word "love" at the end.
(Tale of The Nine Tailed)
I can really do anything you ask.
Please tell me...
That will never happen.
Get it together. Mr. Lee told me to give this to you.
You'll get used to it. I'm sure you'll have to walk...
the path we walked together, alone,
but please let me go.
I love you, Ji A.
I heard the rumors and came to see that old man.