From the moment you open an image to process  through Capture One or through Camera Raw,
you begin the process of setting  up your image for retouching.
In this chapter, we will go  over how I set up an image.
Setting up an image correctly is crucial in  setting the tone of the image and its workability
as you go through rounds of  revisions with your client.
These are the steps I take for introducing  images to the world of high fashion and its
partner scrutiny.
As you can see here I have  this image in 16-bit depth.
I process in 16-bit depth, because it gives  us a much better starting point as opposed
to just starting an 8-bit.
Although Photoshop is much more workable in  8-bit, and we will be converting to 8-bit,
the transitions between pixels are much  smoother when you give yourself this starting point.
I also make a couple moves in 16-bit that  help preserve the integrity of the pixels
such as unsharp mask, which  I'm going to do right now.
So Filter, I go down to Sharpen and I go right  to Unsharp Mask, and I start with this formula
right here with the Amount of 100, the Radius  at 1, Threshold at 0, and we'll zoom in right
here, and I'm just going to turn the preview  on and off so you could see the bit of a
pop that it gives it; just a little bit  of a crunch and I use this formula--this was
handed to me from another retoucher, as I  was learning how to retouch, and I have used
it as the base of my sharpening ever since.
This particular kind of sharpening gives it  a little bit of grit that's very similar to
what you'd feel on an actual  prints and not a digital file.
So I like the way this feels, so we're going  to hit OK and zoom on out, and now we're going
to check the image size and I'm at a 20  height, a 300 resolution, and that's good.
If you do need to change the image size  interpolating in 16-bit also gives you the advantage of
preserving the integrity of the  pixels without damaging it too much.
So we're at a good point right now, so I'm  going to now convert it to 8-bit which is
through Image > Mode > 8 Bit.
For my own workflow I have my quick key setup  for Shift+Command+L which just automatically
puts it to 8-bit.
So we have our image now in 8-bit,  and we are ready to start working.
So in our next movie we will be  setting up our color and contrast.
【本字幕由CGSUB.COM独家制作发布】
【www.cgsub.com】