Is the lightning back?
No, this is something else.
- What's that sound?
- I've never heard that before!
Is it them? Is it them?
We gotta go.
Where do we go?!
Robbie, this is your house.
No, no, no, wait!
Are we still alive?
Down here.
Were you on this plane?
Are you--?
Are you a passenger?
How you doing?
Wanna help me open this?
Are you a passenger?
He's deaf.
The shell went off right beside him.
Camera on his shoulder saved his life.
You hear that, Max?
Your stupid camera
saved your stupid life.
Where were you?
Out there in the Pine Barrens.
We were attached to
a National Guard unit.
The 83rd Mechanized.
They moved on one of those things
around midnight.
They got some kind of shield
around them.
You can't see it, but everything we fire
at them detonates too early,
before we can get close enough
to cause any damage.
When they flash that thing,
everything lights up like Hiroshima.
There's more than one?
You gotta be kidding me, right?
We were feeding New York,
but New York went dark.
So we patched over to D.C.,
they went down.
L.A., Chicago, uplinked to London.
Even called the affiliates to try
to get them to catch the feed,
but nobody answers.
It's the same everywhere.
Once the Tripods start to move,
no more news comes out of that area.
My God.
You ain't seen nothing yet.
I saw that storm. I was right
in the middle of one of those.
Well, you didn't see it like this.
Those machines come up
from under the ground, right?
So that means they must've been
buried here a long time ago.
So who's driving the goddamn things?
Watch the lightning.
Watch it.
Keep watching the lightning.
What is that?
That is them.
They come down in capsules,
riding the lightning into the ground,
into the machines, right?
You hear that?
We're getting the hell out of here.
Get in, get in, get in, get in.
Hey, were you on that plane?
That's too bad.
It would've been a really great story.
Look at me. Look at me.
You keep your eyes only on me,
understand?
- Okay.
- Don't look down. Don't look around.
I'm taking you to the car.
You're gonna wanna look around.
But you're not going to.
- Are you?
- No.
You're doing good. You're doing good.
Keep your eyes on me.
I'm going right to Boston.
- We're gonna see your mom.
- I'm not gonna look, Dad.
That's a girl. That's my girl.
Now listen.
- I want you to close your eyes, okay?
- Okay.
Got them closed? There you go.
- Keep them closed for me.
- Okay.
Robbie, get in.
- Robbie, get in!
- Why are you yelling?
It's okay.
Get in.
- Why aren't we on the turnpike?
- I don't want everybody
to see that we've got a working car.
We'll stay along the Hudson
till we find an open bridge or ferry,
then we're gonna cross the Hudson.
We'll take the back roads across
Connecticut, all the way to Boston.
- Where is everybody?
- I don't know, running, hiding.
- In their basements.
- If we had balls, we'd go back
- and find one of those things and kill it.
- Right. Yeah, good.
Why don't you just let me
make the big decisions.
Which would be when? Never, Ray?
- Never's about your speed.
- Stop it.
Enough of the "Ray" shit. All right?
- It's "Dad," "sir,"
- Don't fight.
or if you want, "Mr. Ferrier."
That sounds a little weird to me,
but you decide.
- Dad?
- Yes, Rachel.
I've gotta go to the bathroom.
Really?
- I gotta go.
- Not so fast, not so fast, all right?
There's two things
we gotta watch out for.
And the second is people
who might want our car.
- There's nobody around.
- Yeah. I gotta go.
All right, Rachel?
Rachel, it's good right there.
I'm not going in front of you guys.
- Just go where I can see you.
- Are you crazy?
- Don't look!
- I'm not gonna look.
- Just stay in sight!
- That's looking!
Okay, well, listen, every time
you guys don't listen to me,
I'm telling your mother, okay?
I'm making a list.
Making a list.
- I told you to stay where I could see you.
- Sorry. I'm sorry.
Stop! Stop!
Wait! Stop! Let me on!
Let me on! Give me a hand!
Wait! Stop!
- Stop! Give me a hand!
- Kid, you're gonna get run over!
- Give me a hand! You have room!
- Robbie!
- You wanna go in that direction?
- Stop! Stop!
There's nothing living
in that direction, Robbie.
What do you care?
You never gave a shit before.
- You never gave a shit!
- Okay, hard-ass,
what's your plan, huh?
You're in charge now!
- Tell me what we're doing.
- Catch up with these soldiers!
Hook up with whoever else isn't dead,
and we get back at them.
We get back at them.
That's what we do.
Let's try one that doesn't involve your
10-year-old sister joining the Army.
- You have anything like that?
- Just tell us the truth.
- Wanna try that?
- You have no idea which way to go.
You wanna come off all wise and shit!
You only chose Boston
because you hope Mom is there.
And if she's there,
you can dump us on her.
You can dump us on her, then you'll
only have to care about yourself,
which is exactly the way you like it.
Robbie!
Where are you trying to go?
What are you trying to do?
Who's gonna take care of me
if you go?
This is a test of
the Emergency Alert System.
If this had been an actual emergency,
official messages
from federal, state or local authorities
would've followed the alert tone.
This concludes the test
of the Emergency Alert--
I'll close my eyes.
Why don't you drive for a bit.
I don't have a license.
Since when has that stopped you?
Ray.
Ray! Dad!
You think you could--?
Do you think you could--?
Don't stop.
Don't take your foot off. Okay?
I got it, but keep your foot on.
Okay, I got it. I got it.
- Where is everybody going?
- I don't know, Rach.
But we do, right?
Yeah, we do.
Why did he do that?
- Why is he doing that?
- He wants a ride, Rach.
- Everybody just wants a ride.
- Can we give him one?
Sit back and put on your seat belt.
Robbie, put on your seat belt.
Put on your seat belt, Rachel.
- Be careful.
- How'd you fix this?
- How'd you fix the car?
- Please! Why won't you help us?
I'm sorry, I can't. I can't.
Please, get away from the car.
Hey! Stop the car.
- Stop the car!
- Get off the car!
You could carry 20 people in there!
- Stop the car!
- Get off the car!
Stop the car!
Hold on.
Look out!
Watch out! Hold on!
Are you okay?
No, wait! Wait!
No! Just wait! Okay! Wait! Stop!
- Just stop!
- Daddy!
Rachel!
Get out of there!
Robbie!
- Ray!
- Get in the car!
- Help!
- Rachel! Get out of the car!
Rachel, get--
Get out of the car.
- Get out!
- Daddy!
- Take it easy!
- Get off the car!
Get off!
Get off the car! Move!
Move!
- Where's my son?
- You don't need that, man.
- Where's my son? Robbie!
- Cool down, man.
- Put the gun down, man.
- Robbie!
Dad!
Okay, now, listen.
- Put down the gun. I'm taking the car.
- My daughter's in the car.
- I'm taking the car, man.
- Please. All I want--
- Put down the goddamn gun!
- All I want is my daughter.
- I'm taking the car, man.
- Please, I just want my daughter.
Let me just take my daughter.
Can I--?
- All I want is my daughter.
- Yeah. Okay, go ahead, man.
Robbie.
Take me with you!
Have you seen this girl?
This is my daughter.
He needs his medicine.
We've got it the worst,
that's what I heard.
The U.S., mostly.
South America and Asia, some.
There's nothing going on in Europe.
Europe got the worst of it,
that's what everybody's saying.
- Completely wiped out some of it.
- I don't give a shit who it is.
I got up close to one of those things
in Stanfordville.
If they're all over the place,
we're dead.
- Looks like the power's still on here.
- Yeah.
Yeah, power's still on.
Because nothing bad's come up
from the ground.
- Hold on. Hold on, move back!
- Watch out there, lady!
I said, move back!
Unless you are O-positive
and RH-negative,
thank you very much, but we already
have more blood than we can use.
Again, if you are O-positive,
RH-negative, identify yourselves.
If you are not, thank you very much.
We already have more blood
than we can use for the transfusions.
Let's go, folks.
This way. This way.
Keep it moving.
Keep it moving. This way.
Let's go, folks. Keep it moving.
Please move forward calmly.
The boat can make more than one trip.
I
Please move forward calmly.
Take your time. Don't rush.
Ray! Ray! Ray!
- Sheryl?
- Yeah. Hey.
Oh, my gosh, is this your--?
- Are these your kids?
- Rachel.
Hi, I'm Sheryl.
This is my daughter, Nora.
- Nora. I've heard about you, Nora.
- Hi.
- This is my son, Robbie.
- Just like Dad.
- It's good to see you as well.
- Trees are funny.
We're gonna move a few cars out
of the way to make some more space.
You're gonna have to give us
a few minutes.
But don't worry,
there'll be plenty of room for everybody.
We got sick people here.
Let us on.
Cast off. Get that ramp up.
Cast off now. Get that ramp up.
Cast off.
No more people. No more people.
We're taking the ramp up.
Stay close. Stay close.
Everybody stop. Everybody stop.
- Wait, wait, wait. Just--
- Back up. Back up.
- There's room.
- Just stay back.
No more room.
There's no more room.
Just listen to me.
There's three of us.
- Five. There's only five of us.
- There's no room.
Okay, man, just don't push me.
- Sir, there's no more room.
- There's plenty of room.
- There's room for hundreds more.
- Sir--
- Everybody, wait.
- Hold on.
- You just stay with me.
- Okay.
Grab my jacket.
Everybody back up.
Back up.
I got you, Ferrier.
- Oh, Jesus.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
- Okay, Jesus. Oh, my God.
Watch out.
Come on.
Oh, Ray.
Ray!
Come on. Come on.
Go. I can go with him.
Sheryl?
Go with them. Go.
- Ray.
- Sheryl?
- Everybody--
- There's room on the boat.
- Let us through, goddamn it.
- There's still room on the boat.
- She's a child.
- Robbie.
- There's room on the--
There's still room on the boat.
There's room on the boat.
- Robbie.
- Just stay with me.
Stay with me, Robbie.
Robbie!
- Robbie, Robbie.
- Robbie!
Robbie!
- Robbie.
- Come on.
Here. Grab my hand.
Here. Hold on.
I got you. Hold on.
Take my hand.
Take it. Take my hand.
Here!
Oh, my God.
Robbie!
Swim. Swim this way!
- Robbie, help me with her.
- Here, Rach.
Don't stop. Don't stop.
Don't stop.
Oh, my God.
Robbie, slow down.
- Robbie.
- We gotta stay together, Robbie.
Robbie?
Stay together.
Robbie!
Get back here!
No, Robbie!
Come back!
Robbie.
Don't move. Don't move.
Now for God's sake, stay right here.
I'm coming right back.
- Robbie!
- Stop those people.
- Turn around. Turn around.
- Robbie.
Robbie.
What the hell?
Why are you doing this?
Pull back.
Five hundred meters to my 1 0 o'clock.
Jekyll, no effect on target.
No effect.
Roger. No effect.
Our mission, lieutenant,
is to delay their advance
till those refugees get to safety.
Now, keep firing.
You've gotta listen. Turn around!
I want you to listen to me.
Listen to me.
Go back down the hill!
All of you, just turn around!
- Don't do this. I know you wanna fight.
- I wanna be here.
I need to see this.
It seems like you have to,
but you don't.
- Please, let me go.
- You don't.
Okay. Wait. Wait.
What are you doing here
all by yourself?
Sweetie, you gotta come with us,
please.
No. My dad's getting my brother.
I have to stay here.
- You can't stay here.
- Gotta go.
- I'm not gonna leave her alone.
- Leave.
I'm not letting you do this.
You can hate me.
- You can hate me.
- Let me go.
- But I love you.
- Please.
- I'm not letting you do this.
- Dad.
I can't. No. Please.
Please don't pull me.
It's gonna be okay. You need
to come with us. It is not safe--
Please. I can't go with you.
- My dad's right there.
- Please, come.
- Please, my dad's right there.
- Listen to me--
I need to be here. I want to see this.
Wait. Wait-- Just stay for Rachel.
Stay for your sister.
Please, let me go.
You need to let me go.
All right. Okay. All right.
- You're coming with us.
- Dad.
- We're going now.
- I can't.
Dad!
Dad.
Let me go! Dad!
Guide on. Guide on.
Black Six. Attack. Attack. Attack.
Stop.
- That's my dad.
- I'm her father. I'm her father.
- We're so sorry.
- We thought she was alone.
- She was standing by the tree--
- She's fine. Let's go! Let's go!
Robbie.
Robbie!
Over here.
Over here!
Hurry.
Are you all right?
Hey.
What about you, huh?
There you go.
Is that comfortable?
I need you to close
your eyes now, okay?
You need some sleep.
Dad?
He's gonna meet us.
Hey. Robbie's gonna meet us, Rach.
In Boston, at your grandma's.
What do you think
Mom's doing right this minute?
Mom?
Boston. She's waiting.
And I know she's not sleeping,
because she is so worried about you.
And she's in Grandma's kitchen,
and she's...
She's making that awful tea
she makes.
And they're all just...
They're all just counting the minutes
until they see you again.
What is this?
I won.
You won?
The walk, trot and canter.
Third place.
Sing me "Lullaby and Goodnight."
I don't know that one.
Sing me "Hushabye Mountain."
I'm sorry, Rach. I don't--
I don't know that one either.
I'm not bragging, babe
So don't put me down
'Cause I got the fastest
Set of wheels in town
Something comes up to me
They don't even try
'Cause if I had a set of wings
Man, you know she could fly
She's my little deuce coupe
You don't know what I got
Just my little deuce coupe
Peach schnapps.
Disgusting, I know it.
Found a whole case of this shit.
Thank you.
I'm sorry about your son.
We got separated. He's--
He's gonna meet us in Boston.
Did you--?
Did you lose anybody?
All of them.
Harlan Ogilvy.
Ray Ferrier.
I got water.
Food enough for weeks.
You're welcome to stay. Both of youse.
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna get some sleep.
Those machines, those...
...Tripods they got?
They buried them.
Right under our feet.
Since before there--
There were even people here.
They've been planning this
for a million years.
We're beat to shit.
Please.
- My daughter--
- Think about it.
They defeated the greatest power
in the world in a couple days.
Walked right over us.
And these are only the first.
They'll keep coming.
This is not a war
any more than there's
a war between men and maggots.
This is an extermination.