>> Jack: I've made mistakes,
horrible mistakes.
But I regret them.
I'm truly remorseful.
So I'll confront what happened
head-on.
I'll admit what I've done,
get it out there,
nothing hidden.
I will fight crimes
against women.
I'll make a clean environment
a key part of my platform.
>> Jennifer: I don't care about
your platform, Jack.
I care about you.
But the big issue is,
when Eve was urging you to run
for mayor, did she bother to
remind you about any of this,
Jack?
>> Jack: No.
>> Jennifer: Right!
Because she has an agenda.
It's not about you.
It is all about Eve.
It always is, Jack.
Why are you letting her use you?
>> Jack: At least she
supports me.
It's more than you're
willing to--
>> Jennifer: I'm trying
to protect you.
>> Jack: Protect me--
>> Jennifer: Yes.
>> Jack: I got that. I got that.
Don't you think I'm smart enough
to see through Eve?
>> Eve: What the hell are you
doing here?
>> Xander: You and I have
unfinished business.
>> Jennifer: Jack,
I did not call you stupid.
>> Jack: Naive, maybe?
>> Jennifer: But you can only
remember the last
couple of months...
>> Jack: Mentally challenged,
perhaps?
>> Jennifer: Because Eve wants
you to see the sides of Eve
that she wants you to see.
>> Jack: Because you know
better.
>> Jennifer: I do know better.
She's been doing this to me
since high school, Jack.
So if you don't believe me,
ask anybody.
Really, as anyone.
>> Jack: At least she believes
in me; she has confidence in me.
Eve thinks I'd make
a terrific mayor.
>> Jennifer: She doesn't care
who the mayor of Salem is, Jack.
Are you kidding me right now?
She's pushing you to be mayor
because she wants something.
>> Jack: You really hate
her guts.
>> Jennifer: I don't hate her.
I hate what she's doing to you.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
>> Eve: How the hell did you
get in here?
>> Xander: Don't you know?
I can get in
anywhere I want.
And once I'm in,
I can take anything I want.
>> Eve: What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
[cell phone beeps]
♪ ♪
>> Leo: Don't stop on
my account.
>> Sonny: [sighs]
[soft knocking]
>> Marlena: Oh, hi there.
>> Will: Hi.
Um, any news from John?
Any update on Leo's mother?
>> Marlena: Well...
I spoke to him this morning.
He wishes he had more to go on.
>> Will: Huh.
>> Marlena: Oh, honey.
I know how much this means
to you.
>> Will: It's just that Leo is
driving Sonny crazy.
>> Marlena: Yeah, well, Leo
is despicable.
>> Will: Agreed.
You know, Sonny says the only
time he's ever seen Leo
vulnerable is when he was
talking about how much
he hated his mother.
>> Marlena: Hmm.
I just hope all this pays off
for you and Sonny.
>> Will: Well, if it doesn't,
we're both kind of
out of ideas.
>> Sarah: I was so angry at Rex,
and then you rejected me, and--
>> Eric: I was trying to stop
you, Sarah.
I was trying to stop you from
doing something you will regret.
>> Sarah: Well, it didn't feel
that way.
It gutted me.
Because all I saw was a guy that
I have come to know and--
>> Eric: And what?
What is it?
>> Sarah: It's just...
you've been...
[door opens]
>> Rex: Huh.
What the hell
is going on between you?
>> Eric: Nothing.
>> Rex: Oh.
Sorry, my bad.
You're just...
holding hands and looking
soulfully into each other's eyes
for no reason?
How long?
How long has this been
going on behind my back?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
>> male announcer: Like sands
through the hourglass,
so are the "Days of Our Lives."
[soft orchestration]
♪ ♪
>> Will: You know Leo told Sonny
that he wishes he could pay
somebody to get rid of his
mother for the rest of his life?
>> Marlena: Whew, wow.
Those are very strong words.
Oh, John would like to know if
Sonny has any more information
past what he knew after
that first conversation.
>> Will: [sighs]
Apparently, um, Leo had been
drinking heavily that day,
which is why he opened up.
And now he's just back to
ruining Sonny's life.
>> Marlena: Hmm, I'm so sorry.
You know that John is doing
all that he can.
>> Will: I-I mean, you know,
we both know it's a long shot.
>> Marlena: And with any luck,
maybe Leo's mother can give us
some insight as to why Leo is
the way Leo is.
>> Will: I can give you
some insight.
Leo was the scum of the earth
when he was born,
and he, uh, stayed that way.
>> Marlena: I know this seems
insurmountable.
But you'll find a way
to get through it.
You know, when two people
love each other the way
you and Sonny do,
you find a way.
I do know that from experience.
>> Will: Keep saying that.
>> Marlena: I will keep
saying that.
>> Will: You know...
um, the best part about, uh,
getting my memory back
was remembering
how much you mean to me.
>> Marlena: Oh.
You are the child of my child,
and I love you with all
my heart.
>> Will: I love you too.
You have always been there
when I needed you.
>> Marlena: Always will be.
>> Sonny: Knock it off.
>> Leo: What is with you?
>> Sonny: You.
>> Leo: What is so strange
about me wanting to sleep
with my husband?
>> Sonny: Maybe because you
blackmailed me into marrying you
and I hate your guts.
>> Leo: Oh, that.
>> Sonny: Look, I try to keep up
appearances in public.
I don't get down on you
for spending all of my money
and drinking all the alcohol
in the house.
But when we're alone
like we are right now,
I don't want any part of you.
>> Leo: There were parts of me
you used to want pretty badly.
>> Sonny: Get out of here.
>> Leo: Oh, come on.
I'm not that hard on the eyes,
and I am a rock star in bed.
>> Sonny: If you want
to sleep with someone,
sleep with someone.
It's not gonna be me.
>> Leo: [sighs]
I can't take this anymore.
It's bad enough your cousin
turned me down.
Now my own husband.
>> Sonny: Wait a minute.
Are you talking about Xander?
>> Xander: The only thing I took
from here is what you owe me.
>> Eve: No, I don't
owe you a damn thing.
>> Xander: Actually, you do.
We had a deal, and I
came through for you.
I found Jack, and now
you're lording it all over
his ex-wife and kids.
But you promised to give me
something that would force
Victor to make me CEO of Titan.
Well, that ship has sailed.
He just gave the job to your ex.
>> Eve: Brady?
>> Xander: I didn't think
you'd like the sound of that.
>> Eve: Well, I certainly like
it a hell of a lot better
than the sound of you as CEO.
>> Xander: You didn't hold up
your end of the bargain.
>> Eve: I did, Xander.
I gave you what you asked for,
but you're the one that blew it.
>> Xander: Hmm.
Eve, don't you know that I never
give up?
>> Eve: Oh, you son of a bitch!
>> Xander: I've got Dr. Rolf's
diary now,
the one that explains
how to get Jack's memory back.
So I think that makes you
my bitch.
Wouldn't you agree?
>> Eve: Give--
>> Rex: I've been honest
with both of you,
and you both told me off,
and I took it,
said I deserved it
because I did.
Man, you know, I've been--
[laughs]
I've been sensing that there's--
there's been something
going on with you two.
So right now,
all I'm asking for
is that you're as honest with me
as I've been with you.
>> Eric: Sarah, I know
you're mad.
>> Sarah: Rex slept
with my sister, which is
the worst kind of betrayal
imaginable, and I want him to
know what that kind of betrayal
feels like.
And I know that this is gonna
make me feel a whole lot better.
>> Eric: What you walked in on
may have looked suspicious,
but it wasn't.
There's nothing going on
between Sarah and me.
>> Rex: Then why do you look
so nervous?
>> Sarah: This is just how I
look when I'm accused
of something that I didn't do.
>> Rex: Oh, yeah?
Then why did I find condoms
in your bedroom?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
>> Sarah: You went through
my stuff?
>> Rex: No, I didn't go through
your stuff.
I just went to your room,
and the condoms were lying
all over the floor.
>> Sarah: Our engagement is
broken, Rex, so whether or not
I have condoms is none of your
damn business.
>> Rex: There it is.
I knew it.
The two of you are just--
>> Eric: She didn't say that.
>> Rex: Oh, so she's just
throwing condoms around her room
for fun, as one does?
>> Eric: No, that's not
what happened.
>> Rex: Then who was it
if it wasn't you?
>> Sarah: Xander!
>> Rex: Uh, wh--
Excuse me?
>> Sarah: Xander Cook.
>> Rex: Isn't that the guy--
>> Eric: That killed Nicole?
Yes, it is.
>> Rex: So that's why
you're so upset.
>> Eric: Oh, I'm more
than upset.
She had a fling with the man who
is responsible for the death
of the woman that I love.
>> Rex: [sighs]
Oh, man, I--
This is not
what I was expecting.
>> Eric: Yeah, well,
neither was I.
>> Rex: Well, how do you...
Why do you know about this?
>> Eric: I don't know.
Just ask her.
I'm out of here.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
>> Jennifer: You just don't
remember anything about
Salem, Jack--
the issues, the--the problems.
>> Jack: I'm researching
all that.
I used to be a newsman.
>> Jennifer: I know.
I didn't say that you weren't
smart or capable, Jack.
I'm just saying if you don't
know who you are,
how can you know this town?
>> Jack: And you think that Eve
is manipulative?
>> Jennifer: Yes!
>> Jack: At least she tells me
what I've accomplished,
what I was good at.
All you do is tell me
about my failings,
how corrupt I was,
how I polluted the town's
water source,
how I poisoned our daughter.
>> Jennifer: Don't you think
it's important for you
to know all of this before you
run for mayor, Jack?
>> Jack: You just don't want me
to run against your good pal
Abe.
>> Jennifer: Don't you say that.
He has been such a good mayor,
no matter what Eve has told you.
>> Jack: [sighs]
Eve tells me what I can do.
All you do is tell me
what I can't do
or shouldn't do.
Well, I'll tell you this.
I'm not turning my back on Eve.
I don't care if you hate her
or not.
>> Eve: That diary--
that diary is mine.
It belongs to me, Xander.
>> Xander: Yours?
>> Eve: Yes.
>> Xander: And how did you
come by it, exactly?
Did Rolf come up to you one day
and say, "Oh, hi, Eve.
Here you go.
Everything tickety-boo?"
Of course he didn't!
You nicked it, just like I did.
Now it's mine.
>> Eve: You're not gonna leave
this room until you
give it back to me!
>> Xander: You want it?
Come get it.
>> Eve: Oh, very--
Xander, give it! Give it!
>> Marlena: Mm, mm-mm-mm-mm.
>> Will: All right, you'll--
you'll--you'll let me know
if you hear anything
from John about--
>> Marlena: Do you need to ask
me that, really?
>> Will: I'm sorry.
I-I'm crazy.
I'm a basket case.
>> Marlena: No.
You're in love.
>> Will: Well, I'll talk to you
soon--I hope.
[both chuckle]
>> Marlena: Oh, where can I
reach you if I need to?
>> Will: Um, I'm gonna grab
some lunch at the pub.
And after that, I'll just--
I'll--I'll keep you updated.
>> Marlena: Okay.
>> Eric: Hey.
I'm sorry. Am I interrupting?
>> Will: No, no, not at all.
I was actually just, uh,
heading out.
It's--it's good to see you.
Good to see you, Uncle Eric.
>> Eric: Hey, you too.
>> Marlena: Come in.
You seem upset.
Is there a problem?
>> Eric: I just don't know if I
need a parent or a shrink.
>> Marlena: Luckily,
you've come to both.
>> Eric: It's, uh--
it's Sarah.
I can't believe what she's done
to me.
>> Sarah: All right, go ahead.
Call me a slut.
>> Rex: Oh, God.
Really, Sarah?
Like, who am I right now
to call you names?
Do I like the fact that you
slept with anybody,
much less Xander Cook?
No.
Do I think I had it coming?
Yeah, absolutely.
>> Sarah: Don't you dare say
that this makes us even,
because I was faithful to you
our entire relationship,
and what did I get?
While I was sitting by the
fireside, you were out there
knocking up Mimi Lockhart
and sleeping with my sister.
My sister!
And you were just gonna marry me
and not tell me any of that!
>> Rex: Listen, I had--
I had no intention
of saying we were even.
In fact, we will never
be even, Sarah.
Unless, of course,
you slept with Eric.
I mean, I-I thought that's
what was going on.
I come in here.
The two of you are--are
holding hands.
You're looking all intimate
and intense.
But he was angry with you,
so I-I-I guess that--
>> Sarah: You guess what?
That revenge sex is
off the table?
>> Rex: He was pretty thrown,
Sarah...
more than I would be.
You see, Eric is the type
of guy, he doesn't--
he doesn't understand
why people do mean, bad things
deliberately.
Me, on the other hand?
Yeah, I understand. I get it.
After what I did to you,
you wanted to hurt me as badly
as I hurt you.
>> Sarah: Pretty much
sums it up.
>> Rex: Problem is, I think
you hurt yourself and Eric
much more than you hurt me.
>> Eve: Give it to me, Xander!
>> Xander: No chance.
This is--
this is way too much fun,
and I think I'm getting
a little turned on, so...
>> Eve: Oh, God.
You...you're a pig.
>> Xander: And you are
a very silly girl
if you think you're getting this
away from me.
>> Eve: How did you even know
I had it?
>> Xander: Because I'm the one
that told you about the bloody
diary in the first place
and then heard Rolf whining
about how he lost it,
and I thought, "It's her."
I knew there was no way
that you would leave this
loose end untied,
because Jack might get
his memory back.
>> Eve: [sighs]
>> Xander: You're making this
whole town dance to your tune
because of me!
Whereas I have absolutely
nothing to show for
all of my hard work...
until now.
So we're going to do things
my way until I get what I want.
>> Eve: God, I can't make
Victor hire you!
>> Xander: Huh.
Well, then...
I'll just have to settle for
mucking up all of your plans,
won't I?
Works for me.
>> Jack: I'm tired of hearing
about a past I don't know
or remember.
And there's no magic potion
that's gonna bring my
memory back either.
>> Jennifer: Actually, there is,
and he's standing
right over there.
>> Jack: Who's he?
>> Jennifer: His name
is Will Horton...
and you two have a lot
in common.
>> Sonny: My Uncle Vic says
you've been sniffing around
Xander ever since he showed up.
You do know he's straight,
right?
>> Leo: I'm desperate,
all right?
I haven't gotten any action
from my husband since way
before the wedding.
All of a sudden, this really
good-looking guy shows up...
often wearing very little.
So yes, in exchange for sex,
I offered up the leverage
I had over you.
>> Sonny: You didn't!
>> Leo: I did.
Figured Uncle Vic would do
anything to get his hands on
those photos I have of you
and Will disposing of my carcass
that he would make Xander CEO.
>> Sonny: Does Xander have
those photos?
>> Leo: No.
He didn't deliver the goods,
so neither did I.
But that does not mean
you are off the hook.
>> Sonny: What does that mean?
>> Leo: It means I'm horny.
And if you don't make me happy--
often--I can still give Xander
those photos.
Or I can give them
to the press...
or to the cops.
So many options, really,
all of them bad for you.
Makes my head spin.
>> Leo: Come on, Sonny.
What's the big deal?
Aren't you sick of living
like a monk?
>> Sonny: Yes, I am
really sick of it.
But sleeping with someone that
disgusts me is not the answer.
>> Leo: I know.
You want meaningful sex with
Will, the love of your life.
But I don't see that happening,
not anytime soon.
And you're a young,
sexy guy with needs.
>> Sonny: Do you really think
you can blackmail your way
into my bed?
>> Leo: A guy's gotta do
what a guy's gotta do.
I have nothing to lose.
But you, you could end up
in prison.
And in prison, you'll be
referred to as "pretty."
Come on, Sonny.
It'll be our secret.
I won't tell Will if you won't.
>> Jennifer: Um, Jack.
Will, you remember Jack, right?
>> Will: Sure.
Yeah, I've--I've known you
all my life.
>> Jennifer: Will got...
caught up in Dr. Rolf's magic,
too, and lost his memory
in the process.
>> Jack: Well, then how do you
know that you've known me?
>> Will: Uh, that's a good
question.
Uh, Rolf actually developed
a serum that could counteract
the--the side effect
of the drug.
>> Jack: You're kidding.
>> Will: Yep, it took a couple
of injections, but then stuff
started coming back to me, and
now I, uh--I remember
everything.
>> Jack: All right.
So--so where is this drug?
Where do I get it?
>> Jennifer: Well, the FDA
has it right now.
Kayla told me that the hospital
had to turn it over to the FDA
for testing, and--and--and it's
just a long process, Jack.
>> Jack: Long. Okay, long.
How long is long?
>> Jennifer: I don't know.
I mean, it could take years,
but--
>> Jack: Years?
Oh, great.
Never--never mind.
>> Will: What about, uh, Rolf's
original notes from his diary?
>> Jennifer: Seth Burns
lost it, apparently.
>> Jack: Oh, this gets better
and better, doesn't it?
>> Jennifer: I know, Jack.
I know.
>> Jack: That--that's all right.
Okay, Will, you tell me,
are you glad that you got
your memory back?
>> Will: Um...
well, it was--it was
a big relief,
but at the same time,
it did make my life
a little more complicated
than it had been.
>> Jack: Complicated,
complicated.
>> Will: Yes.
>> Jack: How?
>> Will: Well, um,
when your memory is a blank
slate, you can kind of--
you can reinvent yourself,
you know?
You can choose who you want
to be.
But when it all comes back,
you have to live with the--
you know, with the memories
of the things that you did
that you regret.
>> Jack: Right.
Right. I got that.
>> Will: But even if you
don't get your memory back,
you don't live in that, uh--
that guilt-free state that
you're in when you first
open your eyes, you know?
>> Jack: Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that phase is over
pretty quick, isn't it?
>> Will: So whether you want to
or not, you know
you hurt people.
Sometimes it's the people
that you really, really love.
>> Xander: Yes.
All I have to do is turn this
over to some deserving soul,
and they'll mix up a big batch
of that serum.
And soon word will spread of
this miracle cure for amnesia,
and Jack will come running
to take his medicine
and then go running back to his
deserving, grateful family.
>> Eve: Ugh.
>> Xander: And poor old Eve,
oh, she'll be stuck out
on her ass again.
Clock's ticking, love.
>> Eve: Xander, what do you
expect me to do?
I'm not the one that blew it
with Victor.
You did that all by yourself.
>> Xander: What you gave me
wasn't big enough to overcome
Victor's hatred.
>> Eve: Oh, my God,
Victor hates me too.
But I had to convince him
that he needed me.
Then we were able to work
together.
I mean, what have you got
to offer him as a CEO?
All you know is
hurting people and killing.
So, you know, why don't you
leave town?
'Cause everybody hates
your guts.
>> Xander: Not everyone.
More than one person
found me quite desirable.
>> Sarah: You heard Eric
before he left.
It's pretty clear that he wants
nothing to do with me.
>> Rex: Well, I'll go talk
to him.
>> Sarah: No.
>> Rex: Let me talk to him.
I'll tell him it's my fault.
>> Sarah: Just let it be.
You've done enough!
>> Rex: Look, just...
Okay, come on,
please don't go anywhere.
I just--
>> Sarah: I just said
I don't want you to talk to him.
>> Rex: I don't want to talk
about Eric.
I want to talk about us
and where we go from here.
>> Eric: Sarah and I, we've
gotten really close since she
came back to Salem, and, uh...
you know, she's been kind to me
after I lost Nicole.
She's been supportive, you know,
when Chloe and I were arguing
about who would raise Holly.
>> Marlena: Yeah.
Y-you said that you--
you can't believe what she did
to you.
>> Eric: I found her in bed
with Xander.
>> Marlena: What?
>> Eric: Yeah.
You know, I mean, how could she
do that to herself,
I mean, to me?
>> Marlena: Well, my first
thought is, I'm--I'm not sure
it has anything to do with you.
>> Eric: No, it did.
>> Marlena: Why?
Why do you think so?
>> Eric: Because before she
slept with Xander, she was
trying to have sex with me.
She was determined to make Rex
pay for what he did.
>> Marlena: With Mimi?
>> Eric: No, because he slept
with N--
he slept with Noelle.
>> Marlena: Oh, her sister.
Well, no wonder she was
distraught.
>> Eric: Mom, I wasn't very
sensitive to it at all.
I pushed her away,
and she ran out, and before
I realized what I'd done to her,
I...
[sighs]
She ran back to the Kiriakis
mansion, and there was Xander,
who--who pushed--
he wasn't pushing her away.
He took advantage of her
because he hates me.
I mean, how could he do that,
or how--
>> Marlena: Okay, calm down.
Let me ask you something.
Are you upset because
Sarah slept with the man that--
that killed Nicole
or because Sarah slept
with anybody?
>> Eric: What are you saying?
What, that I'm, like, jealous?
>> Marlena: No, I'm not
saying that.
I'm just asking you
the question.
>> Eve: Well, goody for you,
Xander.
Somebody finds you desirable.
I guess there's a lid
for every pot.
Frankly, I'd rather
slit my wrists
than ever have you touch me.
>> Xander: What I want from you
isn't a shag.
>> Eve: What, you want money?
>> Xander: You don't have enough
of it to make it worth my while.
>> Eve: Well, then what else
is there?
'Cause all you seem to care
about is sex and
your rightful place
in the Kiriakis family.
But that's never gonna happen,
because you blew that
a hell of a long time ago.
>> Xander: All I know is that
you are useful to me...
>> Eve: [sighs]
>> Xander: Especially now.
But I refuse to leave Salem
empty-handed.
But I might lie low for a while.
I've had enough drama.
Right now...
I just want to have a good time.
>> Eve: [sighs]
>> Xander: But I promise,
as soon as I work it out
to use you in my plans,
I'll be in touch.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
>> Rex: Sarah...
I want you to know how ashamed,
embarrassed, humiliated I am
by my behavior.
There's no excuse
for what I did.
>> Sarah: Then why were you
sneaking around in my room?
>> Rex: I wasn't--I wasn't
sneaking around your room.
I went there to look for you
to apologize for everything.
But everybody I know was telling
me, "Don't go over there.
She's not gonna listen to
a damn word you're saying."
And I knew--I knew that they
were right.
But I couldn't help myself,
because...
I cannot stop thinking
about you.
I miss you so much.
The worst part is, I just feel
that what I did
drove you to do something
that's so self-destructive.
I don't want you to turn
to a jerk like Xander Cook.
I want you to turn
to a jerk like me.
>> Sarah: [chuckles]
>> Rex: Look, before you found
out about Noelle and me,
you were gonna give me
another chance.
Is there any way that we can
get back to that place?
'Cause I will do anything,
anything.
Can I just have one more chance?
[somber music]
♪ ♪
>> Eric: But I still love
Nicole.
>> Marlena: Darling, a part
of you always will.
>> Eric: I can't begin to feel
anything for anyone else.
>> Marlena: You can't...
or you think you shouldn't?
>> Eric: What kind of man would
I be if I started to
move on so soon?
>> Marlena: Well, you'd be
human.
Honey, I understand the guilt
you feel...
because Nicole died in that
explosion and you didn't.
But you have to go on
with your life,
even if you don't feel like it.
>> Eric: [sighs]
>> Marlena: You know, if you
have--have formed
a-a-a special friendship
with Sarah...
that is not
a betrayal of Nicole.
Honey, Sarah came along in your
life when you were
really troubled.
She helped you all out.
She helped you work through
all that.
Look...
I do know how much you
and Nicole loved each other.
And I really believe...
she'd want you to be happy now.
♪ ♪
>> Marlena: Honey, I think you
need to talk to Sarah.
There's a lot going on here,
and it's--it's so complicated.
I think you need to...
to get things out in the open.
>> Eric: Yeah, Rex is back
in town.
He really wants to win
Sarah back.
He loves her.
He even wants me to help him
change her mind.
>> Marlena: Well, as I said,
I think you need to talk
to Sarah.
She's got some very big
decisions she has to make.
>> Eric: Rex is my brother.
I don't want to hurt him
the way I hurt Brady.
>> Marlena: Let me ask you
something.
When you and Nicole were
trying to deny your feelings,
do you think that helped Brady?
>> Eric: No.
>> Marlena: Then why do you
think that--that you and Sarah
denying your feelings
is going to help Rex?
>> Rex: Sarah, I will never
lie to you again.
I will never cheat on you again.
I'm saying that from
the bottom of my heart.
>> Sarah: Then why'd you do it?
>> Rex: I-I guess I was afraid.
I was scared of the--of the
commitment that we made.
>> Sarah: What's different now?
>> Rex: I was faced with the
possibility of losing you
forever...
and I don't like that idea.
>> Sarah: So I'm--I'm just
a challenge now, is that it,
'cause nobody dumps Rex Brady?
>> Rex: What? No.
No, that's not--
that's not it at all.
What it is, is that I finally
realized that my life
without you in it
is meaningless.
Sarah, I promise, for the rest
of our lives, I will love you.
I will take care of you.
I will--I will make you laugh.
I'll make you happy.
I will make up for the pain
that I've caused you.
I'm not perfect...
and far from it.
And I know that I'm not the
most patient man in the world.
You know that.
But with this, I will
be patient.
'Cause right now, I am not
deserving of your forgiveness.
I love you.
I love you with everything
I got.
And whether or not you give me
another chance,
that's never gonna change.
>> Sonny: We may have a piece of
paper that says we're married,
but in my heart,
I'm married to Will.
And he and I have been through
way too much for me to betray
his trust with someone like you.
>> Leo: Well, I guess that gives
me the green light to do
whatever I want with those
pictures I have.
>> Sonny: Then go ahead, Leo.
But you need think
about something.
If you turn those photos in
to the cops and to the press,
Will and I may get in trouble,
but you're also gonna lose
everything: this cushy life
you have at the mansion,
the spa days,
the shopping sprees,
the servants,
all the champagne--
everything gone.
Are you ready to say good-bye
to that?
>> Leo: I'll think about it
and get back to you.
Or not.
Maybe I'll just surprise you.
[sly music]
♪ ♪
>> Will: Uh, I-I know I
probably left you with more
questions than answers, but, um,
if you ever want to talk,
I'm around.
And if anybody can understand
what you're going through,
it's me.
>> Jack: Thank you.
Thank you, Will.
>> Will: All right, see you.
>> Jack: Mm-hmm.
>> Jennifer: Thank you, Will,
so much.
>> Jack: So tell me.
Why did you leave it to him
to tell me about a medication
that you knew damn well
I could never get my hands on?
>> Jennifer: You know what?
I have been trying really hard
to understand what you have
been going through, Jack.
And I thought maybe it would
help you
to meet someone who's been
through the same thing.
I thought--I don't know.
I don't know what
I'm trying to accomplish.
I just thought maybe I was
giving you hope.
>> Jack: Hope?
>> Jennifer: Yeah.
>> Jack: Hope, hope, what hope?
Hope for what?
>> Jennifer: Hope to get
your life back.
>> Jack: That's not gonna
happen, is it?
Is it?
>> Jennifer: No...
not to the man you are now,
anyways.
>> Jack: What's that supposed
to mean?
>> Jennifer: It means that you
look like the man that I fell
in love with
and the man that I built
my whole world on...
but you're not that man.
Because the real Jack Deveraux,
he cared about integrity
and love and his family.
Yeah, you've been through
some hard times.
So have I.
We have been through some hard
times together, Jack.
But you know what?
You always, always
found the hope in every
situation, and that's what
you gave me too.
You gave me hope.
But this guy?
This guy standing here
who shrugs and whatever?
I don't know this man.
I don't like this man.
That makes me really sad.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
>> Xander: [sighs]
Hi.
>> Jack: You, I know.
Xander, what the hell
are you doing here?
>> Xander: Oh, I just popped by
to say cheerio.
>> Eve: Yes, Xander is leaving
town, and it couldn't be
soon enough for me.
>> Xander: Careful what you
wish for.
You know...
I really hope it all works out
for you two crazy kids.
[clicks tongue]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
>> Sonny: Oh, good.
You picked up.
>> Will: Something happened.
>> Sonny: Leo was here.
>> Will: Wanting sex?
>> Sonny: He's desperate.
He even propositioned Xander.
>> Will: Xander?
>> Sonny: Leo told Xander
that if he had sex with him,
he would give him something
that would guarantee him
the CEO position.
>> Will: The pictures.
>> Sonny: Exactly.
>> Will: What happened?
>> Sonny: Nothing.
But if I don't cooperate,
he's threatening to take
the pictures to the press
or the cops.
>> Will: Oh, man.
>> Sonny: And I even told him--
I pointed out that if he does
this, he's gonna lose
everything.
I-I just don't know, because
he's a loose cannon, Will.
Hey, what did--what did
your grandma say?
>> Will: That--that John told
her he wishes he had more
to go on.
>> Sonny: I wish he had more
too.
Will, I don't know how much
longer I can deal with this.
>> Will: Do you want me
to come over or--
I mean, or meet you somewhere?
>> Sonny: I would love to see
you more than anything,
but I-I just can't chance it
with Leo, not today.
>> Will: Okay, well,
hang in there.
>> Sonny: I'll do my best.
>> Will: I love you.
>> Sonny: I love you.
♪ ♪
>> Will: [sighs]
>> Marlena: [shuddering]
Hey.
>> Will: What? What? What is it?
>> Marlena: I wanted to tell you
the good news.
John's found Leo's mother.
Oh.
>> Leo: Maybe a little
sex on the beach
will turn the tide
in the right direction.
[doorbell rings]
Xandy?
[clears throat]
Oh, sweet mother of God.
>> Eric: What is this?
>> Rex: You're looking
at a happy man right here,
'cause Sarah has decided
to give me a second chance.
♪ ♪