宗瑜、宗浩的爷爷自制Vobsub IDX/SUB字幕
112 "112"
我是112 This is "112"
112 你为什么不回答? "112", why didn't you reply?
引擎起火 Fire in the engine
我可以用灭火器吗 Can I use the extinguisher?
系好灭火器 Belay extinguisher!
你不能再次发动引擎 You won't be able to start the engine again!
收到 That's affirmative
滑翔至3000英尺 飞机对准田野 Drift down to 3000 feet, aim the plane to the field
然后跳伞 收到吗 And bail out, copy?
收到 滑翔 That's affirmative, drifting down
马克洛夫 飞机准备好了没有?马克洛夫 你聋了吗 Markelov, did you prepare the plane? Markelov, are you deaf or what?
你去掉弹射椅的安全掣了没有? Did you remove the pin from the catapult?
112 列昂诺夫?怎么了 "112", Leonov? What's going on there?
你为什么不回话?我命令你... Why aren't you answering? I order you to...
可恶... 他关闭了引擎 Damn... He turned off the engine
搞什么... 径直驶向跑道 - 是 长官 What the... Drive straight to the runway - Yes, sir
上校同志 委员会来了 - 哪个委员会 Comrade colonel, the committee has arrived - Which committee!
坎曼宁将军 General Kamanin
好像他在启动引擎 It's like he's blowing the engine
快 伙计 快 Come on, buddy... Buddy, come on
走一个 There we go!
坚持 Hold on!
廖谢 Lyoha... Lyoha!
马克洛夫 Markelov...
无赖 Scallywag
中将同志 第294非综合侦察司令... Comrade Lieutenant General! The commander of the 294th non integrated reconnoitring...
稍息 At ease
你在这里做什么 And what are you doing here?
马戏表演 视觉效果不错 Circus performance, you know, with visual effects
廖谢 你没事吧? Lyoha, are you OK?
你为什么不跳?我们脸都灰了 Why you didn't jump? We all almost turned grey!
藏起来 Here, hide it
我们怎么解释 廖谢 And what will we say? Eh, Lyoha?
就说 我们替国家节省昂贵的苏联设备 Well, uh, uh... We'll say we were saving expensive Soviet equipment
快 Come on!
设备太旧... 引擎熄火了 The equipment isn't new... The engine went wack
但我们会处理的 找出谁的责任 But we'll deal with it and find whose that's fault
谁是飞行员? Who is the pilot?
列昂诺夫中尉 Lieutenant Leonov
会与他特别谈话 Well, there will be a special talk with him
说真的 他疯了 Honestly, he's crazy
派他来见我 Send him to me
我们需要这样的人 We're just looking for ones
实验建筑一厅 1963年 Experimental Construction Department No 1. 1963
必须1965年 In 65th!
1965年内 In 65th
你们走吧 You all free
我说 你们可以走了 I said, you are free
1965年 怎么可能? How so, in 65th?
为什么 Why?
原计划是1967年 It supposed to be in 67th
到那年 上升二号百分百准备好 为什么 By that year Voskhod 2 could be prepared hundred-per-cent. Why?
因为美国人已经开始太空计划 Because the Americans have moved their flight
他们正在计划太空行走 抢在我们前面 Now they are planning their spacewalk before us
这不能接受 It's unacceptable
但是让尚未准备妥当的飞船进入太空 But to allow an unprepared product into space
贴着"苏联"的标志 那合适吗 With "USSR" letters on its broadside... Is acceptable?
万一在全世界面前丢脸 合适吗 To fall flat on our face in front of the whole world. Is acceptable?
并收获两具英雄尸体 而不是活着的英雄和宇航员 And get to heroic corpses instead of two alive heroes and cosmonauts
我们将尽可能仔细地准备太空船 We'll prepare the spacecraft as carefully as we can
但时间太短 But the period of time is too short...
两个航天器 Two spacecraft
第一个用于测试 The first one is a test
我们会解决所有的错误 We'll work over all our mistakes on it
然后 上升二号进行实际飞行 And then... Our Voskhod 2 will fly
谢天谢地 我们有两个最好的飞行员 Thank God, we have the two best pilots
你有过多少作战任务? How many combat missions did you have on the front?
别烦我了 廖谢 Stop bugging me, Lyosh
我们正接近跳伞点 We're approaching the disembarking point
上升限度真的很低 风越来越大 The ceiling is really low. And the wind is increasing.
多低? - 上升限度是1300英尺 没有光隙 How low? - Ceiling is 1300 feet, without light gaps
风力12级 阵风 我们要回去吗 The wind is 12 points, gusty. Are we going back?
我们跳 We are
为什么 和风斗 有乐趣 Why? It's fun with the wind
这种风的概率是十分之一 很有乐趣的 抓住机会 With such a wind, it would be fun if out of ten times, at least one was without consequence. Take it!
我们在太空中也能后退吗 Will we back off in space too?
在太空中 会有不同的指令 廖谢 There will be different instructions in space, Lyosh
不然他们为什么选我们? What did they choose us for?
为什么选我们 而不是别人? Why us, why not someone else?
我还没想过呢 I haven't thought about that yet
因为得处理不可能的任务 To handle impossible tasks
吃吧 苹果很好味 Eat, the apple is tasty
我拿回家吃 I'll eat at home
廖谢 你没明白吗 我们现在不跳 Lyosh, you didn't get it? We aren't jumping now
谁说的? - 说明书 Who's to say? - The instructions
别无聊了 伙计 Don't get bored, chap
弗拉德 Vlad!
关舱门 Close
保持镇静 帕夏 Stay calm, Pash
放松 Unwind!
脚并拢 Feet together!
什么 What?
来吧 Come along
快 Come on
廖谢 Lyoha!
不要碰 Don't touch
亲鸟不会回来的 如果被它发现你摸过了 The bird won't come back if it knows that you touched them
这是它的房子吗 Is it its house?
是 It is
它也睡在这里? And it also sleeps here?
谁知道呢 Who knows
但是爸爸 告诉我 鸟儿在哪里睡觉? But dad, tell me, where does the bird sleep?
如果你想知道 你自然会发现的 来吧 If you want to know, you'll find out. Come!
廖谢 Lyoshka!
我们走吧 Let's go
意思正确 但形式不正确 The meaning is correct, but the form is not
缺乏正式用语 There is a lack of formal tone
将军同志 允许发言? - 不 Comrade general, permission to speak? - No
对不起 我可以... I'm sorry, may I ask...
请您下令 让我去探望耶夫中校 Give a decree, so they let me visit lieutenant colonel Belyaev
医生们会决定的 - 他们已经决定... The doctors will decide - They have already decided...
但他不想见任何人 他不高兴 But he doesn't want to see anyone... He's upset
我想保持同志士气 拜托 I want to maintain my comrade's morale, please
你的腿怎么了 - 暂时睡着了 What's with your leg? - Oh, it just fell asleep
列昂诺夫 Leonov
知道我为什么不给你口头警告吗 Do you know why I didn't give you a kick in the pants yet?
不知道 长官 Negative, sir
我也不知道 Neither do I
继续进行培训 - 谢谢 Continue the training activity - Thank you
将军同志 我们会成功的 Comrade general, we'll do it!
帕维尔将离开医院 你会看到的... Pavel will leave the hospital, and you'll see...
赫鲁诺夫少校是你的新搭档 - 为什么 那帕维尔...? Major Khrunov is your new partner - How so? But Pavel...?
请听我说 老实说 那不是他的错 我先跳的 你明白 Please, listen! That's not his fault, honestly. I jumped first, you understand...
我激将了他... - 我知道 我在你的报告里读到了 I provoked him... - I know, I read it in your report
别担心 耶夫同志会休息一阵子 治疗一下 Don't worry, Belyaev will rest for a while, get some treatment
他不年轻了 几乎四十岁 The officer isn't young, almost forty
让他恢复健康 Let him regain his health
但我们没有权利减慢治疗过程 But we have no right to slow down the program
你现在先和赫鲁诺夫上校训练 You are training with Khrunov for now
是 长官 Yes, sir
晚饭快凉了 The dinner is getting cold
看起来像 Looks like it
斯维塔 我告诉过你 "看起来像" Sveta, I've already told you, that "looks like it"
是对艺术家最糟糕的赞美 Is the worst compliment for an artist
对艺术家不算恭维 但你是拿画笔的宇航员 It's not a compliment for an artist, but it's for a cosmonaut with a paintbrush
意思是有潜力成为好艺术家的人 Who, by the way, could have become a very good artist
你挡住了我的光 但是太空呢  Please, you're blocking my light... But what about space?
对于真正的艺术家 为了进入太空 For a real artist, in order to get into space
没有必要乘火箭前往吧 It's not necessary to fly there on a rocket
但我看穿天花板 望见天空的星星 But I see the stars throught the ceiling
不 其实... No, it's rather...
我看不到天花板 只有天空 I don't see the ceiling, but only the sky
我会骑自行车到达月球 I would.. I would reach the Moon on a bike
但没有这样的自行车 But there are not such bikes
晚餐准备好了 Dinner is ready!
爸爸 我可以吃苹果吗 Oh, daddy, may I take the apple?
晚饭后 - 我们现在去吃饭吧 Hey, after dinner - So let's go have dinner now
你好 Hiya!
我明白了 Well, I see...
继续保持沉默吧 Right, keep silent
我来说话 I will speak
那么 So...
我们启动物理肉体恢复程序 We start the program to restore physical form
我只有一次生命 I have just one life
只有一个工作搭档 And just one workmate too
我不会和别人一起飞的 I won't fly with others
我现在与赫鲁诺夫训练 但这是为了保持训练 Of course, I'm training with Khrunov now, but that's to keep the trainings going
你一回来 我们就去找主管 And as soon as you're back, we go to the supervisors
并提交医疗委员会报告 一切都会好的 And file a report for the medical board, understand, and everything will be fine
这很好 你没有骨折吧? That's good that you don't have a fracture, right?
真的很好 That's really good!
旧伤更严重了 但那是... An old injure got worse, but that is...
一件小事 这是"关闭" 就是愈合 That's such a trifle, that's "off", it'll heal up
有些人的脑袋都裂了但你只坏了一条腿 Some people get their head split open. But you a leg
阿列克谢 看着我 听我说 Alexey, look at me and hear me
我将和你一起飞翔 I will fly with you nowhere
为什么我这么讨厌你? And why do I disgust you so much?
才不是 That's not it
你不恐惧 这很糟糕 You have no fear, and that's bad
我给你说个故事 我的童年... Hey, I'll tell you a story from my childhood...
滚远点 - 你会明白我的意思 Get away! - And you'll understand at once what I'm talking about
你不懂我吗 You didn't understand me?
别傻了 列昂诺夫 就这么走人吗 Don't be ridiculous. Leonov doesn't leave just like that?
等我做件事 然后就离开 I'll do my work now and then leave
放松 Easy, easy
很好 摆动 OK. Swing
一 二 And one, two..
一 One!
二 Two...
我帮你 痛吗 Let me help! Painful?
滚 Ah! Get away!
怎么了 耶夫同志? What happened, comrade Belyaev?
赶紧滚 Go away from here!
一切都很好 我们没事 Everything is fine, we figured it out
滚开 Go away!
好吧 Right
你好 Hello
什么 要挠挠吗 What's there? Do you want me to scratch?
你自己挠 You scratch yourself
一小时内 In an hour
所有零重力阶段 Why, during all those zero-gravity sessions,
你进入气闸的举动为什么都没有成功? Didn't you have any successful attempts of entry into the airlock?
有什么障碍 少校同志? What is the hindrance, comrade major?
原因有很多 其中之一是 Well, there are actually a number of reasons. One of them is... the spacesuit
总设计师同志 太空舱虽然外号"雄鹰" Comrade chief designer, it's called "Eagle"...
但实际上更像石棉棺材 抱歉 But it's rather an asbestos coffin. Sorry
我有个建议 可以吗 But I have a suggestion, can I?
鲍里斯·维克多李维奇 Boris Victorovich!
为了拉起绳索 控制动作 So in order to pull up the tether and control your movements
需要有更多的灵活性 You need more agility
请注意 连接接头 Here, please, note – linkage joints
肘部 膝盖 腕关节弯曲 At the elbow, knee, carpal bends
可获得更大的行动自由 For greater freedom of movement
你自己画的吗 - 是 先生 Did you draw it yourself? - Yes, sir
它们与宇航服的总压强有关 They correlate with the total pressure in the spacesuit...
伙计 做这样的航天服需要两到两年半 Boys, making a spacesuit like that will take two or... two and a half years
我们没有时间 列昂诺夫同志 We don't have such time, comrade Leonov
我明白了 谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 I see, Sergey Pavlovich
但是如果把绳索附着点移到头盔上 But what if we shift the tether attachment point to the helmet
对不起 什么 Excuse me, what?
为什么 Why?
宇航员进入气闸 脚先进入 对吗 Our cosmonaut enters the airlock feet foremost, right?
我觉得更好的是 如果宇航员能看到目标 I feel, it would be better, if the cosmonaut can see where he is going
所以头部可以先进入气闸 And get into the airlock head foremost
同志们 离开我们三分钟 Comrades, leave us for three minutes
去吧 Go ahead
我吗 - 是 Me? - Yes
你到底想怎么样? How exactly do you want?
头部不先进?请您做一下 Head foremost? You are requested
快 Come on
很好 Well
现在请回头面对舱口 And now turn back to face the hatch
为什么 Why?
关闭外部舱口啊 In order to close the outer hatch
手动的 Manually
但它是自动的 But it's automatic
自动概率是九成 It's automatic 9 times of 10
假设你运气不佳 Let's assume you are out of luck
现在想象一下 你穿了一套硬邦邦的宇航服 And now imagine, that you are in an inflexible spacesuit
氧气耗尽 And oxygen is running out
你有想象过吗 - 好吧 Have you imagined? - Yes
就这样 你已经死了 That's all, you're dead
还有你的队友 And your mate too
现在我们懂了 谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 Now we know, Sergey Pavlovich
我们继续训练任务 We'll be working on the running task
抱歉打扰你 And sorry for bothering you
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 Sergey Pavlovich
即使穿着盔甲 我们也时刻准备好飞翔 We are ready to fly even in shackles, even in mail
既然我们是人类 早就在出生的枷锁中飞翔了(指娘胎) We're already people, who fly in shackles from birth
但试想 如果失去脐带 But imagine, if they were removed
会是... What would be...
我们会失去平衡 并崩溃 We'd lose balance and crash
这就是人类 That's who we are
去吧 Go
是 长官 Yes, sir
蓝图 The drawing
留下 Leave it
切斯拉夫·阿纳托利耶维奇 Yevgeny Anatolievich
耶夫发神经了 Belyaev is bad!
如何啊? How?
耶夫同志 Comrade Belyaev
亲爱的 你在做什么 Dear, what are you doing?
正如你所说 锻炼腿部 As you said, exercising the leg
但我的意思是一点一点地 But I meant little by little
渐渐地 慢慢来 Gradually, with time
我没时间了 叶夫根尼·阿纳托利耶维奇 I don't have time, Evgeny Anatolievich
惊奇的老飞行员 The old pilot amazes
你知道 我最喜欢你什么 赫鲁诺夫? - 什么 You know, what I like most about you, Khrunov? - What?
你的微笑 Your smile
再微笑一下 Smile again
好一个微笑 What a smile!
帕夏 Pasha!
欢迎回来 Welcome back!
全体立正 Squad! Draw up!
俯卧撑姿势 Front leaning rest position!
对不起 I'm sorry
耶夫同志 请加入 - 是 长官 Comrade Belyaev, join up - Yes, sir
欢迎回来 - 谢谢 Welcome back! - Thank you
一 二 And one, two...
实验建筑一厅 发射前120天 Experimental Construction Department No 1 120 days before launch
尼基欣 Nikishin!
是时候回家好好睡一觉了 It's time to go home and get enough sleep
明天完成 Finish tomorrow
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 人们需要休息 Sergey Pavlovich, people need rest
他们已经辛苦了三周三班倒 They've been toiling for three weeks three-shifts
视察之后再说 Right after the visitation
届时每个人都可以休息一天 Everyone will get a day off
一天 One day
也许 我们把委员会主席请进太空船 Maybe, let's put the chairman of the committee in the spaceship
给他加加林一样的感受 说不定就满足了 To feel like Gagarin and be content
然后庆祝晚宴 被口头警告 Then to the celebration dinner and a kick in the pants
随便口头警告 A kick in the pants is OK
没有外人可以进入太空船 哪怕勃列日涅夫 But no outsiders in the spaceship, even Brezhnev
怎么了这是?尼基欣? What is it? Nikishin?
靠边站 Step aside
击中了胸部和头部区域 Shine it on the chest and head area
怎么了 What?
死了 Dead
上帝 My God
我想知道到底发生了什么 I want to know exactly what happened
确切的 Exactly
鲍里斯·伊欣维奇 半小时内提交报告给我 Boris Evseevich, report back to me what occurred in half an hour
该电气事故 With the electrics
当然 Sure
视察会被取消吗 I take it that the visitation is cancelled?
不 我想让他们看到这一切 No way! I want them to see all this
我们迫切需要他们看到一切 We desperately need them to see it
然后他们可以向上级汇报 May they report back to whom they should
今天的开头比昨天好 上校同志 The beginning was better, comrade colonel
麻烦您 Half a second
请交给斯维特拉娜·华西里莎 Please, give it to Svetlana Egorovna
当然 - 为了纪念美好的晴天 Yes, sure - In honour of a nice sunny day
好的 - 还有她明智的决定 OK - And her wise decision
这是什么 - 有人要我转交给你的 What is this? - Someone asked to give it to you
放在这里 Put it here
上校同志 So, comrade colonel
到现在为止 我没对你作要求 By now I don't have claim to you
我们改变工作负荷 然后检查压力程度 Let's change the workload, and then we'll check the pressure
敬女士们 Well, for our ladies!
万岁 Hooray!
那个 And...
顺便问一下 我怎么称呼从事宇航员的女士? By the way, what do I call a lady who is a cosmonaut?
女性宇航员还是女士宇航员? Female cosmonaut or lady cosmonaut?
我们已经说过了 "女士们" We've said already, "for ladies"...
医疗委员会怎么样了 How did it go with the medical commission?
他们说了什么 What did they say?
他们决定 不让我通过 Didn't let me pass. Their decision
等一下 Stop, wait a second...
你说 "决定" 是什么意思? What do you mean, "decision"?
他们给出了什么理由? What did they give as a reason?
有什么具体的吗 Anything specific?
他们说 "禁止出发 年龄 受伤 " "No go. Age, injuries," they say
"一条腿跑不好" "You can't run well with a bum leg"
我明白 I see
所以你退缩了 So you backed off?
那我现在要和谁一起飞翔? So who I'm going to fly with now?
你是我的同事 You are my workmate
你为什么要抛弃我? - 廖谢 你在干什么 Why are you deserting me? - Lyosh, what are you up to?
我是你的同事吗 Am I your workmate?
那里才是你的同事 There is your workmate
我们不能因为自己一时冲动 而是要共同的目标 We don't serve our own whims, but the common goal
医生是对的 我不适合这项任务 The doctors are right, I'm ill-suited for the task
我不在乎医生 如果要我飞 只和你一起 I don't care about the doctors. If I fly, it's only with you
你真想在太空中奔跑吗 Are you really going to run in space?
总设计师来了 集合 The Chief Designer is going! Fall in!
立正 'ten-shun!
跑或不跑 Run or not
你不能逃脱命运 You can't outrun fate
对我来说 诸事不顺 Things didn't work out for me
不能逃脱? Can't outrun?
廖谢 Lyosh!
看来征服太空 无需他们了 It seems we must conquer space without them now
少校同志 你疯了吗 Are you out of your mind, comrade major?
你想被赶出队伍吗 Do you want to be thrown out of the squad?
将军同志 请允许发言 长官? Comrade general! Permission to speak, sir?
你想要什么 列昂诺夫同志? Did you want anything, comrade Leonov?
你看见他跑了吗 看见吗 Did you see him running? Did you?
所以他是全能 不是半能 So he's able. Not half able
说完了吗 - 是 我说完了 长官 That's all? - Yes. I mean yes, sir
解散 - 是 先生 You're free - Yes, sir
你也解散 You're free
我想看看医疗委员会的结果 I'd like to see the results of the medical commission
"零重力" "Zero gravity"
阿尔玛兹2号 进入气闸 Almaz-2 in the airlock
干得好 阿尔玛兹 Well done, Almaz
发射无人测试模块 当天 The day of the launch of the unmanned test module
好了 宇航员同志 Well, comrades cosmonauts...
在测试期间 我们将制作一部你们的日常电影 During the test operations, we'll make a film about your everyday life
我觉得自己是穆斯林·马格马耶夫 I feel myself Muslim Magomayev
很好 不是艾迪塔·彭哈 It's good, that not Edita Pyekha
场景 1 第3次 Scene 1, take 3
今天我们聚集在这里 不是为了庆祝胜利 Today we gathered here not to celebrate victory
而是验证 But to verify
胜利的可能性 The possibility of victory
注意 准备...开始 - 来爸爸这里 Attention, get ready and... start - Come to dad
爸爸 哎哟 - 慢点 Daddy! Ouch! - Easy, easy
停止 Stop
我们再来一次 Let's go again
"点火钥匙" "Key to ignition"
我做了个恶梦 I had a bad dream
多么愚蠢 Hey, what a silly thing...
停 Stop
发射无人模组 The launch of an unmanned module
将于今天实施 Will be implemented today
莫斯科时间上午10:30 At 10:30 am Moscow time
"记录 2" "Record 2"
众所周知 飞船将会到达轨道以测试 As you know, the ship will reach an orbit for testing purposes
"排水钥匙" "Key on drainage"
拜托 斯维塔 人们都来了 - 没事的 Come on, Svet, people are here, really - That's OK
"空间告别" 第2部分 场景3 第1次 "The space farewell", part 2, scene 3, take 1
我们的任务是对飞行器进行全面测试 Our task is to run a full test of the machinery
"点火" "Ignition"
上升二号的所有关键部件 包括充气气闸 All key parts of Voskhod 2, including inflatable airlock,
应为完全测试 Will be understood to be fully tested
一旦无人驾驶舱返回地球 Once the unmanned module returns to Earth
"开始" "Start"
爸爸 Dad!
我们必须确定计算的准确性 We must be sure about the accuracy of our calculations
在航天器发射前 Before the launch of the spacecraft with
宇航员: 帕维尔·耶夫和阿列克谢·列昂诺夫 Pilots-cosmonauts: Pavel Belyaev and Alexey Leonov
"太空船已到达轨道" "The spacecraft has reached the orbit"
我们的英雄 肩负着特殊使命 Our heroes, who we pin a special mission
"气闸打开" "The airlock is open"
我们将第一次走出太空舱 We will go outside the capsule for the first time ever
在太空中进行太空行走 And have a spacewalk in outer space
"条件太空行走已经实施" "Conditional spacewalk has been implemented"
本次飞行的成功将有助于我们将来的那一刻 The success of this flight will help us in reaching the moment
我们将与太空平起平坐 When we can be with space as equals
像朋友一样 Be like friends
注意 Take heed!
"警告 与测试模块失去连接" "Attention! The connection with the test module has been lost"
"重复 与测试模块失去连接" "Repeat, the connection with the test module has been lost"
确认 观察残骸云形状 Confirm, observing the cloud of wreckage
很高兴见到你 谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 Good to see you, Sergey Pavlovich
很高兴见到你 - 请这边 Good to see you - You are kindly requested
"我宣誓苏联政府" "I pledge the Soviet government"
"尊敬的共产党" "Esteemed Communist Party"
"所有苏维埃人民" "All soviet people"
很高兴见到你 雷奥尼·伊里奇 Good to see you, Leonid Ilyich
等一会儿 谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 Wait a moment, Sergey Pavlovich
先看完电影 再谈 Let's finish the movie and talk
我没有时间看电影 I don't have time to watch a movie
我能感觉到脚下的地球正在转动 I can feel Earth slipping under foot
你并不会感到足下地球的转动 除非那些止步不前的人 It doesn't slip under foot, only for those who make no headway
你是科罗廖夫 进步的引擎 And you're Korolyov, engine for progress
我有完整报告 含所有技术细节 I have a complete report here with all technical details
我试着简短地告诉你 Let me try to tell you in short
如果有什么不清楚 请提问 If something isn't clear, ask
我知道 I know...
宇宙飞船到达了轨道 The spacecraft reached the orbit
实施了有条件的太空行走 Conditional spacewalk was implemented
现在再重复一次 Now repeat the same
两个宇航员 获得金星奖章 With two cosmonauts. And get a Gold Star
但是宇宙飞船崩溃了 我们不知道为什么 没有数据 But the spacecraft fell apart. We don't know why. Don't have data
进行了太空行走吗 Was there a spacewalk?
有条件地 是进行了 Conditionally, yes
现在无条件地做 Now do it unconditionally
美国希望在5月发射太空船 The United States want to launch their spacecraft in May
我们的上升号必须抢飞 Our Voskhod must fly before
让全世界都知道 So that the whole world knows
我们是第一个 That we are the first
太空时代正在开启 苏联的时代 Our space time is happening. Soviet time
先锋的时代 The time of pioneers
我不在乎美国人是否会先发射 I don't care if the Americans will launch first
我明白 对我们来说 国家大事... I understand that the main thing for us, for our country...
不能被我们丢脸 Not to fall flat on our face
但 But
既然我负责管理 While I manage all this
没有准备的宇宙飞船不能去太空 An unprepared spacecraft won't go to space
如果要我的人加入 All the more, if my people are inside
必须踩过我的尸体 Only over my dead body
这是事实吗 - 是 Is that a fact? - Yes
你知道吗 You know what
考虑一下 Think over that
明天去上班 And get to work tomorrow
没有人 只有你 There is no one but you
是我们不可或缺的人 Our indispensable
宇航员旅馆 拜科努尔 发射前一天 Cosmonaut's hotel. Baikonur. One day before launch
我想知道 莫斯科也在下雪吗 I wonder, is it snowing in Moscow too?
如果是这样 如果我能与姑娘们滑雪 If so, if I can to ski with the girls
堆雪人 吃馅饼 Yeah, right... Build a snowman, get some pie
我们什么都没准备吗 Did we prepare for nothing?
尽情享受吧 Enjoy yourself if you want
我们不飞了 We won't fly?
我什么都不想 I don't think anything
有章程的 There is the regulation
我们花了很多时间和精力 We've spent so much time and effort
所有的嘶吼 没有牛排 但有监管 All sizzle, no steak. But the regulation
他们在想什么 What do they have for a head?
你想要什么 What do you want?
你想让科罗廖夫相信运气 并指定发射? You want Korolyov to trust luck and appoint the launch?
不靠运气 帕夏 我们拆过那艘飞船 Not luck, Pasha, we took apart that ship
齿轮对齿轮 并装配回去 Cog by cog, and put it back together
我有信心 就像在娘胎里一样 I have confidence in it like in my own mother
但你只是站在那里打包 But you're just standing and packing
你认为你是唯一想飞太空的人吗 Do you think you're the only one who wants to fly to space?
我也想啊 I want it as much as..
好吧 OK, well...
因为祖国会说... As Motherland will say...
我需要你命令吗 Do I need your orders?
我不会后退的 I won't back off
喂? Yes?
早上好 谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 - 早安 总设计师同志 Good morning, Sergey Pavlovich - Good morning, comrade Chief Designer
早上好 Good morning
你们已经起来一阵子了 - 不 刚起床 You've been up for a while? - No, just got up
饮过茶 Drinking tea
如你所知 试飞失败 As you know, the test flight failed
启动载人的上升二号 太冒险 Launching Voskhod 2 with people is too risky
我们会在你们的火箭上再次发射一个空舱 We'll repeatedly launch an empty module on your rocket
并在一年内建造一艘新的 We'll build a new one in a year
你们会飞的 And you'll fly
好 Alright
你为什么心烦?因为会被美国人抢第一吗 Why are you upset? The fact that the Americans will be the first?
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 我们处于身体状况的巅峰 我们努力... Sergey Pavlovich, we are in peak of physical condition. We worked over...
经历过3000种紧急情况 Three thousand emergency situations
太空里将有第3001、第3002和第3003情况 There will be 3001st, 3002nd, and 3003rd in space
我不能让你去 那是送死 I can't let you go, that's death
雄鹰 Eagles
没有讣告 Without an obituary
那你为什么来? Why did you come then?
你们是乡巴佬 You're a hillbilly
是的 列斯特雅坎村 Yes, Listvyanka village
就在克麦罗沃旁边 That's next to Kemerovo
我本来死于三岁 我的父亲作为"人民的敌人"被带走了 I could die at three, when my father was taken away as "enemy of the people"
我们被称为"破坏者家族" And we were inked as "family of saboteurs"
邻居们立刻突袭我们 The neighbours raided at once
抢食物 砸家具 然后房子 Took food at first, the furniture, then house
让我们露宿霜冻的街道 Put us out on the street in the frost
妈妈怀孕了 Mom was pregnant
我们共八个孩子 And we, eight kids
邻居又折回 脱掉我的外衣 我就这样呆着 The neighbour came back, took off my outerwear, I stayed like that
穿着一件长衬衫 In a long shirt
感谢上帝 姐姐和她的丈夫庇护我们 Thank God, the older sister with her husband sheltered us
工人宿舍房间 A room in a dormitory for workers
170平方英尺 170 square feet for all
我的家就在床下 My place was just under the bed
但我们幸存下来了 But so what, we survived
然后战争开始 Then the war
所有男人上了前线 All men to the front
其余的去移动医院 重建行业 防御 The rest to mobile hospitals, to recreate the industry, defense
至于学习 我妈妈带我去上学 我看了一眼... And to study... My mom brought me to school, I had a look...
我很骄傲 站着 她看着我的脚 I'm proud, standing. She looked at my feet
冰融化成水坑 我没有鞋子 The ice melted into puddles. I didn't have shoes
但我们经受住了 我们幸存了下来 But so what, we withstood, we survived
然后是胜利 但代价是 所有的叔叔兄弟都死了 Then the Victory, yes. But at what price... All uncles, brothers were dead
整个国家都一样 每个家庭 And the whole country like that, every family
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 Sergey Pavlovich
我们经历了那一切 We went through that
我们还站着 We have so much left
所以不害怕紧急情况 Not to get scared of an emergency situation
我会啃破舱口 咬个洞出去的 I'll gnaw through a hole in the hatch and go out
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 Sergey Pavlovich
我们准备冒险 We are ready to take a risk
果然浓茶 Strong tea
回头见 See you later
立正 Attention!
将军同志 Comrade general!
我们准备发射 We are ready for launch
向勃列日涅夫同志和阿列克谢·柯西金同志汇报 Report back to comrade Brezhnev and comrade Kosygin
上升二号太空船 准备发射 That spaceship Voskhod 2 is ready for launch
是 长官 Yes, sir
曙光号 这是阿尔玛兹 我们准备好了 Zarya, this is Almaz, we are ready
注意 我们还有一分钟就发射 Attention! We are one minute to launch
点火钥匙 Key to ignition
已点火 Key to ignition go
排气 Venting
已排气 Venting go
排水钥匙 Key on drainage
已排水 Key on drainage go
发射 Launch
已发射 Launch go
点火 Ignition
已点火 Ignition go
中阶段 Intermediate
已中阶段 Intermediate go
主阶段 Main stage
已主阶段 Main stage go
出发 Start
已出发 Start go
祝你好运 Good luck
雄鹰 Eagles
升空 Lift off
已确认解除联系 Lift off contact confirmed
所有系统工作正常 All systems work well
25 25
30 30
火箭结构参数完美 The rocket construction parameters are good
50 50
60 60
俯仰、偏航、旋转 完美 Pitch, yaw, roll are all good
70 70
飞行很顺利 The flight is going well
注意 莫斯科广播电台 "Attention! This is Moscow broadcast"
我们正在所有电台广播 We are broadcasting across all radio stations...
苏联中央电视台 And the Central Television of the Soviet Union
今天 1965年3月18日 10点 Today, March 18th, 1965, at 10 am
人造卫星和宇宙飞船 上升二号 Artificial satellite and spaceship Voskhod 2
射入地球轨道 Was placed in the orbit of planet Earth
与飞船连续保持无线电联络 With the ship continuously maintained radio contact
耶夫和列昂诺夫同志正在进行工作 Comrades Belyaev and Leonov are carrying out their work...
"按照既定飞行计划" "In accordance with the flight program"
曙光号 这是阿尔玛兹 Zarya, this is Almaz
轻微震动 Slight vibration
所有设备正常工作 All devices are working normally
感觉好极了 Feeling excellent
我们随时准备执行任务 We stand ready to implement the task
阿尔玛兹 开始执行任务 Almaz, start to implement the task
收到 曙光号 Copy, Zarya
拉长气闸 Elongating the airlock
曙光号 气密室已经拉长了 我们正开始平衡气闸压力 Zarya, the airlock has been elongated. We're starting to equalize the pressure in the airlock
曙光号 准备进入气闸 Zarya, getting ready to enter the airlock
曙光号 气闸压力已经均衡 Zarya, the airlock pressure has been equalized
切换到背包氧气供应 Switching to the oxygen supply from the backpack
曙光号 宇航服压紧 打开气密室内舱 Zarya, the spacesuit is pressure-tight, opening the inner hatch of the airlock
不要感到无聊 Don't get bored
我很快的 I'll be soon
帕夏 推我 就一点点 Pash, push me. Just a little bit.
这是阿尔玛兹2号 This is Almaz-2
我在气闸内 I'm in the airlock
阿尔玛兹2号 收到 Almaz-2, copy
曙光号 这是阿尔玛兹 关闭气密室内舱 Zarya, this is Almaz, closing the inner hatch of the airlock
曙光号 这是阿尔玛兹 开始减压气闸 Zarya, this is Almaz, starting to depressurize the airlock
阿尔玛兹2号 气压舱减压需要5分钟 Almaz-2, pressure-relief in the airlock is 5 minutes
压力升高 但在范围内 Pressure is elevated, but within range
阿尔玛兹2号 你的氧气消耗高于正常 Almaz-2, your oxygen consumption is above normal
廖谢 呼吸均匀 Lyosh, breath evenly
我几乎没有呼吸 I'm almost not breathing
注意 准备 Attention, get ready
曙光号 气闸压力为零 Zarya, the airlock pressure is zero
打开气闸的外舱门 Opening the outer hatch of the airlock
阿尔玛兹2号 给出状态报告 Almaz-2, give a status report
这是阿尔玛兹2号 报告 This is Almaz-2, reporting
一切都很顺利 Everything is going well
准备去船外 Ready to go outside the ship
开始向外太空移动 Begin moving into outer space
收到 Copy
阿尔玛兹2号 Almaz-2
移动到外太空 Moving into outer space
被允许 Is permitted
廖谢 做两次来回 Lyosh, make two trips
第一次是测试 带着负载 The first is for testing, with loads
第二次 拍照 The second one, for taking photos
收到 阿尔玛兹 Copy, Almaz
曙光号 Zarya!
这是阿尔玛兹2号 This is Almaz-2
我在气闸的边缘 I'm on the edge of the airlock
感觉... Feeling...
非常好 Excellent!
我看见云彩 大海在下面 I see clouds, the sea below
高加索全境 Caucasus range
马上 刚刚路过 Right now! Just passed
我看见天空 I see sky
我看到陆地 I see land
伏尔加河 右下方 Volga! Right below
工作环境良好 Good working conditions!
阿尔玛兹2号 准备出发 Almaz-2, get ready for departure
是 收到 Yes, copy that
从照相机中卸下镜头盖 Remove the lens cap from the camera
我已经移动 取下了镜头盖 I've removed. I've removed the lens cap
我可以把它放在哪里? Where can I put it?
在哪里? Where?
把它扔掉 Just throw it away
收到 Copy
扔掉 Throwing away
曙光号 这是阿尔玛兹2号 Zarya, this is Almaz-2
拉出绳索 Pulling out the tether
"苏联宇宙频道正在分享来自太空的广播" "Soviet Cosmovision is sharing another broadcast from space"
来自从上升二号太空飞船 From the Voskhod 2 spaceship
我们正在目睹这一事件 We are witnessing the event
而昨天我们只是在幻想... That just yesterday we spoke of only as fantasy...
阿尔玛兹2号 Almaz-2
开始推送 Begin push off
阿尔玛兹2号 你可以离开 Almaz-2, you can depart
好的 等一会儿 OK, OK, wait a sec
好吧 我要走了 Well, I'm off
星辰服务仓 曙光号 Zvezda, Zary!
这是阿尔玛兹 This is Almaz
人类进入太空 Man went into outer space
他现在在自由飞行 He's now in free flight
"今天 1965年3月18日" "Today, March 18th, 1965..."
莫斯科时间 上午11:35 At 11:35 am Moscow time...
在太空飞船上升二号飞行期间 During the flight of spaceship Voskhod 2
有史以来第一次太空行走已经实施 第一次人类步行... The first ever spacewalk has been implemented; the first man has gone...
到外太空 Into outer space
位于飞行第二轨道 On the second orbit of the flight
第二名飞行员 宇航员少校列昂诺夫·阿列克谢·阿奇西波维奇 The second pilot, cosmonaut Major Leonov Alexey Arkhipovich
穿着特殊宇航服 In a special spacesuit
拥有自主的生命支持系统 With an autonomous life support system
走进了 Went into
外太空 Outer space
爸爸是个真正的宇航员 Dad is a real cosmonaut!
真正的 Real!
所以 现在我们只需要学习对接 So, now we only need to learn docking
然后就可以形成空间力系 And then we can form space forces
干得好 每个人都做得很好 Great job! Everyone did well!
专心点 Stay focused!
将军同志 Comrade general
克里姆林宫在线 The Kremlin is on the line
他们要求直接与宇航员联系 They ask to connect directly with the cosmonaut
好 连接他们吧 Well then connect them
让他们通过 - 是 长官 Put them through - Yes, sir
廖谢? Lyosha?
是? Yes?
你是谁? Who is this?
勃列日涅夫在线上 Brezhnev is on the line
雷奥尼·伊里奇? Leonid Ilyich?
哇 Whoa
你怎么样 孩子? - 报告 How are you doing, son? - Reporting
头脑清楚 视觉无干扰 My mind is clear, my vision is not disturbed
空间方向感正常 Spatial orientation is normal
人可以在太空工作 Man can work in outer space
人可以工作 Man can work...
在太空中 ...in outer space
我看到你在那里翻滚 Oh, yeah.. I see how you're tumbling around out there
整个国家都在注视着你 The whole country is watching you
还有整个世界 And the whole world
谢谢 Thank you
我们以你为荣 We are proud of you
谢谢 真的谢谢你 Thanks. Really thank you
最重要的是 活着回来 You come back alive, above all
这是命令 你听到了吗 That's an order, do you hear me?
以服务苏联为荣 Proud to serve the Soviet Union
他的参数怎样? What are his parameters?
血压和体温略有上升 但总的来说 Pressure and temperature slightly going up, but in general...
所有参数很好 All parameters are good
氧气? The air?
氧气持续可用27分钟 The air lasts 27 minutes
我们进入下一个步骤 Let's move to the next step
阿尔玛兹2号 Almaz-2
准备好推送 以测试前庭器械的反应 Get ready for push off to test the reaction of vestibular apparatus
保持身体空间位置 For the position of the body in space
我们走吧 Let's go!
阿尔玛兹2号 你感觉如何? Almaz-2, how do you feel?
非常好 Excellent
为摄影的最后阶段做好准备 Ready for the last stage for pictures
他的血压上升到140 超过90 His pressure rose to 140 over 90. Pulse...
脉搏125 体温98F 125, temperature 98 F
他有点担心 He's worried
谁不会? Who wouldn't be?
阿尔玛兹2号 Almaz-2
拍几张照片回家 Take a couple of photos and go back home
但不要突然运动 But without sudden movements
慢慢地 - 收到 Slowly - That's affirmative
帕夏 Pash!
你在笑吗 Are you smiling there?
我是 I am
我在拍照 I'm taking pictures
时间很短 拍照片然后返回 廖谢 Time is short, take the photos and go back, Lyosh
等等 Oh, wait
怎么了 What's this?
压力怎么了 What's with the pressure?
阿尔玛兹2号 你没事吧? Almaz-2, are you OK?
阿尔玛兹 怎么回事? Almaz, what's going on there?
阿尔玛兹2号 没有答复 Almaz-2 is not replying
太空船船体有撞击 There was a knock on the spaceship hull
与阿尔玛兹2号失去视频 Visual contact with Almaz-2 was lost
连接是怎么回事? What's with the connection?
所有设备工作正常 All devices work well
从技术上说 连接没有损坏 Technically, the connection isn't broken
他的参数怎样? - 血压 脉搏 体温 What are his parameters? - Pressure, pulse, temperature...
都在上升 All are rising
阿尔玛兹继续呼叫 阿尔玛兹2号 Almaz, continue calling Almaz-2
重复 阿尔玛兹 继续呼叫 阿尔玛兹2号 Repeat, Almaz, continue calling Almaz-2
一切都太顺利了 太天衣无缝了 Everything went too well, too seamlessly
停止所有直播 Stop all on-air broadcasts
是 长官 Yes, sir
"现在表演谢尔盖·谢尔盖耶维奇·赫普罗科菲耶夫的芭蕾舞蹈" "We are presenting to the audience the ballet of Sergey Sergeyevich Prokofiev
"石花传奇" "The Tale of the Stone Flower"
"在国家学术剧院的舞台上..." "On the stage of the State Academic Bolshoi Theatre... "
我们继续等 We'll wait
阿尔玛兹2号 你听到了吗 完毕 Almaz-2, do you read me, over?
阿尔玛兹2号 完毕 Almaz-2, over?
曙光号 无法联系阿尔玛兹2号 Zarya, cannot connect with Almaz-2
继续尝试 Continue trying
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 Sergey Pavlovich
这种情况一定有指示 There are certain instructions for this situation
如果阿尔玛兹2号不能回到船上 If Almaz-2 cannot get back to the ship
我们得准备扔掉气闸 We have to get ready to blow-off the airlock
血压155 超过100 Pressure 155 over 100
脉搏150 体温101F Pulse 150, temperature 101 F
曙光号 这是阿尔玛兹 Zarya, this is Almaz
允许去气闸? Permission to go out to the airlock?
到死区要多久? How long to the dead zone?
大约5分钟 直到连接丢失 It's about 5 minutes until conection is lost
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 第二个宇航员出去意味着... Sergey Pavlovich, the exit of the second cosmonaut means...
飞船全部降压 The full depressurizing of the ship
他们将不得不自己回来 And they will have to come back by themselves
不会有任何指导 There won't be any connection
在减压后 飞船将如何表现 And how will the ship behave after the depressurization
只有上帝知道 Only God knows
开始祈祷吧 Start praying then
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 Sergey Pavlovich
如果我们扔掉气密室 只有一个宇航员会死 If we blow-off the airlock, only one cosmonaut will die
如果你下令 两个都可能死 If you give the order, both could die
阿尔玛兹 准备降压飞船 Almaz, get ready for depressurizing the ship
收到 曙光号 Copy, Zarya
2分钟 待命 2 minutes. Standby
如果耶夫不能做到 上千苏联公民... If Belyaev cannot do it, the results of the colossal work
的辛苦工作成果将遗留在轨道上 Of thousands Soviet citizens will stay in orbit
现在我认为不是上千 大约两千人 Now I think not about thousands, but about two
曙光号 这是阿尔玛兹 Zarya, this is Almaz
我准备好去气闸 I'm ready to go to the airlock
等待命令 Waiting for the order
我们无权让整个太空计划失败 We don't have any right to fail the whole space program
只为一个人 For one man
一分钟后到死区 One minute until the dead zone
取消命令 谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 Cancel the command, Sergey Pavlovich
阿尔玛兹2号的参数怎样 What are the parameters of Almaz-2
血压170+ 超过110 脉搏165 Pressure 170 over 110, pulse 165
体温102F Temperature 102 F
活着 Alive
他还活着 He's alive
明白了 Got it?
曙光号 这是阿尔玛兹 重复 准备去气闸 Zarya, this is Almaz, repeat, ready to go out to the airlock
等待命令 Waiting for the order
我相信你知道你在做什么 I'm sure you know what you're doing
30秒后进入信号死区 30 seconds until entering the dead zone
曙光号 重复 等待命令 Zarya, repeat, waiting for the command
开始降压飞船 Start depressurizing the ship
15秒 15
他在那儿 阿尔玛兹2号在气密室旁边 There he is! Almaz-2. Next to the airlock!
曙光号 确认 阿尔玛兹2号在气密室旁边 Zarya, confirming! Almaz-2 is next to the airlock
阿尔玛兹2号 Almaz-2!
跑回家 Run off home!
他们进入信号死区了 They are in the dead zone
发生了什么事? What happened?
太空服正在充气 The spacesuit is inflating
胳膊 腿 手指 我几乎不能移动 Arms, legs, fingers... I can hardly move
你为什么沉默? Why were you silent?
不想打扰你们 Didn't want to bother you all
明白了 I see
好的 OK
我有多少氧气? So, how much oxygen do I have?
一点点 A tad
廖谢 快点 Lyosha, hurry up
廖谢 没有时间了 Lyosha, there's no time at all
拿着相机进入飞船 Take the camera and get into the ship
好的 好的 拿着相机 帕夏 OK, OK... Taking the camera, Pash
去吧 Go, go
干的好 Well done
去吧 试试看 Go it, try
这是唯一的办法 That's the only way
快 Come on!
真是一团糟 What a mess
试试看 Try, try!
振作起来 Brace yourself!
停止 Stop!
绳子 你敢! 只有脚最重要 Belay! Don't you dare! Only feet foremost!
关闭 Close
关闭 Close!
我说关闭 I said close!
赶快 Do it!
没关门吧? It hasn't closed, right?
没有 No
明白了 I see
所以 我必须转身 手动关闭 So, I have to turn around and close it manually
那行不通 廖谢 That won't work, Lyosha
还有其他选择吗 But what are the other options?
我会打开舱门 I'll open the hatch
拉你起来 Pull you up
减压飞船 And depressurize the ship
但我们将承担风险 So, we'll take the risk
什么 冒着整个行动的风险? What? To risk the whole operation?
不 帕夏 No, Pasha
我会试 I'll try
廖谢 Lyosha!
廖谢 不 Lyosha, no!
停下来 你只有一点点的空气 Stop! You only had a tiny bit of air
现在你什么都没有了 Now you won't have anything at all
你可以把我和气闸一起吹走 So, you can blow me off together with the airlock
你是牛头 You're bull-headed!
可恶 Damn
我被卡住了 I got stuck
我动不了 I can't move
廖谢 少说话 省空气 Lyosh, talk less, save air
好吧 我沉默 OK, I'm silent
如果我们把...腿 And what if we put... The leg
就像这样 Like this!
快 Go, go!
快 廖谢 Come on, Lyosha
快 Go, go, go
气闸压紧了 干的好 Yes! The airlock is pressure-tight! Well done!
现在坚持 Now hold on
至少坚持几分钟 Hold on a couple of minutes at the least
廖谢 Lyosha
廖谢 不 Lyosha, no!
完了 - 什么 That's all - What?
我的比赛结束了 My race is over
干得好 廖谢 Good job, Lyosh
我明白了 但你能告诉我们吗 OK, I see, but can you tell us?
我明白 但这意味着什么 I understand, but what does it mean?
好 Okay
谢谢 Thanks
{\move(750,20,-250,20)\fnMicrosoft YaHei\fs15\b1\alpha&H25\q2\bord2\shad0\3c&H000000&}澳门贵宾厅 www.149.net 提供真人百家乐，龙虎斗，彩票游戏，电子游艺，新用户注册送77元，可提款，百家乐日送88万，以小博大，100万提款30秒火速到账，官方直营，大额无忧！
他们说 飞行是正常模式 Well, they say that the flight is going in normal mode
廖谢 总是这样回答 当有人打扰他的工作 Lyosha always answers like that, when someone disturbs him from work. Or...
或者一切不妙的时候 Or when everything is bad
举办展示活动 纪念莫斯科和列宁格勒之飞行 The demonstrations were held in honour of the flight in Moscow and Leningrad
请斯维特拉娜安娜·列昂诺娃参加 Svetlana Leonova called
茶? - 不 谢谢 Tea? - No, thank you
她问的是情况 她担心啊 She asked what's what. She's worried
她为什么担心?有什么事吗 Why is she worried? Anything happen? No
上升二号 会在一分钟内逃离死亡地带 Voskhod 2 is going to escape the dead zone in a minute
开始呼叫 Start calling
廖谢? Lyosha?
廖谢 回到地球上来 Lyosha, come back to Earth
阿尔玛兹2号 Almaz-2
我们正在逃离死亡地带 We are escaping the dead zone
我想啊 Hey, I was thinking
下一次 Next time
当我们飞往月球 When we fly to the Moon...
指挥中心上线 Command Center is on the line
我们会挨骂的 We’ll be getting a scolding now
阿尔玛兹 这是曙光号 听到了吗 Almaz, this is Zarya, do you read me?
曙光号 这是阿尔玛兹 讯号清晰 Zarya, this is Almaz, reading you loud and clear
阿尔玛兹 阿尔玛兹2号 怎么回事? Almaz, what is with Almaz-2?
曙光号 阿尔玛兹2号 讯号清晰 Zarya, Almaz-2 reads you loud and clear too
真是个流氓 What a rascal
阿尔玛兹2号 Almaz-2
欢迎回来 Welcome back
感谢您的服务 Thank you for your service
谢谢 Thank you
以服务苏联为荣 Proud to serve to the Soviet...
你为什么不联系? Why didn't you get in touch?
曙光号 我们的连接有问题 Zarya, we had some problems with the connection
我们无法确定原因 We couldn't establish the reason why
阿尔玛兹2号 Almaz-2...
你不能自己回答? You can't answer for yourself?
我确认 I confirm
曙光号 这里一切都好 Zarya, everything is alright here
准备释放气闸 We are ready to blow-off the airlock
准备 Get ready
释放气闸 To blow-off the airlock
准备释放气闸 Getting ready to blow-off the airlock
阿尔玛兹 提醒你 目前为止 Almaz's, we need to remind you, that we implemented the test cycle
都只进行过实验 Only until this stage
我们不知道释放气闸后的真实情况 We don't know what can happen after blowing off the airlock
做好一切准备 Be ready for everything
不可能更糟 It can't get any worse
阿尔玛兹 检查舱压 Almaz, check the pressure in the cabin
舱压正常 The pressure in the cabin is normal
检查点火接触方式 Check the contact of the igniters
已接触 准备释放气闸 There is contact, ready to blow-off the airlock
释放 Blow-off
曙光号 释放完成 Zarya, the blow-off is complete
未观察到降压或其他故障 Depressurizing or other faults are not observed
除了旋转 But it spun
转角多少?阿尔玛兹? How much has it spun? Almaz?
大约 Approximately...
概约20度 20 degrees on the contour
可以打开自动定向 会稳定的 We can turn on the auto-orientation, it will stabilize
这样会烧掉所有手动着陆的燃料? And burn all the fuel intended for a manual landing?
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 自动定位我可以用脖子保证 Sergey Pavlovich, I can put my neck on the line for the automation
无需手动着陆 The manual landing won't be needed
阿尔玛兹 你感觉如何? Almaz's, how do you feel?
我们感觉很好 曙光号 We feel good, Zarya
那么 So...
我们去兜风吧? Let's go for a spin?
进入着陆区之前 绕地球15圈 It's 15 orbits before entering the landing zone
大约22小时 It's about 22 hours
你们怎么想 能忍受吗 What do you think, will you endure it?
我们会的 曙光号 We will, Zarya
坚持住 老鹰 Hold on, Eagles
坚持 Hold on
22小时 22 hours
就像去图阿普谢 It's like going to Tuapse
睡在上铺而已 In the upper berth
飞行第20小时 2小时后自动着陆 The 20th hour of the flight. 2 hours to run the cycle of the automatic landing
好久没睡了 你得睡觉了 还剩10圈 Hey, it's been long time, you need to sleep. There are 10 orbits ahead
必须坚持 我需要完成画作 It will keep! I need to finish the drawing
列季亚科夫画廊等着呢 Tretyakov Gallery is waiting
列季亚科夫画廊? - 你怎么想的? Tretyakov Gallery? - And what did you think?
太空中的第一张画作 The first picture made in space
那不是画花盆里的花 That isn't a drawing flowers in pots
他们会把它挂在"松树林的早晨"的旁边 They will hang it right next to "Morning in a Pine Forest"
你知道 他们怎么抢我去艺术学院的? Do you know, how they called me to go to the art Academy?
他们保留了我的名额 直到最后一刻 They kept the place until the last moment
你为什么不去? - 有什么意义? Why didn't you go? - What's the point?
你可以飞行时画画 You can fly and paint
但画画时飞行 不太可能 But paint and fly... It's unlikely
他们叫我去古巴 Well... What's about me, they called me to visit Cuba
你吗 - 是 You? - Yep
你知道 他们从大使馆打电话到飞船上 You know, they called right from the embassy to the ship
祝贺 Congratulated...
"来吧" 他们说 "帕维尔·伊万诺维奇 来度假" "Come here," they say, "Pavel Ivanovich, for holidays."
但我在哪里? - 我不知道 你去了什么地方 Ah... But where was I? - I don't know, you went somewhere
对 Right
勃列日涅夫同时祝贺我 Brezhnev congratulated me at the same time
他说 他会来机场接我 He said, he will come to the airport to meet me
"廖谢" 他说 "就在你下梯子的时候 左手边" "Lyosh," he said, "Just when you descend the ladder, to the left..."
"你会认出我 凭我的帽子" "You'll recognize me, by my hat..."
然后去首都 Then to go to the country
不是 首先是克里姆林宫 然后到首都 Not, to the Kremlin first. Then to the country
我宁可你画画 廖谢 I wish you would draw instead, Lyosh
廖谢 Lyosh
廖谢 Lyosh!
你感觉如何?正常吗 How do you feel? Normal?
正常 只是有点反胃 Yeah, just a little bit queasy
但应该是这样的 But it should be that way
氧气是怎么回事? - 等一下 What's with the oxygen? - One moment
不可能 No way
近300 Almost 300
打电话 Call
曙光号 这是阿尔玛兹 Zarya, this is Almaz
这里的分压是正常的两倍以上 The partial pressure is twice above normal here
确切值是多少? What's the exact value?
296 296..
还在上升 And still rising
阿尔玛兹 Almaz's
不要突然运动 No sudden movements
没有空气 只有纯净的氧气 There is not air, but pure oxygen
最小的火花 会立即燃烧 The littlest spark and you'll burn instantly
收到 Copy
该怎么办? What to do?
关闭主照明 Turn off the main lighting
准备指示 Stand by for instructions
收到 Copy
氧气从哪里来? Where is the oxygen from?
他们会找到的 They'll find out
有漏点... - 来自背包吗 There is a leak somewhere... - From the backpacks?
列昂诺夫把背包留在了气闸 那是耶夫的背包吗 Leonov left his in the airlock... So, it's Belyaev's?
值是296?只因为一个背包? And the value is 296 at once? Because of just one backpack?
或者来自某个补偿泄漏罐 Then it's from one of the compensation leakage tank
但系统没有任何故障 But there are not any failures in the system
机舱的严密性也无损 Tightness of the cabin isn't damaged either
释放的时候 也许舱口移动了 Maybe the hatch shifted away during the blow-off?
但那样会看到剧烈的温度下降 But then we would see a drastic temperature drop
同志们 他们的脉搏和血压正在下降 Comrades, their pulse and pressure are decreasing
很快就会氧气中毒 It will be oxygen toxicity soon
我们需要中央天花板区的蓝图 We need a blueprint of the central ceiling zone
最详细的 The most detailed
阿尔玛兹 最有可能的是微裂 Almaz, most likely there is a micro fissure
不要试图搜索它 其本身并不危险 It's useless trying to search it, it's not dangerous by itself
但系统检测到有泄漏 并自动开始补气 But the system has detected the leak and automatically started pumping air
补偿检测器只能手动关闭 The compensation detector can only be turned off manually
你得拆开某些东西 You'll have to disassemble something
收到 That's affirmative
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 决不能这样做 一切都在压力下 Sergey Pavlovich! We must not do it! Everything is under voltage there
还有别的选择吗 Do you have any other options?
阿尔玛兹 Almaz
就在你上方 中央天花板区 Right above you, at the central ceiling zone
补偿泄漏检测器设置在襟翼旁边 用于降压 The compensation leakage detector is set next to the flap for dropping pressure
除掉部分内饰 Cut the upholstery on the contour
这是一场赌博 记得 This is a gamble... Remember...
在装配过程中 技术员死了 但他是个合格的专家 During assemblage, the technician died. But he was a qualified specialist
布线密度很大 没有工具 没有照明 Do you see the density of wiring, and the have no tools and no light
上帝 My God
曙光号 我们已经切掉内饰 Zarya, we've cut the upholstery
探测器系统设置在电线后面 The detector system is set behind the wires
要做到这一点 需要削减电线绑定 To get to it, you need to cut the binding holding the wires
收到 曙光号 Copy, Zarya
廖谢 照过来 Lyosh, shine it here
后果是什么 What will happen with them?
四肢麻木 Numbness of the limbs at the beginning
强烈的肌肉痉挛 Painful muscle spasms
间杂部分听力丧失 并产生视觉幻觉 All these amid a background of partial hearing loss and visual hallucinations
停止 Stop!
放松 Easy... Easy...
坚持 Hold on, hold on...
慢点 Easy...
仔细点 Carefully
让我来 Let me do it
你负责照明 And you'll shine the light
然后他们就会入睡 Then they will fall asleep
在最后 At the end
入睡?就这样? Fall asleep? That's all?
对 Exactly
就这样 That's all
阿尔玛兹 Almaz
我来吧 I'll do it
阿尔玛兹 你听到了吗 Almaz, do you hear me?
坚持 Hold on
坚持住 帕夏 Hold on, Pash
阿尔玛兹 Almaz
你听到了吗 Do do you hear me?
阿尔玛兹 你听到了吗 Almaz, do you hear me?
帕夏 你得保持光照 Pasha, you're shining the light so well
均匀点 Evenly
如此明亮 So bright
好 Good
很好 That's good
曙光号 Ah, Zarya
我看到了 I see
看到了 See
我看到了探测器 I see the detector
做得好 现在最重要的 Well done, now the most important...
你看到黄色的线了吗 Do you see a yellow wire?
拔掉它 在电线巢后面 Unplug it. It's behind the nest of wires
电线巢 Nest of wires
你听到了吗 Do you hear me?
曙光号 重复 Zarya, repeat
在电线巢后面 Behind the nest of wires
重复 曙光号 Repeat, Zarya
拔掉黄线 在电线巢后面 Unplug the yellow.. Behind the nest of wires
啊 Ah...
电线巢 The nest
原来它住在那里 That's where it lives
我没有你的回复 阿尔玛兹 I didn't get you, Almaz
那是它睡觉的地方 那是她的房子 That's where it sleeps. That's her house
什么房子? What house?
我没有你的信号 阿尔玛兹 重复 I didn't get you, Almaz, repeat
我们会拔掉它的 We'll unplug it
你拔掉了吗 Did you unplug?
你的房子在哪里? Where is your house?
你拔掉了吗 阿尔玛兹? Have you unplugged it? Almaz?
我发现了 OK, I've found
等等 帕夏 Hold on, Pasha
阿尔玛兹 Almaz
阿尔玛兹 你听到了吗 Almaz, do you hear me?
你拔掉了吗 Have you unplugged it?
不要沉默 说话 你拔掉了吗 阿尔玛兹? Don't be silent, speak! Have you unplugged it? Almaz?
阿尔玛兹 阿尔玛兹 Almaz, Almaz...
没有信号 这艘船脱离了视野 There is no signal. The ship is out of the field of vision
自动定位系统... The system of automatic orientation...
在逃离死亡地带之前保持运行 Will run before escaping the dead zone
4圈绕地后 着陆 Cycle 4 will land them
他们有机会吗 Do they have a chance?
妈妈? - 怎么? Mama? - Yes?
在太空也有夜晚吗 Is it night in space too?
是 It is
去睡觉 Go to sleep
爸爸也在睡觉吗 Is daddy sleeping too?
对 Sure
每个人都应该睡觉 Everyone should sleep
当我醒来 When I wake up...
爸爸会飞回来吗 Will daddy fly back?
他会努力的 He will try
他真的会努力 He will really really try
飞行的第22小时 25分钟后 自动着陆 22nd hour of the flight. 25 minutes past the cycle automatic landing run
我们一直在等待信号 但一直寂静 We've been waiting for the signal, but it's silence yet
没有视频联系 There is no visual contact too
恶心 Disgusting
一群强壮健康的男人坐在沙发上像马铃薯 A crowd of strong healthy men sitting like couch potatoes
像葬礼一样叹息 And sighing like it's a funeral
如果我们不能帮助我们的同志 If we cannot help our comrades
我们不要举行过早的葬礼 Let's not hold a premature funeral
女士 Ma'am
请给大家来杯咖啡 我也要 Please, coffee for everybody. And me too
我们逻辑点思考 Look, let's think logically
飞船应在23分钟前着陆的 The ship should have land 23 minutes ago
或许在重返大气层的过程中脱离 Perhaps during the re-entry the atmosphere it was off course
然后坠入计划外的区域 And it ended up at an unplanned area
你在重复你自己 鲍里斯·维克托罗维奇 You're repeating yourself, Boris Viktorovich
"可能 也许 似乎" "Probably, perhaps, it seems..."
给我所有着陆可能性的计算 Give me the calculations for all landing possibilities
当然 Sure
准备计算 Prepare the calculations
我们不能再等了 We can't wait any more
派飞机空中搜索 Let's send some aircraft to search from the air
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 克宫打来电话 他们要祝贺成功 Sergey Pavlovich, there is a call from Kremlin. They want to congratulate the successful...
他们会再来电的 They will call back
是 长官 Yes, sir
他们有参数了 Their parameters!
他们还活着 They are alive
我们从船上收到 We are receiving from the ship
信号 有一个信号 Signal, there is a signal
这是阿尔玛兹 完毕 This is Almaz, over
告诉他们 科罗廖夫离开去见宇航员 Tell them, Korolyov left to meet the cosmonauts
阿尔玛兹 Almaz
我们读取到了你 We read you
是你们吗 老鹰? We are you? We are you, Eagles?
在座位上呢 In the seats
我们没有去任何地方 We didn't go anywhere
曙光号 这是阿尔玛兹 Zarya, this is Almaz
我们感觉正常 We feel normal
还有4圈 Cycle 4 hasn't been run
重复 还有4圈 Repeat, cycle 4 hasn't been run
只是逃离死亡地带 Just escaping the dead zone
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 我 Sergey Pavlovich, I...
我还没有解释 I don't have an explanation yet
也许 飞船旋转太多了 Perhaps, the spin of the ship was too strong
这是特殊情况 That's an extraordinary situation
真的吗 这不是第一次 Oh, is it really? It's not the first
有人计数过吗 Did anyone count them?
我有 I did
尝试重新启动系统 Let's try to restart the system
在下一圈时 即刻降落 And land them on in the next orbit
我们无权在下一圈着陆 We don't have right to land them in the next orbit
这艘飞船将通过竞争对手的领地 The ship will be passing rival territory
英雄们该回到地球 The guys should be returned to Earth
领土问题以后再说 And you will be dealing with the territory later
曙光号 这是阿尔玛兹 Zarya, this is Almaz
请允许立即将飞船切换到手动控制 Permission to switch the ship to manual control immediately
并立即着陆 完毕 And implement the landing right now, over
阿尔玛兹 我们需要计算着陆点 Almaz, we need to calculate the landing point for that
现在没有足够的时间 We don't have enough time for that now
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 不用担心 我们有所有的计算 Sergey Pavlovich! Don't worry! We have all calculations
所以 我 瞎猜... So, I guesstimated here...
我们将降落在乌拉尔山 彼尔姆区附近 We'll land in the Urals. Somewhere in the Perm area
廖谢 Lyosha!
理智点 计算结果如此吗 Be reasonable. Is that calculations?
"他瞎猜..." "彼尔姆区附近" "He guesstimated,""Somewhere in the Perm area."
另一方面 他们都是经验丰富的飞行员 On the other hand, they both are experienced pilots
但没有人在手动模式下着陆过宇宙飞船 But nobody ever landed a spaceship in a manual mode
手动控制 我不知道 Manual control, it's like, I don't know...
就像救命稻草 A straw for a drowning
完全只为绝望情况设计 Exclusively only for desperate situations
现在情况如何? And what is the situation now?
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 Sergey Pavlovich
来一分钟 For a minute
就是这样 That's it
会议已经开始 The meeting has begun
现在他们会召集大家 Now they will gather everyone
选择主席 Choose the Chairman
然后 他们会对着扬声器 Then they will listen to a speaker
开始讨论 Start the discussion
你问我为什么不回复? And you asked me why I didn't reply?
我本该长眠了 I would be pushing up daisies by now
来吧 我们要降落老爷车 帕夏 Come on, we will land our clunker, Pash
我们曾经降落了很多生锈的铁桶 We landed a lot more rust buckets in our day
你会着陆的 不是吗 You will land it, won't you?
我们没有其他选择 - 为什么 We don't have any other option - Why that?
要么手动着陆 要么永远留在轨道上 Or we land it manually now, or they will keep us in the orbit
简而言之 就像祖国所说的 In short, as Motherland will say
你认为他们会不允许吗 You think they won't permit it?
是我就不允许 I wouldn't
我们不是仁慈的修女 谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 We are not sisters of mercy, Sergey Pavlovich
国家机密不是实验对象 State secrets are not subjects for experiments
老实说 我不明白你 Honestly, I don't get you
或者我明白 但更糟的是 Or I do, but that's even worse
你愿意让他们留在轨道上吗 Are you offering to keep them in orbit?
我能让你明白吗 Do I get you right?
我们在打仗 We are at war
冷战 但相当真实 Cold, but quite real
万一他们最终落在欧洲呢  What if they end up in Europe?
或者 上帝保佑 飞入中国(顶这句) Or, God forbid, fly into China
我们太空计划的所有秘密都将落入敌人之手 All the secrets of our space program will fall into the hands of the enemy
那又怎样?他们就这样呆着吗 So what? Should they just stay like that?
这样他们就不会"飞到某个地方"? So that they won't"fly into somewhere"?
他们是士兵 They are soldiers
士兵们必须死 为了国家利益 And the soldiers have to die. In the interest of their state
我明白 I see
好吧 OK, well...
这不是新想法 但是 The thought isn't new, but...
很有建设性 谢谢 Constructive. Thanks. Thanks.
也许 我会考虑的 Maybe, I'll think about it
阿尔玛兹 Almaz
这是曙光号 This is Zarya
切换到手动控制 Switching to manual control...
被允许 Is permitted
从密封服开始 Start with sealing the spacesuits
"曙光号" 收到 "Zarya", copy that
启动 Get started
还好不由你做决定 It's good that you're not the one who decides
"曙光号" 重复 着陆面积大约是... "Zarya", repeat, landing area is approximately...
廖谢 他们听不到你 Lyosha, they can't hear you
他们会想办法找到我们的 如果着陆 They'll find us somehow. If we land
我们就在红场上着陆? Let's land right on Red Square?
话说够了 开始稳定飞船 Enough talk, start stabilization of the spaceship
看来我们已经对齐了 It seems we've aligned
你看 心想事成 You see! You can when you want
我们现在所需要的 就是回到地球 All we need now is to make it to Earth
廖谢 Lyosh
我很涨 I'm crammed in
如何... And how...
我该看到什么 How am I supposed to see?
也许我该离开座椅? Maybe I should go out?
指挥方向 Direct it
我准备好了 I'm ready!
西 West
完成 Done
西南 South-west
北 North
不 不 西北 No, no! North-west
北还是西北? - 慢点 North or north-west? - Easy, easy, easy...
顺时针 Clockwise
好的 轻轻的 更温柔 Okay, gently. Even more gently
西 - 完成 Yes, now west - Done
太多了 退后 停止 停止 Too much! Back it up! Stop! Stop!
再一次 All over again!
准备 Ready
西 West
西 West!
帕夏 我们正在失去时间 Pasha, we're losing time
那行不通 廖谢 That won't work, Lyosh
我自己来 I'll do it myself
你在干什么 重心会转移 What are you doing? The gravity center will shift
解开座位 Free the seat
那我该去哪里? So where should I go?
去那里 在舷窗下 Go there, under the porthole
我会试试 I'll try
好的 抓住我的腿 OK, hold my legs
我抓住了 I'm holding
廖谢 我来瞄准 Lyosha, I'll take aim
我们要非常小心 And we'll very carefully
安静如同小老鼠 Quiet as little mice
坐回去 Sit back
快点 伙计 否则我们将登陆中国 Do it quick, buddy. Otherwise we'll land in China
别催我 如果我滑倒 我们将飞回太空 Don't rush me. If I slip up, we'll fly into space
慢点 Easy
回到座位上 Back to the seats
地球稳定吗 Is the Earth steady?
在漂流 It's drifting
多少? - 大约超过7度 How much? - About 7 degrees already
氮气是怎么回事? What's with the nitrogen?
几乎为零 Almost at zero
廖谢 你有连接吗 Lyosha, are you attached?
是 Yep
已检测到制动引擎运行 Retro engine run has been detected
最好知道他们的最终着陆点 It'd be great to know where they will end up
我们最终会在监狱 如果有万一 We'll end up in jail, if anything
但他们会降落 But they will land
遥测器探测到一些倾向 The telemetry detected some inclination
看来 他们离开了自己的座位 自行瞄准了 It seems, they left their seats to take aim
他们坐回去后 重心将转移 And when they were sitting back, the gravity center shifted
那又怎样? So what?
着陆路径可能被改变 The landing path can change
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 可以吗 Sergey Pavlovich, can I?
倾角超过六或七度 With the inclination over six or seven degrees
他们将进入大气层 They will get into the atmosphere
过于锐角 With a very acute angle
宇宙飞船可能会弹飞 The spaceship might ricochet off
再次回到轨道上 And get back to the orbit again
重力会把它们拉回来 The gravity will pull them back...
还有时间 But that won't be soon
鲍里斯·维克托罗维奇 计算所有可能的着陆位置 Boris Viktorovich, calculate all possible landing positions
保持专注 Stay focused
拭目以待 Let's wait
发射机信号 The transmitter signal
希望 And hope...
平安 For the best
今天是星期四吗 Is it Thursday?
还是星期五? Or Friday?
我不知道 I have no idea
孩子们起床了吗 You think the children have got up?
我想知道维卡去托儿所还是... I wonder if Vika went to the daycare or again...
廖谢 别担心 Lyosha, don't worry
如果我滑倒 那么大约有三年 If I slipped up, then in about three years...
重力都会起作用的 The gravity will work anyway
被光荣埋葬 Be buried with honours
那么 So...
我们吃点东西吧 Let's have a bite to eat
怎么样 美味佳肴 How about that! What delicacies!
罗宋汤 Borscht
可惜没有大蒜 It's a pity there's no garlic
你要来点吗 Do you want some?
廖谢 Lyosha!
你... You are...
好像有重力 Seems like gravity
系好美味佳肴 回家去 Belay the delicacies! Going home!
绝对要 指挥官同志 That's affirmative, comrade commander!
释放储备制动引擎 Blow-off reserve retro engine
分离确认 Separation confirmed
准备仪器模块分离 释放 Get ready for instrument module separation. Blow-off!
部分模块尚未分离 Partial, the module hasn't been separated
廖谢 坚持住 会旋转的 Lyosh, hold on! It's going to spin
好了 分开了 Okay! It came apart!
活着吗 Alive?
帕夏? Pash?
我活着 Yes, I am!
你这个笨蛋 You fool!
你害怕吗 - 你为什么要这么做? Were you scared? - Why'd you do that?
玩够了吗 - 是 Done? - Yeah
我们走吧? Let's go?
准备好? Ready?
会很大声 It will be loud
等一下 Wait a sec
你准备好了吗 - 是 So are you ready? - Yep
着陆后3小时 3 hours after the landing
"我们在24区 没有信号" "We are at square 24, no signal"
"22区 仍然没有" "Square 22, still nothing"
"在整个短波范围内 没有信号 继续搜索" "...in the whole short-wave range, no signal. Continue searching"
为什么凭借苏联科学的力量 Why, with all the power of Soviet science,
我们无法探测到一个无线电信号 We cannot detect one radio beacon
在给定的正方形区内! In a given square!
信号在重返大气层时消失了 这可能意味着 The signal disappeared during re-entry into the atmosphere. It can mean...
没可能 It can't
我们需要特定的版本 We need specific versions
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 Sergey Pavlovich
显然他们降落在我们没料到的地方 Apparently, they landed somewhere we didn't expect
已部署全面搜索行动 A full-scaled search operation has been deployed
你需要冷静 You need cool it
并休息 And get some rest
我会休息的 等我们找到他们 I'll get rest when we've found them
有什么假设? What are the assumptions?
首先 信号塔可能损毁于硬着陆 First, the beacon might be broken from a hard landing
第二 可能内饰已经损坏 Second, they might have damaged it when they were cutting the upholstery
他们有便携发射器 以备不需 They have a portable transmitter for that case
手动发送信号 To send signals manually
为什么不能检测它? So why can't we detect it?
发射机的电池在低温下不工作 The batteries of the transmitter don't work at low temperature
那又怎样?他们不知道如何暖和电池吗 So what? It wouldn't dawn upon them how to warm a battery?
首先 他们必须解决如何暖和自己 First they have to work out how to warm themselves
太空服 失去了生命支持系统 它不是为低温设计的 The spacesuits, unplugged from the life support system, are not designed for low temperature
他们无法在舱内栖身 一小时内就会变成冰箱 They cannot shelter in the capsule as well. It will be like a freezer in an hour
也许 无线电波只是无法穿透 Perhaps, the radio waves just cannot pass
短波信号的质量很大程度上取决于地形和天气条件 The quality of a short-wave signal depends a lot on a terrain and weather conditions
在恶劣的天气条件下 Let's say they turned out to be in adverse weather conditions
他们能撑多久? How long can they hold out?
一天 A day
针叶林带 挡住了信号 Taiga. It's turning off the signal
但我们将使用莫尔斯电码 But we will use Morse code
我们使用完美古老的莫尔斯电码 We'll make it with good old Morse code
莫尔斯电码是非常可靠的 Morse code is very reliable
你最好防寒 阿列克谢 You'd better winterize, Alexey
没事 It will keep
V-N V-N
V-N, V-N... V-N, V-N...
什么是"V N"? What's"V-N"?
"一切正常" V-N,"Everything normal"
你有良心吗 Do you have a conscience?
他们着陆了 我们的老鹰 V-N They've landed, our eagles! V-N!
什么 - VN代表"一切正常" What? - It's V-N."Everything normal"
所以你"一切正常"? So you're"everything normal"?
等等 现在是最有趣的时刻... Hey, wait! It will be the most interesting moment now...
救援行动 - 别担心 没有你 也会拯救他们的 ... Rescue operation - Don't worry, they will rescue them without you
明天 电视上会有一切 They will show everything on TV tomorrow
你为什么总是... - 去吧 Ahh, why do you always... - Go, go..
干涉国家机密 Enough to intervene in state secrets
克里姆林宫 The Kremlin
正在等待正式声明 ...is waiting an official statement
我们必须在明天10点之前完成 We have to do it tomorrow by 10 AM
我们什么都没准备 We have nothing to make yet
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 你得好好休息 Sergey Pavlovich, you need to get some rest
现在一切都取决于你 Nothing depends on you now
直到早上 都有充裕的时间 如果不浪费 There is a plenty of time until the morning, if we don't waste it
中将同志 允许我说... Comrade lieutenant general! Permission to speak...
天气预报来了 预计在乌拉尔山脊上会有大雪 The weather report has come. Heavy snowfall is expected all over the Ural ridge
北极气旋在那里移动 An Arctic cyclone is moving there
夜间气温将下降到零下31华氏度 The temperature will fall to -31 F at night
晚上 At night
但现在还是白天 对吗 But it's still day now, right?
还是白天 It's still day
着陆后6小时 6 hours after landing
如果搜到信号 还需要大约两个小时的三角定位 If they have got the signal, it's about two hours for triangulation...
所以他们很快就要来了 So they are going to come soon
他们很快就会的 They'll be soon
如果搜到信号的话 If they got it
拿去 Here
该你了 Your turn
冷静 Chill out
我们知道我们要做什么 We knew what we were getting into
如果他们找到了日记 If they find the journal,
就算 任务已完成 Consider, the task is completed
你说完成是什么意思? What do you mean completed?
你忘了你的女儿了吗 Did you forget about your girls?
他们在熨你的制服 准备迎接他们的爸爸活着归来 They are ironing your uniform. Preparing to meet their dad alive
你明白?活下去 You understand? Alive
不是变成冰冻的猛犸狗屎 Not a frozen piece of mammoth shit
不 伙计 No, buddy
帮我一把 Give me a hand
不 No!
我的家人不会原谅我的 My family won't forgive me for this
谁将第一次带维卡去学校? Who will take Vika to school for the first time?
听好了 耶夫同志 So here it is, comrade Belyaev
没有接到放弃的命令 There wasn't an order to give up
别无聊了 我很快就回来 Don't get bored, I'll be back soon
好吧 Alright
传令 Pass the order
所有飞机出动 Put everything into the air that flies
搜索区域加倍 Double the search area
是 长官 Yes, sir
坎曼宁将军有令... General Kamanin's order...
发送记录文本 Send the text for the record of the message
哪一个 尼古拉·彼得罗维奇吗 Which one, Nikolay Petrovich?
两个都要 Both variants
晚上好 同志们 Good evening, comrades
"机组死亡 "death of the crew"
我可以喝点水吗 May I have some water?
我准备好了 I'm ready
"预备" "Ready"
3月18日 March 18th
1965年 1965
在苏联 以测试为目的 In the Soviet Union, for the purpose of testing,
上升二号航天器被送入地球行星轨道 The Voskhod 2 spacecraft was sent to the orbit of Earth planet
由苏联两名飞行和宇航员驾驶 It was manned by two pilots and cosmonauts of the USSR
中校帕维尔· 伊万洛维奇·耶夫 Lieutenant Colonel Pavel Ivanovich Belyaev
少校阿列克谢·阿奇西波维奇·列昂诺夫 And Major Alexey Arkhipovich Leonov
在试飞期间 历时超过一天... During the test flight, which lasted more than a day...
着陆时 因降落伞的绳索扭结 During the landing, the ropes of the parachute twisted
宇宙飞船高速坠落 And the spaceship continued falling with a high speed
造成 Which was the cause of
机组死亡 Death of the crew
你们精神错乱了吗 还是在耍我们? Are you guys off your rocker? You kidding us?
嘿 Hey!
你们在哪里? Where are you?
你们没脑子吗 Ain't you got no brains?
我们还活着 We are alive here!
我们还活着 Hey! We're alive
你聋了还是怎么了 Are you deaf or what?
嘿 Hey!
我们还活着 We're alive
嘿 我们还活着 Hey, we're alive
"过早死亡" "...Untimely death"
卓越的研究人员和宇航员 Of the remarkable researchers and cosmonauts
帕维尔·伊万诺维奇· 耶夫 Pavel Ivanovich Belyaev
阿列克谢·阿奇西波维奇·列昂诺夫 And Alexey Arkhipovich Leonov
沉重而无法挽回的损失 Is a heavy and irreparable loss
为了全体苏维埃人民 For the whole of the Soviet people
他们被授予 They have been awarded the title of
苏联英雄的称号 Heroes of Soviet Union
于死后 Posthumously
帕夏 Pasha
你没事吧? Are you OK?
不要睡觉 Don't sleep!
嘿 帕夏 Hey, Pash
帕夏 Pash
别想睡觉 不要睡觉 Don't think of sleep! Don't sleep!
就是这样了 廖谢 That's it, Lyosh
帕维尔·伊万洛维奇 Pavel Ivanovich
好吧 Alright
你知道我们现在要做什么吗 Do you know what we're going to do now?
我们将为记者排练演讲稿 We will rehearse the speech for the reporters
因为你总是站着 像... - 你自己处理 Because you're always standing like a... - You'll handle it by yourself
你现在是英雄了 You're a hero now
我吗 不 Am I? Nah
当我照顾奶牛的时候 你就是个英雄 You were a hero when I just helped to farm cows
你已经去打仗了 And you'd already been to war
你已经飞过多少架飞机了 我只梦见天空 How many battle flights did you already have! And I was only dreaming about the sky
一 One
一什么 One what?
一次飞行 One flight
我甚至没有开过枪 And I didn't even shoot
老家伙打仗 年轻人准备飞机 The older guys fought, and we, younger guys, prepared the planes
横扫机场 Swept the aerodrome
最后 他们给了我一次战斗飞行 And finally, they gave me a battle flight
我想 轮到我了 I thought, here is my turn!
也许我会好好表现 Maybe I'll be useful for something
敌人没有攻击我们 The enemy didn't attack us
我们飞回了基地 We flew and returned to the base
就像我们根本没有飞过 As if we didn't even fly
第二天 他们投降了 And on the next day they capitulated
好吧 这是你所谓的"英雄" Well, here's your"hero"
帕维尔·耶夫 Pavel Belyaev
你知道吗 Do you know...
为什么我去了飞行学校? Why I went to flight school?
为什么 - 津贴比艺术学院更多 Why? - The allowance was bigger than in the art Academy
现在 我本该照片挂满大街 Right now I would be painting my pictures living on easy street
但不是 全世界都看到我吊在绳索下 But no. The whole world saw how I dangled from the tether
太夸张了 我差点在宇航服里拉屎 It was inflated so much, I almost shit my spacesuit
这就是征服太空的阿列克谢·列昂诺夫 Here is a conqueror of space Alexey Leonov
帕夏 原谅我 Pashka, forgive me
我把你带到这个境况 That I got you into this
不 不 No, no
还好 That's good
好什么 What's good?
还好 It's good that
你没有成为一个艺术家 You didn't become an artist
不然我还能和谁一起飞翔 Otherwise, who else would I fly with so well
也许我们会再次飞翔 Maybe we'll fly again
取决于祖国的说法 Depends on what Motherland will say
祖国会说什么 What the Motherland will say
他们降落了 They've landed
成功了 Successfully
寻求救援 Asking for help
但没人会来 But nobody's coming to them
但他们会来找你 你会进监狱的 But they will come for you, and you'll go to jail
非常成功 Very successful
但我没有人可求助 But I won't have anyone to ask for help
但还有选择吗 But how else?
着陆9小时后 9 hours from the landing
天气转坏 The weather turned bad
我必须暂停搜索行动 I have to pause the search operation
明白了 I see...
等暴风雪停止 As soon as the storm stops...
是 当然 Yes, yes... Of course
我们必须通知 We have to inform...
这些家庭 The families
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 也许 Sergey Pavlovich, maybe...
我们不应该着急? We shouldn't hurry?
但你想怎么办? But what do you want?
你想让他们从电台播音员那里听到吗 Do you want them to hear about it from the radio announcer?
我们收到信号了 We've got the signal!
谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 看起来 我们有信号了 Sergey Pavlovich, it seems... We've got the signal
你的意思是"看起来" What you mean,"it seems..."
对不起 中将同志 I'm sorry, comrade Lieutenant General
有委员会的电话 There was a call from the Committee
来自库页岛的无线电爱好者与他们取得了联系 Some radio fan from Sakhalin got in touch with them
他说 他不小心得到了宇航员的信号 He says, he accidentally got a signal from the cosmonauts
不小心? Accidentally? How's that an accident?
不小心 Accidentally...
无线电爱好者 Radio fan...
库页岛 Sakhalin...
哪个区域? Which square?
根据三角剖分的结果 62区 According the triangulation it turns out... square 62nd
我们62区有没有人? Do we have anyone at the 62nd?
我们有一架直升机 一英里内 Yes, we have one helicopter within a mile from there
打电话给他 Call - Call him
216号 有来自宇航员的信号 位于62区 Craft '216'! The signal from the cosmonauts was located at the 62nd square
你们距离最近 尝试肉眼搜索 You are the closest. Try to gain visual contact
重复 尝试肉眼搜索 Repeat, try to gain visual contact
这是"216" This is '216'
我在62区 I'm at square 62
气象条件不好 The meteorological conditions are bad
趁天气尚可继续搜索 - 是 长官 Continue the search while they can - Yes, sir
听到了吗 You hear?
那是找我们的 That's for us
他们发现我们了 They've found us
在哪里? Where?
信号枪 The flare gun
帕夏 Pash
信号枪在哪? Where's the flare gun?
我丢了吗 Did I lose it?
笨手笨脚 Uh? Klutz
指挥官 油箱快干了 Commander, the tanks are almost dry
我们应该回去 否则我们可能无法返回基地 We should get back, or we might not make it to the base
这是'216' 燃料几乎耗完 This is '216', the fuel is almost out here
他们必须返航 They have to get back
让他们回来 - 是 长官 Let them get back - Yes, sir
"216"返回基地 '216', return to base
"216" '216'
我是科罗廖夫 This is Korolyov
谢尔盖 Sergey
你叫什么名字? What's your name?
少校马克洛夫 Major Markelov
你的名字呢  And by your first name?
弗拉基米尔 Vladimir
洛迪亚 听我说 Volodya, listen to me
在树上的某处 Somewhere on the trees there
必有降落伞 There must be a chute
非常的大 It's really big
很显眼 Noticeable
请仔细看 Please, look closely
很难不注意到它 It's hard not to notice it
你听到了吗 Do you hear me?
肯定 That's affirmative
搞什么... What's the...
我把它放哪儿了啊? Where did I put it, ah?
为什么老是半途而废 Why all half-assed
来吧 帮忙 Come on, help
廖谢 救命 冻死了 Lyosh, help, it froze
帕夏 Pashka!
拜托 伙计 Here you go, man
坚持 Hold on...
我们有紧急燃料 我们必须去 We have emergency fuel. We must go
廖谢 给个信号 什么也看不到 Lyosha, give a signal. Can't see anything
坚持住 帕夏 Hold on, Pashka
你是男子汉 You're the man
等等 我来帮你 Wait... I'll help you
坚持 Hold on
指挥官 我们必须离开 否则我们将无法到基地 Commander! We must leave, or we won't make it to the base
这是"216" This is '216'
我们看不见降落伞 We can't see the chute
没有来自宇航员的信号 There is no a signal from the cosmonauts
我们试过了 We tried
我们很抱歉 We are sorry
我不能弯曲手指 - 来吧 慢慢来 Can't bend my fingers - Come on, do it slowly
帕夏 慢慢来 Pasha, do it slowly
快 快 Come on... Come on
我不能 I can't
"216"返回基地 '216', return to base
收到 返程 That's affirmative, going back
这是"216" This is '216'!
信号弹 A flare!
信号弹 Signal flare!
派救援队 Send the rescue team
"216" 我们正在接收精确坐标 '216', we're copying the exact coordinates
布里雅克镇东南20英里 20 miles south-east of Bereznyaky town
坐标56度37分... The coordinates: 56 degrees, 37 hours...
谢谢 Thank you
洛迪亚 Volodya
能给我点什么吗 Can I get something?
当然 谢尔盖·帕夫洛维奇 Sure, Sergey Pavlovich
切克洛夫斯基机场 莫斯科州(地区) 发射后的第三天 Chkalovsky Aerodrome. Moscow Oblast (Region). The third day after the launch
爸爸 Daddy!
爸爸 Dad!
廖什卡 Lyoshka!
你在做什么 孩子?你半夜去哪儿了 What are you doing, kid? Where did you go in the middle of the night?
她到处睡觉 She sleeps anywhere
谁? Who?
鸟 The bird
还好你在 That's good for you!
你不害怕吗 Weren't you scared?
你的心跳很快 Your heart is beating fast
你到处跑吗 - 不 爸爸 我没有跑 Did you run around? - No, dad, I didn't run
我在飞 I flew
"莫斯科广播" "This is Moscow broadcast."
莫斯科广播 This is Moscow broadcast
苏联电报通讯社 The Telegraph Agency of the USSR message
3月19日 在莫斯科时间 下午12:02 March 19th, at 12:02 pm Moscow time
上升二号太空飞船 The Voskhod 2 spaceship
载人飞船 包括 That was manned by the crew, consisting of
指挥官 上校耶夫·帕维尔·伊万诺维奇 The commander, Colonel Belyaev Pavel Ivanovich
第二飞行员 中校列昂诺夫·阿列克谢·阿奇西波维奇 And the second pilot, Lieutenant Colonel Leonov Alexey Arkhipovich
已成功着陆 Has landed successfully
在彼尔姆地区 In the area of Perm city
耶夫和列昂诺夫同志都很好 Comrades Belyaev and Leonov are well
"献给我的朋友和指挥官 帕维尔· 万诺维奇耶夫" 阿列克谢·列昂诺夫 "Dedicated to my friend and commander, Pavel Ivanovich Balyaev,"A. Leonov
首杀字幕组 [太空第一步 V1.1蓝光3D版] 20171001