Let's do it differently this time
Very different
His name is Miles Morales
A radioactive spider bit him
And he wasn't the only one bitten.
Problems are not always easy for him.
And he is not alone in this problem.
Now it has to finish itself.
And once again he is not alone.
You think you know the rest of the story.
But you don't know.
I thought I knew the rest, but...
...I do not know.
I don't want to hurt her.
But I do.
And he's not the only one I've hurt
Hey
Def Leppard (rock band)
Gwen
Chelsea, New York Ground-65
Spider Gwen World
Is the song over?
Apparently they have.
Ok my friend if you don't follow us and want to talk.
I don't join groups to talk about my feelings.
That's why I joined…
... to beat my feelings with this stick.
If you don't talk about your problems, possibly from somewhere...
I'm fine.
A sane person would not respond like that.
They say I'm great, thanks, how are you?
I'm fine thanks.
Wow   -How are you?
Really?  Gwen, don't worry.
I don't understand you.   -You are right.
I sing to the drums.
I always wanted to be in a band.
I don't think I've found the right one yet.
In this job, you always know it's best to go it alone.
Before Miles.
It's Peter.
I think it's great, I don't know.
This is a dangerous masked man
I don't know, he seems like a nice guy.
If he has nothing to hide, why is he wearing a mask?
Okay, let's stop politicizing this matter.
Thank you, Meg
But they really don't know me.
And I really don't know him that well.
If you touch it again, man
Gwen, it's okay.
Until it's too late.
Hi Gwen.   -Hi
Peter.
What the.
Not.
No no no.
What are you doing?
I just want to be special.
Like you, Gwen.
Gwen?   -Do not worry
Who is Gwen?
Everything went well.
Everything is going well.   -no... don't leave.
Peter.
hey hey hey
Peter?
After that incident, I really didn't find any other friends.
Except for one.
But he is not here.
And there's no way you're going there.
I have to announce that Captain George Stacey is leading the team after Spider-Woman.
who is this
And why doesn't he show his face?
Peter Parker, an innocent student.
Peter Parker, often at my table, at meals.
He is my daughter's boyfriend.
I won't rest even until I find Spiderwoman.
Oh, hey, hey, hey.
how is the band
Yeah, that's great, I give up.
So dad knows, it's okay.
In the case of Spiderwoman, I accomplished something.
Okay, that's great.   -I approached him.
Let me say I feel it.
And I.
Catching him is good for us.   -Don't be so sure.
He killed your friend.
I do not understand.   -What do you want to say?
I know what happened, I was there.
... fled the scene.
Maybe he had no other choice.
I have to do my job, Gwen.   -He won't bring her back.
I also lost someone you love.
Good?
Yes, dad can say that.
I just wanted to say...didn't you hug your dad?
We have the ability to have a superman for all units.
...a suspect in the museum.   -Maybe this is him.
Some kind of eagle   -See you later
Does not matter.
I will call you.
The situation is very bad here.
We need help.
Captain Stacey spoke, I'm five minutes away.
I need you to pay attention.
Chances are a girl will be found.
Tonight, it looks like we're going to catch Spiderman.
Oh that's good.
Please sir.
Explain how a person with a 12 meter wingspan could enter the Guggenheim without being noticed?
The Ugliness of New Yorkers Everyone has a story.
Do you know what he wants?
do you know Italian
I am Irish.
Maybe he likes pasta.
We all enter at my command.
Watch out for signs of Spiderwoman.
Hi
I found her.
Stop following me?
Okay shut up.
Eagles!
Calling their name usually works.
I think it worked.
I'm not an Eagle.
The pinnacle of human genius.
You're not an Eagle in my world, who are you?  Are you made of parchment paper?
What world did you bring me to?
Bully, I was like that.
Where are you from, my friend?
I am an artist, I will finish my work here.
Oh, that's great, you're from the Renaissance.
Yes.    -Let me guess.
You drink espresso the old fashioned way from Da Vinci's era.
A portal opens and you are thrown here.
I'm right?
Yes.  Only this
Do you think that maybe there is no need to destroy art museums like Alki?
This is not art at all.
That's what we're talking about, right?
Oh, that's cool.
That is, this is what we call the art of metaphorical interpretation.
But it's still art.
Oh no, cousin.
I don't play with fire, my friend
You are made of paper
Goodbye, little girl
Oh no.
Excuse me, who are you?
This is a secret.
Are you a blue leopard?   -Not
Cider with a blue cap?   -Not!
Dark Garfield?  Freeman?   -You have to finish it.
I'm from another dimension.
Really?
Actually, I'm not confused at all.
My name is Miguel O'Hara (Spiderman 2099)
I lead an elite task force committed to protecting the Multiverse.
Actually, it's not a problem at all.
Can you go anywhere with that bracelet?
It's sadder than a bracelet.
Okay, how sensitive are you now?
Look, it's a Renaissance flying turkey.
Gotta do justice... so we're good.
No problem, son.
From now on I take over.
Good
So stay away.
Why do you say that?
You're not funny at all.
I do not know.
I must say that the work you have brought is very hard.
What nonsense?   -Interworld Kingpin device
What do you say?
What about you, Ghar Ghor   -Shut up.
We save the multiverse.
You opened a portal for people like this to accidentally walk into another dimension.
And now let me return them all to their rightful place before time and space are broken.
Don't let me tell you the story of Doctor Strange and the schoolchildren of world 199999(MCU world, number 199999)
Who is Doctor Strange?
Maybe it's better not to do drugs.
Captain, stay here, I'll be right back.
Do you want me to do this right?
Oh, good
It has Hammerspace.
Hammerspace: This is a timeless, interdimensional storage space where cartoon characters pick things out of thin air and make them appear.
layla can you do it  you know that.
No, you have to say it.
Call for help.
I can not hear.   -Call for help.
... please call.
Okay, I'm calling.
But I like what you have to say.
spider woman
And I.
You are...?
Oh, this?
I don't know if it's a boy or a girl, it will be a surprise for my husband.
He thinks mature.
But it is very good.
Are you going to adopt me?   -What the?
Can you guys focus on this threat across time and space?
How is the girl?   -Not!
We can get some help from him.   -Not.
Because he called you Dark Garfield?   -Not.
Can you say anything but no?   -No, no.
Why did you say no?   -You know why.
Well, that's enough
Feel this Bomb.
Don't let him run away.
You ruined everything.
I thought something was wrong.
Surrender that you are under siege. "Get out of here right now."
I am a good person.
It seems you are not a good person.
Just shut your mouth and... no.
Help!   -Need help.
Yeah, I think it's Bansky.
That's what I thought too.
Raise your hand!
Captain, come on.
Armed suspect.
What weapon?  I do not have.
get down!
Which?  Should I raise my hand or lie down?
You are under arrest.
I just saved a lot of people.
For killing Peter Parker.
Don't worry captain.
You have the right to remain silent.   -You do not understand.
You do not understand.
Father.
I want to tell dad.
But you know why I don't want to say that.
I understand why.
I didn't kill Peter.
He didn't like it... I didn't know it was Peter.
I have no choice.
How long have you been lying to me?
Can't you be a cop for a while and be my dad and listen to me?
Do you really think I'm a murderer?
Dad did this to help people, right?
It's not like that?
And I.
And now the way to help is to listen to me.
Please, father.
Father is the only thing I have.
You have the right to remain silent.
All your words will be in court.
Father, are you afraid of me?
You have the right to call a lawyer.
Without stopping.
Don't come near!
Father.
Calm.
We've got you covered.
Isn't that right, Miguel?
Layla, scan this vandalism.
There are no more discrepancies to be seen.
The main place is safe.
We can't just leave it.
He faced it alone.
I don't know how to fix the situation.
Yes.
Okay, join the team.
Brooklyn Earth-1610
I know Miles is still in second grade.
But we wanted to talk about his college interview...so.
I'm sure it can be found at any time.
He doesn't joke with anyone about his future
Excuse me, do you have an ATM?
Yes, there.
Better not be tied to the wall   -What?
It's ok.
It should be pretty simple.
Just drill a hole and take the money.
Not that one.
should.
Take the money and leave the car.
where is your money honey
hey man what are you doing there
No, it's not good at all.
I forgot my password.   -Go away.
Let me steal from you.
I will beat you.
No need.
I never stole.
Don't give me a bad robbery experience.   -bad robbery?
This store is my life.
I have a problem, you also have fairy powder.
See, I was a scientist, I still am.
By the way, have you ever heard of the company name Alchemex?
I worked there.
Then something happened.
I had a little accident.
Now I...
...I apologize.
First of all, I'm not stealing from you.
I mean, this ATM isn't yours, is it?
It's a bank, they're the criminals.
You are a criminal who stole from me.
You know, with this look, it wouldn't work anywhere else.  So I have to do it.
I don't want to work.   -Why bring an ATM?
Who is?
Why carry an ATM.
Spiders!
Hey Lenny, how much is this steak?
Spidey, if you catch him, it's free.
Oh, Spider-Man.  This is true.
So are you a cow or a spotted dog?
I am... (Stain)
We meet again, Spider-Man.
Ah, are you funny?   -Of course not.  Not!
So this is your costume?   -Unfortunately, this is my skin.
Oh shit.
You know, I'm your past.
A year ago.   -One moment.
Come on.
Look, I'm having fun   -Who are you talking to?
But we have to finish quickly.   -No, no, go on.
This is my job, sometimes very boring.
He is still there.
Okay, let's do it one last time.
My name is Miles Morales.
A radioactive spider bit me.
And for the past 1 year and 4 months, I've been the only Spider-Man in Brooklyn.
And everything went well.
hey hey hey
You are so painful.
I fight all kinds of bad guys.
In this villain, we see Frog-Man
Can't you act like a common criminal so I can catch you?
I designed my own costume and made it easy on the outside.
Aunt is going to Florida.   -Is ready.
I think I could be the judge.
I'm advertising baby powder.
I'm sorry I promoted baby powder.
I made a mistake.
Mine is out.
Error.
Then you go out.
I made another mistake.
New power options.
Excuse me.
How much longer can I lie about my identity?
I heard Spiderman is from Puerto Rico.
No, I think it's Dominica.
I mean, if I tell them, will they understand?
We love you and understand you even if you lied to us for a year.
Maybe in another world.
Sometimes I tell myself I wish I wasn't the only Spider-Man.
I'm bored.
Sometimes I miss them.
smile.
Although he turned out to be a thief.
I tried to do what he said.
Just to move on.
Dad: Where are you?  We are waiting for you.   -You read the message?
You know this is a life and death fight, right?   -Sorry Sorry.
Wait a minute my friend   -Dad: Honey, this is important.
No, no, no, just relax and do your job.
You turned your phone off at the movie, then didn't turn it off while you were fighting me?
"Finally," he said, "back up."
He wrote everything in one word.
Cool, right?
this child.
My godfather!
... sorry, the problem is somewhere
He wrote for a moment
I think this is going well
He is still writing
You know, I don't think that's a problem.
*
They are getting closer to us.
I've been waiting for this moment for a long time, so...
Hey, what's this goose?
I don't think I'll ever want this suit again.
I'm almost there, a mother with a smiling face.
*
In the end.    -I caught you.
I'm Spiderman and no one can run away from me.
Come back, we are sworn enemies.   -Do not run.
The back of your suit is very tight.
hi how are you
I am writing an article.
The bad guy on the roof is Peterson.
You can call the police. Tell them to arrest him.
I don't know, I feel like this is going to be my thing forever.
Only this time.
It started with calls, then wireless calls, then smartwatches.
Next month, I'll be your assistant.
I'm not your assistant
Are those my Jordans?
If they are the same size, I can't tell the difference.
See, everyone is the world.
And my job is to write your son's world on this piece of paper.
Goal   -That's great
I don't know this kid at all.
I don't know what he knows.
And he has to decide that he wants to commit to his future.
Or they engage in what they do when they come to school.
You can't have an ass and a date at the same time.
Unless you have a snorer.
Miles   -Of course, I know this is a good joke.
How are you?   -We have been waiting for a long time.
You're late   -You should have come earlier.
I know, I know, look.
I have to get back to homework, so can we get this over with?
Good.
Miles scores are almost good.
You are in the 18th grade of physics.
This is My Son.
And also in workshop art.
It disappeared.
You have 17 in English.
The teacher gave a difficult grade.
And the Spanish got 15.
What the?   -Oooh.
*
Mom, it's not my fault.
Does that mean it wasn't my fault?
Are you taking Spanish classes?
I just don't go to some classes.
Oh, so how much did you miss? How much means how much?
I mean there are 5.
Five?   -Five?
Actually 6.   -I'm going to skin you.
*
The whole story happened to me   -Very good.
We can still get out of this situation.
Excuse me, this situation?
Miles has a story to tell.
The story is not interesting at all.
Smith Miles Morales.   -Correct.
You grew up in a struggling immigrant family.
I'm from Puerto Rico, that's part of America.
We have a house in Brooklyn so we don't have a problem.
It doesn't matter, you're struggling too.
I will be captain next week.
And now he plans to get into the best physics program in the country.
We will do anything for him.
At Princeton University.
The one in New Jersey?
No, not at all, never too old.
New Jersey from New York?
There are many good universities in Brooklyn.
Princeton has the best quantum researchers in the country.   -Quantum researcher.
They transport electrons to the threshold of dimensions.  – Size threshold.
You could tell they were scanning the meter darkly.
No, I don't understand what he's saying.
I can help them find a way to travel to other dimensions.
Ah, good   -I think it's a good job.
Dad, when you were my age, you followed your dreams.
And you started your cartoon with Uncle Aaron, right?
He is different.
... i used to... see, when you were born... I was just my mother before
You see, life is an adventure.
You brought me to this school because you thought I could do something amazing.
And now I'm thinking the same thing.
And this is an amazing thing that they do.
Someone who can really teach me what I want.
But not all of them are in Brooklyn.
Here is your story.
Well, let's continue with that in mind.
Have you noticed?
Did Namusa get the joke?
Well, I have to go.   -Good.
It's a great topic to talk about.
See Miles Vaisa.
Did you order cake tonight?
Yes, Bau, you know, call me, I have to go.
Good?  Goodbye.
God, what should we do with this child?
For all units, we have supercriminal cases.
I have to go   -What?
You go too, Miles, everybody. Why should I stay?
Know.  Excuse me   -Why should I stay?
But we will find a way together.
And he.
I'm sorry, I'm very, very sorry.
He lied to you.    -Jeff?
Your son lied to him.
And I think you know that.
how is your article
The final work remains, it is part of the job.
No dad   -I think the guy ran away.
Thanks for saying I would see it.
Yes, you seem very busy.   -I agree.
You are too busy   -Yes, same conclusion.  Come see this.
Not very bad.   -Know.
What is the death of this child?
I don't know, God!  Hi
Spider-Man   -Mr. Morales, I mean Officer Morales.
It's not what you think
Hi!  Hey   -officer.
My son is a student here.
I am a member of the parents' association.
Do you know how much I have to pay for all this?
You gave up in the middle of the fight and left.
Your steps are very careless and rough.   -Namusa?
And the first thing is to show yourself.
Yeah, I agree with this guy.
Give it to me, this guy isn't even the villain of the week.
What are you telling me, do you know it's here?
Don't worry man.
Everything is under control.
And he.
We will definitely come back here again.
Know?  You are so much like that boy.
Really?
It's so stupid.
Imagine this.
We're going back to where it all began.
The birthplace of our connection.
Hey, don't try to please me with nice words.
I break tables every day.
Do you remember everything that happened?
what are you saying
Creative events.
What the.
Yes?   -Well, the call has been cut.
*
Look, we're in the middle of a story.
Fate brought us here.
You understand now, don't you?
I don't understand at all.
I am your sworn enemy.
You are not my sworn enemy.
You made a mistake.
*
Do you really not remember what you did to me?
What have I done for you?   -Um, no.
I worked at Alcomex.
I did an experiment on the interworld device that brought Spider-Man here from another dimension.
From size number 42.
*
The spider runs and bites you.
My Spider turns you into Spider-Man.
What the.
You go to the buffet.
You hit me sweet
I beat the bad guys with a lot of food.
You flaunt your cheeky chops and everyone loves it.
But nobody knows what it means to be on the other side of the joke.
I just want to create a happy atmosphere.
i created you
You also created me.
Spiderman, why did you create this guy?   -I didn't get to Mola.
Tare said sleepily
When I was in this room, you blew it up.
Because of you, I lost my job, my life and my face.
My family doesn't even want to see me.
I made you a hero.
But you make me like this.
Look at me.
You brought me this disaster.
I will make you respect me.
I am your sworn enemy
So where did it disappear to?
He held her tight.
You know you have to catch the bad guy, right?
I always understand.
Usually.
Gutierrez, get the crane.
Good sir.
That's why they don't like our people, son.
We?
Look, I'm trying to do the right thing.
I said I was trying.
So you need to be a better role model.
I am a very good role model.
Hey Gutierrez, abort the crane.
Do you want to talk about it?
Are you confused about something?
Well, men of your generation neglect their mental health too
Oh boy
what am i doing wrong
Because no matter what I do, there's always someone who thinks I'm wrong
I know how it feels
So how is your son doing?
Do you think he can handle his life?
tell the truth yes
He's a good kid   -seriously?    -
you know, scary
He said very wise things
... It is so good.  Well, I have to go little by little
And then he did this really stupid thing
I just don't want him to ruin his life
Maybe it's best to leave him alone
excuse me, what   -What?  What happened?   -
I do not know
And I hate that he's not honest with me
Maybe he is afraid to talk to you
Why would anyone be afraid to talk to me?
What should I know?
The point is, you think you're a
good father, you think everything is fine
And then they grow
I just don't want to lose him, you know?
Well, as someone who is not in this position and is not in your family
I say you should let him stand on his own two feet, man
so yes   -
You are right
If that's not good, then what is?
I have to go now
Yes, and catch him on
bastard, don't worry
I don't think that person will ever show up again
What happened?
Good
I think I threw myself into it
Well, it's new
!Hello
One, two, three, three, three, no, no echo
assumption
I stuck my head in the hole
!Hello
Stop it, stop it
How cool is that?
My hole can take me anywhere
Chinatown Earth  -688 Venom World Tom Hardy
Sorry, hello
Sorry to bother you, I know you are busy
What do you want?   -I know it's weird.  I found Abad out of nowhere   -
But I think I've turned into an extraordinary metadimensional being
GOOD?    -GOOD?    -
I literally tore apart the fabric of time and space
It's like Thursday night for you
You act like these weird things always happen to you
can i have a piece of gum please
The power of the multiverse is in the palm of my hand(a dialogue similar to that of the famous Doctor Octopus)
My hole is not a curse
They didn't answer
Can you stop talking about your holes?
A series of tormented children
No, no, no, you'll love it
Look, look, look
My place is over, you don't understand
Um, get down to business, gentlemen
I'm coming for you, Spiderman!
Oh no
Peter Parker, Spider-Man Earth  -13122
Tomorrow morning, there will be a picture of Spiderman on the front page.
The photos have to be good this time. You're absolutely right, boss.
shut up get out   -hey boss...
I'm going to work, God, I want a replacement
Miguel, I'm Peter
We have an anomaly
Thanks Peter, you are one of the best
Jess, who's gonna get it?
Can't you see Miles?    -Not
Haven't you seen Miles?
What are you doing now?
Give a speech   -what?
Okay, everyone's listening.   -Not.
Everybody's listening, I'm with everybody.
Have mercy, Lord
Rio, speak up
Hello
And I want you to know, no matter what.
Even though we have had our ups and downs, I am
so proud of you today, I will always be proud
Write in parentheses
Most of the time lol
Hey Mr. Spiderman
It doesn't go well with the cake
Congrats on the promotion, Dad!
Can't you write smaller?
Can you say a little more text?
come to us again
What else can I say about Jeff?
As a child, he weighed almost 4.5 kilograms
I know, I know you're ashamed of yourself for saying that
his mother must have died in childbirth
Look at his shoulders
Oh no.  Well, that's enough.  fine
Oh gosh
Very good.
Just give me the microphone, that's enough
Good.  Thank you Rio John for your speech   -Who is this child?
You know, I don't always know what to do with my life
When I was young, I was drawn to many different paths
When my brother and I came to this neighborhood, there were only a few people on Jalan Velo
You kicked us out of the store and now no one thinks I'm protecting you
And then I had a baby and things started to get better
And I don't know why you drink for my health because I have to drink for your health
...Meanwhile, the cake is in the car
So out of respect for my brother who misses us everyday I bet he's laughing out loud right now
Aaron Davis, the dear uncle of his soul mate
Brothers, they made me captain
Out of respect for my wife my love I don't even know where to start because it never ends
Don't take my microphone
And in honor of my son
The main reason I do these things is because I'm in love with Miles
And I will always be there for you
Benny June, please play again
I will kill this child
Hey, congratulations
Thank you for coming
Hey Miles, where have you been?   -What is it?    -
Hey, did you study well?   -Yes, i read it...
Hello
Hey, your parents are looking for you.  I
don't know why I've been here all this time
Aha, I understand
Hi, you should be here at 5...
I know, I know, I know   -you disrespect your father   -
Yes   -you lost the beautiful Sankhrani   -
Never mind, have you seen Kika yet?
Well written posts
"I'm not proud of you"
I don't want to say that
Your father studied for eight months
Nine months is like a pregnancy
No, not at all   -of course not   -
you have to sit in that lady's office and we'll talk without going anywhere
It was an emergency, what was
this just now? Emergency graffiti?
Is there an emergency party with your friends that I've never come across?
explain think you have
explained completely
funny
Our son Jeff is
funny, I'm not laughing
Hello
Ahab, what a beautiful family
mature boy
I don't feel mature
Wow, what a beautiful dress
Good, good, good
did you eat that food
hey where
Who do you live with?
...just   -Genki?    -
I never liked
You do not like it
He called me by my first name
Oh how I hate this job, I have
other friends besides Ganki
For example, who?
For example, Peter, yes, you know Peter, but he's left town for now
Oh, Gwanda, he left town too
Miles, don't worry about who you love
do you speak spanglish
Has it ever occurred to you that maybe I'm not in front of you?
Am I doing normal personal work safely?
absolutely not   -
I am 15 years old and I am considered an adult
Oh, that's right
you don't even have a driver's license   -not even mom   -
Because we live in New York, we never plan to go
This is my life.
This is not your life.
This is my life, your father's life and your grandfather's life, whoever brought you here.
Okay, now anything, anything.
Up to you?
wow
I can say?
Please tell me that
I know you're not allowed to go out
What is it   -
While?  Dad   -a month   -
Ma'am, are you serious?
Yes, we're serious
1 you don't understand
You're right, I have no
idea what's going on here
So why didn't you tell me?
just listen to me
Okay, Pahlavi, I'm listening,
tell me to see
Say whatever you want
What do you want to tell me?
you know what doesn't matter at all
Very well, go
Because your sentence is already two months
Isn't that great?
two months
I'm sick and I'm not allowed to go out
The Amazing Fantasy Comic 1962 #15
Miles, Miles
Do you have a minute?
... how... how is it here?
How are you, um... how are you?
I'm fine thanks
Yeah, it's good
to see you grow up
Growth spurt during puberty yes
The mute became even pinker
Is this the room you grew up in?
Here he was
But my dorm room is very mature
So cool, I used to play with this when I was younger
This for the collection
I have the same thing
In fact, it is extremely rare
Why is it still in the package?
Good
Is this your design?
They are good?
wow how much
I miss you too
So what are you doing here?  I thought... that I would never see you again
Do you want to get out of here?
I... I'm not allowed to go out
against the present
Spider-Man is not allowed?
... Well
Miles
Your father is ready to listen to you now
It's three months
Okay, let me see
Is there an anthology community where all Spideys belong?
Well, there is also a woman, Jess Drew (who is white)
The car works
God, how much can I learn from him   -cars?   -
Yes, I learned a lot
I've improved a lot, see?
Seriously?
So let's see
!Let's go
Get started!
That's not a problem at all
And he said it changed everything
Who are Sahih and Miguel?
He's a ninja vampire spider, but he's a good person
Good vampire?  I never saw him in my dream
So how long has he been inviting you?
That was just a few months ago
A few months is a long time, right?
One or two months
see you
look at me
Thanks James
Well, this group of you   -look at those idiots   -
how do you work   -The man is striped, he wants to carry a bag   -
We are trying to prevent the collapse of the multiverse
I think I've done this before
For example, last week we had an assignment based on Shakespeare
John?    -... and me and the husband   -
Hey, let's see who's Hobby?
God, you're going to love it
Sometimes he let me follow him
What this means?
... are you a monkey all night?
Don't worry, they're very strict about me coming and going, otherwise I'll see you sooner
Correct
So why are you here now?
Inka... don't do that, uncle
Hey go... Gwen?
Where do you want to go?
Where is he going?
hello so you are here
What are you doing now?
I'm waiting for you
It's a good place to think   -don't you agree?   -
I mean, who needs a treadmill when you've got the Williamsburg Bank Building right at your fingertips
So you and your dad haven't talked yet?
What exactly do we want to talk about?
Hi dad, how long has it been?
Do you still think I killed my best friend?
I do not know
... I mean, my family might if I told them that
Do not say
Hear me on this matter
Well, maybe some things are meant for us
What an interesting way of thinking
Just smart guys with emotions
Out of the norm
You know, it's always a pleasure talking to you
Really?
Yes
How many people can you talk to about such things?
you don't even think about me
What the?
you were the only true friend i found after peter's death
Other than Hobby?
That case is different
Huh?  I don't know what you say
... you and me... you are the important thing
We are alike
Know
In any other world, Gwen Stacy fell in love with Spider-Man
And that doesn't end well in any other world
Well, everything has a beginning, right?
Wow, no matter what I eat, I can't get enough
This palantano will open a space in your heart(famous Cuban food)
The girl was very white and blonde
I bet he can't even speak Spanish
Does not matter
Does this prevent you from interfering in other dimensions?
Yes, it's very cool
How long did it take Miguel O'Hara to notice Miles Morales?
I will compliment you, I said the same thing,
if I had a bracelet I could come with you
See Miles I saved the multiverse
They were just a small elite strike force
I can become invisible, I
have power like electricity
There is no more room
Oh right
... look, if it's really my hand, I   -yes, I know, I know, I know   -
Oh, no, no, don't do that
Miles
ok now
It is very sensitive
Sorry, I didn't mean to yell
No problem, very good
Excuse me
Hello!
Hi, I want to be a mother
Hello Rio!
I hear a lot from you
You say my first name
Very good
...I found this in Miles' room, so I assume you were there too
You must be Jeff too   -You call me Jeff
So sweet, Jeff
You mean Lieutenant Moralze, soon to be Captain
hey captain
Gwanda and I have only been friends since school
Yes Yes.  We wondered for a while
Don't Take My Mailzo   -Mom   -
I joked
He can't go out until you come
Don't break her heart   -Mom   -
!Damn it!
Damn, I have to go   -really?    -
Yes, I forgot to take a walk today
I really want to stay longer
Excuse me
Goodbye
I can even hear your silence, mother
I... I hope I didn't mess things up
No one my age says those words in that order, Mom
It is very hard to see that my little boy is no longer a child
I understand
you can tell me anything you want
*
...GOOD
...I
I'm sorry I'm late
Go
She seems like a good girl
Do you want to touch my head?
No, I do not want
Lord
...what are you doing   -let me mend your clothes   -
I've been taking care of this little boy for so many years, haven't I?
I'm sure she will be loved
So that he feels a sense of belonging wherever he wants
Now he wants to go out into the world and do the dirty work
And what worries me the most is that they are not as careful as we are
They can't support you like we can
... that's how it was decided then
Wherever you go from now on, you must promise to take care of that little boy
Make sure he never forgets where he came from
There is no doubt that he is loved
And he didn't allow anyone in that big, fancy place to tell him he didn't belong
And he better come back every time he comes home
you can't be late
And it's better to have a good regular cake
Good
You have to promise Miles
I promise
Just...don't get lost
OK   -do you understand?    -
Yes
Hilaire
Goodbye, dear mother
God bless you my dear
Now get out of here
When you return, your punishment will continue
I'm smiling like it's a joke, but it's true
Yes I understand
see you
With cake
!Damn it!
Hey, hey, the car's gone
Oh shit
Darkness detected counter
Dr. Jonathan Ohne, former Alcomex employee
Earth  -42 is dead
show me what happened
Start playback
!stain, yes, I want more stain
my god!  I don't really have eyes in front of me
I just need the next dose of fuel or whatever
I never gave it a name   -dammit   -
I never knew how to give a good name
Power lines in the city can generate more dark energy for my prototype device
Damn   -I love this science   -
It just needs to take me to a place where I can find the device in the real world
And Spiderman, I'll make you pay back
everything you took from me, you must answer
Or vaporize me and everyone in this building
Sacrifice my head
damn it   -
I did
What happens
your dog
Playback is complete
No, why, why, why, why?
Gwen, Gwen, Gwen, Gwen, Gwen
Gwen!
Hello
What is it?
Nothing ah, everything is fine
Everything is fine, yes, everything is fine
Goodbye
Where is the person you should be paying attention to?
He went for a short walk   -Hajj   -
Look, he's just a common criminal.
... oh, no need   -follow   -
Look here, I found it, no, I didn't
Wait
How much round trip?
Did you go meet your friend?   -What the?  NOT   -
... miles?  Means
Namosa, are you putting your head on mine now?
I see her a little
Far   -how far?    -
you know, so... no, it's too close...
!Face
I just want to know how things are going
I really don't like this card at all
Look, I know I messed up, okay?
He should have no role in this case
Know
I'll never see him again, okay?   -What the?    -
I'm not kidding
Hey guys, he made a portal
What   -He can go anywhere he wants   -
Can now completely destroy all main events
You said this guy was a common criminal
Do you have any idea how bad this case is for you?
Whenever there is an Alcomex company, it will shut down
What's the plan, Gwen?   -I do not know   -
It got stronger so you can beat me
It is so beautiful!
This is from my smart student
I'll take it, okay?
I can compensate
...If Miguel finds out, I'll leave you
Don't tell Miguel
What if he kicks me out and sends me home?
I found him
Land  -505101
So what should we do?
Have you never done anything wrong?
Have you ever been too close to someone?
Why
But I got over it
Tell Spider-Man there
Tell him Gwen met him.
Thank you very much
He promised you he wouldn't let you down.
Now shut up
You have one hour to make this story
Otherwise, I can't help you
Hello Miles
Sorry sorry sorry
Sol  -50101 Barrier
See?  Great, I feel like a new
person, where do you want to go?
If I look in the mirror now, I don't recognize myself
Stay somewhere else
But I envy the old me
I see your confusion
Try to get it
Stop complaining, you're really complaining
Hello, sorry, locals
It is very dangerous for four people to sit on a motorcycle
Looks delicious
Where is Alcomex located?
How sharp it is
Where there is a large device between the worlds
Hey shepherd, come here
Is your sense of humor natural?
Gwen, I'm here to help you
Miles?    -How does the palm feel?    -
you didn't expect it, did you?
Oh no, me neither
I did it well
i have you if you follow me
No, I just saw where you were going and went there
not realizing you shouldn't be here
what did you say?
I always... no
No, fog, no, no, no, no
I shouldn't have come to see you at all
hi dad
Hey, who's that new guy?
Hi, this is a letter and not an invitation
Oh, you weren't invited, but you're back
NOT?   -Hey, this new guy must be in love with you   -
Ah, no   -no, no   -
I am very good at meeting people
No, it's not   -who are you?    -
Glad you asked the newbie   -I'm not a newbie   -
My name is Pravitra Prabhakare
...and the last six months   -six?   -
And does this even have a bracelet?
Yes   -it's easy to be Spiderman   -
I wake up, I don't work out because I'm naturally fit and I don't want to gain too much weight, you know?
I have almost nothing to do with superhuman hairstyles
Does that mean you don't put anything in your hair?
Just coconut oil, prayers and some good genes
Then I sneaked off to school.  There's really no need for this, but I'll do it again, I'll fight
with the bad boys, I will feed the street dogs, take a short break and have tea with my aunt.
i love tea what are
you saying now tea tea?
Tea means tea
brother, you say tea tea
Did I say I want coffee with cream?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
After that I spent some time with my friend Gayatri
He is a very stylish teenager
Hello, girl
I'm thinking about tonight
Hello Police Inspector Singh
She's your daughter and I don't know her
And most importantly, I live in the best city for Spiderman, Mombatan
A quick introduction here is traffic
There is traffic here, there is more traffic here, there is traffic everywhere
Here the British stole all our equipment
hello spiderman   -hello   -
Hey   -I'm not with you guys   -
... with me or him or   -who are you talking to?   -
I think he means me   -yes, I mean him   -
I got it guys
oh how are you
Are you trying to make my game harder?
I am on the road to self  -realization
Boy!  you came to india
This is a Western cultural stereotype
*
No, no, no, no, I didn't mean it like that
Now let me guess
By now you must be asking me about turmeric, cardamom and non  -non  -cai tea
Oh, I like tea
NOT!
no worries man i think
there was a misunderstanding
Let's talk
Okay, you make me feel empty
It was as if a hole had been made inside me
Many potholes on the road
But now I understand what to fill this hole with
More holes
This makes absolutely no sense
Makes sense
Good.  I'm fine, don't worry
This emotional conflict is very real
Did they contact me? Can't you reach me?
If Spot makes more holes, he will become invincible
...can't we let him go to Alcomex?   -
How can you focus?
Hey, do you know anything about Hobie?   -What should I know about hobbies?    -
It's like he doesn't know
please go and see you later
Hey, can you help us disable this powerful energy wall?
It cannot be turned off until the device's activity between worlds is finished
Devices between worlds?
You have to stop   -what are you doing man...
I will become more than just a criminal
I'm sorry I said that, okay?
you are a big criminal
Well, not yet
Setting up an interworld device
!NOT
What is the situation now?
!Very good
Does anyone have any idea how to open it?
I have many ideas, but
that's not why you sit back
I'm working on something new
I do not understand what is going on
Just give me a second
Do you want us to do something or just sit here?
For example, are you uploading?
No, I pulled it so I could shoot
*
Save your question for
later, i can't open it like that
Let me do my job
Interests
O Hobby, in  -laws   -Hobby?    -
See here, one more thing I like
the difference between your versions
I'm doing it in slow motion
Do you agree?
What is this person's name?
The English term for us is we are close friends
*
Do you understand what he said?
Hey Hobie, thanks, you cracked the shield
I gave it free   -I have a suggestion   -
Use your palms, not just your fingers
What's wrong with your clothes?
Are they bleeding from their armpits?
Miles, this is Hobie Hobie, this is Miles
Hi, I haven't heard from you since Gwen didn't say anything
Hi, my name is Hobie, Hobie Brown
Did something bite me, you say?
...and for the last three years I just waited, waited, waited, waited
Do you think I want to reveal my secret identity?  Do not worry about me
Then he was involved in a show of hostilities with the fascists, singing on stage,
Political activist and performer of art or past, you
want me not to be with Amkau, I am not a good role model
I was a Ferrari model for a short time
I hate mornings, I hate nights,
I hate headlines, I'm not a hero
When you call yourself a hero, you become a very
ambitious narcissist, I think you hate titles
Gwen, you left your clothes at my house
Which dress?    -sweater  -
how many shirts do you have
This is not a permanent job
And you left my toothbrush   -Vaisa, what?   -
it's my shoe
Team Khafni Mishida
I don't believe in the team   -aren't you a band?   -
I don't believe in stability
Boy, how nervous is this guy
It will be good for us, Spiderman
You and I will finally live up to our potential
You'll finally have a tough villain to fight and I'll stop being a joke to you
You're not a joke, are you?
Of course   -much taller than you   -
I don't believe in humor at all
Just kidding
See?
No one thinks you're a joke
After that, no one will think so
!NOT
Well, this is from a light Spider-Man adventure   -no, no, no, no   -
What else is this?
our future
I will take everything from you like you took everything from me
What the
see you at home
Spider Man
!Mile...Mile
Come on son... we have to go
*
Guys, move, move
We take people off the street, you stop our building
Okay, I'm fine, but not because you told me to
They all evacuated here
*
Gayatri
!NOT
Gwen, be careful
The indicator predicts the occurrence of major events.  Act carefully
Hilaire
someone help
Everyone hurry up!  Faster
Don't worry, I'm coming
Inspector Singh
I can do both
I like it, I like it   -Miles   -
Do not worry *
It's very dangerous   -we can't do this.  I promise   -
Miles and miles!  NOT
Miles
!No No no no no NO
Please no
Miles, Jr
Are you ok?
I promise
Are you ok?  I'm so worried about you
I mean you look like a pretty young woman I don't know
Father
Gayatri
Not bad?
The main event had a problem
this is correct
I've never seen him so excited
The card is wonderful
Miles has nothing to do with me
So what do you think?
Something I always think about
You are extraordinary
We will be a good team
NOT?
Yes
What are friends?
It is a memory for the capitalist system
Much worse than that
All right, guys, evacuate the area and get the people out of here
And let's control this quantum hole
Hi, I'm Miles
Actually, we've met before,
when i was invisible i know who you are
Will everything be okay?
OK, let me explain
Miguel wants to go to headquarters
Miles walks away slowly
You guys didn't follow
orders and neither did they
Was I invited to the headquarters?
How are you even dumber behind your mask?
I'm always angry
Wow!
New York Earth  -928
Hey, over here
Wow, it's so stuffy in here
Any news about the place?   -let me ask   -
Hey, has anyone seen that place?  (In English also means visible point) Malala Windsor, Spider UK Earth  -835
Oh how cute, does anyone else want to say Jack?
There's a whole line of dialogue here that can't be subtitled, sorry
That's great
It's just a hallway
Welcome to the spider community
A lot, right?
What happened to that task force you mentioned?
Many of these are part  -time
Gwen, how much did you tell her about that story?
About the place as a whole here?
The first
Maybe you didn't say enough
come over
Bracelet for me!
For temporary travel only
It just stops you from being that way
Hi Gwen   -Hi Peter   -
hi i want
Hi Gwen, One ​​of Spiderman's versions of "bag man" (wears a Fantastic Four outfit with a paper bag over his head
Hi Peters, I'm a new member
Peter, take the team to the transport station to help collect this terrible place.
I wouldn't call it terrible
More like continued success
Ben, I need you
Sorry, I can't talk right now(Ben Riley/Scarlet Spider Earth  -94)
I think about my past
We really need you here for some reason
It was a particularly heartbreaking
reminder of the way he was
Hi, my name is Tarkesh.  >
Why does the horse wear a mask?
to cover his face
!Let's go
Who is in this laser cage?
Anomalies are those that are the wrong size
We serve their mouths and send them to their blood
Not very interesting   -what?    -
We have lots of Doctor Octopus   -oh my gosh   -
A mistery
And other mysteries
Gamers   -I love games   -
Others in the game(Spider-Man Insomniac Company  -1048)
You're talking to me the font
Go to hell Spiderman
How insolent   -what a strange pencil   -
Boring Rhino
Thief?    -
Prowler is not your Donald Glover as Aaron Davis in the world) (Tom Holland's Spider-Man. That's Prowler right there
Hi
The look is rude
I brought you here   -I made a mistake   -
what do you do i do everything
How many missions have you done together?   -
Not much   -twenty or thirty   -
So cool
Excuse me
Margo Cass aka Spider Bite Earth  -22191
i am spider man
Not my son?  All of us
Can we continue our journey?
What are you?    -I profiles   -
My body is next to my parents, I'm sitting on the chair eating Fritos
It's better here
Yes I understand
what is he doing
He has a very cute name
Bring home the device I said
I am against this name
DNIT will detect it from any dimension and send you there(this guy is a version of Rhinoceros)
*
We better go
See you later   -don't you like keeping Miguel waiting   -
!Let's go
Hey, good luck
!Good see you
Miguel looks angry
He likes empanadas from the buffet
Don't ask him why
My name is Miguel O'Harast
I'm the only Spiderman in this dimension
At least it is
But I'm not like the others
I don't always like what I have to do
But I knew I had to be the one to do it
I have lost so much that I want to quit my job now
Oh no
I'm sure it won't do anything
Maybe he will before you hit him into the wall
Da'wah, man
It distracts you from the truth
And what is the truth?
I'm not from Brobach Scooby Doo, a punch(Scooby Doo is a term for having ideas and clues)
Because that's what they want
Why do you want to be part of it?
to get a bracelet
A bracelet for you?
But you don't have a cool device?
you have good parents   -not bad   -
I mean, we fight, but they want what's best for me
It's so embarrassing
Why?
Because you're not ready for someone else
listen to me brother
The point of being Spiderman is to be independent stay
alone you don't need these things if you are your own boss
so why are you here
Looking for female drama, this is it
all i want to be in a band
I want to see my friend and for that I need a bracelet
Don't move guys ok give up
Don't sign up, you know what kind of fight we're in
Yes, I know it drops very slowly, but it works
Meet Miguel O'Hara and Miles Morales
Hello how are you?
I speak spanish
I brought you empanadas
That's great
Look, I'm excited to get started.  Oh good.
I have some crazy ideas about how to catch Spot
He just wants to be taken seriously
He is worried about Spate.
I'll worry about Spot
what did I do   -Miguel, it's not his fault   -
error?  Let's see you make
another hole in the multiverse
He knows nothing
Of course you do... Well, what don't I know?   -But you know, Gwen...
And you... I want to ignore you
But I can't... I can't   -I'm not on the team at all
Maybe I what happened
Hey Miguel
Don't be hard on the kids.
He has a bad coach.
He didn't stand a chance.
Peter   -Peter
God, this is the humble Spider-Man
Miles
Fear not, friend Miguel
It just looks scary
But don't bite
Peter
Look how tall you look, look
at your legs too, you know?
It depends on what you mean
by the way what happened?
Are your armpits bleeding?
Peter   -don't worry about his clothes   -
We will buy you new clothes
PETER you have to tell him... what is it?
you give
Do you have kids?  Yes I have.
My wool
Be careful dear, your temporary bracelet is not lost
You have one too.  I didn't know they made it for adults too
Just give me a second!
This kid is a true anarchist(anarchist means someone who likes to riot)
I will eat you now
I caught you
I know I'll regret making a web shooter for it
I shouldn't have done that, it's totally wrong
Hey, do you want to see the picture?   -I said he was here   -
Look at this picture   -Oh, you took a picture   -
Oh, this
He is amazing
Yes   -that's a ridiculous look   -
hahaha
Here, for example, he is angry
It also has the appearance of a workhorse
Be careful, you will laugh when you
see the next one you will laugh out loud
Oh, Miguel is dying
Miguel, look at this I'm trying
to have a serious conversation with adults
You know, you're the only Spider-Man who isn't funny
you should be nice
The Fate of the Multiverse
You always bore me with these lines, you say
the destiny of the Multiverse and my brain says so
Did you hear that too? must have sabotaged
Yes, he's a parker too
Miles, you ruined a big event
The main event?   -The child does not think   -
It does not work that way
It's insulting that you did such a
bad job at the unit, I'll applaud you
Vaisa, why are you angry?
I saved those people
And security issues
Layla, do it
Inn?  which job
What job do you mean?
It is the job of explaining information
GOOD
What is this?
Only this
(very similar to the sacred timeline in the Loki series)
Can you be more specific?
Can't you talk for a second?
Yes Yes
What you see is all of us
Our entire life is woven into a beautiful web of life and destiny
spiderverse spiderverse?
It's a stupid name
This is called the arachno  -humanoid multiverse
I think that sounds stupid
And are these nodes where the lines meet?
They are the main event
Part of the ever  -present Spider-Man  -Han story(That's right, the famous kiss scene between Peter and MJ)
Some of them are good
Some bad (poison)
Some of them are pretty bad
go ahead
uncle aaron
This, the Amazing Spider-Man show from the 90s.
The police captain who is an acquaintance of Spider-Man
In the fight between Spider-Man and his bloody nemesis, he dies saving a child from under a collapsing wall
Captain, Stacy
I apologize
(Amazing Spider-Man Movie Event 1)
Does this happen to you too?
For me too
Keep going?
The story is destined to go like this
The main events that connect our lives
But the connection may drop
This is why anomalies are so dangerous
Inspector Singh's death was a big event, wasn't it
you should have been there and you shouldn't have saved him
That's why Gwen tried to stop you
Miles, I thought you
were trying to save me
tried
I... I'm having a wedding
And now, Miles, since you changed the story,
Then Pravitra collapsed
... if we're lucky
We can prevent it
We are not always lucky
That's none of my business...that's Spot's business
This is what happens when you destroy the main event
how do you know?
Because I ruined it once
I found another world where I have a family
Where I am happy
At least a version I like
my bag
And that version of me was killed
So I replaced it
I guess it's harmless
But I was wrong
Father, please help
Am I right Peter?
Yes
If we disrupt the main event enough... and save the captains' lives
We might lose everything
My father will soon be a captain
I want to take what you have and what you don't have
I came as if you would take everything away from me   -
Rear wheel
He will kill my father
When it happened
when it happens in two days
When he took his oath
Of course, that's what the algorithm says
I am sorry that
Miles sends me home
I cant do this
At least not now
What do you say I should do?
Should I let him die like this?
But about your father
He's also the captain, right?
Yes
You won't do anything about it
All right, Uncle Ben, what?
It won't be a problem if you know and let it happen
Many of us wouldn't be here if this hadn't happened to Uncle Ben, Miles
And all these good things we do will never happen.
So we have to let people die at the words of a bunch of algorithms?   -...Good   -
You do realize how long this is, right?
Between a person and a
world, you have to save any world
I can choose a partner
...Spiderman, always
Not always
Miles, we all want to live the life we've always dreamed of
Trust me, I tried
And the more I try, the more I hurt myself
You can't have it all, honey
To be Spider-Man you have to make sacrifices
This is our job
When you become Spiderman, you accept it
Miles
Annie?
What happens?
can you all calm me down
We know it's hard
But actually Miles (The Spectacular Spider-Man)
Is that why you're here?
that I could easily care?
It worked last time, why not try again, right?
Wait wait
You're right, Gwen
You shouldn't have come to meet me at all
Honey, look at me   -don't say honey
It began   -Husband, your words do not help   -
It is so good
Miles, please understand that I don't
you can ask me not to save my father
Not a request
Wait a moment
Stop
If we let it, it will hurt us more, you know
both that it doesn't end well   -end   -
You will only be here for a few days
I don't want that to happen, son
I said don't say honey
Miles
Well, I'm sorry I did that
Good parents don't do that
As soon as I know, I will fix the problem
Drop all units no matter what you do and stop Spider-Man
do you mean   -Wait, with you?    -
with me
I?    -Me?    -
I'm spitting on you, Miles
Miles Morales
He entered zone 4
The mirror?
huh?  Does tar stick to my face? What is the problem
Miles and miles!
It's right back there
Hey boss, what's all the fuss about?
Is that weird?
I think it is possible
Excuse me
I see the audience and that
Let me guess, dead?
In the number of three, we shoot
One I didn't say three
can you take our picture
This is the first follow up
Get me out of this mess
Miles?    -Hello, write   -
I'm a big fan   -thanks   -
Don't you think humor is like a stick for Spiderman?
you got?  sugar cane
Anything He Could Do, I Can(Spiderman Animation 1981)
Hey, I think I have a stretch somewhere in my body
Hi Peter (Alfred Molina's dialogue as Doctor Octopus in New Way Home)
What is it?    -No way out   -
It's my fault, guys
It's like an exit
No Trespassing
So don't follow me
you confused me again
I know he's your friend, but it's the only way
But Hashem told me this   -so use that word   -
This is called ventilatory sleep
I use my hands to hug you
Miles
No, no... let me go
Running away is madness
Either way, running away was the most rational thing to do
I do not feel well
It is so good
But the situation is the same, you won't win this time
I can't reach you   -no, no   -
moving so fast
NOT
Do you want to hug my baby?
What the
Hold the baby once, we'll talk about it later, it'll change your mind.
!NOT
It brings energy to a person
that they are quite good at
When you hug this miracle baby chest to chest, you will feel better
Now you don't have to speak to me from the heart
Take the baby, then we'll see what happens
you are the reason, right?
... I thought
If they raise him right, there's a chance he'll turn out to be just like you
And that makes me happy because you are a very funny person
And I love traveling with you
So why don't you come see me?
...Because
I can not
I really want to be with you
But that's not what I thought
...See
Bad things happen either intentionally or unintentionally
They make us who we are
And good things happen beside him, you know?
Like your existence
And where is this girl
Hi!
I don't want to... listen
And you are very stupid to hug a child
That's your position, Peter. Done   -wait, wait, no   -
you don't have my position.  whole
Send to everyone
No, no, Miles, I don't know, I promise
Please, mate, let's talk about it
we speak
It's a good discussion
is here
Miles
Where do you think this will go?
I don't think he has a plan
If I haven't told you by now, you're a terrible coach
He just beat you
So I'm not a bad coach
You two are awful, aren't you?
Stop pretending you don't know
what you're doing, I have a plan
I just... haven't told you yet
*
It's not good
they are claws
Dude, are you sure you're Spiderman?
Who do you think You Are?
My name is Miles Morales
A radioactive spider bit me
And I'm sure you know the rest of the story yourself
how are you buddy
I don't understand that you are an anomaly
Not if you let me go home
seller
you are an anomaly wherever you go
basically you are an anomaly
Miguel!
The spider that gave you power is not yours
It shouldn't bite at all
Miguel, don't do this
There is a world where there is no Spider-Man to protect it, because Spider-Man bit you.
You weren't meant to be Spider-Man
!NOT!  Lying!  Are
Spiderman, you are wrong
If Peter Parker hadn't bitten you, your world would have lived on
Instead, he died saving you
He will stop the device between worlds before things go wrong
There is no room
And none of these things happened
And all this time, I was the only one who maintained everything…
Miguel, don't be hard on
him, you don't belong here
you were never part of it
Let me alone
Miguel is fed up
That's not what we're talking about
are you talking about this?
Know
Do you all know?
...I do not know
How can I tell you?
That's why you never came to see me
Miles, this is for your own good
Who determines my goodness?
I'm not a child, Gwen
You are perfectly right!
Just a child!
He didn't know what he was doing at all
OK
I dragged hundreds of people from your spider community here with me
I think he has a plan
And I want to do it
Everyone is always telling me how my story is going to turn out
No, I'm doing my job
Shame on you, Miguel
I'm home
Goodbye, Gwen
Miles
I taught him how to do it
So I must be a good coach, I did
NOT
This is not good at all
Oh no, not at all
I was like that.
But not now
Inn?
Turn on the device, take it home
Next sign detected Target DNA detected) (Earth  -42 DNA
move one
No no
!NOT
!no no no
What happened
The device is activated automatically
How is that possible?   -Not
Impossible
What do you say about this?   -No no no!
Wait, now what?   -You are hands and feet.
Step in front of her
Now!
What do you think I'm doing now?
Do something!
!NOT
Miguel!
Stop
Start rebooting the system
!NOT
Okay, that's enough
This is not a device malfunction
All you have to do is listen to me
Why doesn't he listen?
Maybe because you didn't take it hard enough
Gwen, don't
this, let him go
I?    -you don't understand, Gwen   -
Okay, let's all take a deep breath
Peter, do you want to defend me?
Good
Miguel, as a father to a daughter and a son to a mother   -yes, you better stop talking   -
Ok, I understand
let me talk to him
I tried this, he is my friend
Yes, and that's the problem
Are you sure what would happen if the main event broke?
Do you want to understand?
I told you it was trouble
You are wrong
Jess, tell him he's wrong
He was not wrong
you are serious now
,I told.  If you let go, I can't help you anymore
I won't go with you
You are right
What the
What's wrong with you?
Go home, Gwen
For example, we should be good people
It is
We are good people
Jess, Ben, come with me
Of course
Someone took the place
Yes, it's a shame I have
to put the baby to sleep
not you
I'm tired of you
how it works
I do not know
Peter, are you making our kids fight again?
... bring us the son
our no no no
Because you asked me not to
So that's why I don't have it
did it, I won't do it
Access is not possible
Do you think I will be a good father?
Are you asking this now?
There are no books to raise someone like that
Or... be yourself
You just have to make the right decision in the shortest possible time
Furthermore, this is a metaphor of
the sport that I made myself
Too bad, I'm a sports junkie myself and I still don't get it
I watch sports
good hero   -awesome   -
Would you like to be cuter with Mr. Penguin?
You can...don't even look at me
What the?
What else is this?
I see you the way you want
you are skin and bones
where are you?
I'm there to kill all my friends
Oh, it's funny, ok yeah
Good
Where are you going?    -I do not know   -
You're a good cop, Dad
You know, you wear that police badge because you know that if you don't, someone who shouldn't wear it will.
But you must understand that this mask is my logo
And I try to be good
I tried so hard to wear it the way you want
And I can not
I can't, I can do many things, but I
can't help the people I love the most
And I can only know half of my identity
That's why I'm all alone
And now... I don't even know what's good anymore
I don't know what to do... but I do
I can't lose any more friends
Gwen I taught you
always follow the rules
Yes, but where did he go?
I ate some
So catch me, daddy
Solve the case   -I... I can't   -
Why?
Because I'm resigning
When
Almost in the middle of your big speech
You... I'll see
Are you not the captain anymore?
... Means
My job, being a captain, all these things don't matter anymore
Raising you was the best thing I ever did
It's a great speech, isn't it?
No wonder you're 19 in
English, I'm actually 16
I didn't go to some classes
I do not know what to do
But I think it will help you
The person who gave this to me is a big punch
As a precaution, if your wristband does not work, Hobby   -
I will be right back
I promise
Being a father is a problem
Mysterious problem
You are wrong
If Peter Parker hadn't bitten you, your world would have lived on
And none of these things happened
Miles, the hardest part of our job is that you can't
save everyone  I'm going to make you pay back everything you took from me
Between one person and one world,
you have to save one.  I can do both
...Spiderman, always
Not always
Whatever you want to do, don't lose your way
Bad things continue
I don't know how to tell you that
you shouldn't be spiderman
Keep it up
have you checked the situation?
Yes   -no news about them   -
Layla, can you send them all? Send them anywhere
Anywhere I can
Congratulations, Captain
Captain, you can't call me Captain Saddam until I swear
You know that
We are all proud of you
Molay's attitude
There might be some disturbance in the driveway, I'd better check
Now something unusual is coming my
way.  I look at the walls, they are normal
... but I'm facing something
NOT
I did
my house
Miles?
Is now a bad time?
I'm late?
what are you doing with your hair are you ok
say you are fine
I'm fine
You are right
you are right about everything
Obviously, I'm right, I'm always right
Now what am I right about?
I've seen a lot of bad places and met a lot of bad people
But
what's the problem my dear
But they don't want me
I thought about what you said
I broke it, mom
I took them all
Now I know how strong I am
My strength is because of you, father and me
Ma'am, something's coming our way
...something
Something really bad
Myles, what about you?
His name is Spates
He is my enemy.
And I will stop it
I know you know I lied to you
Because I thought that if you knew, you wouldn't love me like you used to
But then I'm out
And now... I'm not afraid of anything now
what you want to tell me must
promise me nothing will change
Sugar honey I will always
love you must promise
Always
I don't care what you say
I understand you
Mother?
…I
i am spider man
who is spider man
He is a super hero
A spider bit him
It gave him spider powers
this is me
Did you say you dress up as your favorite character?
What's that thing called?
Oh, Comic Con, I
don't know what that is
I really thought the news was Spiderman
What imagination do you have?
For example, do you have eight hands?
Do you have silk coming out of your butt?
I've had nightmares like this once before, but no
Are you sure you woke up after that?
Mom, enough jokes
Serious talk
Dad works with Spiderman
...he doesn't understand that I'm Spider-Man, but I wish he was here right now to explain
Miles, please
I have to pay attention to you
I have to take care of myself
So first help me   -Mom, wait, wait   -
... I need to talk
Oh no
He was wrong in the world
The spider that bit me
It's not for me
The following symptoms are identified
... that device
He didn't send me home
Uncle Aaron?
Hi
Earth  -42
Are you ok?
i really miss you
OK, OK now
Have you changed your hair style?
deliberately?    -Yes   -
Yes, I'm still at peace with it
At the hospital, they will give me more shifts, so next month, I swear, I will
Enough, we don't
need to be family
Be grateful
Meanwhile on Earth  -1610
Hello how are you doing?    -Hello
How about Miles?
Well, do you remember telling him he wasn't allowed to go out?
GOOD?
I leave what you do
First of all, of course
*
Oh Miles, I have to work late tonight
This list bought I'm
sure he will buy it
ok come on
The security key came at six
Do we still have a chance?
Yes indeed
I totally get what you're saying
Are you ok?
*
So come on
Are you sure you remember the map?
Yes, but we better start again... as soon as we can
Does not matter
This is not Spider-Man
Captain Jeff Morales, husband, hero, father's soulmate
...Father
Sorry, honey, but you
You gave him this permission unilaterally
I'm just not worried about the Nabob finding friends
Probably because of the same girl
What did she think of him being with her?
I have some ideas
... baby, you're really no help
The girl has come this far, Miles' eyes light up
I just hope the girl isn't upset
Does that mean these things are my fault too?
No no
Maybe this is all my fault
don't worry honey
you are an amazing
father it's so hard
It's like having a new baby that wants to grow up fast
And maybe we should grow up
Little bit
Maybe we should leave it
take the lid off, Haji Haji?
It is not your fault
it's my fault
Oh, that's okay, what are you doing here?
Oh, her bedroom window was open... so I came to you
This is completely normal
I want to talk to your parents
Okay, it's hard to communicate with my dad
Oh really?  What is this
Storage materials?
police
I take back what I said
Yeah, well, I'll call the station, I
don't think Miles is there or anywhere
So where is this jacket, Emo Miles?
I don't know   -don't you know?    -
Don't know what you want to say?
I go
Where do you think you're going, miss?
i will find it
I don't know exactly where, but I know where to start
One thing I learned from Miles is that anything is possible
He loves you more than you can imagine
I see what I'm saying
If you find it
Tell him he will be punished for five months
And let's just say we love him
Hilaire
Miles Morales: Spider-Man The Prowler Claw
Uncle Aaron?
to my ear well waits
You don't understand that I don't belong here
I belong to another dimension
Vaisa Vaisa Vaisa
I beg you
I was sent here by mistake
Uncle Aaron Vaisa Vaisa
Vaisa Vaisa uncle Aaron
Please, Uncle Aaron, listen to what I have to say
A spider bit me and gave me strength
He shouldn't bite me
It will bite other people
One of this world
I don't belong here
should i go home
I also have my uncle
Aron that I have
He is a bad person
In the name of Prowler
He dies for me
He did a lot of bad things, but I could tell he wanted to be good
He just doesn't know he has the right to choose, but you do
you can be a good person
folks?
Trust me
I know you don't want to be a thief
I do not
*
Is your father still alive?
What the
your father
You said you were still alive
Yes
Oh
Who are you?
My name is Miles Morales
...but you
You can kill Saddam, Prowler
If the house is soft, our
father will die your father
Help
you have to let me go
Why do I have to do this?
How to talk to kids who will listen
don't tell mom
I never found a suitable group to join
So I started my own group.
With some old friends.