How lucky I am today, I got two cocks. Two alive cocks, cocks, cocks.⊂↹⊃今天好运气，活捉两只鸡。活捉两只鸡，两只鸡，两只鸡。
Hurry, hurry, invite Bear, enjoy the feast together. Very very tasty. Ha ha ha, he will be happy.⊂↹⊃快去快去找老熊，一起来吃鸡。鸡肉鸡肉香又美，保管他满意。哈哈哈哈哈，管他...保满意。
Stop jumping!⊂↹⊃让你跳，你再跳，你再跳！
Time to invite my old friend Bear.⊂↹⊃该去请老熊了。
Today I’m so lucky, Wolf invited me to eat tasty.⊂↹⊃今天好运气，老狼请吃鸡。老狼请吃鸡，请吃鸡，
Eating chicken with good wine, fill my belly. Hurry, hurry, for my greedy tummy! Ha ha ha, I am so hungry!⊂↹⊃请吃鸡。鸡肉鸡肉配美酒，正好填肚皮。快步快步朝前走，嘴馋心又急。哈哈哈哈哈，嘴馋...心又急。
Miss Fox, what happened?⊂↹⊃狐狸大姐，你这是怎么了？
Oh, Brother Bear, help, help me, please, please!⊂↹⊃唉，熊大哥，不好了！你快救救我吧！
Who is bullying you? Let me help you kick his ass.⊂↹⊃谁欺负你了？快告诉你兄弟。
You see, my ear was almost cut by a badass.⊂↹⊃你瞧我这耳朵，差点就叫人家割下来了。
Who did it?⊂↹⊃是哪个混蛋干的？
Hush, it’s the damn Wolf. He invited me to eat chicken. But when I entered his house, he tried to cut my ear with a blade.⊂↹⊃嘘，还不是那个该死的狼呗，他请我去吃鸡，我就去了，谁知一进门，他就揪着我的耳朵，举刀要割。
Really?⊂↹⊃真有这种事？
You bet. Thanks God, I ran away. Ouch, look at my ear.⊂↹⊃可不嘛！嘻嘻嘻，幸亏我逃得快，要不，爱哟哟哟，你瞧。
Gosh! It’s blee...blee...bleeding! That Wolf also invited me.⊂↹⊃啊！血！他他他他，他还请我来着。
You fool, forget the chicken dinner. Don’t be taken in. I saw Wolf was sharpening his blade.⊂↹⊃哎呀，你别只想着吃呀，喝呀的，小心上人家的当！我看那老狼正在家里磨刀，他准是要割你的耳朵。
Ah, wha...wha..what should I do?⊂↹⊃那那那那那
Believe it or not, I’d better run away now.⊂↹⊃信不信由你，哎呦。我可得先逃了。
Whoops!⊂↹⊃哎呦
All right, now, only need to wait for Bear.⊂↹⊃好嘞，就等老熊来。
Brother Wolf, oh, Brother Wolf ..., bad news.⊂↹⊃狼大哥，狼大哥，哎呀，狼大哥，不好了
I just heard a bang, and came over to see what happened.⊂↹⊃我刚才听见 啪的一声响，过来一看，
Guess what. I saw Bear slipping out of your house, holding two chickens in his hands. I guess, ah, he must have stolen your chickens.⊂↹⊃你猜怎么着，只见老熊从你家里溜出来，手里啊，拎着两只鸡，我看啊，准是偷的。
Don’ t worry, I invited him.⊂↹⊃啊，是我请他来吃鸡的。
Ah! You’d better have a look at your chickens. They must have been eaten by Bear.⊂↹⊃哎呀，你快去看看吧，你的鸡啊，早就进了老熊的肚子里了。
Gosh!⊂↹⊃啊，啊！
Damn it! I invited him, how could he steal my chickens!⊂↹⊃这家伙，我好心请他来吃鸡，他反而把我的鸡给偷光了。
Brother Wolf, You've been tricked! We must seize the thief.⊂↹⊃我说狼大哥，你上当了，有贼啊！抓贼啊！抓贼啊！
Stop, damn Bear!⊂↹⊃站住！
Stop!⊂↹⊃看你往哪儿跑！
Screw you!⊂↹⊃去你的!
You stole my chickens, you hit me hard. What kind of friend you are!⊂↹⊃你偷鸡，还打人，真不够朋友。
What? I stole your chickens?⊂↹⊃啊？我偷鸡？
Fox told me that.⊂↹⊃是狐狸说的。
Fox? Oh, I understand.⊂↹⊃狐狸？哦！