Oh, Kim Na Na...
It's a good thing you're here.
No matter how I make my coffee,
I can't make it the way you do.
Can you make me a cup of coffee?
Lee Yoon Sung.
Oh, our contract ended.
Then just tell me how you make it.
Lee Yoon Sung.
Who gave you permission to keep meddling
in my life whenever you want?
Who do you think you are to buy my house?
Do you feel sorry for me?
Am I that pitiful?
Can you say it so I understand
what you're talking about?
My house...
I heard you bought it.
And you had the title
transferred to your name quickly, too.
Did you really want to show off
how wealthy you are to a girl...
who lives in constant fear of being evicted?
How pitiful must I have looked, what with
all my odd jobs, scraping by through life...
Kim Na Na.
Isn't it my right to choose whether or not
to buy a house with my own money?
Why do I have to be questioned by you?
You have your own house
and a very nice one at that!
Money shouldn't be left idle.
It should always be rolling.
That's my father's theory.
Your house is really old and rundown.
But you're the person who first told me
that the house was going into auction.
When I saw it,
I realized it's close to the Blue House
and I'll make a huge profit
on my investment, if it's ever rebuilt.
Why do I have to give that up?
Then you're really going to live
in that house?
Yes.
You're going to leave that nice house...
to live in a house in a horrible
neighborhood, that's about to collapse,
where you have to use washing bins
to catch leaks whenever it rains?
Yeah.
You will purposely leave your house
to suffer in that old house?
Does that make sense?!
How many times do I have to tell you?
I was going to ask you
to vacate the place soon anyway.
When do you plan to move out?
Kim Na Na, be a little more honest.
Didn't you come to beg me to let you
keep living there a little longer?
Then plead your case nicely,
And maybe I’ll change my mind.
It's not fun if you get all
argumentative.
Lee Yoon Sung, you're the one
who seems to have misunderstood.
It seems you bought that house
to reign over me,
but that will never happen.
Because to me,
people who play with love through money...
are jerks to the bone.
I'll move out of there
so meet me after work.
What?
Humans are the type of beings
who make mistakes as they live, right?
Just get to the point.
I heard you brought me home last night
and I didn't get to say thank you.
All right, I've accepted your thanks,
so what's your point?
I didn't make any mistakes last night,
right?
I blacked out so...
You don't remember anything?
Nothing?
Nope, except one thing...
I think there was a girl next to you
last night.
Oh, you remember that?
It's not Shin Eun Ah by any chance, right?
Shin Eun Ah?
Oh, nothing!
That's what you wanted to verify?
Let's just get to work.
- Hold on.
- What again?
I really didn't make any mistakes, right?
Yeah, you did!
A lot of them, too!
Man, what do I do?
Agent Kim Na Na.
We have to guard candidate Seo Yong Hak.
If we don't leave now,
we'll be late for our shift.
Then let's go.
You keep sighing.
Did something happen?
No, nothing happened.
That's the person.
He put a gun to my head...
and said that if I want to live,
I must get off the bus instantly.
Both Lee Kyung Wan and Seo Yong Hak...
were both shot at and kidnapped
at the same time.
Could these be schemes
plotted by a terrorist group?
North Korea?
I heard these two
have been friends for decades.
Then could it be that person,
the City Hunter?
I don't think so.
To deliver the man to the Prosecutor's
Office, then try to kill him after?
That makes no sense.
That's true.
You had the letter on the Seo Yong Hak case
examined for fingerprints, right?
Yes, but I was told it might take a while
because it contained multiple fingerprints.
Run a comparison
of the fingerprints from the elevator
to the ones from the truck
to the fingerprints from the letters.
Seeing as how these two cases occurred
at such close time periods,
they could both be plotted
by one person or organization.
There were two suspicious people
at the building.
One was either injured or walks funny...
Prosecutor.
That man's movement was a little strange.
His movement?
I thought it was because we were on
a moving vehicle,
but now that I think about it,
how should I explain this?
One of his legs seemed to have a problem.
Investigator Jang, find all Korean residents
between the ages of 40 and 60
who are handicapped with one leg.
Yes.
Investigator Kim.
You said the sniper's gun
was an American made AR -15, right?
Yes, that was the result
of the bullet forensics analysis.
Find out if there is a handicapped person
who came from abroad within the last year,
with more attention towards the US.
Prosecutor,
there are probably a lot of them...
We need to find him
even if we have to work all night!
If ever needed,
this place would be a good place to hide.
Wow. What the heck...
So you want me to cover all the windows
and doors with iron bars?
On a house that may be reconstructed
any day now?
Yes.
Why don't you just make do for now?
It's such a waste of money.
Will you do it or not?
I can give you the money now if you want.
Give me a 50 percent deposit now
and pay me the rest once it's done.
Then please install it now.
Don't worry about the price and use only
the strongest and most reliable materials.
This guy...
Don't you see I'm busy?
I'll have it done tomorrow morning.
Tomorrow morning?
I have to go to work...
You can just leave the keys.
I won't touch anything in the house.
The keys?
Kim Na Na, just live in that house
until I tell you to leave.
I'll just let you stay
since you have nowhere to go.
No, not like that...
Kim Na Na.
I'm sorry about before.
I just bought the place as an investment,
so stay as long as you need.
Okay?
Oh, my God.
I said right after work
and you're right on time.
Are you really that desperate
for this house?
If I wasn't, why would I buy it?
Give me the keys.
You came to get the keys.
Not a penny you've spent goes to waste,
so you'll become wealthy in no time.
Follow me.
I'll pack everything then give you the keys.
No, just give me the keys first.
I will...
I will, okay?
I won't insist on living here
and not give you the keys, okay?
Hey!
Hey, Kim Na Na!
Flower Pretty Boy?
Is she giving this to me?
Why do you touch other people's things
without their permission?
Do I need permission
to touch this little thing?
It's not just a little thing, okay?
A first impression is always right.
I knew the moment I drove your car while you
had a great time with a girl in the back.
Hey, Kim Na Na.
I thought I judged you unfairly, seeing you
helped me with my father's hospital fees...
and how you were with Mi Jin and Do Jin.
But...
Just put your stuff back.
If you need this house, just stay.
Are you joking?
I don't know if you're playing around
because you're wealthy
or if you really bought this
as an investment,
- but since I was seven, this house...
- I know.
It's a house with a table your dad built
and a tablecloth your mom made.
So I'm telling you to stay here!
Here.
Just feed her once a day.
Ddorong is smart. She'll do her business
in the bathroom if you keep the door open.
When I find a place, I'll get
the rest of my things and pick up Ddorong.
You're asking me to live with this dog?
Says who?!
Can't you do at least that much since you're
forcing me to move out with a day's notice?!
It's my choice whether I'll do it for you
or not! I'm the house owner.
Ddorong, even if this ahjussi annoys you,
just put up with it for now.
I'll be back to pick you up soon.
Here are the keys that you wanted so badly.
Hey, Kim...
Kim Na Na.
Did I tell her to leave?
Did I ever brag about being rich?
She's the one who started everything
and got angry about me buying this place.
She lost her temper first!
Carefully,
What am I going to do about her?
I want to tell you,
Oh, I'm your lovely girl,
While in your embrace
Hello, hello, you shiny boy
Cupid's arrow
shot straight through my heart
Hey, Kim Na Na!
Hello, hello, you shiny boy
Kim Na Na, wait!
Your sweet laughter sneaked into my heart.
I'm nervous all day.
You got my heart
My love, my love, my love, my boy...
Hey, Kim Na Na!
Stop the bus!
Come out!
Hey!
Wait a minute!
Oh... She...
Dad, why are you so skinny?
Are you upset that I don't visit often?
I've been busy lately.
I was guarding and I almost got shot.
I'm not that bad, huh?
I'm sorry, Dad.
The director says I'm insubordinate
and I don't have the skills to be a guard.
My salary was cut,
and the house was bought by another person.
Dad, what do I do?
My life is a joke right now.
I don't even have a place to sleep.
I survived because of this person...
Because I felt like dying...
It's funny, huh?
Yeah, I'm at Dad's hospital.
I don't know.
It's okay.
Excuse me for a moment.
I'll call you back.
What is it?
This may seem a bit sudden,
but do you see the guy in the back?
He really likes you.
No, don't look now.
He's good looking.
You won't regret it.
Get a cup of coffee with him
or just coolly reject him.
Hello.
What is it?
I heard from your friend,
but I'm sorry, you're not my type.
Excuse me.
Can you give me your friend's number?
He's my type.
What?
What the...?
Hey, you have to be bark
when someone comes in.
How can I entrust Na Na to you
if you're like this?!
What's going on?
What's wrong with this?
What decade is this?
Nothing works here.
Kim Na Na,
why don't you ever let me finish talking?
Why are you so stubborn?
Making people feel sorry...
What the heck?
Ah! Kim Na Na...
Hey! How could you leave the house
in that shape?!
Nothing works!
Raise the house to your standards
or adjust your standards to the house.
Why won't the toilet flush?
Do you have to stick your hand in
every time?
The shower head always falls off.
I turned on cold water for a shower,
but it spewed out water
hot enough to boil me alive.
What do you expect from a building
that has almost been torn down 3 times?!
Don't make me angry so early in the morning.
Let's just pretend we didn't see each other.
Dr. Lee! Good morning!
Wow Dr. Lee,
you're so amazing with this service!
Sorry,
but this coffee belongs to someone else.
Lee Kyung Wan was kidnapped
and Seo Yong Hak was almost shot.
Anonymous letters, hacking,
and a City Hunter on top of that...
Please eat breakfast and then work.
We all need to eat to live!
I bet Seo Yong Hak and even the
City Hunter are eating breakfast right now.
The results from the letter fingerprints
aren't out yet, right?
If the results don't come out soon,
the evidence won't be valid anymore.
Please calm down.
Every time we call the forensics center,
they yell at us that we're rushing too much.
Excuse me.
We found the person who crashed
the servers in the Blue House yesterday.
- You did?
- You...
You mean the one who put up a huge picture
of a military boot riddled with nails?
and crashed all the servers?
But it was a Blue House employee.
From the National Communications Network
Team Office of the Security Service.
That's where experts work.
But the work wasn't that of an expert.
Overloading to hack the system
is an outdated method.
Lee Kyung Wan and that letter writer too...!
- Investigator Kim, please get a warrant.
- Yes, Sir.
Lee Kyung Wan's case, Seo Yong Hak's case,
the military boots and the letters...
They are all related somehow.
I'm Prosecutor Kim Yong Joo
from the Seoul Prosecutor's Office.
Where is Go Ki Joon?
Over there...
What is the problem?
I'm sorry to barge in at this time.
Go Ki Joon.
I'm sure you know why we're here.
You'll have to come with us for breaching
Section 72 of the Securities Exchange Law,
in committing a hack
into the information securities network.
What do you mean he has to go with you?
Investigator Jang.
Let's go.
Huh?
Get up.
Sorry for interrupting.
Wait...
Can you please explain?
The hacking case from yesterday
was traced to Go Ki Joon's house.
The IP address was verified to his house
and the prosecution has opened the case
for further investigation.
The hacking did not cause any harm...
and the servers were down
for merely two minutes.
It's not only for the hacking.
The anonymous letters, the recent shooting,
and the kidnapping seem to be connected,
which is why we obtained
a high priority arrest warrant.
Letters? Shooting? Hacking?!
Na Na.
Your face is healing well.
Thanks to you.
It seems we'll be
running into each other quite often.
Excuse me?
I've been put in charge
of investigating Seo Yong Hak's case...
and I heard
you're responsible for guarding him.
Yes.
Please help me out.
Yes. But wait!
What happened with Go Ki Joon?
I thought Go Ki Joon was odd
the very first time I met him.
He cried while we were sparring
and I thought he was a bit different,
but how could a Blue House employee
hack the Blue House?
Is he a spy like the rumors say?
A spy that the CIA planted?
Does that sound plausible to you?
He's tall but everyone in the Blue House
knows he and Lee Yoon Sung are wimps.
What?
The movies always show it like that!
Disguise.
Maybe that's just part of his disguise to
mislead everyone.
Shooting, letters, hacking!
Those are all big deals!
Thanks to him
there will be more trouble for us.
Now we have to all show our IDs
when we come to work.
Don't even start.
Even the trunk of my car was searched.
We're even restricted to surfing only within
the communications network.
There are now
3 levels of firewall security too.
Why do we all have to suffer
because of one person's mistake?
They should investigate into
a person's background more meticulously.
You shouldn't talk like this!
What are you doing, agent Shin Eun Ah?
What's wrong?
Talking about someone behind his back
is not a polite thing to do.
Even though Go Ki Joon didn't graduate
from a prestigious university,
and he's very clumsy, a little dull
and not very likeable,
but he's not a bad person.
I can attest to that
as his drill instructor.
I find your actions to be wrong,
when you do not know
all the details of the situation.
I'll be going.
Agent Kim Na Na, let's go.
But I didn't finish eating...
So Seo Yong Hak's youngest son
was on the basketball team,
ruptured his ligament
and had surgery done on it.
And now he's in the midst of re-applying
for exemption from the military.
What's wrong with that?
Listen carefully to what I'm about to say,
Sir. It's pretty interesting.
This boy...
went to a growth clinic until high school
senior year and they did a lot of imaging.
Senior year of high school?
I guess his treatment at the clinic worked,
he was able to join the basketball team.
No, no.
He's only about this tall.
It even makes you wonder
how he made it into the basketball team.
It's possible because it's just a club.
So?
But after only a month in college,
he received an exemption from the military
for his ruptured ligament.
We're not doctors, how are we supposed
to decipher these images?
Wait...
Did you find something?
The shape of the leg is different
even though the pictures are similar.
You're saying the shape of his leg changed
that much in a span of a couple of months?
Of course not.
The patients were switched.
He brought these images
of a ruptured ligament to the exam,
and had surgery on a perfectly healthy leg
to get to where he is now.
In other words...
Unquestionable military service corruption.
Bingo.
The former Minister of National Defense
has nothing better to do...
than come up with ploys to get his sons out
of military service?!
You see?
We should have just
taken cared of him that time.
Now that we know everything,
I won't let him get away.
Father, leave everything to me.
Nice to meet you.
Yes. It's nice to meet you.
Hello! It's nice to meet you!
Is your business running okay?
We're getting by.
That's good.
Sir! Sir!
Move!
Sir!
What are you?!
Get out of my way!
Sir!
I told you I have something to say!
Move!
Oh, my back!
This security guard is out to kill!
What are you doing?!
We asked you to guard us,
not show off your Judo skills!
Are you going to take responsibility
if people accuse us of being overprotected?
I'm sorry, I'll be more cautious.
I'm so sorry.
The shooting incident
occurred pretty recently...
so all the guards
are still nervous from that.
I will apologize on their behalf.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
He came in such a rush so...
Ah, yes...
What are you doing?
Hurry, accompany this man to the hospital!
Oh, my back!
Are you all right?
- Ow... I feel like I'm going to die.
- Are you okay? Let's get you up.
You can't tell from first glance.
Please work on
honing your natural instincts.
If the reporters find out,
they won’t write anything good.
What kind of security agent
throws a citizen around in the marketplace?
At a time when every vote is vital.
Goodness.
Even the shooting incident...
Was also the result of the
security agents' negligence.
Ma'am, I'm so sorry for today.
We're doing are hardest to
ensure your safety.
Of course...
That's why you're hired.
Please be cautious so that there is no
unnecessary gossip before the election.
Yes, Ma'am.
Come clean the dog poo.
What's going on?
This...
Clean it up.
I asked you to look after the dog.
You said all I need to do is feed her,
you didn't ask me to pick up her poop.
Taking care of her includes that!
Did you think you could only feed her?!
Then leave me a dog that doesn't poop!
Oh, my God...
I just won't say anything.
You said it's smart.
How could such a smart dog
poop on the floor like this?
I think the dog has trouble holding it in*,
just like its owner. (*short-tempered)
You didn't leave the bathroom door open,
did you?
My Ddorong is smart!
As long as you leave the door open,
she'll do her business in there.
Did you tell me that?
Why are you looking at me like that?
I won't ever clean up dog poo
so come and clean it up yourself every day.
Or take her with you.
You know I have nowhere else to go,
aren't you being too much?
Then just live with me!
Stop joking around!
Who said I'm joking?
If that wasn't a joke,
are you really expecting me
to live together with you?
You're playing with me again, aren't you?!
Hey, the ventilator is broken,
the toilet seat is broken too,
and the shower head falls off
if you breathe on it.
And how can there be not a single channel
on TV? You take responsibility.
What should I take responsibility?
I only bought the house
because I believed it could be redeveloped,
but I realized my investment
was a bad choice.
It's all right if you don't pay rent,
but you have to come over everyday
to cook and clean.
Also, the toilet seat, faucet,
the shower, and the TV,
fix all of them for me.
Also, when you have the money,
according to the auction price I paid,
you can buy it back.
That's what I mean by taking responsibility.
For you, those conditions are quite good.
Do you refuse?
It's not that...
But living under a single roof with a guy...
Ah... a guy and a girl?
Kim Na Na, you're good at judo, right?
You're a 4th Level?
Then, even if I have wayward thoughts
about you,
then I know clearly what you'll do to me,
would I still want to touch you?
Am I stupid?
I clearly know this,
would I go looking for a beating?
It seems that way.
Also, the ultimate deciding factor-
You...
are a B cup, right?
Anything smaller than a C cup,
I don't view as a woman.
Plus, Kim Na Na, don't you dislike me?
Then you won't secretly attack me.
What other problems can there be, right?
It seems you're still quite reluctant.
Then, forget it.
Hold on!
Give me some time to think about it.
All right.
Everything he said is true.
I don't like him
and he doesn't like me either.
So nothing like that would happen.
I don't have a place to go.
I don't have to pay rent either.
He just wants me to cook a little more
and do household chores.
Mom, Dad, till I get this house back,
just till I get this house back,
please close your eyes.
If you don't want to, don't do it.
I won't have any regrets.
All right, let's live together.
But, I have conditions.
Conditions?
You have to sign a contract that says
there will never be any physical contact.
Hey, how many times
do you want me to say it?
You're not my type at all.
You would never ever,
ever be the type that I'd fall for.
I'm just taking precautions.
If, you grab my hand,
50,000 won!
You've gone crazy thinking about money.
Don't worry, if I grab your hand,
I'll give you 50,000 won too.
Then, what if I were to grab your shoulder?
100,000 won.
How about
if I put an arm around your shoulder?
200,000 won?
Then, what if I were to hug you?
300,000 won.
A peck?
500,000 won!
Then, what about a kiss?
1 million won!
1... million... won?
Why are you acting like this,
all of a sudden?
Go over there.
Wow, it takes a lot of money
to be in a relationship with you.
What are you saying?
It's a million won for a kiss,
which guy would want to date you?
No one would be able to afford it,
even if it were a buy one get one free deal.
No...
If one were to prolong the kiss,
then it might be worth it.
Lee Yoon Sung!
Since you've already decided,
then you should go get your stuff.
Oh, right.
The hospital...
Ah, my bag...
Hey, if you keep this up and Boss finds
out, I'll be dead too.
Even so, I feel like Na Na is in danger,
I have to stay by her side.
Na Na?
What's wrong with Na Na?
The guy I encountered while I was pursuing
Lee Kyung Wan
knows Na Na and even where she lives too.
He's not your average guy, it seems.
What will happen
if you're discovered by someone?
Don't worry.
I'll be careful not to let anything slip.
Aigoo, I don't know, no matter how
I think about it, I still feel uneasy.
Ahjussi, just follow my father closely,
if you feel like something's about to slip,
just let me know.
I know, don't worry about me
and take care of yourself.
You, if you dare touch a hair
on Na Na's head...
I already told you my standards
are really high.
But, what is your relationship with Na Na?
No relationship at all.
Shall I pack some side dishes for you?
You can take them and share it with Na Na.
When I was buying fish,
they said it was buy one get one free,
so I bought quite a few.
Just bring some over.
There's also some pickled crab, it's just
pickled nicely, bring everything over.
Am I being married off?
What is this, really...?
Just... if Ahjussi is asking you to take it,
just take it.
Who gets to use the bathroom first?
Of course, I get to use it first.
That way, you can clean it every time.
Then I get to use a clean bathroom everyday.
Oh, right.
You have to clean the dog poop, too.
[Contract]
Kim Na Na.
What?
Do you have anything casual I can wear?
I didn't bring anything to wear to sleep,
the old judo gi was really comfortable
the other time.
What's the use of such a big suitcase,
when you didn't even bring a shirt
you can sleep in.
Hold on.
It's something anyone could forget.
If I had these looks
and was well-prepared too,
it would be too tiring to live.
Ah!
Na Na, you have to give me
the belt too. This...
You really don't know how to do things.
I'm going to use this.
Oh!
You can't use that!
- Why? I'll just use...
- I'll get you another one.
Use this one.
[Kim Na Na]
I'm going to use the bathroom!
Ah! It's so cold!
If you lift the cover up,
you need to put it back down!
Hold on!
Jerk.
Hey.
You...
Why do you wash your hair at night
and not in the morning,
you'll get dust in your hair.
There's so much to do in the morning.
I'm so busy, where can I find the time
to blow dry my hair?
I'm going to bed first.
Hey, this...
It would be nice
if we could watch together.
It's so boring watching by myself.
[Kim Na Na]
Mom, don't leave me by myself!
Mom!
Mom.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Are you crazy?
How could you follow right behind me?
What if someone sees you?
Hey, no one cares.
You're the one acting really strange.
I've lived in this neighborhood for
a really long time, everyone recognizes me.
I'll walk towards the market,
count to 20 and walk in the other direction,
understand?
You're going to the market?
Isn't that out of the way?
I'll get on the bus at the earlier stop.
Hey, you seem quite experienced at this.
You're so meticulous.
Who is it?
Keep your voice down, people can hear you.
I asked you who it is!
Count to 20, 20.
I've already summoned
Candidate Seo Yong Hak as a witness.
Have you not been able contact him?
He was admitted into the hospital,
after that he got discharged.
He has a packed schedule
and says it's really difficult to make time.
Are you going to make a trip personally?
I don't have time to meet him today,
I have an appointment.
We'll just reschedule the summoning
of Candidate Seo Yong Hak for tomorrow.
Yes, I will make preparations.
Oh, right.
Hudson of Maris Company is coming to Korea
the day after tomorrow, right?
Yes, that's right.
I'm sorry.
The team is a mess, right?
Would someone who knows how to worry
about the team do something like this?
Why didn't you just tell
the prosecutor honestly?
This wasn't something
that you, Go Ki Joon, did.
I did it, it's true.
We're both professionals,
you can stop lying to me.
Anyone with a smidgeon of hacking knowledge,
wouldn't use that type of method nowadays.
That day, after you drank a little,
you spilt the truth, didn't you?
Go Ki Joon,
after your brother went to the army,
he contracted tetanus
because of his defective boots,
which led to his leg being amputated.
And here I thought it was foolproof.
Tell the truth to the prosecution.
Since I just have to find a new job,
it's fine.
But what about my brother?
That kid really enjoyed taekwondo.
But now his life is over.
His dream was to run a taekwondo school
and teach children.
But just because of those stupid boots
with soles that fall off,
and their refusal to change it,
he ended up with tetanus.
Everyone, including the Board of Inspections
and the Ministry of Defense,
all of them pretended nothing happened.
As his hyung,
I couldn't do anything to help.
Then do as you like.
I don't have a brother,
so I can't really understand.
Life is a matter of choices,
Nothing is forced.
Shouldering this amount of regret,
can get a bit tiresome.
Although it's really a shame
that your leg became this way,
but asking your brother
to take the rap for you,
you're destroying him too. Is that it?
Hyung, won't listen to me.
Do you not have a mouth?
When the incident happened,
Go Ki Joon was at the Blue House.
If the truth is uncovered,
that will prove
that Go Ki Joon testified falsely.
That will definitely be enough.
The issue with the defective boots,
the Public Prosecutor's Office
has already started looking into it.
I think revealing the truth now
might be a good thing
for both of you.
Why are your shoulders so hunched?
Do you not know how to set
your feet wider apart?
Straighten your upper body,
so your two feet are the same
distance apart as your shoulders.
How many times do you want me to repeat it?
How did you ever get your PhD?
How can a man be so easily frightened?
Lower your chin!
Professor Lee Yoon Sung!
Da Hye,
access is restricted to staff members only.
What am I allowed to do then?
You don't let me do anything,
anything.
I want to learn how to shoot too.
It's not that you want
to learn how to shoot,
it's that you want to see Professor Lee.
Wow, that's so cool.
Teach me too!
I want to learn how to shoot too, okay?
Ms. Da Hye, if you really want to, let me...
I hope Professor Lee Yoon Sung can teach me.
Me?
Da Hye, then wear this,
if not, you're going to get hurt.
Unni, thank you!
Wow, wearing this,
don't I look really stylish?
Right?
Stand in the correct position first.
Like this?
Your feet have to be the same distance
as the width of your shoulders.
Like that, like that.
Then?
You have to be focused.
Then your right hand grips that gun,
and your left hand goes over your right.
Aigoo...
Is he good enough to be teaching someone?
After you hold your breath, and focus...
Pull... the trigger.
It's a lot simpler than I imagined!
Don't you know that the more off target
you shoot, the louder the gunshot?
What a show-off.
Wow! It's within the 10 point ring!
I must be naturally talented at shooting!
Can my university entrance exams
include marksmanship?
I would easily be able
to get into Seoul University then.
All this was the work
of Professor Lee Yoon Sung.
Can you teach me one more time?
All right? All right?
- I'm really busy.
- All right? All right?
- Teach me.
- Pull her off me!
Teach me one more time.
You've had a difficult journey.
The representative is waiting for you.
Yoon Sung.
Hudson is here.
Seo Yong Hak's secretary
came to greet him personally.
If we had mistook his arrival time
for tomorrow, we'd have been in big trouble.
Okay, later.
Did a friend arrive from America?
Yes.
If the incident with Go Ki Joon
didn't happen,
you could have let your friend
come visit the Blue House.
How nice would that be.
Who knew Go Ki Joon
would do something like that?
I'm heading out first,
my friend is waiting for me.
Then, of course you have to go see him.
If America asks you to join them,
it's a definite no, no!
You're here so early?
I'm not late, am I?
I can be touched, can't I?
Is this something to be touched about?
Of course.
When we were living together,
wasn't that how it was?
Not fulfilling your promises is a given,
and if you do,
I should be weeping with gratitude.
You don't have to feel sorry.
I bought you that tie for your birthday.
Is that so?
You don't even remember.
Do you remember
you are the one who bought all my ties?
What does that mean?
Have you not gone shopping
since we broke up?
Let's go.
Hi, Hudson.
- Nice to meet you.
- Welcome.
Recently, there have been
a lot of first year celebrations.
Families usually want to spend
their weekends together.
Emerald Hall...
Which way should we go?
Young Joo...
I'm sorry, Sae Hee, but you go ahead first.
I'll be there in a little bit.
Oh, where are you going...?
Now, this is like Kim Young Joo,
always putting work
ahead of everything else.
Why do I feel hurt again?
Ah, Prosecutor Kim...
What are you doing here?
You've even rejected all of my summons
because of your hospital stay.
What are you doing at a hotel?
I... passed by here during my inspection
of preparations for the press conference,
and I happened to run into someone I know.
But, do I have a duty,
to report everything to you?
Mr. Hudson, I'm Prosecutor Kim,
with the Seoul D.A.'s Office.
Wow, prosecutor, huh?
Prosecutor Kim!
Maris Company
better not make any illegal moves,
or tax violations
in its arms trade with Korea.
Excuse me?
I'm warning you.
Don't look down on Korea.
I'm sorry, but I don't understand
what you're talking about.
Hey, I haven't been coming down hard
on you because you're a friend's son.
But you have to have a limit, stop now!
Even if it's a friend of my father's,
the law is still the law.
I'll see you
at the witness cross-examination.
Is the D.A.'s Office
still investigating you?
A while ago, there was
an assassination attempt on my life.
I knew about that,
but this atmosphere now...
No matter how I look at it, it is because
I gained a fair bit during the elections.
That's why there will always be things
that people want to malign me for.
Ahjussi, hold on.
If they order room service
from Seo Yong Hak's room,
intercept it midway.
It's room service.
We didn't order it.
But an order was placed.
A foreign guest ordered coffee and fruits,
that's why I'm bringing it over.
Come in.
I was right.
Hold on.
What?
Just leave.
All right.
Wait.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Hey, Hudson tipped me 50,000 won.
Didn't you decide that
you will help me sell 30 fighter planes?
But why are you reneging on your decision?
Can you take a look
at the material I prepared?
Here.
Already...
There are defects in the fighter planes
so no one else wants to buy them,
and you want to sell them to us?
Fighter plane crashes
causing the death of a pilot,
in Russia, Georgia, India,
these three countries?
Look here, if we make these purchases
and something goes wrong,
you know exactly what will happen, right?
Even if I become president,
and an issue like this come up, I would be
impeached and removed from office, too.
Then, are you trying to say
you won't help me?
Would you do the same if you were me?
I will report that this deal
has completely fallen through.
What's the rush?
Sit down, sit down.
Can't we just import them?
But I have a condition.
In this transaction, as a handling fee,
I want 20 percent of the profits.
20 percent?
We've never paid such a steep commission
before.
It's better than letting them become scrap
metal because no one buys them, right?
Think about it.
Once I become president,
I will increase the defense spending
and buy more arms.
That's one of the first priorities
in my policies.
If it really happens,
and I become the president of this country,
Maris won't suffer any losses.
Do you understand?
Then, I'll draw up a contract,
stating that when you become president,
you guarantee not to change your mind.
All right.
One more thing.
Now, in order to achieve my goals,
I'm doing a deal with Maris.
But, if I become president,
I will never buy such inferior weapons.
When that time comes,
what we buy from Maris will be
the cream of the crop, with no flaws,
the best weapons.
Why?
Because more than anyone,
I love this country, understand?
To achieve your goals,
you're buying defective fighter planes?
You can never become the president.
The fact that someone like that wants to
become the president, is the problem.
Look at this society.
I didn't think things
had gotten to this level.
Report to Dad
and we'll set the date to take action.
Of course! We have to quickly set the dates
to get rid of this bunch of fellas.
It's enough to just get rid of them.
What's wrong, Ahjussi?
Yoon Sung,
I've already finished what I needed to do.
Can I go home first?
I have something important
to do back at home.
Something important?
The Home Shopping Channel is replaying that
show where the Fat Dad cooks the octopus.
You don't know how delicious it is,
it's sold out everyday. I must get it today!
We should give it a try too, see how
delicious it is, and cook for your dad.
Then, what about the bug
and the hidden camera in the next room?
Of course we should pack it up...
- You do it. Good work!
- Ahjussi... Ahjussi!
Will anything really happen tomorrow?
After that incident,
we can't let our guard down.
The criminal hasn't been caught yet,
we don't know what else they'll do.
Even if we're supposed to be bullet shields,
Are you, Agent Kim, really willing
to block a bullet with your body?
Of course we have to.
Because I'm an agent.
The vents in the ceiling are all checked,
now we just have to check the walls.
Congratulations.
After having given birth to three babies,
you guys are the true patriots.
You guys have to start loving the country,
too.
It's been already been 5 years,
why is there no news yet?
What about Sae Hee?
What did Sae Hee say when she got here?
Sae Hee?
Is Sae Hee here?
I haven't seen her.
[Kim Young Joo]
Dr. Jin Sae Hee.
Oh, it's Lee Yoon Sung.
[Sae Hee]
The number you dialed
is currently unavailable.
We're connecting you to the voicemail.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Oh, Prosecutor Kim Young Joo.
Na Na.
What are you doing here?
Are you on duty?
Yes.
There's a press conference tomorrow for the
elections, we came earlier to take a look.
Oh, you've become even busier
after the incident.
Oh, right...
Is the investigation going smoothly?
Look here.
Prosecutor Kim.
Are you even investigating
the agents now?
No.
I'm asking how the investigation is going
with the sniper attack.
Is that so?
With regard to the sniper at large,
he has a personal vendetta against you,
Sir.
There are a lot more areas to look into.
In order for us to wrap the case up quickly,
please offer us your assistance.
All right.
The person who is the most curious
about who the sniper,
is me.
This is boring.
You actually came here to drink by yourself?
Ah, that's right.
The first year celebration...
I came here for a first year celebration.
A first year celebration?
Although I'm happy to see you,
I have to go to the celebration.
I've not even given birth to a single child,
but my friend has already delivered three.
She got married because of me,
but she's leading a better life than I,
what a funny friend.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What should I do?
No, it's fine.
You don't have an important appointment,
do you?
No, my friend is here.
I came to find him.
I'll go and just get cleaned up.
Then, let's go together.
You should take your jacket off,
and I'll wash it immediately
then return it to you.
It's fine.
It seems you're quite drunk.
You helped me the other time
when I was in trouble,
how can I pretend nothing happened?
Sae Hee!
[17th Presidential Primary Election,
New People's Party National Convention]
It should be safe tomorrow.
There are no places anyone can hide either.
As long as we keep a close eye on
the identities of the reporters tomorrow,
there shouldn't be a problem.
All right, those whiny reporters,
won't be able to write nonsense
anymore, right?
Oh, Agent Kim.
Yes.
Can you please go up to Room 26
on the 19th floor.
Tell them you're my bodyguard,
and bring the documents that I forgot.
Don't look at them
bring them here directly.
I'll make a phone call to let them know.
Yes, I understand.
1925...
5...
6...?
Ah, you idiot.
How could you forget that already?!
Yes?
What is Prosecutor Kim Young Joo doing here?
Prosecutor?
Have you found it?
It looks like he isn't
an easy prosecutor to go up against.
Your parents are really lucky
to have such a good son like you.
I don't have a mother.
You have to pay special attention
to how you act.
Are you saying
you want to bring me down?
Candidate Seo!
Go ahead and try!
Is it really because of a girl?
It isn't because of a girl.
Why are you still hesitating?
The time isn't right yet.
You've become really arrogant
after not seeing you in such a long time.