During the period of the
'Warring States', 257B.C.,
Emperor Chin was tyrannical
Encroaching others' territories,
he killed mercilessly
He attacked the State of Chao
& took several cities
Imperial palaces were renovated
extravagantly
People of Chao are in great suffering
The troops led by Emperor Chin himself
are heading towards Han Dan
The State of Chao will soon fall
in the hands of Chin
and our State of Wei will be next
Master Hau, no need to say it
I believe that they'll be stopped
sooner or later
That's impossible
I'll be crossing the river immediately
You'll be getting good news in
about 3 days' time
What's your name please?
I am Zhu Hai
Da Liang City hero;
your great reputation precedes you
You flatter me
I'm just a nobody
I only hope to do something
Goodbye
Hero
Since you are in a hurry,
I shouldn't say more
I hope that you will take
good care of yourself
I'll be visiting you again some other time
Yes Sir
"Ping Yi Palace"
Yin Yue, listen carefully
Be careful in what you say
Catch him, chase...
Chase...
Men, catch the assassin
Yes
Catch the assassin
Stand still
Your Highness
It's no use, the assasin has escaped
I deserve death for my lax security
The assassin is trapped owing to
Sire's sharp-Wit
Come
It's lucky that you are smart
and didn't fall into Emperor Chin's trap
I'm ashamed
If it were not because of that palace maid
whose etiquette was not
appropriate for an Emperor
I would have killed 2 fake ones and gone
Wouldn't have bothered perhaps
looking for the third
The third one is fake too
Please take a seat...
Brother, this morning someone saw him
giving orders to attack the city
Emperor Chin is ruthless
He'd of course take precautions
against assassins
It's easy for him to find someone
to die in his place
That's why mere courage won't solve
the problem
Even if it succeeded by sheer luck
Chin could easily appoint another one
It'd simply be changing one tyranny
for another
A true hero should first
unite all feudal princes...
against tyranny, and rescue
the State of Chao
I am nothing but a commoner...
No, all play a part in the rise
and fall of a nation
You should make good use of your skills
to join force against tyranny
Our State of Wei has no news of
sending troops
That's right, Brother Bai Chi
is a palace guard
of course he'll know
Sooner or later, Prince Shun Ling
will join hands against the tyranny
of Chin
Also, the State of Chao
& feudal princes of our nation
...are relatives
Your Highness
Bai Chi who's ordered to act as
State of Wei's spy
is here for Your Highness
By the order of His Highness,
send Bai Chi in
Send Bai Chi in
Greetings to Your Highness
Rise
It is...guilty, I won't dare to
Sire, I've found the whereabouts
of the assassin
You've done well, rise and speak
Thank you, your Highness
You've found out his whereabouts
He's Zhu Hai from the State of Wei
I have pretended to befriend him
and intend to get rid of him by fraud
You should rather watch closely
to see if Wei
will send troops to Chao's rescue.
This way...
your identity as Wei's palace guard
won't be exposed
It's quite unlikely that Wei
will send troops
In Yeh Ha which is 60 miles away from here
Jin Bi is leading a troop of 1 00,000
But Wei's prince for the sake of Chao
wouldn't dare offend Your Highness
You should know that
Chao's Princess is the sister
of the prince of Wei and
pretty close to her younger brother
Prince Shun Ling
At the critical moment
she will definitely seek help
from the prince of Wei
Did you come because of this?
Yes
Han Dan is in great danger
It'll be too late
to wait till tomorrow
Sounds reasonable
but it's not that easy to re-locate troops
Jin Bi is leading a troop of 1 00,000
in Yeh Ha
They can arrive in one day
to release Han Dan
But Jin Bi's troops...
His troop guards the border
and cannot be relocated
Your Highness, I travelled non-stop from
the State of Chao, hoping that
for the sake of our relationship,
& considering that
Ruthless Chin has been invading
others' territories
The State of Wei is also in danger
Rescuing Chao is...is...
beyond our power
In terms of relation Lady Ping Yuan
is your sister;
the States of Chao and of Wei
are neighbours
The tyrannical Chin after acquiring
the State of Chao
will attack the State of Wei
Please rescue Chao for the sake
of our brotherhood
It's an important matter to save
the State of Chao
We'll wait until tomorrow
when the court meets
and seek Su Song's advice
As the saying goes, to each his own
Although you are the brother
of His Highness
you both are so different
Sending troops in Chao's aid is
risking self for others
His Highness won't agree to it
His Highness may seek advice
of the lmperial Teacher
Please explain what I've said just now
to His Highness
It won't be easy
After all, it's not his own business
States are interdependent on each other
This is something which will happen
in future
It may not be easy to convince
His Highness now
So Lady Ping Yuan will waste her effort
His Highness won't be able to send troops
I can't be of any further help
If this is the case, I can only lead
all my guests, servants
and Lady Ping Yuan to fight for
the State of Chao
Well...your followers & servants
are no more than
a few thousand
Compared with the Chin troops
they are up against insurmountable odds
It's worth dying for a cause
we shouldn't think too much about
winning and losing
Goodbye
Prince
Sister
What you've just said deserves
great reverence
You will be well respected if you lead
your followers and servants
to fight for Chao
But what good will there be
for the State of Chao?
Father and I have just been
discussing about the affairs
of the State of Chao
We were talking about Jin Bi's troops
when you arrived
I guess not only is the king
against sending troops
the generals & the army is also
afraid of Chin's terror
Go ahead, feel free to say it
Han Dan and Yeh Ha are only
tens of miles apart
If Jin Bi can make a show of power
Chin won't dare to march in
Good idea
If we can convince His Highness
and you lead
the army on behalf of Jin Bi,
Chao will be saved
As long as the State of Chao can be saved
I am willing to risk my life for it
Even without any military power
you are already revered by all
His Highness may not give you
the military power
There's no way you can replace Jin Bi
His Highness admires sister
Dad, is this true?
Yes, about half a month ago
His Highness gave me a piece of jade
Pisces Jade
It is as famous as Wo's Jade
There is a yin jade and a yang jade
His Highness is wearing the yang jade and
it's for obvious reason that
he gave me this yin jade
Dad, what do you mean?
No one knows a daughter better than
her own father
I'm just pretending not to
understand his real purpose
and wearing the piece of jade all the time
His Highness hasn't raised the issue again
If you agree
Sister would be like a hostage
to His Highness
With you leading the troops of Wei
His Highness would not have to worry
What do you think?
No
You are focused on rescuing
the State of Chao
Although I'm not able to convince
His Highness
I'll try my best
This...
and convince him of the pros and cons
I better get writing tomorrow's memo,
please excuse me
Looking at the moon, I muse
While my heart is full of perplexity
It used to beat only for the moon
But he bathes all in his light
Why won't it shine only on me?
It does not appreciate my song
Nor does it understand my meaning
I can only pine in vain
Pine until my heartstrings break
Yes, I was on guard that day
and heard Su Song talking like this
at the palace
but Prince of Wei did not agree
That's why His Highness sent me over
to help you
This...
What? Are there problems in
killing Su Song?
Originally you were to assassinate
Prince Shun Ling
but I told His Highness that
Prince Shun Ling has many followers
and is an expert in kung fu
Therefore it will be hard to kill him
Killing Su Song may help
to teach them a lesson
I'm afraid that my identity will be
exposed and then
I won't be able to stay at
the State of Wei anymore
You don't have to do it yourself
Use this as a false accusation
against Su Song
and convince Zhu to assassinate him
Is he supposed to come today?
Yes
Zhu Hai is here
Let's retire
Coming...
Brother Bai
Please have a look
Dear Su Song, you're the man
of Emperor Chin
This is real
It's the fact
Before you came
I've decided to kill that traitor tonight
but I'm afraid that I'll fail
so...I'd like...
Brother Bai, can I help?
You are a great fighter, you will succeed
but this is too dangerous
What? You think l...
Yes, that's for the people,
please accept my salute
I'm getting old
It's late now
Why don't you rest?
I've been thinking about what you told me
Will the State of Chao be saved
if we send troops to their rescue?
Of course
Presently Chin acts reckless because
they think that no one dares
to go against them
Dispatch of troops from Wei
is psychological warfare
Chin will be less tyrannical
if it knows that
the princes are united in
fighting against tyranny
Is there any other way
other than sacrificing me?
Hardly
His Highness will not trust me in leading
Jin Bi's troops if you are not his wife
What about the Prince?
If he is not able to rescue
the State of Chao
he will regret it for the rest of his life
There must be a better way
Zhu Hai's greetings to teacher
At this late an hour with your sword...!
I'd like to seek your advice
His Highness agreeing to aid
State of Chao; is it true?
Why do you say that?
Didn't you write a memorial to Chin?
You come here at this late hour
talking nonsense
Don't be angry, please have a look
It's a fake one
I deserve death, I trusted the liar
Bai Chi
Bai Chi the palace guard
It's him, he gave me this memorial
I'll come to apologiZe after
I settle this with him
Yu Er, you can see for yourself that
even he wants to fight
against tyranny, but you...
Yu Er
Dad, don't say it
I will fulfil his wish
Who are you?
Guards, there's an assassin!
Bai Chi
Dad
What is it?
It's been poisoned
Stop joking
This is the wine Bai Chi
has prepared for celebration
after Zhu Hai has killed Su Song
Where's Zhu Hai?
Not back yet
Zhu Hai saw through our plan
Let's go, hurry
Okay
Where's Su Song?
He's been killed
Hurry, pack up and leave Dai Liang
Alright
It's too late now
You've to payback for Su Song's life
Sister
What's done is done, don't be sad
Yes
I've just spoken to Master Hau
about revenge
Bai Chi is from Chin
He serves as a palace guard
but actually is a spy
Last night Zhu Hai killed his whole family
but Bai Chi escaped
I've decided to send Nam Gung Fei to Chin
Zhu Hai blamed himself
and wished to come along
and took Bai Chi
Prince, I let you make the decision
Sister, don't cry
My sister will help you
to take care of the affairs
I'll arrange for Zhu Hai to go to Chin
By His Highness' order-Bai Chi
being the palace guard
of the State of Wei served loyally
for our country
He will be sent to the Slave Camp
Come...
How dare you, Lord Yu
I was promised promotion
after I've killed Su Song
I'm willing to render service in gratitude
That's correct
To the slave camp
This is how you'll be rewarded
You have great achievements
at the State of Wei
A lot of people know you
that's why you have to be defaced
Lord Yu
I risked my life for the services
please plead with His Highness
to change decision...
Sire said you may also seek merit
for service to nation
So you'll have many complaints
at the encampment, too
For this reason your tongue
will be cut off too
Go...
Lord Yu...
"Slave Camp"
Get in
Come, release all the slaves out
to fend off the Chin troops
Alright
Don't move...
Don't be afraid, I'm here to rescue you
Good news?
How can there be good news?
His Highness wants to take Miss Su
as his concubine
Su Song pretended not to understand
This is now the golden opportunity
But...if sister is reluctant to...
No need to worry
If Your Highness could avenge her
Miss Su will agree
True. Prepare for ceremony
and escort her to the palace
Yes
Bai Chi has been arrested at the
Chin's slave camp
Unfortunately his tongue has been cut off
Everyone in the camp is like this
Strange. He has accomplished
great services for Chin
how come he ends up in the slave camp?
Bai Chi can no longer stay
at the State of Wei
He's of no use
to Chin anymore
Prince, this is the piece of jade
found on him
Pisces jade
Report to the Prince,
Lady Ping Yuan is back
Where's Miss Su?
Haven't seen her
Your Highness, Miss Su arrives
No need to stand on ceremony
Thank you, Your Highness
Beg your pardon for not changing
to right attire
Rise
My wish has been conveyed to you
Yes
Thank you for your great kindness
No need to stand on ceremonies, rise
Don't worry, I've issued great awards
to avenge teacher
Thank you, Your Highness
For your own safety
you should stay at the palace
This mansion will be cleaned up
for your stay
Thank you, but my father
has just passed away
I'm in mourning; such an
elegant mansion isn't apt
That's easy. Remove all the decoration
Yes
Please forgive me, I've still to
observe mourning
It's for your safety that I asked you
to move in
and besides, we can see each other
more often
Are you disobeying my order?
I don't dare to
That's good. Rise
I don't dare disobey Your Highness' order
but I still have to avenge
my father's death
Please forgive me for not seeing you
Then...can't I even see you here?
Please forgive me
If I'm forced to, I'd rather die
Alright, as you wish
Thank you, Your Highness
The murderer is caught
Sister has gone to the palace
That's right. Since she's there she could
convince His Highness to
send troops in Chao's aid
It's no use
How is that?
His Highness wants to take Miss Su
as his concubine
but he can't succeed
Now he took her into his palace
There is nothing else His Highness desires
there's no hope for the troops to be sent
Then Han Dan is in great danger
Sister, Master Hau must find a way
Stealing military tally is the only way
You will lead Jin Bi's troops
to rescue Han Dan
But the military tally is placed
in the vault
The key of which is always
with His Highness
That's not difficult, Miss Su can do it
Then...
Now that Bai Chi is caught
Miss Su should declare her vengeance
Yes, sister has sworn an oath that
she'll marry whoever avenges
her father's death
Madam must now visit Miss Su
& secretly tell her that
the murderer will be sacrificed
before Teacher's grave
You ask Ms Su to steal the tally
and bring it to you
But the vault is guarded strongly
That's not difficult either
Pick a brave but not reckless man and
bring Bai Chi's head along with him
to the palace
as a moral support to Miss Su
I can go to the palace and
be Miss Su's support
Alright. Good
Do as planned
Dad, Prince has caught the murderer
In order that I can avenge your death
I swore that
the Prince would decide my fate
I've been asked to steal
the military tally
and I have agreed
Dad said that Prince and
I should not be separated
In Prince's heart, I am not
as important as
rescuing the State of Chao
In order to fulfil his wish
I'll sacrifice my love for honour
Sister
I cannot repay your great favour enough
I will try my best to fulfil your wish
Thank you, Sister
I've discussed this matter
with Master Hau
The military tally of Yeh Ha
is of the shape of a tiger
I remember when Jin Bi was sending troops
The key to the vault is carried by
His Highness
Only those close to him
can have access to it
We've to wait until Bai Chi
is killed and sacrificed
Zhu Hai will bring his head
to His Highness to seek
offers as guard, but in fact
to liaise with sister
Stealing the tally deserves death penalty
therefore...
So I hope sister can go with me
to the State of Chao
Return to the State of Chao?
Yes, I swear an oath in front of
Teacher's grave
Prince
Sister
Prince, the time has come,
please offer the sacrifice
Yes, offer the sacrifice
This is really the head of Bai Chi
You are loyal to the country; and...
since you requested to serve as
palace guard, enter
Thank you, Your Highness
His Highness arrives
No need to stand on ceremony
You have your revenge
This is the head of your enemy Bai Chi
Take it away
Yes
It's too terrible
Sister
Thank you, Your Highness
No need to stand on ceremony
Pisces jade
Teacher had prophesied joy
when both pieces match
This has finally come true, reward him
The divine intelligence of His Highness
Your Highness, General Tung Gou Chung,
reports to your majesty
Bring him to the front room
He...he is at the palace gate
May I be excused
Send him in
Yes
Tung Gou Chung's greetings to
Your Highness
I've collected the rice tax from Mong Man
and there's a total of 50 carts
It's all been delivered to
General Jin Bi at Yeh Ha
and I'm here to return the tally
Good
Lord Tung Guo will take the post
as Minister of the lmperial Guard
Yes
Lord Tung Guo transferred to be
the Minister
and is in charge of the lmperial Guards
Thank you, Your Majesty
Sister
Your Highness
Please wait
I'll put back the military tally
in the vault
Yes
Your Highness
What is it?
Bai Chi's head is frightening
please let someone else take the tally
Well...
No one can get into the vault
except me
Can I not go in with you too?
Of course you can
Let's go
His Highness arrives
"The Vault"
Let's go
Guards
Yes
Sister
Why are you crying?
Aren't you happy at this?
I...I am just too happy
In that case, laugh. One cries only
when sad
Please pardon my inappropriate behaviour
From now onwards you will be the princess
Yes
Don't have any doubts,
& you shouldn't cry today
You should smile
Laugh
Lady, His Highness won't trust anyone for
the military tally
How dare you disobey orders!
You disobey orders by entering the vault
How dare you!
Disperse
Back off
Lady, please wait
Allow me to seek the advice of
His Highness
Attack
Wait
Lady will die if you come any further
Please convey to the Prince
I've to bid him farewell
What? Aren't you leaving?
Prince said he'll be waiting for you
at the Yi Gate
I'd be like a fugitive going with
the Prince to Chao
This was not thoroughly thought out
You...
Have you forgotten the Prince's oath
to you?
Prince has a strong ambition,
he won't miss me
Besides, I am different now
You are now a princess, you're different
I'm leaving
Huh!
What is it?
Yu Jiang leading Zhu Hai with the key
to the vault
entered it by force
The 1 2 men guarding the vault
tried to stop them
There were serious casualties
One of them who was seriously wounded
came back to report and
is now outside the palace
Order General Bai Li Ho
wait for further instructions at the vault
Yes
Prince, I believe even if you wait
until dawn
the Lady won't come back
If you see the Lady
please convey my wish to her
wishing her riches and glory
Speak, who sent out the tally for you?
Fight against Chin not only means
rescue of...
the State of Chao, it's also saving
our own country
Any man with a vision will do
the same thing
Nonsense
Calm down, Your Highness
Prince Shun Ling's men are
a band of scoundrels
It's not difficult to take
the tally out of the palace
He has to leave by the Yi Gate to go
to Yeh Ha
I'll stop him there
Alright
You anticipated correctly
Speak
Prince knew that you will stop him
at Yi Gate
so he has detoured via the South Gate
Tung Guo Chung
Yes
You hurry to South Gate. Just nab
& execute him
Yes
"Yi Gate"
The troops are behind us
Prince, come and hide over here
Wait
You said the Prince has left
via the south gate
Luckily I took a short cut and
passed the Yi Gate
Prince, surrender please
Chase
Yu Jiang stole the tally for Wu Ji
How can you take her word
& go to the South Gate
I deserve death
Your Highness
The Prince just pretends to be good
his followers are a band of scoundrels
It's difficult to guard against treachery
Since there's just Lady Ping Yuan
in Prince's home
I fear there'll be an ambush
at the Yi Gate
If Master Bai Li fails to get
to Yeh Ha and
meets Jin Bi, he'll catch up
with the Prince
I'm afraid that he's no match for Wu Ji
Your Highness, I am willing to take
the short cut
to Yeh Ha to arrest Wu Ji
Alright, go to Yeh Ha then
Send orders to Jin Bi to arrest Wu Ji
Thank you Your Highness
Greetings to the Lady
I'm sorry to have troubled you
What happened today is really amaZing
Before the stealing of the military tally
I've already prepared for the punishment
You'd have then left with the Prince
to State of Chao
Once Chao is rid of danger,
Prince will be prosperous
Do you know that the Prince almost
messed up when you didn't show up
at the Yi Gate
I'm already the wife of His Highness
If I went with him to the State of Chao
he would be guilty of stealing the tally
and taking his brother's wife
Why I don't let the Prince to get
fame and the glory
and let me bear the guilt
Then the Prince would have misjudged you
In the process, I only hope that
I don't owe anyone
Prince will...
...He'll know one day
You've really suffered
I'll let my brother know
Order him to send Han Chi to Yeh Ha
Master Bai Li
Master Lin?
I don't deserve it
Master Bai Li, you are in Mong Yi
at this late hour...
By His Highness' order, I'm here to
arrest Wu Ji
Isn't Prince Shun Ling in Da Liang?
He stole the tally and left for Yeh Ha
I've searched all the inns
at the main road
Seems he's taken a shortcut
as there's no sign of him
Short cut, huh! Then Mong Yi
must be the only way
Master Bai Li, you may wish to go in
& have a look
He really hasn't been here
You really foretell things accurately
Master Bai Li is here for the tally
But the courier chief said the Prince
is not here
Sir, I feel I owe an apology to the Prince
He's inside
Wait, in case the Prince resists
and fights on
I'm afraid there'll be unnecessary
casualties
I've some drugs here
That's right, let's drug them first
And then...
Good, let's do it
I'm leaving
Goodbye, Master Bai Li
Prince, I apologiZe for being away
for so long
No need to stand on ceremonies
Master Bai Li...
He's gone, I'm afraid that he'll come in
so I've advised him to search
at the other inns
Thank you for your kindness
No problem
Prince, please...
Bring the wine
Yes
It's important that you should all
be careful
Yes
Prince, let's drink
Please
Prince, the wine is poisoned, don't drink
It's Han Chi
Tomorrow night, we'll be at Yeh Ha
but you are now dead
Prince
General Han, something happened
at Da Liang?
Yes, the princess is imprisoned
Sister
Lady Ping Yuan went to visit the princess
and found her out for the sake
of the Prince
She bore the guilt in stealing
the military tally
Being angry, His Highness imprisoned
the princess
& sent troops after the prince
to execute them both
Princess asked the Lady to convey
to the Prince that he has to take
extra care
and fulfil the wish of rescuing
the State of Chao
Sister
General Han
Yes
Go to Da Liang and pass on my message
Say that Wu Ji is grateful
for princess' favours
and is not able to repay her
The good news is
I can go to Yeh Ha without any obstacles
With the tally I can replace
Jin Bi to lead his troops
to rescue the State of Chao
Jin Bi guarded Yeh Ha for 1 0 years
Generals outside the capital
won't submit to orders
Just with half of the military tally
I can hardly hand over my 1 00,000 troops
How dare you disobey His Highness' order
and befriend Chin for our own safety!
His Highness asked me to come
all the way for
fear that you might follow
the Prince's order
when you see the tally
Naturally I won't listen to him, but...
Prince Shun Ling is honourable
It's hence even our troop leaders
support him
Unless, of course, they don't know
about this matter
Then...
General Chung
Yes
Lead your troops
and block the road from the camp to here
As soon as Prince Shun Ling is here
don't let any of our men come over
Yes
General Tung Guo, the prince is
digging his own grave
Yes, His Highness wants to
capture him alive
Your current plan
might injure him
and His Highness won't like this
Kill him & say he stole the military tally
with the intention to revolt
General
Prince Shun Ling is at
the inspection podium
That's quick
Please hurry
Yes
Prince
No formality, please
What brings you to Yeh Ha
at this late hour?
I'm here to lead the troops by
His Highness' order
Please hand over the tally
Such insolence
Prince, allow me to check the tally
You dare disobey an order?
Disobey order?
Guards
Prince, you are arrested
General, soldiers at the camp want to
go with the Prince to rescue
the State of Chao
and started a fight with those
who stopped them
There were serious casualties
on both sides
They are charging towards us
and are at the podium
Stop, Prince
Since the soldiers wish to go
with the Prince
I'm willing to hand over the tally
General
This is inevitable
But the soldiers cannot be appeased
Prince, please do something
We want to go with the Prince to
rescue the State...
Things will go out of hand
if they go on like this
Please match the tally and
pass down orders
in order that the soldiers will calm down
Please
Stand still
Jin Bi, how dare you hurt the Prince
The soldiers' sentiment is turbulent
I have no other alternative
but to use Prince's head
Announce to the troops
Yes
The Prince is treacherous,
he will be executed on spot
Yes
Please
Prince
Wu Ji was to lead the troops to
rescue State of Chao
Jin Bi was executed because
he disobeyed orders
Do you generals have anything to say?
We'll follow the Prince to save
the State of Chao
Save the State of Chao...
You are here in time
I've begged His Highness
for granting me my own death
& have finally had it
Why do you have to do that?
Han Chi met my brother at Mong Yi
and is on the way to Yeh Ha,
he understands everything
Do you really have to die?
Yes
The Prince have stolen the military tally
and have committed serious crime
If I don't face justice
the Prince's honourable act
will be besmeared
I feel so ashamed
By the order of His Highness,
Lady will be executed
Yes
Madam, please retreat
To repay him for fulfilling her wish
But that also makes me frightened
Her name will live on in posterity