公众号：VC星球英语
微信：VCPlanet
Hello.
Ricky here with your
Thursday Newsround.
First up, President Trump has
stopped travel from lots of European
countries to America to try to stop
the spread of the coronavirus there.
New rules will come into force
tomorrow but won't affect
those travelling from the UK.
Meanwhile Prime Minister Boris
Johnson has a big coronavirus
meeting later today to decide
what the government's next steps
are for this country.
Mr Trump says he's focussed
on keeping Americans safe.
To keep new cases from
entering our shores,
we will be suspending all travel
from Europe to the United States
for the next 30 days.
The new rules will go
into effect Friday at midnight.
In Italy, many shops,
public areas and schools have been
closed to help stop the spread
of the coronavirus there.
So what's it like living like that?
Well, we asked Evie
who's in northern Italy.
Hi, Newsround.
I'm Evie and I'm 11 years old.
I live with my family here in Italy.
It's kind of boring.
I don't have my friends
so I've got nobody really
to talk to about school.
At first it was quite
nice because it was only
two weeks, we thought.
It was like, "Oh, it's a little
holiday," but now it's proving to be
a bit more difficult.
It is a sensible idea
to be on lockdown because
it means less people
and less people in hospitals
and less rush, so I do think
it is a better idea.
For me, it sounds a lot scarier
than it really is because it's
really just like a holiday with work
and it's not that scary.
You don't have to be scared.
It's just, you know,
you'll be limited.
Sometimes we do go out for hikes.
I have been once with my mum and dad
to the supermarket and we actually
all went as a family trip
because everybody was getting kind
of fed up so we had a family
trip to the supermarket.
Everybody knows that they need
to keep their distance and they do.
You kind of have
to live like a ghost.
When you are walking to school have
you ever had to step
onto the road or squeeze past a car
because a driver has
parked on the pavement?
Well, a new ban could be coming.
It already exists in London and now
more local authorities around
the country could get powers
to tackle the issue.
OK, time for a quick
round-up of some of the big
sport stories today.
It was bad news
for the Lionesses after England
failed to defend their She Believes
trophy after a seventh
defeat in 11 games.
They lost 1-0 to Spain
in their final match
of the tournament while USA beat
Japan 3-1 to win the competition.
Last year's
European champions Liverpool
are out of the Champions League
after they were beaten 3-2
by Atletico Madrid last night
with some goalkeeping mistakes
by Adrian costing them dearly.
And Neymar helped French
champions Paris St Germain
beat Borussia Dortmund to reach
the quarter finals.
But due to the coronavirus,
the game took place in an empty
stadium because fans are banned
from attending matches.
Keepy-uppies are tricky
at the best of times but how
about doing them while crossing
the world's largest frozen lake?
That's what Kickabout's freestyler
John Farnwoth's latest
charity challenge is all about.
Let's get going!
I think we are, well,
maybe halfway through.
I'm not sure exactly where we are.
It's very hard to get a perspective
because it's just miles and miles
and miles of ice and snow.
Non-stop keepy-uppies across this
frozen lake in Siberia,
that's half a million touches
across 50 miles, and at times
the pain is just too much.
The back of my left knee
has just seized up.
It's really, really painful.
I can't even move.
So I've had to stop
and massage it out.
I was in pain but I feel a little
bit lighter actually.
It's good to know we've got
supplies in the van.
We'll just see how it goes.
Back on the move and John Farnworth
completed his challenge in just 48
hours to raise money for charity.
Time to put your feet
up, John, I think.
Grab a cuppa and settle down
in front of Kickabout.
And talking of charity challenges.
it's Sport Relief on Friday
when loads of you will be putting
on your PE kit and getting
sporty for good causes.
So we want to hear from you about
what you've got planned.
Head to the Newsround website to let
us know what you'll be doing.
Just take a look at this view.
You're seeing one
of the world's highest
outdoor sky decks.
It's just opened its
doors in New York.
The mega platform is on the 100th
floor of a new skyscraper
in the heart of New York City
in the US.
Visitors can walk over this glass
floor and if you're feeling brave
you can even take a selfie
with the rest of the city
as your backdrop.
That's all from us for now.
Head online for loads more including
the Harry Potter book that
sold for a fortune and
everything you need to know
about Little Mix's new talent show.
公众号：VC星球英语
微信：VCPlanet