Alexandria Motel
I'm telling you, something happened,
something changed.
It's been weird between us lately.
Lately?
Kate, it's been weird for four years.
No, this is different.
He's different. It's like he's pulling away.
Well, can you blame him? He's probably tired of waiting.
Waiting for what?
What do you think?
The guy is crazy about you.
And despite your little act, you're crazy about him.
Oh, what, was that supposed to be some big secret?
Yes.
No.
Do you think he knows?
You remember how he used to be,
girl on either arm?
You really don't see that guy too much anymore.
Why do you think that is?
He's waiting for you.
Yeah, but, Lanie...
I know. You're dealing with stuff.
But you cannot ask him to wait forever.
Unless, of course, you're okay with him pulling away.
What if it doesn't work?
What if it ends up like you and Javi?
Well, at least we gave it a shot.
And so it didn't work out. So what?
Now we can move on, give or take the occasional booty call.
I just... I don't want to lose what we have, you know?
Girl, please.
What exactly do you have, really?
A friendship.
No. What you and I have is a friendship.
What you and Castle have is a holding pattern.
How long can you circle before the fuel runs out?
Beckett.
Don't think you were saved by the bell, Kate Beckett.
As your friend, I'm not gonna let this drop.
So what, you think I should tell him how I feel?
Yes.
You Hunt murderers for a living. You can do this.
Okay. Okay.
I just... I-I have to find the right time.
No time like the present.
What the...
On second thought,
maybe you should wait a bit.
What's that? Ryan's calling. I gotta go.
I'll call you in about an hour.
Hey there.
I feel like I just walked into a bad episode of "Miami Vice. "
Okay, first, there are no bad episodes of "Miami Vice. "
Second, who died?
You from the looks of it.
You look like you just got run over by a truck.
Yeah,
a truck delivering a shipment of awesome.
No, I just flew into Vegas for the weekend.
Just needed a little change of scenery.
And you won the blonde in a high-stakes poker match?
No, I met her on the flight back.
And you just gave her your car?
Jacinda happens to be a very trustworthy person.
She's a first-class flight attendant.
It's not like I gave her my social security number.
Castle...
Is everything okay?
Never better.
Our victim's Naomi Allen, age 25.
Her green card indicates that she's a British national.
Ryan is notifying the consulate.
Her address is in Soho.
What was she doing all the way down here?
Don't know, but she checked in
two hours before she was killed.
I hope they prorated the room.
Good news is, we have a witness.
The maid who discovered the body saw a guy run out.
Did the maid get a good look?
She's with the sketch artist now.
Well, whoever he is, he was looking for something.
This place has been searched.
The one thing we do know is that she was not robbed.
Her wallet, watch, and cash were untouched.
Hey, Lanie, how does it look?
Like you waited too long.
The vic.
She was strangled but she went down with a fight.
Prelim suggests a sign of a struggle.
She took one to the face.
A well-dressed, attractive woman in a seedy motel
and a guy who flees the crime scene...
This might have been a one-night stand gone wrong.
Are we talking about the victim or Castle?
Hey, Espo.
Yeah.
Can you contact the next of kin and canvass the area once the sketch is done?
Yeah, no problem.
Hey, Beckett.
Found the vic's business card
in the side pocket of her purse.
Looks like she works in Manhattan.
"Naomi Allen, Kittman Group. "
Kittman Group
Yes, I was her U.S. booking agent.
Naomi was one of our top models.
So she was in the city for work?
She split her time between here and London.
The good ones usually end up spending at least half the year in New York.
Now do you have any idea why she was at the Alexandria motel last night?
Uh, no. I've never even heard of it.
It's one of those, um, pay-by-the-hour places.
Do you recognize this man?
No. No, I don't.
But you do have an idea of who he might be.
It's just...
lately,
Naomi was making some choices.
What kind of choices?
Well, she seemed to have lost interest
in standard modeling jobs.
Recently, she had been booking more, uh,
unconventional gigs.
Like what?
Well, I heard the London office booked her to attend
the birthday party of some foreign dignitary
a few months ago.
She was hired to go to a party?
It's common for models to get hired to pretty-up an event.
Some girls do it to pick up extra cash.
And other girls do it as a way of connecting
with wealthy men.
Uh, wait. Are you saying
that Naomi was hiring herself out as an escort?
You just don't see girls as good as Naomi
taking these party jobs.
Not unless there's a bigger payout involved somewhere.
Do you know if she took on
any of these kinds of gigs recently?
It's not really what we do.
She did want me to try to get her into an event last night, though,
uh, an album launch party in midtown.
But I didn't have any connections to it.
Last night?
Yeah.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
Yeah, that we should throw a party
and hire a bunch of models.
No.
That maybe Naomi somehow got into that party last night
and that that's where she met her killer.
That's what I was thinking.
Weird. We're usually more in sync than that.
Hey, Ryan.
Did you find anything at Naomi's apartment?
No, but someone else might have. It's been tossed.
Not only that, but a neighbor said
they saw a man leaving the apartment late last night.
The neighbor I.D.'ed him off the sketch.
It's the same guy who fled the murder scene.
He couldn't find what he was looking for
in the motel so he searched her place.
Yeah, but this time, he left a footprint.
Meaning?
Well, UNIS canvassed around the apartment with the sketch.
He bought a bottle of single malt with a credit card
a couple of blocks away.
Colin Hunt. What do we have on him?
Nothing in the system, but I ran a trace on the credit card.
He checked into the mondrian Soho this morning.
Here.
NYPD. Show me your hands.
You're making a mistake.
Yeah, like I haven't heard that before.
Hands in the air now.
If you insist.
Whoa. Dude. Whoa
Allow me to introduce myself.
Detective Inspector Colin Hunt, Scotland Yard.
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
灵书妙探 第四季第20集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
时间轴：感冒柚
You're a long way from home, Detective Inspector Hunt.
How did you end up in that dead girl's motel room?
I was at a seminar in D.C. last night when Naomi called me, panicked.
She said she was in trouble and needed my help.
So you knew her?
Naomi was like a sister to me.
Her dad Terence was my first partner on the job.
When he passed away,
I promised her family that I'd look after her.
After she called me, I grabbed the next flight,
but by the time I arrived, it was too late.
And your first instinct was to flee the crime scene?
I didn't flee. I left.
She was dead.
There was nothing else to do.
Yeah, except maybe to hang around
and give the police a statement.
You and I both know that if I stuck around,
it'd be hours of questioning, and then you'd send me off
with a "cheers, we'll keep you posted. "
But I suppose you had something more important to do.
The room had been searched.
Whoever killed her was looking for something.
I thought they might try her apartment next.
By the time I got there, it had already been tossed.
Look, I know I shouldn't have been investigating,
but if you were in a foreign country
and someone you loved was killed, what would you do?
What were they looking for?
When he was on a job, Naomi's dad used to stash a gun
in the lining of his kevlar.
When Naomi started modeling as a teenager,
he didn't want her on the underground without any protection,
so he taught her to cut a tiny piece
of the lining in her jacket to stash pepper spray.
That's where I found it.
You found what?
A message to me about her killer.
What kind of message?
Not until I'm on the case.
Excuse me?
Detective, please,
I owe this to Naomi.
I owe it to her family.
You do realize that I could arrest you
for withholding evidence?
And since you don't know what that evidence is,
I could deny it.
And none of that will get us any closer to catching her killer.
Let me work this case with you,
because if you don't, I swear,
I will go out there and catch the bastard on my own.
Okay.
But I have to check in with my captain first.
What's she like, your captain?
You ever see that Youtube video
of the grizzly bear that decapitates a moose
with one swipe of its paw?
Comforting.
It's nothing personal.
She just doesn't like outsiders in her precinct.
I don't need her to like it. I just need her to allow it.
This whole thing with Naomi doesn't add up.
Turning down conventional modeling jobs,
booking sleazy gigs at private parties...
That just doesn't sound like the Naomi I know.
Yeah, well, sometimes it's the people we think we know best
that we don't really know at all.
Well... You're in.
Thank you.
What?
Seriously?
Yeah, your supervisor at Scotland Yard said you're one of the best.
Even captain gates was impressed with your record.
Well, I guess it's not outsiders she doesn't like.
It's just me.
Look, we had a deal. What did Naomi give you?
This.
A key?
You said she left a message. - This is the message.
She put it in there for me to find.
I guarantee, it has something to do with her death.
This looks commercial.
It's an Arco-Rifkin 11-30-R,
mostly used for lockers like those found at train stations or health clubs.
All right, well, I'll have Ryan canvass the area
around her apartment and the motel.
We'll see if any of the businesses have lockers
that use this kind of key.
Yo, Beckett.
I got something.
Uh, yeah, detective Esposito,
this is Detective Inspector Colin Hunt.
He's from Scotland Yard.
He's gonna be consulting on this case.
He knows our victim. - Hey. How's it going?
Pleasure, mate. - So what do you got?
Well, Naomi did make it to that album release party last night
at a club in midtown,
but she was kicked out by security around 10:00.
Why?
She had an altercation with the host, female rapper
and ex-felon Nicky Jay.
And she wasn't afraid to take a swing in front of paparazzi.
Wow. What was the fight about?
Unclear, but uniforms are bringing her up to interrogation now.
Do you usually question them solo?
No, Castle and I usually go in together.
Actually, you know what? Why don't you guys take this one?
Are you sure?
Yeah, absolutely.
Besides, Colin's got a personal interest.
And I really don't now, do I? - Ah. All right.
It's settled then. - Yeah, I guess it is.
Yeah, besides, my lunch date is here.
I'll be back in a few hours.
You guys call me if you find anything interesting.
Hell, yeah, I clocked her.
She was trying to make a move on my man.
Your man Biggie Slim? - That's right.
She had the nerve to say that he told her to put her digits in his phone.
Did he?
That ain't the point!
That skinny bitch wasn't even supposed to be there.
When I got up in her face,
she said Biggie Slim's cousin Drew told her about the party.
But I knew that was B.S. because Drew wasn't even invited.
It must make you so bloody mad
to know your man has a wandering eye.
I had a girlfriend like that.
Traveled for business.
She'd ring from the airport to say her flight was canceled.
I come to find out, she was seeing some other bloke.
She sound like a ho.
All I'm saying is, I understand your instinct
to lash out at the person you believe is responsible.
I protect what's mine. You should do the same.
Is that why you followed Naomi to the motel
and strangled her with your bare hands?
You must be high.
That skank wasn't worth another second of my time.
I told security to give her the boot,
and that was that.
Really? Can you prove it?
My driver brought us home.
And I was with Biggie Slim the rest of the night.
Yeah, I went home with Nicky Jay.
After the tussle, she was all worked up.
But I like it when she gets worked up, when she got something to prove.
She said that the fight started because you were
spending time with this girl.
Oh, yeah, that girl.
Hey, what can I say?
Women are powerless against my good looks and charms.
Yes, it's a real curse.
You and Naomi... What did you talk about?
Ah, a little bit of this, a little bit of that.
She was a bad chick, you know?
But a little off. You know what I'm talking about?
No, what are you talkin' about?
I mean, she was acting paranoid, man,
said somebody had followed her to the party.
I figured she was just blowing smoke.
Why is that?
Look, I don't just produce Nicky Jay, all right?
I'm building my brand.
I got Biggie Slim records, Biggie Slim clothing.
Hell, I even got a Biggie Slim energy drink.
So some filly comes up trying to make her time,
it's just a everyday thing in my life.
Did she tell you who she thought was following her?
Sure didn't.
I guess she wasn't lying, though, huh?
Naomi left that party
and then three hours later, she was dead.
Based on what she told Biggie Slim,
Naomi knew somebody was after her.
All right, let's canvass the area around the party venue,
see if she was being followed.
And let's track down Nicky Jay and Biggie Slim's driver.
I want to see if they went straight home.
On it.
So... that story
that you told Nicky Jay about your girlfriend...
Total pants.
I just wanted her to think I sympathized.
And honestly, after meeting Biggie Slim,
I do.
Well, maybe she's hanging on,
hoping that he'll change.
Guys like him never do.
Our M.E.'s finished the autopsy.
Her larynx is crushed.
Whoever did it was strong.
Large hands, probably a male.
That's like half the city.
We may be able to narrow it down a little further than that.
The pressure from the killer's grip
left a print on her neck.
Were you able to pull a print?
We recovered a partial
thanks to the body lotion she was wearing.
Is it in the system?
Not enough to run it, but you bring me a print
off a suspect, I can tell you if it's a match.
Excuse me. I have to make a call.
Easy on the eyes.
Cute accent, too. - Mm.
- I just got one question.
- Mm.
Where's Castle?
He took off...
for a lunch date.
In a Ferrari full of flight attendant?
Yeah, he's probably trying to rack up
his frequent flyer miles.
I'm sorry.
But you know she's just a passing thing.
Do I? I mean, the guy has been divorced twice,
and he's still chasing bimbos.
Maybe that's just who he is.
Look, maybe it's the wrong time
or maybe he's even the wrong guy,
but if he is, how long are you gonna wait to find out?
Ten years, I've been keeping them company
while they spend a night or two here
on their way to where we're all going.
They all had plans, Kate,
things they were gonna do when they got around to it...
Go on a cruise, lose 10 pounds, fall in love.
They thought they had all the time in the world.
But nobody does.
The personal ones are tough.
No call.
What's my tell?
The brooding lean.
Ah, yes.
Rookie move.
You know, even with a mouth full of braces,
she was the prettiest girl in her class.
Although having a cop for a dad didn't do much for her social life.
Terry used to interrogate her dates
when they'd drop her off.
I could see how that would weed out the lightweights.
And then when she was 22,
she fell in love with a young doctor, good guy.
He died last year in Africa doing God's work.
I don't think she ever really got over it, because hearing what she was up to,
it's like she was a different person.
People change when you're not looking.
Excuse me.
Hey, Ryan. What's up?
Are you sure?
Where?
Okay, great. Call in a warrant.
They found a gym near the motel.
Naomi bought a day pass there the night that she was killed,
and the clerk said she was in and out in three minutes.
Just enough time to run in and hide something
in one of the lockers.
She bought the day pass at 10:24 P.M.
That's 20 minutes after she called me
to say she was in trouble.
She was leaving me a message.
She did better than leave a message about the killer.
She left us a picture of him as well.
Anything on the number sequence?
We're running it through every database,
but nothing so far. - Naomi wrote it on there for a reason.
What about the photo?
Well, based on the light and background architecture,
this photo was taken in midtown New York.
Hey. What did I miss?
Not much.
Oh, we did manage to find that mystery locker.
And that guy in the photo,
he's probably our killer.
So, how was your lunch?
Oh, I loved the special.
I'll bet. Wait a minute.
Can you blow up this one section?
Yeah, sure.
Rounded and gold? It's a plaque.
It's the British seal.
This picture was taken right outside the British consulate.
Pull up a list of the consulate employees.
Here you go.
Well, he's not on this page.
There he is.
Nigel Wyndham.
Deputy general of the British consulate.
Which means he's just under the consulate general in rank,
so he's responsible for the daily operations
in financial and logistical matters.
What the hell was Naomi doing mixed up with this guy?
That was my mate at Scotland Yard.
He found out some intriguing details on Nigel Wyndham,
like the fact that a girlfriend in college died rather mysteriously
while they were on holiday in Rome.
Well, was he ever charged?
No, and after that, he had a string of bad investments
until he married Cynthia wadlow.
It was her prominent family
who pulled strings that got him a position,
first at the ministry of culture,
and then here at the consulate. - Yo.
So we've been reconstructing Naomi's movements
since she landed in New York a couple of weeks ago.
Her financials indicate
that she booked a car service last week
that dropped her at nobu...
Now we showed the host Nigel's picture,
and he confirmed that they met for dinner.
Did the host notice anything?
Yeah, he noticed the C-Note that Nigel dropped
to secure the romantic table in the back.
I just called the consulate.
The day after the romantic nobu dinner,
security removed Naomi from Nigel's office.
Well, it sounds like a fight.
Uh, security heard Naomi yell something about Cynthia
as they escorted her out.
Well, it makes perfect sense.
Stuck in a marriage of convenience,
Nigel meets the young and beautiful Naomi,
finds her irresistible.
A chance meeting turns to dinner, dinner to a tryst,
but then Naomi wants more.
Nigel realizes that his affair has become a threat
to his position, his reputation, to the life he built
on the backs of his wife and her family.
Sir, if Nigel's wife found out about an affair,
it would kill his marriage and his career.
Detective Inspector Hunt,
I take your silence to mean that you don't agree?
Well, the Naomi I knew
would never fall for someone like Wyndham,
but she wouldn't have left his picture in that locker
if he weren't connected to her death somehow.
Nigel Wyndham's position at the consulate includes diplomatic immunity.
Which would be waived if he was a suspect in a murder case.
If I pick up the phone to make that request,
I'm gonna need something more concrete than just a theory.
Sir, Lanie pulled our killer's prints
off of our victim's neck.
And given everything that we know right now,
I am willing to bet that they're a match to Nigel's.
A bet's not enough.
But if you can get those prints,
then this is a whole different conversation.
Here's the problem, bro...
foreign dignitaries don't register their fingerprints
with local law enforcement.
And if we put in a request to the consulate, they'll box us out
and alert Nigel that he's a suspect.
Yeah, I thought Scotland Yard would be able to get them.
Even with his connections across the pond, we struck out.
Okay, boys. Here it is.
Here's what?
My foolproof plan for getting Nigel's fingerprint.
Nigel lives in a high-rise apartment
here on Park avenue.
Yeah. High security.
Exactly. Ryan, you'll be here...
Front door... dressed as a flower delivery boy.
Esposito, you'll be here dressed as a hobo.
Question.
Why's the brown man gotta be a hobo?
You want the flowers?
Hobo it is.
You boys will cause a distraction here
whilst I rappel down the side of the building
with Nicolai. - Who's Nicolai?
He's a Romanian gymnast I found on Youtube.
He's extremely flexible and fits in the duffel bag.
Using a glass cutter...
Excuse me, gents. - I can...
Has anyone seen detective Beckett?
Uh, you guys going out?
I pulled some strings and got us into a party
at the British consulate tonight.
Nigel will be there.
We'll get his prints, and he won't even know it.
Cheers, lads.
Cheers.
Or they could do that.
Yeah, sure,
if you want to do it the easy way.
Thank you.
So who is sir Alfred Heath?
Tonight, I am.
The lads back home said the real sir Alfred
is down as a no-show.
Gout or some damn thing.
Yeah, but what if Nigel Wyndham doesn't show either?
He'll be here.
And I expect he'll skip the champagne
and drink something posh and pretentious,
leaving his print on the glass.
Well, what if he doesn't drink?
He's British.
Trust me, he drinks.
May I?
I didn't realize that dancing was a part of the plan.
Oh, well...
It offers a perfect vantage point.
Do you come to a lot of these events?
No, thank God. Why?
You just seem very confident.
Well, that's because my companion
is the most beautiful woman in this room.
That's clearly the champagne talking.
I'm sure you're just comfortable here because you're amongst your own people.
These aren't my people.
My people are the ones carrying the trays.
Yeah.
I grew up on the East End.
My mom cleaned flats. Dad worked in a factory.
They wanted something better, they just...
They couldn't quite get it.
And then?
I was admitted to Eton on a scholarship
where I minored in blending in.
Oh. - What about you?
I grew up in the city
and, uh, went to college in California.
Well, you could obviously do anything
you put your mind to.
Why be a cop?
I guess it was just my calling.
Ah, a crusader.
I know the type.
Doesn't leave a lot of time for personal life, though, does it?
What about you? Are you the crusader type as well?
Married to the bit, I'm afraid.
The job comes first.
Though sometimes, I wish it didn't.
Yeah. I know the feeling.
Wait a minute. Look over there by the bar.
My 1:00.
Let the games begin.
All right. Take care.
Good evening.
Nigel Wyndham. Deputy general.
Jean Harrington.
Bored.
Well, we'll have to remedy that, Ms. Harrington.
Uh, one for the lady, please.
Oh, a ring. That's discouraging.
Oh, well, it needn't be.
To new friendships.
Now tell me, Ms. Harrington, are you here alone?
If so, it would be a grave injustice.
My date's more interested in networking than he is in me.
In that case, he won't object
if I ask you for a dance.
You know what?
I wouldn't care even if he did.
Shall we?
Mm-hmm.
So... tell me, Ms. Harrington,
what should I know about you?
Well, there's more to me than meets the eye.
Well, what meets the eye
is irresistible.
You know, actions speak louder than words.
Meaning?
Meaning, if I'm so irresistible,
then why aren't you using both your hands?
Excuse me, your excellency.
Oh, excuse me. Pardon me.
Coming through. Oh.
Sorry, sir. As you were. - Very rude!
Excuse me. Oh. - Oh!
Excuse me.
Sir Alfred Heath?
Yes.
Might I have a word, sir?
There seems to be two of you here this evening.
Sorry.
All right. Let's try this way.
I- I have to ask,
are you as aggressive in your other activities
as you are on the dance floor?
Ah, you know, what can I say?
I like to lead... all the time.
Well, there's obviously been a serious mistake.
I am the real sir Alfred,
so if there's somebody else, uh, here as sir Alfred,
then they're obviously, uh, an imposter.
Uh, you have any I.D.?
Uh, I-I actually don't have any. - Are you...
no, no, I've left my, um... - Is... is everything all right?
Um, yeah. You know, I'm suddenly...
I feel very hungry. Excuse me.
Would you like one of these? I hear they're great.
I'm not a caviar man myself.
Yeah, but I hear they're an aphrodisiac.
Mm. Not for me, I'm afraid.
I'm sorry to intrude, Mr. Wyndham, sir.
Yes, what is it, Bryson?
Uh, the young lady, I need her to come with me.
Well, for what purpose?
Don't worry, darling.
I know that we'll see each other again very soon.
I had the waiter, then I lost him.
I've bollixed up the whole plan,
and now we've got nothing.
Oh, I wouldn't say nothing.
I swiped Wyndham's card case.
It's got his prints all over it.
You sneaky little thief.
That's bloody brilliant.
Thank you. Now let's go get this son of a bitch.
The print's not a match.
What?
C.S.U. ran the fingerprints off the card case,
compared 'em to the one that Lanie found on Naomi's body.
It wasn't Nigel Wyndham's.
No, that's not possible. Run it again.
Ryan already did that three times.
Wyndham's not our killer.
He's behind this. I know it.
It's why Naomi left us his photograph.
Well, maybe he hired someone to do his dirty work for him.
Like one of his security men.
Can you get Scotland Yard to run background checks
on the security staff?
Or a better path might be to look into this mysterious number
that Naomi wrote on the back of that photo, which is a mystery no longer.
Is this lobster, bro?
Lucky for you, Jacinda's a light eater.
You heat that up, little bit of melted butter...
Are you telling us you know what that number means? How?
Well, as Jacinda and I were enjoying
our succulent lobsters from Maine,
paired with an earthy
yet elegant Pinot Noir from sonoma valley...
Castle, numbers.
Right. Well, we were going over the file.
Turns out Jacinda's quite a little crime solver.
You showed the stewardess the evidence file?
No.
I took a picture of it with my phone.
And the preferred nomenclature is "flight attendant. "
The point is, this code refers to
a diplomatic pouch.
How do you know that?
Jacinda recognized the format.
Furthermore, she told me these last three digits
are a reference code for royal eastern airlines.
Which means the pouch was delivered on that airline.
Exactly. The "W4" refers to the size of the pouch,
the "1949" indicates exactly which pouch it is
in the consulate sequence.
As the deputy general, Nigel signs for all the pouches.
So then maybe this wasn't about an affair gone wrong
between Nigel and Naomi.
It's about smuggling. - Well, that makes a lot of sense.
Diplomatic pouches are sealed and their contents
bypass T.S.A. and customs inspections.
Naomi must have got on to what Wyndham was doing somehow.
We need to know what was in that pouch.
The consulate's never gonna release that information.
Oh, we don't have to worry about the consulate.
The airline keeps a copy of the waybill.
Get ahold of the airline. Let's get that waybill down here.
Ryan, grab a pen.
What?
Castle, you can't just share
confidential police information with an outsider.
Even if it solves the case?
I mean, she gave us a lead.
That's more than you got at the consulate.
And that's supposed to make this all okay?
Jacinda just wanted to help. What's the big deal?
You don't get it, do you?
No, I guess I don't.
No, I gu... I guess you don't.
We found something you're gonna want to see.
The airline e-mailed over the waybill.
The pouch that matches our number
was shipped from the British consulate about a year ago.
It flew from J.F.K.
To Kampala, Uganda.
Uganda? That can't be a coincidence.
What do you mean?
Naomi's boyfriend, the one who died, he was killed in Uganda.
Any idea of what was being shipped?
Uh, just that it weighed 200 pounds.
Well, that's awfully heavy for a pouch.
Well, a diplomatic pouch can be as small as an envelope
or as big as a cargo container.
Whatever's being shipped, it's being sent out
about once a month.
I just combed through airline waybills from the past year.
Ten other pouches, all the same weight,
were flown from here to Uganda.
In fact, one of them is listed as being in J.F.K.'s secure baggage area.
You mean to say, one of those pouches
is at the airport right now?
Finding out what's in that pouch could tell us who killed Naomi.
Yeah, but we don't have any jurisdiction here, Castle.
If the NYPD tries to open up a British diplomatic pouch,
we could risk an international incident.
Then it's a good thing I'm not NYPD.
Good evening, sir.
I'm agent Bauer with Homeland Security.
I'm here for the inspection.
Nobody radioed me about any inspection.
Well, of course they didn't.
We conduct random checks to assess security.
Telling you we were coming kind of defeats the purpose.
Am I right? We'd be tipping our hand,
showing our play book, so to speak.
Two years, I've worked this shift,
and I've never heard of anything...
Look, Morgan, is it? I'm sure you run a tight ship here.
So if things inside are secure,
I'll make damn sure your bosses know about it,
which will reflect well on you.
We're all on the same team here, pal.
I gotta verify this with my supervisor.
Yeah, you do that.
I'm getting more adept
at faking my way past people.
Must be all the practice.
You're in the baggage area?
Yeah, but I don't have much time.
Maybe a minute before the guy calls his supervisor
- to check my story.
- All right, so based on the shipping code, the pouch that you're looking for
is about 5 feet long.
Does the waybill say
if it's a crate, a footlocker, cardboard box, what?
No, sorry, bro.
But it's 200 pounds, so it's gotta be something sturdy.
Something sturdy. Right.
Oh, come on.
Here we go. I found it. It's a crate.
Agent Bauer!
I need you to step outta there, please.
Okay, that didn't sound good.
Agent Bauer... What did he expect?
I heard that.
Uh, I've just about wrapped up here.
Sir, my supervisor will be here...
And he will be mighty pleased with your work, Morgan,
mighty pleased.
It's clear to me that you've been working harder than a...
One-legged man in an ass-kicking contest.
Step outta there now, sir. I will not tell you again.
Hello!
You there? Hello!
Bloody hell.
What's in the crate?
Missiles.
Stinger Missile
Customs and Homeland Security have impounded the crate,
and Interpol is on their way to J.F.K.
How did you explain opening the diplomatic pouch?
Well, everyone's more interested in the missiles at the moment,
but I expect I'll be in hot water at some point.
And where does this leave Wyndham?
Untouched.
What do you mean untouched? He was smuggling weapons.
Well, they'll have an inquiry, of course,
but they can't prove he knew what was in the crate.
And since we opened the crate illegally,
we won't be able to use it as evidence.
At least it all starts to make sense now.
Naomi was trying to solve Aiden's murder.
That would be Naomi's boyfriend... Aiden Miller.
He worked for doctors without borders in Uganda
until his helicopter was shot down
by guerilla forces a year ago.
The British government launched an investigation,
but was never able to determine how the rebels acquired
a stinger missile.
Which we now know came to them
courtesy of Nigel Wyndham.
Yeah, except Nigel's not the type
to get his hands dirty when it comes to missiles or murder.
He must have had a partner
who had a line on those stingers.
And if Naomi started looking into the smuggling operation...
Then perhaps it was the partner who got rid of her.
So then the question is, who is this partner?
Everything Naomi did was about finding out
who supplied the weapon that killed her boyfriend.
That's why she stopped taking modeling gigs.
That's why she came to New York. It's...
Maybe there's someone on that list of attendees
for that, uh, foreign dignitary party.
I mean, it all started when she booked that out of London
a few months ago.
Paulo Makuzi.
And who is he?
A leader of the rebel army in Uganda.
Naomi must have heard something at the party.
That's what led her to the consulate.
And that romantic dinner with Nigel was just part of her agenda
to get the pouch number from his office.
So then there's just one piece
that doesn't fit in her investigation.
What was she doing with Biggie Slim?
I want you to take a close look at this photo.
Yeah, I seen this one.
Paparazzi caught me and Nicky Jay
coming out of the studio a couple weeks ago.
In fact, that is Nicky Jay's black S.U.V., isn't it?
Bought by Biggie Slim himself. - Mm.
Supply and demand. She demands, I gotta supply.
You know, the thing that I find intriguing
is that before you became Biggie Slim,
you're name was Darius Young,
best known for launching several failed Internet start-ups.
Just a man ahead of my time.
Well, the S.E.C. thought you were a man trying to fleece investors.
See, I was never charged for that.
One of your ventures,
a music sharing web site based in the U.K.,
caught the attention of British authorities.
And when they tried to shut it down,
an aide to the minister of culture
lobbied on your behalf.
And do you know who that aide was?
Nigel Wyndham.
In fact, this is Nigel
stepping out of the very same black S.U.V.
No, I don't think so.
Why don't you take a closer look?
It's got the same custom pinstripes on the door.
It's just somebody else's truck with those stripes on there.
Your driver already admitted that he drove you to this meeting outside the consulate.
We also know that your cousin is in the service... Drew Harris.
A staff sergeant. He works at an armory.
He supplied the missiles.
You knew that Wyndham had access
to the diplomatic pouch, and you saw an opportunity.
Supply and demand.
That's a whole lot of speculation there, mate.
Well, we weren't the only ones to put together the pieces.
Naomi wasn't giving you her phone number.
She was looking for evidence.
Once you realized that she was the same girl
that Wyndham caught snooping,
you followed her to the motel and you killed her.
Well, how y'all gon' prove that?
A partial fingerprint on Naomi's body...
And it's a match to you.
You know, the thing
that I still can't figure out is, why Uganda?
Why would you care?
Man, it wasn't about Uganda.
It was just about the money.
I didn't even know where Wyndham was shipping the stuff to.
Good. Uh, call my assistant.
I am, uh, wide open all week.
Actually, you're not.
Or the following week, for that matter.
Told you I'd see you soon.
What is this?
Getting thrown out of here once already wasn't enough for you people?
Security.
They can't help you, mate. Nobody can.
Not even your well-funded ugandan friends.
Nigel Wyndham...
You're under arrest for international arms trafficking
and for abetting in the murder of a British citizen.
Her dad would've been proud...
How brave she was, taking on these men.
But I so wish she hadn't done it.
So what happens now? Do you go back to D.C.?
London, I'm afraid.
Face the music.
You know, they should give you a commendation.
Well, that is wildly improbable.
Well, detective Beckett,
it's been a true pleasure.
The pleasure was all mine, Detective Inspector Hunt.
Please. Colin.
Kate.
You know, I have a few hours before my flight, Kate.
Could I persuade you to let me buy you a drink?
I'm sorry. I have a bit of paperwork to do.
Another time.
Where's Scotland Yard off to?
Oh, he's going back to London.
Um... Castle, do you have a second?
Can we talk...
Actually, I don't. Jacinda has the Ferrari double parked in a loading zone.
Four dates in three days. You like her.
Yeah. Why?
Uh, she just... she doesn't seem like your type.
Well, she's fun and uncomplicated.
I think that's what my life needs right now.
Hi. It's, uh, it's Kate.
Do you still want to buy me that drink?
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入