lt's just senseless.
A man so young as Ray.
lt's God's cruel trick, Nora.
Don't go blaming God, Curt.
You and l know what killed Ray.
Well, we don't know anything for sure.
How does a 41-year-old man
just wither away and die?
lf any of us knew that,
we'd have done somethin' about it.
Maybe it was just his time.
He was a young man
when he went over, Curt.
- Ray got sick because he fought in the Gulf.
- Now, don't go there, Nora.
You just make it worse.
The doctors never said...
They never said. That's right.
My husband's dead, and no one knows why.
Maybe l have to find out myself.
They're gonna pay for Ray's death,
whoever's to blame.
No one's to blame. You're just upset.
- You need a good night's sleep.
- l don't wanna sleep, l just...
You just want Ray back.
We all do.
Get some rest. l'll see you tomorrow, OK?
Ray?
The car's registered
to a Curtis Delario, local address.
So far he's been unreachable.
lt's highly unlikely that wherever he is,
he feels like picking up the phone.
Muncie PD ran some calculations. Based on
distance traveled and length of skid marks,
the car was going at least 40 when it impacted
the object, which, according to their math,
would require something 4300 times
the density of steel to cause this damage.
Hm.
lt's interesting, isn't it?
l mean, in light of the evidence.
From their size and shape,
these look like men's shoes.
l hope you're not suggesting that what this
car hit was a man, because there's no way.
Well, these impressions in the asphalt
look pretty fresh to me.
l admit to the coincidence, but you know
as well as l that if a man were here,
he'd be splattered,
and there's just no evidence of that.
You're right.
Which is suspicious in and of itself.
This car definitely hit something, and the only
evidence that we have are these two prints.
l hate to ruin your beautiful theory with
ugly facts, but stop to examine the incident.
lf a man were standing here,
the driver would have stopped.
lt looks like he tried to.
lf a man were in the middle of the road
with a car coming, wouldn't he try to move?
Unless he wanted to stop the car.
Yes, but if nothing less than
a block of steel could stop this car,
then, ipso facto, it could not have been
a man standing in the street last night.
Or certainly no ordinary man.
Just tell me what happened.
Where is he? Where...?
Excuse me, ma'am.
John Doggett with the FBl.
- You know about this?
- What happened? Where is he?
- Curtis Delario, you know him?
- He was a friend of my husband's.
- They worked at the salvage yard.
- l want you to calm down, Mrs...?
Pearce. How am l supposed to calm down?
Finding this now, it...
- We're not even sure he was driving the car.
- He was.
He came over after my husband's funeral,
then he left...
Agent Doggett.
Meet Curtis Delario.
l guess he won't be much help
clearing any of this up.
l think l got some answers.
So do l. lt wasn't the crash
that killed Curtis Delario.
He was badly injured,
but he was clearly still alive
when his body was pulled
through the car's windshield.
Pulled?
Yeah. These five deep puncture marks
match five fingers of one hand.
- You mean someone reached right in and...?
- Like a bowling ball.
- That seems humanly impossible.
- Certainly for any ordinary man.
From the evidence l've gathered, the man
that did this is actually less than ordinary.
l was able to reconstruct a section of the
windshield and lift a print from the glass.
- Whose?
- Raymond Aloysius Pearce.
Husband of Nora Pearce,
woman l spoke with at the accident site.
Her recently deceased husband.
Well, if he was recently deceased,
then it must have been an old print.
Well, what you would think, except along with
the print, there was evidence of fresh blood.
And it belongs to Ray Pearce too.
Mrs Pearce.
Agent Doggett again. Sorry to bother you,
but there are some things l need to go over.
- Everything all right, Nora?
- He's with the FBl.
This is Harry Odell. He runs
the salvage yard where Ray and Curt worked.
May l come in?
Agent Doggett, l don't understand.
Before, you were talking about Curt.
Now you wanna talk about Ray?
What was their relationship, Mrs Pearce,
your husband and Curtis Delario -
outside of work?
l know what their relationship is now.
They're both dead.
Your husband's medical record says that
he died after a long, debilitating illness?
Gulf War syndrome.
No one will cop to that, but l aim to
prove it. Put the blame where it belongs.
l'm having trouble proving
something myself, Mrs Pearce.
You signed a form to have your husband
cremated, but it appears it never happened.
What do you mean?
They gave me the ashes.
They were at the funeral.
l can't find a record of Ray's body
ever even being at the crematorium.
Oh, for cryin' out loud.
Hasn't this woman grieved enough?
Let me get to the point, Mrs Pearce.
ls it possible your husband is still alive?
Still alive?
- ls this ajoke?
- Because we have evidence to suggest
that maybe your husband was involved
in the death of Curtis Delario.
Are you saying Ray faked his death?
We found Ray's blood
and fingerprints on Curt's car.
l watched him die.
l nursed him when he was sick,
when he couldn't eat.
What you're saying is impossible. He couldn't
even walk or lift his head at the end.
Ray Pearce worked for me nine years.
He was a good man.
He never raised a hand to anyone.
Hey. How you doin'?
Ray, right? They said you're new.
Rough night?
You're eating the tinfoil on the...
My name's Larina. l help out around here.
You might have some questions
about how it all works.
l don't know. lt's pretty basic.
Look.
l've been down the road and back a few times
and l just wanna say you're not alone, Ray.
l mean, l've been where you've been
and sometimes it can help.
You know?
Sometimes it's good to just talk.
Make a connection.
You know what l'm sayin', Ray?
So if there's anything
l can do for you, you know...
You can leave me alone.
OK.
God Almighty.
Ray.
lt's true.
Oh, you got everybody wonderin', man.
And they're lookin' for you.
They blame you for killing Curt.
Now, me and Curt, we're your friends.
You can't blame this on us.
You gotta believe me, it wasn't us.
Well, l can show you.
lt's right here, Ray. lt wasn't me.
This time you stay dead.
Scully.
Did you find anything to go along
with those holes in Curt Delario's head?
Paint on his hands and nails?
- Paint?
- Blue paint, specifically.
Hang on.
No. ls it significant?
l don't know.
But Harry was a busy boy last night.
He must've left Nora Pearce's
right after l saw him,
right after he'd learned
that Ray Pearce might still be alive.
To do what?
lt's pretty clear he was in his office shredding
papers when he was surprised by someone.
- And you think it was Ray?
- Well, somebody took a blast.
There's blood all over the doors,
trailing down the stairs.
- Massive blood loss.
- But the man with the gun is dead.
l saw guys take hits in the war
that kept right on fighting,
holding their insides in their hands.
lt's not impossible.
But to do this to a man's head
after taking two barrels of buckshot...
Or being hit by a car.
l don't see how a man could possibly do this.
Well, maybe the question's not how, but why.
l mean, if Ray Pearce did indeed kill
this man, what would be his reason?
l'm not sure.
but l know where to start lookin'.
Hello?
Ray?
Ray. You OK?
Somebody saw you come in
with blood on you.
l can see it on your clothes.
Look, Ray.
l know it never does anybody any good
getting the cops involved, OK?
Look, l've been there, man.
l know what it's like to feel dark and alone.
l can get a doctor for you.
Get out.
OK.
They're called ''smart metals''. The idea is to
one day build things that are indestructible.
Cars, equipment, built of alloys
with molecular memory.
lf damaged, they'd rebuild
into their original forms.
All by themselves?
- That's amazing.
- And right now, a metallurgist's pipe dream.
But beside the point of your visit,
l would imagine.
Well, you tell me. l found a document at
a crime scene listing Chamber Technologies.
An employee number on the document
was assigned to a Dr David Clifton.
Dr Clifton's no longer here.
- What happened to him?
- He left the company.
l'm actually his successor in this department.
Do you deal with a man named Harry Odell
or a business called Southside Salvage?
No, l don't deal with materials.
Nor did Dr Clifton.
Our work here is all theoretical.
We have an environmental manager
in charge of waste management,
but disposal is done at TSD facilities,
definitely not city salvage yards.
- Thanks for your time, Doctor...
- Puvogel. German, no h.
- You need me to spell it for you?
- No, no. That's quite all right.
Thanks.
- Scully.
- Hey. lt's Agent Doggett.
- l'm at Chamber Technologies.
- Did you find Dr Clifton?
He's left the company, but his successor
says his work was entirely conceptual.
- Everything's done on computers.
- What kind of conceptual work?
Thing called smart metals.
lt's pretty incredible.
Metal alloys designed to rebuild themselves.
l wonder.
As it happens, Ray Pearce's illness
is pretty incredible, too.
l've reviewed Ray's medical records
from the VA.
What his wife was calling Gulf War syndrome
is nothing of the kind.
His entire cellular makeup was affected by
exposure to a non-identifiable contaminant.
A metal.
What are you sayin'? Ray Pearce
has become some kind of metal man?
That only happens in the movies,
Agent Scully.
Does it, Agent Doggett?
Tell you what. l'll press this guy here
a little more on the issue.
Maybe there's a reason why he's
not being perfectly forthcoming.
Police are seeking clues in
last night's bloody robbery and murder
at Muncie's Southside Salvage.
Workmen found the body of 53-year-old
Harry Odell outside his office
at approximately 7:30 this morning.
Detectives have refused to comment on
the cause of death pending an autopsy,
but sources close to the case describe this
as a vicious and grisly attack.
Robbery appears to be
the motive behind this...
- Operator 525. What city, please?
- Muncie.
Number for a Raymond Pearce.
- Sorry l'm late.
- lt's all right.
l just got the blood test back on Ray Pearce,
and it was indeed the same Ray Pearce
pronounced dead three days ago.
But that's not all. By all medical standards,
he should still be dead.
His blood has enough metal alloy in it
to poison an elephant.
Except that he's still a man,
and he'll act and think like one
even if he is more powerful
than a locomotive.
But then the question is, why kill his friends?
l mean, if he was wronged somehow,
wouldn't he go to them for solace?
- l mean, to his wife, at least?
- That's why l was late.
l asked myself that same question.
Ray was an outpatient at the VA.
He had a history of substance abuse.
Did some time for a couple of DUls.
- This was ten years ago.
- Cleaned up his act.
He met Nora and married her in '91,
checked into a rehab and got straight.
This was a guy to root for, that overcame
adversity and made a life for himself.
- Until three days ago.
- l've busted a lot of killers, Agent Scully,
and dollars for doughnuts, they fit a profile.
But the Ray Pearce in this file is no murderer,
let alone a guy that would hunt down
his friends and crush their skulls.
The man that we're speaking about
withstood impact from a speeding car,
and two shotgun blasts at short range.
Even if we can find him,
who's to say we can stop him?
- Make sure that door is secure.
- Dr Puvogel,
are you sure he can't
open that door from the inside?
l've got a manual override on the door.
What the hell was that?
Ray Pearce.
The door is four inches thick.
- l don't think it's gonna hold.
- You'd better hope it does,
cos if it doesn't, he's coming after you,
and l don't know if we can stop him.
Open it up.
Get it open.
There's a rupture in the chamber.
l don't believe this.
Agent Doggett.
Look at this. You see this?
What is that? ls that blood?
Turning itself into metal.
Get him out of the building.
- l didn't do anything to the man.
- You wanna argue, or go someplace safe?
- Where's that? Where's safe?
- lt's not in here.
My God.
- lt's true.
- You shouldn't have come, Nora.
l shouldn't have come?
That's what you say to me?
l'm your wife.
l came here because you didn't come to me.
l had to have some stranger tell me.
Why didn't you come, Ray?
Because l'm not me.
l don't care what's happened.
Whatever it is, it's a miracle.
Don't go.
- There's your miracle.
- Ray, let me help you.
Please, let me help.
They've got to pay for this.
They've all got to pay.
Oh my God.
What's going on?
lt's not enough that my life's been threatened.
- l'm being treated like a criminal.
- And not without cause.
- Oh my God.
- Do you recognize this man?
We're assuming you don't know
too many guys in this particular condition.
- lt's not what it looks like.
- ls this Dr David Clifton, your predecessor?
- Yes.
- You care to explain how he ended up
in a Chamber Technology
hazardous waste barrel?
lt was his idea. l was against it.
lf you knew, you might've told me
about this when l first came to see you.
He was dying, and he was afraid.
- Of what?
- That it would hinder progress, or halt it.
- That it would finish us.
- Oh, you're finished.
- One way or another, your work here is done.
- We didn't know this was gonna happen.
We were just trying to push the envelope,
do the right thing for the company.
Then he got sick.
He was working with an alloy
with a genetic algorithm built into it.
lt converted electrical energy
into mechanical. Gave it memory.
And it poisoned him.
We immediately shut down the project.
But it was too late.
He didn't have any family.
His work was his life. He wanted to leave us
to continue working on the science.
And to ship this barrel and body to Southside
Salvage, where it infected somebody else.
l don't know how that happened,
l swear to God.
That barrel was supposed to go
to a designated site.
Let me talk to you for a second.
l think he's telling the truth.
What the hell is she doing here?
- Who is it?
- Nora Pearce, Ray's wife.
Mrs Pearce?
What are you doin' here?
How do you know about this place?
She was looking for something.
Who'd you call, Mrs Pearce?
Let's check in here.
Police.
- You want us to take her in?
- l want to talk to her.
Your husband just
broke through a second-storey wall
and eluded a dozen cops at St Clare House.
That please you, Mrs Pearce?
Does it please you to know that he killed
a woman volunteer named Larina Jackson?
That makes three people. Three people
that he's killed, and for what?
Because they made him what he is.
They say this young woman he killed tonight
had been concerned for him,
concerned for Ray's welfare.
Whatever Ray is, whatever he's become,
it was an accident.
- lt was not those people's fault, Mrs Pearce.
- Harry and Curt knew about it.
No, they were innocent, just like Ray was.
They didn't know this was gonna happen.
These people here knew.
They got documents on it.
Oh, so that's what this is about?
This is about
looking for somebody to blame?
Ray sent you here, didn't he,
to find that person, to get a name?
The Ray l know died.
- The man responsible should pay for that.
- So who is it?
lt's the CEO here? The owner?
Give us a name, Mrs Pearce,
before someone else has to die.
l never gave him a name.
Get her outta here. Put her on 24-hour watch.
We'll be right outside, ma'am.
Nora?
- They're right outside, Ray.
- Did you get me the name?
You killed her.
The woman who called me.
For God's sake, Ray, why?
Why her? She cared about you.
l need the name.
No one else needs to die, Ray.
You won't do it, not to me.
l need the man's name.
- He's in the house.
- Go. Go.
Tell the FBl agents it's Harris.
Ray made me give him the name.
Owen Harris. Ray's gonna kill him.
No. Owen.
No. No.
- Daddy.
- No.
Owen Harris, don't look away.
- Look at me.
- Why are you doing this?
Because you made me.
- l don't know what you're talking about.
- Southside Salvage.
- l'm just an accountant.
- Daddy.
Daddy.
Ray Pearce.
He came here to kill this man,
but something stopped him, didn't it?
This man, Owen Harris.
He begged for his life.
lt mightjust have saved him.
His attacker got up and ran away.
Makes no sense. Pearce was a determined
killer, lookin' for someone to blame.
Why stop here?
Wherever Ray Pearce went,
the answer to that question went with him,
but l can tell you
why he came after Owen Harris.
lt was his name Nora found in the file.
He authorized the shipment of
hazardous materials to Southside Salvage.
But if Harris is the guy Ray
holds responsible, why'd Ray let him live?
Well, l think that
Nora Pearce may have been right.
Her husband died, or at least his body did.
Whatever killed those people
was an abomination of a man.
- lt was a machine.
- A machine?
Come on. A machine
doesn't know blame, Agent Scully.
Nor mercy.
Unless what drove Ray to kill
is also what saved those people.
Some flicker of humanity.
Visiontext Subtitles: Paul Murray
US ENGLlSH