Casey,be honest with me.
Are my pregnancy hormones
making me seem bitchy?
What?!they're definitely
making you glow,that's for sure.
Lies: 0
Lies: 1
- Wait. Are you being evasive?
- Am i?
- Casey,am I acting bitchy or not?
- no.
What did you do?
It's a new recipe.I remember how excited
you were last time I cooked something fancy.
Lies: 0
Lies: 1
Lies: 2
Lies: 3
I was so excited.
So I made pork a l'orange.
It's supposed to be with duck,but
that sounded wrong to me.Taste it.
The flavors really just work.
- It's different,right?
- Yes!
This is the different-est
thing you've ever made.
So,you know,pork seems a little... Raw.
Are you,uh,sure you cooked
it to the right temperature?
Yeah. I know what
temperature to cook pork to.
Well,it's tuesday night,our
foolin' around night.
Lies:0
Lies:1
Lies:2
Lies:3
Lies:4
Lies:5
Lies:6
It sure is. I have been
looking forward to this all day.
But not as much as I have.
I like it when you do that.
Well... I know what I'm doing.
God,you're sexy.
I know.
- Did you just fall asleep?
- no.
my parents are coming by.They said they
wanted to give us our baby present early.
I bet it's that camera I've been
dropping hints about for weeks.
that would be awesome.
I really wanna document this special time in our
lives Your belly,the baby coming out,his new room.
- I'm sorry. What was that middle thing?
- The baby coming out?
Oh,yeah.I'm gonna take
video all up in there.
Yeah.No,no,no. You will not be doing
any filming south of the equator,okay?
You will be staying
up here at all times.
All right.Seems a little weird to
have somebody else film it,but okay.
joel and vicky.
Okay,we have brought
something for little victor.
Mom,I told you that don't normally
name a baby boy after his grandmother.
What if he comes out
looking just like me?
Yeah,then we got bigger fish.
Well,thanks for the present.Can't
wait to learn how to use it.
Learn how to use it?It's a book.
Honey,he's from vermont.
To him,a book is probably just something
you shove under an outhouse to keep it level.
"the little brown puppy."I loved this
book.I used to read it when I was a kid.
I haven't seen this in 20 years.
I remember the first book I ever read.Started
with a picture of a stereo all in pieces.
At the end,the stereo
was all put together.
Even though I knew it was coming,the
ending always surprised me.
Now this book has been
in our family for forever.
I used to read it as a child,and I am
giving it to my child to read to her child.
I love traditions like that,where
you don't have to buy anything new.
everyone.I have some news.
At the law firm today,I heard
some very exciting scuttlebuzz
Well,you didn't hear
scuttlebuzz,but go ahead.
What?
Well,I'm just saying "scuttlebuzz" isn't
a word.You might have heard buzz or ****
Are you seriously doing this when I'm about
to tell everyon i'm gonna be made a partner?
Oh,my god!Oh,my god.
That's the scuttlebuzz.
They're gonna be naming three new
partners at my firm,and boyd woznack,
who's on the voting committee,told
me I am gonna be one of them.
- That is great! Maddie,congratulations!
- Honey,we are so proud of you.
it's nice to see you bring
honor back to the putney name.
It reminds me of my early days as a money manager,before
what I like to call my... "financial missteps."
Back then,when people
said the word "putney,"
it wasn't immediately followed by "that
son of a bitch drained my savings. Get him!"
Oh,my god!That wasn't a
book.It was a stereo manual!
Wait. I don't understand.I'm
not being made partner?
I write more wills than any lawyer here.
I'm sorry,and ,And brace
yourself.It gets worse.
What?
Because of the economy,the firm is hemorrhang
money.We had to make some tough decisions,and,
We're letting you go.
But boyd woznack told me
I was gonna be partner.
Yeah. He's gone,too.
He was spreading too
much false scuttlebuzz.
I can't believe this.I've been here for eight
years.I've devoted my life to this company.
I don't know what to say.People just haven't
been dying as much as we need them to.
I know it's been slow,but people are gonna
start dying again,neil.I know they are.
I wish there were something I could do.
All these new medicines and technological
advances,and nobody smokes anymore.
It is killing us!
Well,but it'll pick up, A new
disease,tainted food,something.
How about a natural disaster?You're gonna
need people here if there's a natural disaster.
Well,look,um,a big earthquake hits new
york,you'll be the first one I call.
I mean,uh,after my family,ourse.
Can we just give it another week?These
things comes in bunches,neil.
When I was 12,my aunt,a kid
down the street,and my cat died.
- Deaths are coming,neil!I can feel it!
- We can only hope.
Check it out!
That book that your parents gave us, I thought
I'd look online,see if it's worth anything.
You are never gonna believe
how much it's going for.
- Guess how much.
- $1,000?
No.What do you always do that?
You always go super high,and then no
matter what I say,it won't be impressive.
Sorry,baby. Ask me again.
- Guess how much the book is worth.
- 50 cents?
No! $300! 50 cents.
And our copy's in great condition.
We should sell it and use the
money to get the cera we want.
no,we can't sell that book.It's been in my family
for generations.It's like an heirloom or whatever.
Okay.I totally
understand.We won't sell it.
No,no,wait. Don't give
up.Try to convince me.
Yeah,I want to sell the book.I
just didn't wanna feel bad about it.
it's okay.We'll just buy
the camera with ouown money.
All right,casey.You
win,okay?We'll sell the book.Jeez!
Whoa!Howdy,partner!
Get it? It's an old west phrase,but
here I'm using it to refer to your new
I got fired.
You got fired?!What? Why?
They downsized the
whole probate department.
They said people aren't
dying as much as they used to.
What?!Three people died in
my hotel just this past week.
Thank you!Anyway,it doesn't
matter because I turned it around.
I kept my job by telling them
I do not accept my firing.
Is that how that works?
Well,it worked today.
I appreciate everything you're
trying to do here,neil,with firing me,
but unfortunately,at this time,I just
can't accept it,and I do apologize for that.
- but
- Neil,I've thought long and hard about this.
I'm sorry,but my decision
is final.See you tomorrow.
I'm... Not sure that
means you still have a job.
No,I do. No,no.They were just testing
me to see how much I wanna be partner.
It doesn't sound like a test.
Well,to be fair,you're not very good
at knowing when you're being tested.
- Like... Like right now?
- yep.
- Did I fail again?
- Anybody need a drink?
- Yeah.I'd love another glass.
That was a rhetorical question,junior.One
drink per person.This isn't maddie and ben's.
Here's the lady of the hour.
There's the new partner!
Mine were better.
How did it go today?
They escorted me out of
the office.It wasn't a test.
I know,baby.
I wish it was a test.I'm
really good at tests.
- You gonna tell your parents?
- No. I can't.They were so proud of me.
would kill me to see that look
of disappointment on their faces.
Well,yeah. You get used to that.
Hey,dinner,will eady in five minutes.Come
on,joel.Help me with the salad.
All right. So what's going on over here?
What's with all the whispering?
Is this aboucasey's shirt?
'cause it's not like ben
always wears the right thing.
Am I the only one who
remembers the beret?
They didn't make me
partner,mia.They fired me.
What?Oh,my god. I'm so sorry.
it's okay. I didn't accept it.
no.Is this like how you didn't
accept that b-minus in geometry?
That grade is still working its
way through the appeals process.
You can't tell mom and dad I got fired.
Aren't they gonna find out eventually?
No,no,because I have a plan.
I'm gonna call everyone I know and
e-mail my **** to every firm in the city.
I'll get a new job and tell mom and dad
I quit because I got a better position.
All right,so speaking of secret plans,we have
something that you cannot tell mom and dad.
Okay,you know that book that we read
as kids, "the little brown puppy"?
- I love that book.
- Yeah.
Well,we found out it's worth a lot of
money,and we are currently selling it online.
If you can't find a job and you need money,just
grab a couple books from here and sell 'em online.
I already hid two in
the back of my shirt,see?
Day 1 Without A Job
I am so excited to go out
and tackle the world today.
I bet losing my job is gonna be the
best thing that ever happened to me.
Day 3 Without A Job
I didn't find a job,and
a bird crapped on me.
I used to be a lawyer!
Day 8 Without A Job
You know what I realized last
night at 4:30 in the morning
when I was cleaning the bathroom
again for no reason? It is all up here.
If you visualize yourself
getting a job,you will get one!
Day 9 Without A Job
- Hey,honey.
- Look,there aren't any jobs.
It's been over a week.
I've called everyone,e-mailed **** to
every firm in the city.No one's intted.
Apparently word got out that I didn't accept
my firing,and now I'm considered a "risky hire."
Well,o-okay,but we
can't give up,can we?
Don't start with that "we" crap,ben.
You don't know what it's like out there.You
have a job... If you wanna call it that.
say what you want about me,but
leave the hotel out of this.
I used to have everything,and
then just like that,gone.
- Have... You been watching tv all day?
- Yes.
There are a lot of great shows
on during the day.I had no idea.
Before,I saw this really
funny one about an acne cream.
Now I'm watching one about a
juicer.It's more of a drama.
All right.how about we
get you io the shower?
No. I'm good.I wanna see what happens when
they put the whole apple in the juice machine.
It's gonna clog for sure.
- Ben coles.
- It didn't! It didn't clog!
It's for you. It's a law firm.Freeman
and gant? I've heard of them.
Oh,my god. This is maddie putney.
An interview? Now?
I can't come right now.I've been
drinking,and I'm covered in cheese balls.
You don't have to say
that.They can't see you.
You can't see me.I'll come right over.
Oh,my god.You missed it!
Today was the last day of the auction.
There was a bidding war
- People who are desperate for this book,
- Really?
- I know,I know.It's crazy.
The winner's coming
by to pick up the book.
- Guess how much it sold for.
- $1,000?
Damn it! No! $350.
Really? Still,that's crazy.I mean,it's just
a sweet little book about a dog.I had no idea.
This book must be amazing.
"'little brown puppy' by scooter
mcgill." Pretty good so far.
"the little brown puppy was always causing trouble.
He wasn't allowed to mix with the good white dogs."
Is it just me,or is
this book crazy racist?
What? No,it's a book
about puppies that, Whoa.
Oh,my god.Yeah. This is horrible.
Shame on you,scooter mcgill!
I had no idea!
It's like the first time you realize
the california raisins used to be grapes.
I cannot believe that my
parents let me read this book.
I was an impressionable child.
Do you think this book shaped
me and I didn't even know it?
Is this why I don't like "the wire"?
Who are all the people who
wanted to buy this book?
What kind of monster
is coming over here?!
Stereo manual doesn't
look so bad now,does it?
so your *** is very impressive
What would you say is
your biggest weakness?
Great question,miles.
My biggest weakness is probably
that I don't have a weakness.
Okay. A little hard
to believe,but...Okay.
How much experience do you have
in other aspects of the law?
Well,my specialty is probate,but I've always been
interested in family law,contract law,litigation.
I can do anything.The law is my life.
- I have a t-shirt that
says that. - I like that.
Really? You can have it. It's yours.
No. That's gross.
I'll get you a new one. You don't want
a shirt with my old sweat stains on it.
Unless you do,then that's weird,but fine.My
boyfriend put on my bra once.I don't judge.
Maybe your weakness is you
don't know when to stop talking.
Well,I wouldn't call collecting women's
sweat-stained shirts a strength,miles.
I like you. Why don't you come in tomorrow
morning,9:00 a.m.? We'll discuss salary then.
I got the job? Oh,my god! Thank you.
I knew this would happen.I visualized it in
my head while I cried in front of the mirror.
But everyone's cried in front
of the mirror,right,miles?
Stop talking.Okay.
It's the racists.
Oh,no. It's just my mom and dad.
Well...
Okay,we broke down and got you the
camera,so you can stop hinting all the time.
okay.Well,it's a little banged up,and...There
are pictures of strangers on here.
Yes,it is the floor
model,but it still works.
Please,I don't see why floor
models get such a bad rap.
So a bunch of weird people touched it.
Didn't stop me from
marrying your mother.
Okay,good,well,I'm glad you guys are here,because you
know that children's book that you gave me last week?
- It's really racist.
- No,it's not.It is a book about puppies.
- Puppies can't be racist.
- I don't know about that.
Growing up,I had a dog,and anytime
an eskimo came by,oh!good luck,buddy.
Look,mom.
Oh,my.
Okay,you're right.This book is terrible.
Why did my mother let me read that?
Is this book the reason I
didn't like "sanford and son"?
Okay,well,don't worry.We're getting
rid of it.We put it up for sale online.
Someone's coming to
pick it up right now.
- What?You can't sell that.
- Why?
Because it's been in our
family for generations?
Look,you can't rid of something just
because it's offensive and old-fashioned.
I still keep your mom around.Come
on!You gotta give it to me for that one!
sorry,vicky,but he nailed that.
Oh,my god.It's the racists.
I'm here for the book.
Not what I was expecting.
sweetie.You know what? You're
pretty.You don't need to read.
Sorry. I was paying
the cabbie.I'm francine.
This is my daughter katie,and we're
here to buy "the little brown puppy."
come on in.
So can I ask you why you want this book?
well,I read it when I was a little
girl,and I want my daughter to read it now.
yeah.Have you read it recently?
not in-gosh-25
years.
francine,uh,first of all,you should know
that I was in the same place you are.
I read this book as a kid,and I thought it was
great,but I read it today for the first since then,and,
It's really racist.
- no,it's not.
- It is.
Oh,my god. Oh,this is disgusting.
Why would my parents let me read this?
Is this why I didn't like urkel?
no.
Well,what are we gonna do with it now? Can't
sell it,can't read it,can't give it away.
We could send it to casey's
family to prop up their outhouse.
Right,'cause my family's the one
who comes out of this looking bad.
Hey,guys.I have big
news.I left my law firm.
- I thought they made you a partner.
- No,that turned out not to be true.
So I left,head held high,dignity intact,and
just got a different,even better position.
- Where?
- At a firm called freeman and gant.
- The bus bench people?
- What?
Freeman and gant-they have ads
on all the bus stop benches.
"Call freeman and gant if
you get in an accidant."
- they're ambulance chasers?
- Of course!That's how I knew them.
You couldn't remember
that before my interview?
Well,to be fair,I was getting cheese ball
powder off you with a keyboard vacuum.
Okay,I'm confused.Why would you leave a great
firm like braverman to work for those people?
I was let go from my old job.
They downsized the probate group,and freeman
and gant was the only firm willing to hire me.
Why didn't you tell us? We had that whole
dinner. We even sprung for a side salad.
I didn't want to disappoint
you. You were so proud of me.
I mean,I'm the daughter who's
a success in the business world.
On my own company.
Hey,you could never disappoint us.
We're proud of you because of who
are,not because of what job you have.
You turned into a wonderful person,even
though we gave you racist books to read.
Look,and I don't care where you work.
Wherever it is,I'm sure you
will be the best lawyer there.
So what if it's not the perfect job?
You work there for a few months
while you try to find a better one.
No,you're right!No one will
ever know I worked there.
Look,casey,an online relationship quiz.
"how well do you know your mate?"
okay,"where was your mate
born?" that's easy.Vermont.
- texas.
- Really? Okay.
"what was their first pet?"
you told me that adorable
story about your pet goat...
- Frog Pete.
- .Named richard.
You know,these tests are really stupid.
- We should just...
- Make out?
see?You know the answers to
all the important questions.
yes.
Okay,first question,"if your partner was a
type of food,what kind of food would they be?"
grape.
Haven't even read you the choices.
Am I... Cake...Strawberry-mmm!
Or... Toast?
Cake.
You're doing that just to hurt me.I
am a strawberry,and you know it.
You know what? I'm going
back to grape. You're a grape.
I am not taking these
quizzes with you anymore.
Typical grape.
Do you le shady hillsides
or babbling brooks?
- Shady hillsides.
- Me,too.
Do you prefer a cute and cozy
view or sprawling but beautiful?
- cute and cozy.
- Well ,I couldn't agree more.