×ÖÄ»
- Synced and corrected by chamallow - - www.Addic7ed.Com -
That was a harsh stop.
×ÖÄ»
- Happens all the time. - Not like that.
It'll start up again any minute.
×ÖÄ»
That's weird, there's no passengers in the next car.
We're locked in.
×ÖÄ»
What?
It's locked here too.
×ÖÄ»
What the hell is going on?
We'll start up again soon right guys?
×ÖÄ»
Careful kid you could hurt yourself.
How many times did we get stuck on the trains every week,
×ÖÄ»
it's gotta be nothing.
Empty cars maybe, but locked doors?
×ÖÄ»
Maybe 'cause we're stopped.
Forget it, we're between stops.
×ÖÄ»
Maybe if we just give it a minute.
Hey,
×ÖÄ»
you know what's going on don't you?
Yeah, as a matter of fact I do.
×ÖÄ»
Then why don't you say something?
I like to see what I'm dealing with first.
×ÖÄ»
I'm Mac.
Rod.
×ÖÄ»
O-kay.
No one leaves this train until I let you.
×ÖÄ»
Why won't you let us?
Because kid, we got a demon in our midst.
×ÖÄ»
And it could be any one of you.
Don't get too close partner, that includes her.
×ÖÄ»
Her?
Please.
×ÖÄ»
The fact is there's demons all around us.
My job's to seek them out.
×ÖÄ»
Okay whack-a-nuts,
you know, I'm open, I'm open to it.
×ÖÄ»
I've been doing this a long time folks.
I'm damn good at it.
×ÖÄ»
Demons, huh?
I don't know how you expect any of us to believe you Max.
×ÖÄ»
Mac. That's Mac.
I know you've all seen things beyond the usual,
×ÖÄ»
out of the realm of science, beyond our comprehension,
the supernatural,
×ÖÄ»
that's what drew me to you.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
×ÖÄ»
You've all seen things and yet,
you still don't think there's even a chance
×ÖÄ»
that a demon exists on this train.
It's probably you.
×ÖÄ»
No, not me.
Quite the opposite in fact,
×ÖÄ»
I'm what you call a demon hunter.
I got the ability to feel a demon's presence
×ÖÄ»
and contain it.
The problem with these supernatural encounters is
×ÖÄ»
they shield who's who and what's what,
all those memories, they look the same.
×ÖÄ»
But I can tell when you're all going to be
in the same place so I make sure I'm there to grab a lot of you.
×ÖÄ»
Couldn't have timed it any better
but then again, that's what I do.
×ÖÄ»
And I promise you, one of you is definitely a demon,
but who?
×ÖÄ»
How long do you need to figure it out?
As long as it takes,
×ÖÄ»
none of you would be candidates,
if you didn't have a little gray in your past
×ÖÄ»
and one of you has a soul of absolute darkness,
but who?
×ÖÄ»
Let's say there's a hint of truth to what you're saying,
what happens to the demon once you find it?
×ÖÄ»
You can't be serious.
Demon hunting is my purpose in life.
×ÖÄ»
I can only afford to be serious.
What's with the silver tip?
×ÖÄ»
Insurance.
You know what?
×ÖÄ»
I think I'll start with you.
What?
×ÖÄ»
No way, I don't want any part of this.
Then our search is over folks, we found our demon.
×ÖÄ»
Fine, what are you going to do?
Take a peek into your soul.
×ÖÄ»
Ma'am, ma'am please.
Read the sign child, we're closed.
×ÖÄ»
Please, it's an emergency, I need to see the future.
I'm sorry, come back tomorrow.
×ÖÄ»
Tomorrow's too late.
I have plans this evening.
×ÖÄ»
It's all I've got, it's an emergency, please.
You know, I normally don't do this sort of thing.
×ÖÄ»
Thank you.
You're welcome, child.
×ÖÄ»
Here, dry yourself off and then we'll get started.
I saw the sign out front, 100% guaranteed.
×ÖÄ»
Is that really true?
Absolutely, I pride myself on that.
×ÖÄ»
Now tell me why did you feel the need
to come out here at this hour?
×ÖÄ»
I just, I have the feeling like I'm in danger you know?
That something bad's gonna happen
×ÖÄ»
and I need you to help me figure out why.
What's your name, child?
×ÖÄ»
Tabitha.
I'm Madame Renee, you're safe here Tabitha.
×ÖÄ»
My clients are like family to me
and under no circumstances will anyone harm you under my watch.
×ÖÄ»
Now, what would you like today, a palm reading?
Horoscope?
×ÖÄ»
Dialogue with the dead?
Actually, I was hoping for a tarot reading.
×ÖÄ»
Ah the cards, no room for error,
have you ever had one done before?
×ÖÄ»
No, I've never been to a psychic.
I prefer fortune teller my dear,
×ÖÄ»
psychic is so scientific, so negative.
Many of my friends are clients.
×ÖÄ»
They vouch that you've never been wrong with a reading, ever.
You're in good hands, 100% guaranteed.
×ÖÄ»
You see my gift comes with a great responsibility,
I can't afford to be wrong,
×ÖÄ»
my entire reputation depends on it.
Now, shall we begin?
×ÖÄ»
What is your question for the cards?
I guess,
×ÖÄ»
what is this terrible feeling I have about?
In order to protect you,
×ÖÄ»
we are going to have to get to the heart of the matter.
Luckily for us, the deck and I have a spiritual connection.
×ÖÄ»
See how the cards have a mind of their own?
We'll do a standard cross, what has happened,
×ÖÄ»
what is happening and what will happen.
Please Tabitha cut the deck.
×ÖÄ»
Now we're in business.
10 cards,
×ÖÄ»
six in a cross,
four on the side,
×ÖÄ»
present past future, external influences,
hopes and fears.
×ÖÄ»
I've come to fear readings.
You see, fortune telling is a burden.
×ÖÄ»
You never know if the news is going to be good or bad,
but that's the price we pay for having our fortunes read,
×ÖÄ»
the truth.
We start with a major Arcana card, the hermit,
×ÖÄ»
it represents the loner, caution,
vigilance, sound like somebody you know?
×ÖÄ»
Of course it does.
Now, let's find out what your immediate challenge is,
×ÖÄ»
based on your question.
The nine of swords.
×ÖÄ»
Is that bad?
No, in your case I'll assume it means anxiety,
×ÖÄ»
that you need to trust your instincts,
but you're doing that already.
×ÖÄ»
Maybe by looking into your past,
the problem will reveal itself.
×ÖÄ»
This one friend of mine,
she told me you predicted that she would have
×ÖÄ»
a major career change, she was fired three weeks later,
she decided to open her own business.
×ÖÄ»
She followed her dream thanks to your reading.
The greatest reward for fortune tellers
×ÖÄ»
that little push to greater success,
I am very happy for your friend.
×ÖÄ»
Wonderful, the 10 of cups,
it seems that in your distant past
×ÖÄ»
you grew up in a warm, loving family with true friendships
and yet you are lonely now.
×ÖÄ»
Maybe that's due to your inability to trust anybody,
this deficit of love in your life
×ÖÄ»
makes me assume that you are single.
That's exactly right,
×ÖÄ»
but what does this have to do with my bad feeling?
Did somebody ask you out recently?
×ÖÄ»
Actually, yeah, this guy I used to see at the gym,
he talks to me sometimes, asks me out.
×ÖÄ»
I always say no.
Don't fear my child, it's reversed.
×ÖÄ»
You know the death card normally doesn't mean actual death,
that's a common misconception, in reverse
×ÖÄ»
it could actually mean quite the opposite.
Thank God.
×ÖÄ»
In this case, it represents your recent past,
it just means immobility, slow changes
×ÖÄ»
and if that's not it I'm sorry to say,
it could be something more dire than that.
×ÖÄ»
It could be interpreted as a narrow escape from death,
cheating death, I wonder if,
×ÖÄ»
tell me about that guy again.
From the gym?
×ÖÄ»
I bumped into him another time outside, but..
Maybe he's following you.
×ÖÄ»
Maybe he is the bad feeling, no need to fret
we will get to the bottom of this now,
×ÖÄ»
wonderful the eight of wands, my lovely Tabitha
you are in luck, your best possible outcome,
×ÖÄ»
brand new ideas are coming your way,
a new love, a new journey, anything is possible.
×ÖÄ»
Now that we know the sky's the limit for you,
why don't we find a way to get you out of
×ÖÄ»
this path of danger and onto a better one?
Got another one for you.
×ÖÄ»
This guy I work with, he was really down,
unable to muster up the courage to ask for some
×ÖÄ»
promotion at work.
He came to see you
×ÖÄ»
and you insisted the cards were clear
that he should go for it.
×ÖÄ»
And?
What else?
×ÖÄ»
It worked.
This is your second major Arcana card.
×ÖÄ»
It's the Empress and it's reversed.
Your immediate future is filled with indecision,
×ÖÄ»
lack of understanding.
There's something happening around you already, but what?
×ÖÄ»
Four cards left,
factors affecting your situation.
×ÖÄ»
The seven of cups, there's something that you're not aware of
will affect you soon.
×ÖÄ»
A secret, a lie maybe.
The two of swords reversed,
×ÖÄ»
loss of balance in a relationship
violent passion, misunderstanding of love,
×ÖÄ»
oh my dear child you must avoid that man.
I thought it was nothing.
×ÖÄ»
Now that I think about it, I see him everywhere.
I thought it was because he lives nearby,
×ÖÄ»
but I see him at restaurants, on the street.
That sounds like a lot more than nothing.
×ÖÄ»
We must find a way to keep you safe.
Good thing we have the cards to guide us.
×ÖÄ»
The cards never lie.
This reminds me of my other friend.
×ÖÄ»
He said you predicted that something precious
would be taken from him.
×ÖÄ»
He spent hours and hours hiding things,
his money, valuables, all material things.
×ÖÄ»
He had no idea it would end up being his wife.
I remember that man.
×ÖÄ»
He didn't believe me, he didn't listen to the cards.
You believe me dear don't you?
×ÖÄ»
I do.
Some fates aren't ours to decide I'm afraid,
×ÖÄ»
that's why I said I read fortunes with a heavy heart,
but let's finish yours and find a way to help you.
×ÖÄ»
Two cards left.
Another major Arcana card?
×ÖÄ»
Your hopes and fears, the fool.
This can't be good.
×ÖÄ»
This centers around a choice you have to make and soon,
in your immediate future, that man wants you dead.
×ÖÄ»
One card left, the final outcome.
Come on, flip it.
×ÖÄ»
Flip the card.
What is it?
×ÖÄ»
The nine of Pentacles, reversed.
Loss is possible, danger from thieves,
×ÖÄ»
caution,
death.
×ÖÄ»
Based on your best possible outcome, you can beat this.
Please, Madame Renee,
×ÖÄ»
let me stay here a little while longer,
at least until the storm passes.
×ÖÄ»
I suppose a little while longer couldn't hurt.
Thank you, Madame Renee, thank you.
×ÖÄ»
I know,
why don't I do you?
×ÖÄ»
Let me read your fortune, anyone ever done that before?
No, no.
×ÖÄ»
Seriously?
Oh come one, you don't even know what the cards mean.
×ÖÄ»
I'll deal, you explain,
what else are we going to do?
×ÖÄ»
You said what you gave me before was all that you had.
Yeah, and a good thing too.
×ÖÄ»
I mean right, what else are we gonna do?
We'll treat it like a lesson.
×ÖÄ»
Always wanted to try this.
What are you doing with $400 cash in your purse anyway?
×ÖÄ»
No uh, we're doing you now,
cut the deck right?
×ÖÄ»
Okay, so I start with inside of the cross?
Oh no, like this child.
×ÖÄ»
Right.
The magician and the present,
×ÖÄ»
represents creativity, skill, willpower, confidence.
Sounds about right, 100% guaranteed of course.
×ÖÄ»
The two of Pentacles,
I'm able to handle multiple problems,
×ÖÄ»
taking on a new task could be difficult.
Expect a helpful message.
×ÖÄ»
Is Madame Renee stressed out?
Aren't we all.
×ÖÄ»
Hey, maybe this reading will help you.
Yeah, maybe.
×ÖÄ»
Okay, distant past is next, right?
The eight of cups, reversed.
×ÖÄ»
Abandonment of one's original path.
Disappointment in love,
×ÖÄ»
complaining without...
Something wrong?
×ÖÄ»
No, complaining without cause,
the desire to leave one's success for something better.
×ÖÄ»
Remember that friend I told you about,
the one you predicted would have a career change and got fired?
×ÖÄ»
Turns out she lost a flash drive
with a big presentation on it, prepped it for months
×ÖÄ»
for some big account, it just disappeared,
fired on the spot, ruined the entire company.
×ÖÄ»
But you said that you found a new, better job.
Yeah but her startup went under soon after,
×ÖÄ»
the fortune was right, just unfortunate that's all.
The strength card reversed.
×ÖÄ»
That's the second major Arcana card, right?
I guess it means weakness,
×ÖÄ»
since it's facing the wrong way.
Lack of faith, tyranny,
×ÖÄ»
abuse of power,
strength.
×ÖÄ»
I think yes, this has to do with someone I used to know.
Someone you know?
×ÖÄ»
Okay, now we're in business.
Best possible outcome is next.
×ÖÄ»
The hanged man.
Another major Arcana card?
×ÖÄ»
I think you're going for the world record.
But we're not even halfway through yet, that's impossible.
×ÖÄ»
- The odds are... - The cards never lie, best possible outcome,
change, reversal, abandonment,
×ÖÄ»
sacrifice, improvement, rebirth.
What is this?
×ÖÄ»
Who are you and what are you doing here?
I'm just reading your fortune Madame Renee,
×ÖÄ»
immediate future is next.
10 of swords, sudden misfortune, the ruining of plans,
×ÖÄ»
defeat, failure, pain.
This is the worst fortune I've ever seen.
×ÖÄ»
What do you want from me?
Why are you doing this to me?
×ÖÄ»
Four cards left,
the queen of swords, a quick and confident decision.
×ÖÄ»
Someone who can bear their sorrow,
remember that other story I told you
×ÖÄ»
about the guy I work with?
Of course you do, he was competing for that promotion.
×ÖÄ»
Soon after your reading his competition,
mysteriously went missing,
×ÖÄ»
doesn't change that you were right,
just strange how it all happened.
×ÖÄ»
External influences already?
Oh look, the page of swords, so many swords.
×ÖÄ»
We're done here, get out of my shop.
Now, now child, you know it's bad luck to stop
×ÖÄ»
in the middle of a reading,
besides how can we ever solve your problems?
×ÖÄ»
Outside forces you can't control,
an imposter, an unexpected event.
×ÖÄ»
You.
Two cards left,
×ÖÄ»
hopes and fears.
Impossible.
×ÖÄ»
Will you look at that.
Another major Arcana card,
×ÖÄ»
the Moon, deception, trickery,
danger, disgrace.
×ÖÄ»
Cards, 22 major Arcana
... 10 cards in the cross
×ÖÄ»
four major Arcana cards, that's almost half.
That last story I told you,
×ÖÄ»
about the man you predicted would lose something.
He wasn't just some friend, he was my sister's husband
×ÖÄ»
and you murdered her to make your fortune true.
You're not a fortune teller, you're a fortune maker.
×ÖÄ»
You tell fortunes and you keep your reputation
by making sure they come true,
×ÖÄ»
no matter what the cost, 100% guaranteed.
That's right, I'm a fraud,
×ÖÄ»
those cards are random pictures, art, they mean nothing.
That's where you're wrong Madame Renee,
×ÖÄ»
you might be a fraud, but the cards
are very, very real,
×ÖÄ»
at least as long as someone like me is handling them.
So many fortune tellers try to make their clients
×ÖÄ»
feel better by saying the death card
doesn't really mean they're gonna die.
×ÖÄ»
The truth is, it usually does.
Time to make your fortune come true.
×ÖÄ»
So wait, are you telling us
Tabitha murdered Madame Renee?
×ÖÄ»
I didn't murder anyone,
but I can't stop the spirits from casting their revenge,
×ÖÄ»
I'm just the messenger, a medium.
Yeah well she still died,
×ÖÄ»
Mac told it to us all the same.
Yeah but it's not like she didn't come at her with a knife guys.
×ÖÄ»
Right, self-defense.
Yeah but Tabitha didn't have to show up at all.
×ÖÄ»
Madame Renee trusted her, took her in.
For a hell of a lot of money.
×ÖÄ»
Wait Tabitha, so if you're a psychic and can see the future
which one of them is the demon?
×ÖÄ»
It doesn't work that way, I need my cards.
Are you sure of what you saw demon hunter,
×ÖÄ»
what you're telling us?
I told it just as I saw it
×ÖÄ»
as she saw it,
I can't just,
×ÖÄ»
it's like watching TV,
I can see and hear experiences,
×ÖÄ»
but I can't be sure of anyone's intent.
I think he's making this shit up.
×ÖÄ»
What he saw was true.
Why admit to that?
×ÖÄ»
That made you look pretty bad Tabitha.
Yeah exactly, because no one in their right mind would,
×ÖÄ»
it also proves I'm not the demon.
No, it doesn't.
×ÖÄ»
Maybe you and Mac are working together,
acting like your story checks out when
×ÖÄ»
you're really a plant.
Oh please, this guy knew something about me
×ÖÄ»
that nobody possibly could.
You're saying he's for real then.
×ÖÄ»
Yeah, he's for real.
Is Tabitha the demon, Mac?
×ÖÄ»
I don't know
and I won't until I looked through every one of your souls,
×ÖÄ»
one by one, the answer always reveals itself.
I've never been wrong.
×ÖÄ»
I don't think you're a demon.
Thanks, kid.
×ÖÄ»
The two of you are married.
Gee, everyone's a psychic.
×ÖÄ»
I hate sarcasm.
You're both connected, your stories ar the same,
×ÖÄ»
get close so I can look through one eye each got it?
- Synced and corrected by chamallow - - www.Addic7ed.Com -