England are expected to bring James Anderson back into the side.
Hello and welcome to our look ahead to what the the papers will be
With me are the political commentator Miranda Green
and the Daily Telegraph's chief political correspondent,
Thank you for being the first paper reviewers of 2016. Setting the year
off on a good standard, I hope. We can look at the front pages.
The FT's picture is of the shooting in Tel Aviv.
They also feature President Obama's New Year's message and a claim
he is planning to bypass Congress to impose new controls on gun sales.
Pope Francis at his New Year's Day mass dominates the front
It also reports on the potential for British troops to face criminal
charges over abuse and unlawful killing during the Iraq War.
The Daily Mail has comments from the first wife of suspended
Simon Danczuk about the impact which the allegation that he sent
explicit messages to a 17-year-old is having on their family.
"A student cheating crisis" is the headline on the Times.
It says almost 50,000 students have been caught cheating
The I says Jeremy Corbyn must get 35% of the vote in next year's
elections if he's to avoid a coup from fellow party members.
The Sun reports on a former EastEnders actress, Sian Blake,
who has been missing with her two young children for almost three
Government plans to double the fine for littering to ?150
And the Mirror has claims from a couple who say they missed
out on a ?35 million lottery jackpot, because of a mix-up
Welcome. Let's begin with the FT Weekend, a two-day paper, so plenty
of time for people to delve into this but a striking story on the
front page as President Obama enters his final 12 months in office. What
he has done is returned to an issue he has been vocal on before, which
is gun control, which in America is incredibly controversial. The
Republican party refuses to countenance control on who can buy
and keep weapons. Plenty of Democrats feel the same. Because of
the American system it is difficult to get legislation through and in
2013 they tried with a bipartisan Bill after the Newtown school
killings which was blocked in the Senate and President Obama is
determined to return to this is his last few months to try to introduce
a background check on who can buy guns. It is controversial and part
of the rise of Donald Trump, the phenomenon in the Republican
selection as to who will run against we think Hillary Clinton, is the
idea that America and President Obama do not understand each other
and so trying to take on America's love of guns is controversial. It
has legacy written all over it. His comments are so important. When the
most recent massacre happened he said the reporting and reaction is
routine and it must stop. He was so cross. He has woken up to the fact
the clock is ticking. When you read the detail, it says he has been
pushing hard for background checks on those buying guns and would like
them to be mandatory which Congress will not permit. The only power he
has is to expand regulations, for background checks on people selling
the guns. The wrong way round. It is a tiny step towards even having a
conversation on controlling who has the guns. It is interesting when you
talk to Americans about this, they will quote to you, very clear in
their minds, about the right to bear arms. When you look at the
Constitution, it is the right to bear arms as part of a well ordered
militia, presumably when there was no police force and presumably the
police force is armed. They reserve their right to have their cake and
eat it. Loretta Lynch, the scourge of Fifa. If anybody can do it,
perhaps she can. That is an interesting thought. We will find
out more on Monday. In the Times newspaper, and very intriguing
story. An interesting report from the special correspondent who has
done investigations and he says he has found 50 student is caught
cheating at British universities. Many more likely to cheat in exams
rather than coursework. The Times newspaper has done it in a measured
way, but it is alarming. Extraordinary these figures. You try
to get Freedom of Information on these figures but you have to go to
individual university groups and to pull them together in one go is
interesting. Students coming from outside the EU to British
universities are an important source of revenue. Our universities charge
extraordinary multiples of what British and EU students pay. Is
there a debate on whether the scale of fees foreign students pay,
significantly higher than paid by our student is, whether they create
an incentive for people to behave in a way they might not otherwise
behave. It is an interesting point. We are as the UK in competition with
other English-speaking nations to attract people to universities.
Partly because we want the best people from around the world. We
want them to stay here and win Nobel prizes here! That they are a source
of revenue. In the detail of the story, which looks robust as an
investigation, there is an extraordinary one, five cases of
impersonation where students arrange for someone else to sit exams on
their behalf. Imagine getting someone else to turn up to suit your
Ph.D. . Less than 1% of those found guilty of misconduct. If you aren't
getting a lot of money from foreign students, you might not want to
chuck them out. Are they enforcing the rules properly? Presumably it
will raise questions they will have to answer about procedures, and for
the employers who might say, is that degree quite as good as I thought it
was? Colonel Gaddafi, something to do with his Ph.D. In the past... ? I
think there have been a lot of allegations that he is not with us
to offer a response, so perhaps we will move on to the I newspaper.
This man, almost the man of the year in terms of publicity in 2015,
Jeremy Corbyn. This is fascinating. You have written a piece for the
Guardian and about pantomime. I do not what -- know what character he
would be. Dick Whittington? The streets of London paved with
electoral gold? Jack the giant killer. This piece says Jeremy
Corbyn's team are letting it be known they think the benchmark for
success in the May elections is for Labour to get a 35% vote share,
which could lead to do with managing expectations as to what would allow
him to survive as leader. A lot of the backchat has been, will there be
a coup against Corbyn by the moderate wing of the party? We
expect Jeremy Corbyn in the next weeks to probably knife his Shadow
Cabinet who are not onside. The drama will not go away any time
soon. 35%, they are playing down arguably expectations. Roughly 2%
above the average they are polling at the moment. Local elections are
not the same thing but we will try to map this on to a figure for the
next general election. You mentioned reshuffle. What is your sense of
this? There has been debate about whether it would happen. We had it
with that stuff in one of the Labour whip saying it is time to deal with
these traitors. Others trying to slap him down. John Ashworth saying
he should not have said it. Nobody is saying whether the reshuffle is
taking place. They say it is a matter for the leader and we are
told it is next week. How far does it go, dealing with the 11 or so
members of his close group of Shadow Cabinet who voted against him on
Syria. What is the risk? It already is called among the media the
revenge reshuffle, which is a problem because everything he does
to assert his authority is seen as part of the ideological battle and
spirit within the party and it goes back to the phenomenon of someone
who rebelled against the previous Labour leaders over 500 times,
trying to impose stern party discipline. You remember this, I can
remember a former minister under John Major when I asked him about
Iain Duncan Smith's demand for loyalty, saying some expletive rich
responses about what he thought. Because he had been a serial rebel
and made John Major's life hell in that period. In the Independent
newspaper, this is serious. The striking photograph of Pope Francis
kissing a statue of baby Jesus on New Year's Day. What do you make of
this? The context, a rambling about human rights we are seeing at the
moment. They are concerned human rights laws are being used to
prosecute soldiers, British soldiers, in foreign battlefields
is. It is a great story. The reporter has found there could be as
many as 200 people unlawfully killed by British soldiers. It puts it into
context, if you are trying to defend, and thinking about if you
will be sued at the end of that, it conflicts the idea of your job. The
legacy of Iraq is very much with us, domestically also. I agree. We are
waiting for pitch Chilcot report. Which we are told we will get this
summer. I hate to say, let's wait and see. -- for the Chilcot report.
The legacy of Iraq continues to haunt British politics. I am struck
by the idea that the caseload of the group looking into unlawful killing
and torture by British troops in Iraq is exploding. They were
investigating 152 cases and it has swollen to 1500 potential victims of
British troops behaving in a way against the laws of war, allegedly.
We will hear more about this in the course of the coming months. I will
let Christopher start again. I should do with this next one. A drum
roll. The front of the Daily Telegraph. War declared on litter
louts by one Christopher hope. It is a consultation from the government
to increase on the spot litter fine. -- finds. It is something that
annoys our readers. And probably a lot of other people. Some would say,
about time. Also interviewed, a man who is running a clean the country
for the Queen ahead of her 90th birthday and he is concerned that
some people think it is a human rights to drop litter. I trace it
back to when Vince were removed from London underground. An
anti-terrorism strategy. After the King's Cross could be right. --
Kings crossfire. You could be right. It is said we should police it. He
is saying... How do you go to someone and say you have dropped a
cigarette packet. Do it with politeness, he says, oh, you have
dropped something stop hopefully you will embarrass them into doing
something. The government is interested in this and it thinks it
has done it with the supermarket levy. And also sending text messages
to tell people neighbours had paid up, creating the sense you should
play along. Neighbours have picked up their litter and so maybe you
should. This person, a great wit, talks about why everybody should
have to live in a teenager's bedroom, it is bad for your spirit.
He is right. Interesting you have an American talking about it because
Bill Bryson is obsessed with the way we British do not look after our
country and drop litter. If they say we could improve, we should listen.
Let me give you the last story from this review. The front page of the
Mirror newspaper. We will leave the free slimming pull-out aside. The
story at the bottom. This couple say something went wrong with their
mobile phone app with which they bought their tickets, which would
have been a winning ticket and they would have been able to claim ?35
million. Clearly that is not a brilliant start to the new year for
them, thinking what might have been. I am interested in why it is the
splash and the psychology of it. You will you did to the slimming
pull-out and every single front page has a diet, turn over a new leaf
from page. What is the psychology of this? Are we supposed to think we
feel bad for them, or that our New Year will be more cheery? Buy a
paper ticket, that is what I say. I do notice... We do not have the
whole story yet, and I might be unfair to the couple, but they say
the ?2 online ticket purchase failed because they only had 60p in their
recount. That might not be the fault of the app! It could happen to any
of us. We have all thing when we thought we had sorted something.
Misreading the numbers and thinking you have one! It cannot be all of 35
million. It must be a share of that. That is something I cannot answer.
Perhaps we will have more when we come back in an hour. Thank you for
racing through a busy run of stories in the first paper review of 2016.
Now, the sport.