-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:Ö¥Ê¿µ°¸â
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Hung
Season 01 Episode 07
Keep 'em closed.
They're closed. God,ray.
I hope this isn't the part where you hack
me into bits and bury me in the woods.
This is not the outfit I
want to be found dead in.
All right.
Why are we stopping?
'Cause we're here.
Okay,open 'em.
- This is it?
- This is it.
Your tent?
My tent.
Is this your property?
This is my property.
This is my lake.
This is my yard.
My house.
And my tent.
Oh,why can't we just go in the house?
I don't live in a house.
I live in a tent.
Come on.
marcel proust?
Marcel proust. Your tattoo.
Oh,right. Yeah.
I should have gotten sylvia plath.
I had a man-- an ugly
man-- tell me I wasn't ugly.
An ugly man...named floyd.
You're not ugly.
You're not real,are you?
I'm pierce.
This was it.
No more bullshit.
No randall.
No force-fed lines.
No flat tires by the side of the road.
It was just me and her making out in
my tent with the wind howling outside.
oh,fuck.
you're-- you're
unbelievable.
It felt different this time.
It felt real.
Which is why waking up next to that pile of
cold hard cash felt like such a kick in the gut.
Shit,jemma.
I thought we were past this.
oh my god.
Ray,what are you doing here?
Here.
Here's your cut.
She paid you directly again?
Unbelievable.
It just feels fantastic to
be undermined at every turn.
Is it all here?
You know what? Now's not
a good time for company.
Look,I'm sorry. I'm
sorry for last night.
I didn't even want this money.
I just... I don't think jemma
should be a client anymore.
You want to cut her off?
No,I don't want to  cut her off.
I just don't-- I don't
want her to be a client.
What are you sayin
I think...
- I want her to--
- to be a girlfriend or something?
Hey,babe,can I use this eggplant?
You-yeah.
What?
All I know is that there's
something going on between us.
Some...
thing that--
- babe,eggplant?
- It's fine. Just use it.
You want to explain something to me?
Just how do you see this
business venture of ours working?
Because I've been pouring my blood,sweat and
tears into this happiness consultant thing
and you seem determined
to undermine our success.
Me?
Yeah.
Look,you've the one who can't even launch a viral
marketing campaign without leaving a phone number.
It's supposed to enter
through the subconscious.
You know,if you have all the
answers,then you book the clients.
Just let me know when you've
got some lined up. All right?
I could do that.
Oh,crimeny.
Hey,jemma.
Guess you slipped out
pretty quietly this morning.
Anyway,looks like some
cash fell out of your purse.
But since it did,let me take you out.
Give me a call.
This is ray.
It's almost ready.
It smells good.
anything interesting?
Oh,sorry for snooping.
Just,I'm interested in your work.
That's part of a travel
series I did called "bombed."
"Bombed"?
You were bombed?
I was bombed,they were bombed.
The premise is I go to a war-torn
country and I get drunk with the locals.
Is that was I was?
Another drunk local?
No,you-- are
you kidding?
You were art.
What about you?
What's your process
like,you know,as a poet?
Mmm,I don't have a set process really.
Lately my work's been avoiding me.
How long's it been avoiding you for?
About two years.
Two years?
Yeah. I've been pretty blocked.
That's the most tragic
thing I ever heard.
I just-- I hate that,when people say
I'm a poet and they don't even write.
When I was a child I
was really prolific.
My adolescence was so fertile.
I hemorrhaged words.
So what stopped the bleeding?
I think it was my mother.
I can't believe we're doing this.
Don't you have a better
way to spend the weekend?
No. No I don'T.
You're my new pet project.
I'm a man on a mission.
We're gonna get you writing again.
You don't understand.
My mother's a bitter
academic. Always judges me.
So,poets need to suffer.
Okay,listen. Trust me.
This is going to work.
You grow as an artist every
time you walk through that door.
Come on.
Mother?
Hello?
Anyone home?
that right there is the
mother of my unborn child.
Really? The middle finger
to a man you just met?
I don't feel like we just met.
"Tanya skagle,state forensics champion."
Oh yeah,proud of it.
First place,dramatic interpretation.
Voted most likely to save the whales.
Oh yeah. I really dropped the
ball on those whales though.
Oh wait,see? This is from seventh grade.
The year I had really bad B.O. And
my mom wouldn't let me wear deodorant.
I wrote a poem about it.
"Indelible stench"?
You know... I used to dry hump
my neighbor jacob on this carpet.
You want me to show you how I did it?
Okay,he'd say go.
And then,like...
okay.
out of curiosity,did
jacob have any pubic hair?
Because I do,and I actually feel like
you're about to start a brush fire.
What,that doesn't do anything for you?
Hello? Is someone here?
Shit. Get up. Get up. Act natural.
Tanya? Is that you?
In my room.
How did I know it was tanya?
I followed the trail.
Dirt all the way up the stairs.
Hi,mom.
Tanya,again with the yearbooks?
Oh my god. She loves to take boys
up here and show them the yearbooks.
Hi,mrs. Skagle. I'm pierce.
So nice to meet you.
My goodness,he's a teenager.
What are you doing with
an old woman like tanya?
I am-- I'm fascinated
with your daughter.
That makes two of us.
New clients.
I told tanya I'd find some,but how
the hell was i supposed to do that?
How do you tell when
they're good and firm?
Have a nice day.
Being my own pimp.
It was a little harder than I thought.
Mmm,peach.
Smell nice.
Ray!
Jess.
Jesus,what are you doing here?
I was just... stocking up.
On flowers?
Yeah,I like flowers.
I thought you were a
meat and potatoes guy.
No. Not always.
No?
Things change,jess,sometimes.
How are you,ray?
Good. I'm good.
No,really. How are you?
I'm really good.
House is shaping up.
I think I met someone.
- Um,the woman at the game?
- Yeah.
- The blonde.
- I like blondes.
You always did.
Is that who you were
getting flowers for?
Yeah.
You should come by the house sometime.
You mean ronnie's house?
Hey,it's my house too.
Okay. Why?
For dinner.
With the kids and ronnie.
We do barbecues every sunday.
I've got a pretty busy schedule,but...
great. Anytime.
And every fucking friday
she has a fucking potluck.
But of course she wouldn't invite me
to her party of academics and artists.
Your mother is not the blockage,tanya.
She's the source. She is your muse.
No she isn't,pierce. No,she's the bane.
You were prolific under her roof.
So I need you to face your fear
and write a poem about your mother.
And we will go over and invite ourselves to her little
party and you will read it in front of all her fancy friends.
I mean that is-- that's
a creative breakthrough.
Can we talk about something else?
Sure,like what?
Now you're annoyed
with me all of a sudden?
no.
What makes you so different,rita chen?
I want the rita flower
to blossom,not wilt.
Can you excuse me for a second?
What's stopping you from
opening a car wash tomorrow?
An advisor? I'm willing
to be that advisor.
- Floyd.
- Tanya. What a surprise.
Tanya,this is one of my
promising new students rita chen.
Rita,this is one of my
old students tanya skagle.
So is this what you do?
You butter up your students
and you call them a flower?
Tanya,rita and I are in the
middle of a work session.
I'm sorry,is it rita?
Rita. Why don't you ask
him about his millions?
Ask him about his jaguar.
Watch it,sister.
Is everything okay over here?
All right,I think we need
to be alone right now.
But it's great to see you,tanya.
Yeah,well,fuck you,floyd.
jemma,hey.
Sorry I haven't called you earlier.
I've been slammed at work.
Oh,no worries.
Me too.
Listen,jemma.
I was-- I was meaning
to talk to you.
I mean... I like you.
And this money thing,it's kind of weird.
Look,I'm saying...
I'd like to date you,jemma.
So you want me to go on a
real date with you and,like...
then maybe I have sex
with you and maybe I don't?
well,I think we're a little
beyond the maybe part,but...
oh,ray drecker.
You know,when you get all soft and
serious it's very hard to turn you down.
Well,what would we do
on our first real date?
I was thinking we'd get
out of the city. You know?
Maybe go for a boat ride.
Maybe pack a picnic.
What do you say?
I think...
okay.
okay. Okay.
Tanya,I can't get you on the phone
so I guess I'll leave it here.
Look,I did try to drum
up some new business,okay?
But you're right.
It's a lot harder than I thought.
Hi,neighbor.
Anyway,I'm still trying.
I'm definitely not giving up,all right?
I just want you to know how
much I appreciate all the blood,
sweat and tears that you've been
putting into this-- into our project.
I liked your cookies.
Yeah,apparently not enough.
What?
I said I already got two more
citations from your husband since then,
so I guess it didn't do the trick,huh?
Yeah,my husband's kind of...obsessive.
By the way,I noticed your hot water
heater is just sitting over there.
I'll take care of it,all right?
No need to call anyone.
No no,I say this because I was wondering if
you wanted to take a hot shower at our place.
How would your husband feel about that?
Howard's out of town.
Come.
It sure is nice of you to let me
take a hot shower here,mrs.Koontz
look,ray,I am sorry
about those citations.
Howard,he shouldn't have
called the police,you know?
You need an
extra-- holy cow.
Excuse me. I-I-I-I-- I
swear to god,I'm sorry.
I-I wasn't--
shit,ray.
That is one beautiful penis.
Who knew you were hiding that next door?
Thank you,I think.
Ray,I was-- I was thinking,you know,we should
try looking out for each other,you and I.
Oh,what do you mean?
Like,I could take care of what you
need and you could take care of me.
I don't follow.
What do you mean? I scratch your back,you
scratch mine. How is this confusing?
I help you out.
And,uh,compensate me.
Is that right,mrs.Koontz?
Yes,ray.
Am I making you feel too dirty?
I'll live.
Hi,mrs. Skagle.
So sorry to interrupt your dinner party,but
we felt bad about eating your cookies.
So I baked you new ones. Chocolate chip.
What an unexpected delight.
Do these have little sayings in them?
No,mother. These have chocolate chips.
Look. In times of economic crisis,the
arts are the first thing to go.
I disagree.
People need art the most when
they are hungry and afraid.
That depends on your definition of art.
This was a bad idea.
I don't feel well. I feel feverish.
No,you're fine.
You're just terrified of
being judged by these people.
You know,it's not such a good thing
for your poetry to be such a coward.
I am not a coward!
Oh,come on,ray.
Come on,ray.
I want to see it big and happy.
What kind of bed is this?
A stearns & foster.
Why?
Because it's fucking
comfortable,that's why.
It's the pillow top.
Oh,honey,baby,you are beautiful.
I am. I work out seven days a week.
But howard likes to fuck in the dark.
Oh,what a waste.
Yeah.
It's
just--
oh god. Oh,it is a waste,ray.
I like to be looked at,you know?
I like to be seen.
Oh,god,I'm looking.
I am seeing.
Oh shit,ray.
oh shit,ray.
oh shit,ray!
My daughter baked these cookies.
She sometimes tucks a little
fortune into her baked goods.
But tonight
they're empty--
they're chip. I said
they're chip-- --
so you don't have to worry
about choking on any words.
actually,I did bring some
words for you to choke on.
It's a poem,actually.
Really?
Well,that's great.
Why don't you go ahead and stand up?
Oh,please,honey.
Please,take the floor.
Everyone,why don't we give
tanya our full attention?
I swear,she doesn't usually do this.
I haven't heard her poetry in 20 years.
"Says worker ant to queen...
how now,mother?
There you are
sealed in your chamber
away from the light
in this darkness I can see you, mother
but can you see me?
I am shaped in your same image
same fruited wings
same swollen belly
same brown flesh
same chip
same chink
you are blind to our efforts
can you find nothing in us to love?
We are shaped in your image,mother
look again look again."
thoughts?
It's vaguely reminiscent
of sylvia's "medusa."
Only in this case with ants.
Yes.
Its inherent sadness reminded me of a song
the girls of my village used to sing in uganda.
Oh,please,would you share it with us?
Please.
It's in swahili.
Oh,that's lovely.
I can't compete with this shit.
Hey,tanya!
tanya. Tanya,what--
what is wrong with you?
It sucked. My poem sucked.
Maybe.
But hey,you started writing again.
I didn't start anything.
I wrote that poem when I was 14.
I'm a failure.
It sucked then and it sucks now.
It actually wasn't that bad for 14.
I'm not 14,pierce.
I'm much much older.
I just-- I
want to go home.
I just want to go home.
So do you want to help
me out now or later?
What do you mean?
You know,what we discussed.
I take care of you,you take care of me.
Yes,ray,I promise.
No more citations. Okay?
I'll take care of it.
Right,citations.
Is that what you meant
by "take care of me"?
Yeah. What did you think I meant?
So I struck out as my own pimp.
But I've got to say,we
each got a bargain.
Cinderella had to work through blisters.
Cinderella endured two evil stepsisters
rapunzel killed 10,000 hours
up atop that locked up tower
it's not fair
that's a lot of solitaire
a lot of braiding her hair
it gets lonely up there...
Well,we missed the boat,as they say.
But no worries.
We'll just catch a later
one when you get here.
Little red riding hood was followed
little red riding hood's
grandmother was swallowed
sleeping beauty got sick from
her stepmom's wicked trick
it's not nice