[ splashing ]
Hey.
Sprinkler's busted again.
What?
The thing.
Oh. Look at that.
Well, I was wondering
why it was turning brown.
Yeah, the plastic ones --
they always break,
and then the whole system --
it's gonna go nuts on you.
You know, I'll pick up
a couple parts. I'll
come by and fix it.
No, it's all right.
I know how busy you are.
It's 10 minutes.
Right. Well,
I'll get a handyman, then.
No. Why a handyman?
I'll come on a Saturday --
Joe, I didn't come out here
to talk about the sprinklers!
Okay.
[ sighs ]
I'm sorry.
That's all right.
Go ahead. What's going on?
It's Lucy.
There's a boy
who's been bothering her.
Who?
The kid with the hair?
No, a different one --
Travis.
Travis?
Yeah, I thought he was nice,
but I guess it didn't work out,
and now he keeps calling her
and texting and...
of course,
she won't say anything to me,
but, you know, you hear
about these kids these days
who go off
the deep end, and...
Okay. All right. Yeah.
But, I mean, come on.
They're 17.
This is what happens.
It's just some drama.
No. Joe, Joe, this feels
really aggressive to me, okay?
Okay. All right.
Travis.
Not crazy
about the name.
Oh, my God, Joe.
Anyway, I'll just talk to her.
I'll ask her.
No! Oh, my God, no! That would
make her clam up even more.
All right,
I won't talk to her.
Yeah, well,
just pay attention to her
and, you know, let her know
you're there for her,
that we're there
for her.
Just monitor the situation,
okay? And I'll do the same.
(Lucy) Albert! Come on!
Okay? Just --
All right. I got it.
All right. Thanks.
Don't worry.
Don't bring anything up unless
she says something to you first.
I got it. I got it.
Okay. Thanks.
All right.
And just a warning --
she's been really moody.
Bye, mom.
Have a great day,
you guys!
Bye! [ chuckles ]
Hi.
Your hair looks nice.
No, it doesn't.
♫ Men of a Certain Age 1x05 ♫
Powerless
♪ when I grow up to be a man ♪
Original Air Date on January 4, 2010
♪ will I dig the same things
that turn me on as a kid? ♪
♪ will I look back and say that
I wish I hadn't done what I did? ♪
♪ will I joke around ♪
♪ and still dig those sounds ♪
♪ when I grow up to be a man? ♪
-- Sync, HI corrected by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.Com --
[ high-pitched whining ]
[ snoring lightly ]
[ whining stops ]
[ snorts ]
[ exhales sharply ]
[ groaning ]
[ sighs ]
300 bucks, my ass.
Come on!
[ sighs ]
[ alarm beeping ]
[ beeping stops ]
[ smooches ]
Did you break
my wave machine?
No. I set it.
[ exhales sharply ]
I thought it only made
rainforest sounds.
[ chuckles ]
Those make you
go to sleep.
They don't wake you up.
Exactly.
[ sighs ]
This is a much better way
to wake up.
Oh.
No, sorry, pal.
Nope.
I've got to go to work.
You got time.
No. Don't you start
at 10:00?
Uh, 10:00, 11:00.
Mm...Tomorrow.
Oh, must be nice.
Mmm-hmm.
Hmm.
[ grunts ]
Do you want
to have dinner?
Sure.
What time?
I don't know. Uh...
why don't I just
swing by your work later on
and we'll figure it out?
Okay.
I get off at 6:00.
Yeah, we'll figure it out.
Okay.
I'm done at 6:00.
[ rainforest sounds play ]
I fixed it.
(Michael)
Got you! Got you!
(Jamie) No, you didn't!
You got my shirt!
Boys!
Sit down, or I will
eat this breakfast myself!
[ boys laughing ]
Did you, uh,
blow a fuse or something?
Mnh-mnh. The electricians are
running power to the addition.
And apparently,
to do that,
they had to disconnect the whole
house from the main line.
Come on.
Wait -- the addition
is getting power?
As we speak.
They said it shouldn't take
more than an hour.
Sweetie, do you know
what this means?
Hmm?
We are almost done.
Done like done done?
Like done done.
I mean, they still have
things to do on their list,
but yeah.
Done done.
You know, I never thought
we'd see this day.
[ laughs ]
Come on!
Could you pick up a movie
for the boys on your
way home from work?
I'm about to strangle
those two.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll give you a --
Uh,
where are they going?
Supplies, I guess.
[ truck door slams ]
(Powers)
Mr. Thoreau?
Yeah?
Brent Powers -- Department
of Building and Safety.
And this is officer Kearns with
the County Sheriff's office.
And, uh, w-what can we do
for you gentlemen?
Well, sir, I'm afraid
we're here to shut
your construction down.
Excuse me?
Well, you're building
without a permit, Mr. Thoreau.
Our office
has red-tagged this site
four times
in the last month
to alert you that you were
not in compliance.
You know
anything about this?
No! No! Gunther didn't
say anything about red tags.
Yeah, our contractor
never said anything to us
about any problems.
[ clicks tongue ]
Oh.
Why? What's that?.
Well, sometimes
your less-scrupulous contractors
will simply rip the tags down
without alerting the homeowner.
Then they'll hit you up
with as many "surprise
bills" as they can
before we show up
to shut the site down.
Then they just disappear.
No,
this is not happening.
So, uh, what --
what do we do now?
Well,
all work has to stop
until an inspector can determine
the extent of the violations.
And then what happens?
Well, worst-case scenario --
the county could demand
that you tear down
any work that was done
and rebuild
with the proper permits.
All of it?
No, no --
just the new construction.
No, that's all of it.
Oh.
Uh... then yes.
Thank you.
Have a good day.
Hey, Maria.
Hey.
Oh.
We need, um,
more... miller.
miller?
You know,
the silver balloons.
Oh, mylar.
It's pronounced "my-lar."
We're out of it.
All right.
Hey, Maria...
You and, um...
you and -- and --
what's-her-name,
you guys --
you broke up, right?
Kaitlyn.
Yeah.
I'm just -- the only reason
I'm bringing it up
is 'cause my daughter, Lucy,
just broke up with this kid,
and he's taking it
kind of hard, you know,
and -- I don't know.
Did -- did Kaitlyn
ever get... clingy?
She ever, like,
couldn't let go?
Kaitlyn broke up
with me.
Oh.
I mean, not that --
not that --
it's different, though,
right?
I mean,
it probably is way different
'cause you guys
are both...
you're a girl. She's a girl.
It's different, right?
It's totally different.
All right.
My cousin --
she broke up with some guy,
and he came to her house
and killed her guinea pig.
Whoa!
Like, uh, "Fatal Attraction" --
the rabbit.
No, it wasn't a rabbit.
It was a guinea pig.
Yeah. Yeah,
no, I know, but...
You saw
"Fatal Attraction"?
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Yeah, but...
this was a guinea pig.
Anyway, I had a --
I broke up with a girl
in 6th grade,
and she, uh...
If I can remember
the quote --
ahe told everybody
I had no wiener.
I'd rather she killed my rabbit.
[ chuckles ]
I don't mean to make fun.
I'm just -- I'm just trying
to lighten it up.
All right.
Let's get some mylar.
2, 2, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0.
[ marker clatters ]
So, what's wrong
with you guys?
Why do I keep seeing customers
walking out of my showroom?
Don't start telling me anything
about the economy.
In 1979, during
the Arabian OPEC bullshit,
I sold more cars
than anyone else in this city.
And do you know how?
Because I could always, always
find "the key."
When you've got an up,
you don't just
show him the floor model
and ask about a trade-in.
Hell no.
You find the key.
You get inside of his brain.
You know all about
his old lady nagging him,
about how he's nose-deep
in crap-filled diapers.
You work the man.
You find the key.
You got it?
What if the guy's
not married?
Hey, what's going on?
Still no power
at the house.
Still?
I have left five messages
for Gunther.
I'll -- I'll make some calls
to the billing office downtown,
and, um, if the power's
not on by tonight, uh,
we'll just, uh,
check into a hotel.
We can't be spending money
on hotels --
not if we might have to
tear down the house.
What else
are we gonna do?
(Michael)
Grandpa!
Who let these rugrats
in here?
[ laughs ]
We're going to stay
at your house, grandpa!
Says who?
Mommy.
Oh. [ chuckles nervously ]
hi, guys.
Do you understand that my home
has no power?
Because my contractor's
an asshole, that's why!
No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I will not!
I will not change my tone!
Why don't you change --
why don't you change
and actually do something
that's helpful?
No, no, don't put me on hold.
Aaaaargh!
You know,
you watch him move like that,
and it's hard to believe
he's the child of a
professional athlete.
[ shouting ]
more contractor stuff?
I guess.
I don't know.
[ arguing indistinctly ]
I turned him on
to that guy.
He did the siding
on my building. It looks great.
Aaah, shit!
Oh-ho-ho!
Shit, shit!
He's gonna blame me
for this.
You watch.
Oh, yeah. Probably.
[ sighs ]
well, well, well.
Look who's here.
Morning, Laura.
Terrance.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
What?
When did that happen?
I don't know.
Couple weeks ago.
Turns out we both drove
VW buses in college.
Oh.
You should have a choke collar
on your dick.
[ chuckles ]
Hey.
Everything cool?
I don't want
to talk about it.
He's doing
the waitress.
What?
Yeah.
[ sighs ]
Which one?
The -- the tall one.
[ chuckles ] Why you got to shit
where we eat?
Oh, that's nice.
You know,
she's touching our food,
and she's been --
she's been near his business.
Whoa, whoa. Don't worry. We
always take a shower afterwards.
Gross.
What exactly
did you order me here?
Hey, you know, you're 20 minutes
late every time.
You can't complain
about what I order for you.
Hey, I'm not
20 minutes late.
All right, okay. All right, 15.
Sorry. You're early.
Man, my circadian rhythms
are out of whack.
Annie set the alarm
this morning, and --
Hold it. Annie?
So you got the waitress
and the 25-year-old?
I don't "got" anybody.
[ scoffs ] oh.
Anyway, Annie set the alarm
this morning,
which is a totally
unhealthy way to wake up.
So, from 8:00 to 11:00,
I fall straight back
into a rem sleep,
and then, bam!
Every nine minutes, I'm back up.
Yeah, I hate it when I can't
rem sleep through to 11:00.
Who are you kidding,
anyway?
You're up
every nine minutes
going, "I'm sleeping
with a 25-year-old!"
You're high-fiving
your penis.
All right, all right.
I don't expect you guys
to understand.
I get it.
I know why you like her.
She fills gaps, right?
What?
From "Rocky," man. That's, like,
the best scene in the movie.
Paulie says, "hey, why you
goin' out with my sister?"
And Rocky's like,
[ deep voice ] "I got gaps.
"she's got gaps.
You know,
together we fill gaps."
That's the best scene?
[ normal voice ]
mm-hmm.
In "Rocky"?
Yeah.
Not when he's jumping
at the top of the stairs
with his arms
in the air?
Or "cut me, Mick"?
How 'bout "cut me, mick"?
Or the meat, man!
He's punching the meat
and the music's playing?
"gonna fly now"!
That's the best scene.
No, that's what everybody thi--
that's the obvious, but it's --
That's not even
the best song.
Man, you're not --
nah, you don't get it.
"fills gaps" --
that's deep shit.
I could name
80 other scenes...
No.
... that people remember
more than that one.
Forget it, man.
Forget it.
What?
You know he's not gonna
change his mind.
And this is not
how I want to spend
the last part of my morning
before I go downtown
to convince
some asshole inspector
to let some asshole electrician
wire my house
so I can turn on
my asshole lights.
So, forget it.
Forget it.
Okay?
You know, if you want,
I-I can [sighs]
I can help you
get your lights on.
No, no, no. Look.
Two years of stage-lighting
classes in college.
You don't want to let
that knowledge go to waste.
No. No, thank you.
You've... done enough.
I told you
he'd blame me.
[ chuckles ]
This is, uh...
This is not good.
I don't even see
an application for a permit.
Uh, we think our contractor
was lying to us.
Was this
a, um, small job
that maybe you figured
you didn't need a permit for
and then
it turned into a big job?
No. It's the same size
it always was.
I mean,
we added a window
and a, um... portico
or whatever you call it,
but, um, no -- we weren't trying
to get away with anything,
if that's
what you're asking.
Well, I'm sorry,
Mr., uh, Thoreau,
but I'm afraid
I don't have the authority
to allow you
to resume construction.
Wait. You know what?
That's -- that's fine.
Hell, I'm happy
just to have a little break
from all the hammering.
All we really want to do
is get the electricity
in the main house back on.
Why was
the electricity off?
For the construction.
But -- but -- but we're not
gonna do any more work.
I wish I could help you,
but it's out of my hands.
And any changes
to the condition of your house
will be considered work
and then subject to more fines.
Believe me,
I'm just trying to save you
from even bigger headaches.
48.
[ Al Green's "let's stay
together" plays on radio ]
Yo!
What's up, buddy?
Oh, not much.
Where's Lucy?
Who's the guy
she's talking to?
Travis, I think.
Hey. You okay?
Uh-huh.
Yeah? You look
a little... flushed.
What does that even mean?
Oh, just -- you know.
Were you out in the sun
today?
Yeah, I-I guess so.
Yeah. That's --
that's probably it.
[ hums ]
Oh, good.
You found them.
Uh, yeah.
Thanks, mom.
Okay.
I'm going for a run.
Oh, yeah.
You enjoy that.
Owen, I didn't know
that you ran.
Not every night,
but, you know, when I need
to let off some steam.
You know, honey, your father
has plenty of friends downtown.
I'm sure he can
make a few calls
and get this all
taken care of.
Really?
The mayor's
brother-in-law --
he's been a customer
for years.
Yeah,
we can handle it, mom.
Uno!
Grandpa,
that's not fair!
What do you mean,
"it's not fair"?
If you let your cards out
for everybody to see,
you're gonna get stung.
Owen.
Be nice.
I'm supposed to
let him win?
The boy is 6 years old,
grandpa.
Well, he's not gonna be 6
forever, now, is he?
If you let them win now,
they'll think
the world owes them something.
[ chuckles ]
Can we go watch TV now?
Oh, no, no, no.
Loser has to shuffle.
So not gonna lose.
The point is to win.
Okay,
I'll be back in an hour.
An hour?
He can run
for a whole hour?
Mm-hmm.
Don't make to much noise
my neighbors call the cops
on a squirrel
that runs across the lawn.
Yeah, watch --
watch your step.
There's nails and crap
everywhere.
Oh. It's gonna be great
when it's done, huh?
Yeah. It was done
by a criminal.
And it might
all soon be gone.
What am I looking for?
The junction box.
Yeah.
What's it look like?
It -- [ sighs ]
Like a box.
Well, how am I supposed to
know that? I'm a car salesman.
[ chuckling ]
Well, I don't sell cars,
but if you ask me
to find a wheel,
I'm gonna go
with something round.
Just turn
my damn lights on!
[ laughs ]
(Albert) So, I'm not saying I'm
the fastest kid in my gym class,
but I'm at least
in the top eight.
Eight?
Usually when you say a top,
you round it out to, like, 10.
But I'm better
than that.
I mean, if I said "top 10,"
you'd think I was 10.
I'm not.
I'm eight.
Yeah, I get it. I get it.
That's pretty good.
Hey, come on,
thumbelina.
We were gonna put it down
during dinner, right?
Yeah, I am.
Just...A second.
And... done.
Happy?
Yeah. Yeah.
Now, let's -- come on.
Let's talk a little.
I got to pee.
I had two large cokes.
And I licked
all my fries, Albert.
Albert, let me
ask you something --
What do you know
about this Travis guy?
I don't know.
I mean, do you see him
around school? Is he a nice guy?
Yeah, usually.
I guess last week,
he called Lucy a whore.
What?!
Agh! Brain freeze!
What do you mean?
It's like nails
in my eyeballs!
[ cellphone chirps ]
[ whimpering ]
Albert, how do you --
how do you --
How do you open this?
To do what?
I don't know. I don't know.
Just read them.
All of them?
Yeah, yeah. What --
unlock it.
[ beeping ]
What do you think
you're doing?
He had
one of your fries.
Whoa.
All that happened
in the bathroom?
Yeah, I'm just...
A friend of mine is supposed to
swing by and pick me up.
Is it the old guy?
Yeah, the old guy.
[ dog barking in distance ]
You know, if it was just me,
I could handle it. You know?
I'm used to it.
But when he starts
dropping that shit on my kids?
Man --
just hold the light up,
would you?
So, how'd you get
out of the house?
I told them
I was going for a run.
And they bought that?
[ laughs ]
Anyway, thanks for coming out
so quick.
You're saving my ass.
You kidding me?
You saved mine.
Laura from the diner
came by after work,
and I swear to God,
if you hadn't called,
I might have been
cuddled to death.
Okay.
So, here we go.
We got the black --
positive.
Red, positive.
They got this green one
going...
What the hell.
I'll just put it there.
Terry.
Now, whoa. Terry.
Terry, come on, man! If you
don't know what you're do--
[ click ]
Eh?
Son of a bitch.
[ laughs ]
Huh?
Wow.
Who knew that you could
actually do shit?
Surprised the hell
out of me.
(Officer)
All right, guys.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Wait right there.
Keep your hands up.
No, no. No, officer,
this is -- this is my house.
We just had a little
electrical problem.
Let me see some I.D.
Yeah.
And move slowly.
Sure.
No -- no problem.
[ police radio chatter ]
Oh.
What?
These are not my shorts.
Aw, shit.
[ car door slams ]
Really?
They got to cuff us?
Well, they don't know.
We could have been
breaking and entering.
Breaking into what?
We walked in
through a plastic sheet.
Hey,
what time is it?
Hmm?
Aah!
7:30.
Shit!
What the hell --
what is wrong with you, man?
Ah, I was supposed to pick up
Annie an hour ago for dinner.
Ohhhh.
It's -- it's fine.
Oh, good.
Well, maybe now she'll realize
she's dating a dick.
Why am I a dick?
Because only a dick
goes straight from banging
a waitress all afternoon
to dinner with
his 25-year-old girlfriend.
Okay, first of all,
she's not my girlfriend.
neither is Laura.
And I have been totally up front
with both of them
about how I feel about all this,
and they're okay with it.
Oh, so they know
about each other?
[ chuckling nervously ]
What difference
does it make?
They're happy.
I'm happy.
The only one who's not happy
about the whole thing is you.
Of course, you're not happy
about anything lately.
I can't remember the last time
we had a hike or went to lunch
when you weren't bitching
about your life.
"my dad's too tough on me.
The kids are up all night.
The contractor's screwing me."
blah, blah, blah.
That's your fault! You told me
Gunther did great work!
He does do great work!
How am I supposed to know
he does it without a permit?
Look, I didn't hire him.
I just live in the building.
Geez! Man!
Take some responsibility!
You're telling me
about taking responsibility?
You can't even be on time
for shit you want to be at!
Oh, no, no, no.
Not the same. Not the same.
You know
why you're always late?
'cause I know why.
I know exactly why.
Really?
I got a whole theory
about it.
Well, please enlighten me,
o great buddha.
When you're late,
all you can think about
is getting to where
you're trying to go --
Traffic, lights,
whatever.
You got no room in your head
for anything else.
But if you're early,
you're not thinking
about that stuff.
Your brain's not occupied
that way.
So your mind drifts.
Maybe you start thinking,
you know, inward --
about your life,
who you are, whatnot.
But you don't want
to do that.
The last thing you want
is to look in the mirror
and ask,
"who are you, Terry?"
Because then
you might start thinking
about exactly who you are
and what you're doing
with your life.
That's why
you're late all the time.
Well, thank you.
Yeah.
That's for free.
Yeah, but you forgot
one thing.
What's that?
The only reason
I'm late right now
is because
I was helping you.
[ sighs ]
[ radio chatter continues ]
I don't care why!
You have no right
to go through my stuff!
[ door slams ]
Sorry.
It's my fault.
Oh, I should never
have told you about this.
What? No, no. You have to
tell me this stuff, okay?
We got to figure this out
together. Don't --
I don't want to worry
that you're not gonna
include me in this stuff.
Yeah, you know what --
I'm sorry, Joe,
but I did include you,
and look what happened.
Did you know
Travis called Lucy a whore?
What?
Yeah.
That's why -- that's...
Was that in the text?
No. Albert --
he heard about it at school.
But that's why
I was looking --
to try to see
what else he's saying to her.
Which I would have
found out
if her phone
wasn't a damn rubik's cube.
Why didn't she
tell me that?
I don't...
I don't know.
Even when we were together,
I'd feel like I didn't know
what was going on with her
and all that.
Now it just...
[ sighs ]
Look, I don't know
if she's not talking
to me and that's normal,
or if there's something else
going on
because of, you know...
... us.
No, no, no.
Look, it's okay.
It's all right.
We'll figure this all out.
Yeah, okay.
It's all right.
Well, we're definitely
getting her a new phone,
because that thing's
a nightmare.
Right? You couldn't
figure it out, either.
It's impossible.
Soon they're all gonna have
the gps-tracking thing.
Oh, we're getting
that shit.
[ laughs ]
(Sharon)
All we were saying is --
Okay. They're down.
Phew!
So, if it comes up,
I was helping those cops
to look for a dog.
Your father and I
have talked it over,
and we feel like the best way
to handle this situation
is for you
to just pay the fines
and do whatever it takes
to get the job finished.
Well, we may have to rebuild,
and we can't afford that.
If it comes to that,
we'll cover it.
But you two
need a home to live in.
Mom,
that's very kind of you,
but, uh, I'm telling you --
we can handle it.
Your way of "handling it"
almost got you thrown in jail,
today, son,
which is where
you would have been
if they hadn't
recognized me.
What would you
have me do, dad?
Sit here and watch you
make my kids cry at cards?
Melissa,
talk to your husband.
Sharon,
I'm going to bed.
[ grunts ]
Would you just please
think about it?
If they help us,
he will never let me forget it.
You know that.
I do know the man,
yes.
We didn't do
anything wrong.
Honey, I don't think
that's the point anymore.
Well, what, then?
What do we do?
I don't know.
Go downtown again.
They don't want to help you
down there.
All they want to do is
check your name off some list
so -- so it looks like
they did something.
Look, you're --
you're a salesman, right?
So go do some selling.
Find the key.
You know that's bullshit,
right?
Then we're gonna be
spending a hell of a lot more
time with your parents.
[ engine turns over ]
[ engine shuts off ]
Aaah!
Open up.
Did you call my daughter
a whore?
No.
'cause I got to tell you,
as a parent,
that's not the kind of thing
you want to hear.
I didn't call her that.
Really?
'cause I heard you did.
Well, I didn't.
This is stupid.
I'm gonna get Lucy.
We're gonna
straighten all this out.
What?! No, wait!
What?
She dumped me, okay?
And...I don't know.
I...
I kind of lost my mind,
and I got angry.
And when I tried to make her
talk to me about it...
... I called her a whore.
But it was because
she wouldn't let me talk.
It's not because
she's actually like a whore
or anything like that.
I swear.
I mean,
even if she was a whore,
I'd still, you know...
[ voice breaking ]
she's just...
she's so great.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
All right, just calm down.
I just wanted her
to like me again.
I wanted everything
to be the way it was.
Look, you're --
you're in high school.
This is --
it's what happens.
No.
It's not like that.
Like,
when we were together,
it was...
[ sighs ]
I was...
I don't know.
She fills gaps, right?
Huh?
Gaps.
You've got gaps.
She's got gaps.
And when
you're together...
you fill gaps.
Yeah.
Yeah. I guess.
You remember that?
From "Rocky"?
What's "Rocky"?
Doesn't matter.
It's just -- look.
I get it.
So, what now?
Everything go back
to sucking?
Yeah, pretty much.
Not forever, though.
Feels like forever.
Look, Travis...
it's hard. I know.
It's hard.
You found somebody special.
Yeah.
And -- and --
and you probably thought
you're gonna spend
the rest of your life with her.
Yeah.
Yeah, and -- and --
and you think,
"boy, I'm never gonna find
anybody like this ever again."
That's how you feel.
I don't have
any magic words, but...
all I can tell you
is sometimes you got to feel
as bad as you possibly can
before you feel better.
And...
you will --
you're gonna find somebody.
You're gonna meet somebody
again.
I know you don't believe me
right now, but...
you will.
And you know what?
Maybe the next one --
maybe that's --
maybe that's the girl
you're gonna marry.
And who knows?
You may have a daughter
one day,
and there may be a boy
who falls in love with her,
and he may
call her a name.
And you're gonna have
this moment right here.
You know what you're probably
gonna say to that kid?
You're gonna say,
"hey, kid,
"I know you're gonna do
the right thing.
'cause if you don't,
I'm gonna kick your ass."
That's probably
what you're gonna say.
Yeah. Yeah, okay.
Okay.
All right.
Drive safe, Trav.
[ engine turns over ]
[ tires squeal ]
[ indistinct conversations ]
Hey.
[ chuckles ]
I'm so sorry
about last night.
I got
the craziest story.
I wish I had time
to hear it.
I tried to call you later,
but -- but you never answered.
Yeah, I wasn't there.
I made plans with some people,
and I kept them.
Okay, look, um...
[ clears throat ]
I know we were kind of
supposed to have dinner,
but we were keeping it
kind of loosey-goosey.
No. You were keeping it
loosey-goosey.
I was getting off at 6:00
and then waiting until 7:30.
Look, I-I was arrested.
What?
I was trying to help
a friend of mine
turn the lights back on
at his house.
Then the police showed up,
and -- and...
the story's actually
really boring, but it's real.
Okay, then.
O... kay, then.
So...
Uh, you want to try again
tonight?
At an actual time
or "loosey-goosey"?
Look, I feel like I've been...
[ clears throat ]
... pretty up front
about me and relationships.
And...You know...
As far as commitment goes,
I'm not --
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
No one's
talking about that.
Look,
I like being with you.
And I don't care about
spending every night with you,
or even
every other night.
But on the nights that we say
we're gonna be together,
I need to know
that you give a shit.
Can you handle that?
Absolutely.
Good.
Okay.
So...
[ clears throat ]
Tonight?
I get off at 6:00.
You want
to write it down?
Yeah, you know,
maybe I better.
[ "going the distance"
from "Rocky" plays ]
Right? "Rocky."
"gonna fly now"
gets all the press,
but this is the one
that gets you right here.
Hey, you know, Maria,
I meant to tell you --
I know you got a lot of things
going on in your life,
and, you know, it can
get complicated and all,
and I just --
just want you to know,
if you need it, you can always
come to me, you know?
I mean, my door is always open
for you guys.
Okay.
[ rapping ]
♪ I got this song in my head
that I just can't stand ♪
♪ with this beat
that comes from a foreign land ♪
♪ might be sweden
or venezuela -- ♪
Don't ruin it, Dashaun.
(Man)
81!
It's me again.
I notice you don't get
a lot of chances
to get up
from that desk.
I thought
you might get thirsty.
Uh, sir, I told you I've done
everything I could possibly do.
Well, I know you have,
and I appreciate it.
The thing is,
I can see you're a clever guy,
and I thought
between the two of us,
we could maybe come up
with another solution --
something that, uh,
makes sense.
five minutes --
that's all I'm asking.
Hey, um...
you know, my father
played for the Lakers.
Oh. That.
That's, uh,
that's my boss Tim's.
He's a --
he's a huge Lakers fan.
Me, I'm, uh...
More of a football guy.
I got to hand it to you --
you really work.
I mean,
a lot of people,
they show up and fart around
most of the day.
But what you do?
This -- psh! This is work.
Look, uh...
Mr. Thoreau...
I appreciate the compliments
and the effort,
um...
but I'll say it again --
there is nothing more
I can do for you.
If I could, I would give you
the permits right now.
But this is
the City of Los Angeles.
Did you know I can't even
decorate my own work area?
I like plants.
Man.
Okay, man.
I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry.
I get it.
I've been working for my old man
for 20 years, so...
Boy, do I get it.
20 years of showing up,
sitting at my desk,
and trying to fool myself
into believing
that I actually
wanted to be there.
One time...
I tried
to get from under it.
23 years old.
I had this plan
to open my own record store.
I found a place.
I borrowed
one of my dad's ties
and went in and actually
convinced some loan officer
to give me $10,000.
Mm. [ laughs ]
Back then, it might as well
have been a million.
I couldn't believe it.
And I took that check
straight from the bank,
and I dropped it
on the old man's desk.
I was bouncing
off the walls.
I was telling him,
"I'm gonna make my own name,
be my own boss."
You know,
do it the way he did it.
I thought he'd respect me
for it, you know?
He just
folded up that check,
Stuck it in my pocket,
and said...
"you'll be back."
No "good luck"
or, um...
"don't skimp
on those payroll taxes."
Just...
"you'll be back."
And a year later,
when I was sitting
on a mountain of vinyl
and every kid in the world
decided to buy a cd player,
he was right.
[ chuckles ]
I was back.
Just like now,
when I tell him how deep
I'm gonna be into this house,
when I got to go to him
for the money for it.
He'll be right again.
And I'll be back.
You got a father?
[ horn honking in distance ]
[ chuckles ]
Plenty of time.
[ horn honking in distance ]
Who are you, Terry?
[ horn honks in distance ]
[ laughs ]
Oh, no.
No, no!
You piece of shit!
[ horn honks ]
Come on!
come o--
[ tires squeal ]
Hey! Here!
We don't open
till 7:00.
I don't care!
Ooh!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
My bad. My bad.
No shit your bad,
dickhead!
Dude, you are saving my life
right now.
No problem.
[ panting ]
Three minutes. Three...
Shit.
Hey.
Traffic was no good.
Um...
[ sighs ]
I'm sorry.
We're not riding bikes
to dinner, are we?
Actually, uh, yeah.
I guess I didn't tell you --
I've gone totally green.
Wow!
Yeah. Yeah.
Let me ask you --
You ever look in the mirror
and ask, "who are you?"
No.
No, me neither.
[ "going the distance"
from "Rocky" plays ]
-- Sync, HI corrected by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.Com --