ACT I
What are you doing up?
It's 3:30.
It's the seventh night this week
I've sat 'til morning.
Great. Here we go.
Imagining the ways
You might have died.
Ah, yes, and tonight's winner is...
In a freak September
Ice storm without warning...
Because that happens.
There's a gang war;
There's a bird flu; trains collide.
What did we say about
Watching the news?
Now you act all sweet and surly
But you swore you'd come home early,
And you lied.
You've got to let go, Mom.
I'm almost eighteen.
Are you snorting coke?
Not at the moment.
Who's up at this hour?
Your father. Go. Up the back way.
Why does he hate me?
Because you're a little twat.
You can't call me a twat.
Everything okay?
I heard voices.
Just me talking to myself, you know.
Now you head on upstairs.
I'll be up for sex in a minute.
Uh, are you sure you're okay?
Go.
[ 1. Just Another Day ]
They're the perfect loving family,
So adoring
And I love them everyday
Of every week
So my son's a little shit,
My husband's boring
And my daughter, though a genius,
Is a freak
Still I help them love each other
Father, mother, sister, brother
Cheek to cheek
Natalie! It's four in the morning;
Is everything okay?
Everything's great.
Why wouldn't it be great?
It's great.
I've just three more chapters of calculus,
A physics problem, that history quiz,
And two pages on floral imagery in
"Flowers for Algernon", which is,
Like... duh... everything's so under control.
It's just, like, calm.
Honey, you need to slow down.
Take some time for yourself.
I'm going to have sex with your father.
Great. Thanks. I'm so glad I know that.
So it's times like these
I wonder how I take it
And if other families live
The way we do
If they love each other
Or if they just fake it
And if other daughters
Feel like I feel, too
'Cause some days
I think I'm dying
But I'm really only trying
To get through
For just another day
For another stolen hour
When the world will feel
My power and obey
It's just another day
Feeling like I'll live forever
Feeling like this feeling never goes away
For just another day
That was great, wasn't it?
That was great. Christ, I'm late.
Well, that'll teach you to take a whole ten minutes.
Sorry, what?
I said, isn't it a beautiful day?
Okay, sure. I mean, it's cloudy and rainy
And really cold for September, but... beautiful.
Makes you wanna dive in with both feet, doesn't it?
Absolutely.
I never know what she's talking about.
When it's up to you
To hold your house together
A house you built
With patience and with care
But you're grappling
With that gray and rainy weather
And you're living on a latte and a prayer
Prayer
Can you keep the cup from tipping?
Can you keep your grip from slipping
In despair
In despair?
For just another day
In the hustle
And the hurry
You want to wipe your worried pain away
For just another day.
I will keep the plates
All spinning.
With a smile so white
And winning all the way
Cause what doesn't kill me
Doesn't kill me
So fill me up
For just another day.
It only hurts
When I'm here
You're going to be late
And you have a huge day.
You have no idea
What I do all day.
Jazz band before school.
Class. Key Club. Then football.
Not bad.
Now get out of here.
It only hurts when he goes.
Bum bum bum.
Good morning, Sunshine.
So, I got the date for my winter recital.
Do you think you guys can come?
We'll put it on the calendar!
Mom, the calendar is still
On April of last year.
Oh. Well, happy Easter.
Happy Easter, Mom.
Hi, sweetheart.
She is on fire this morning.
Oh, I know.
Eww.
Hon, will you do the shopping today?
I'm slammed at work
And we're out of everything.
I keep cave clean,
You go out get fire.
Absolutely. Again, no clue.
It only hurts when I breathe
It only hurts when I try
It only hurts when I think
It only hurts when I cry
It only hurts when I work
It only hurts when I play
It only hurts when I move
It only hurts when I say
It's just another day
A busy, busy day
And the morning sun is stunning.
I will hold it all together
And you wished that
You were running far away.
And I'll hide the mess away
It's just another day
I'll survive another day
Birds are singing, things are growing
And I will pray to hold on just this way
And you wish that you'd be going
But you stay stay stay.
It's for my family's sake.
I'll take what I can take
And you know that for forever
I'm only just awake
Every day is just another
And another and another
I will hold it all together,
We're the perfect loving family
If they say we're not, then fuck 'em
I will keep the plates all spinning
And the world just keeps on spinning
I think the house is spinning...
Diana, honey.
Dad...
Don't worry about it.
Go on ahead, you'll miss the bus.
Mom...
Everything's fine.
I'm just... making sandwiches.
On the floor.
You go on ahead, you'll miss the bus.
Go.
Sweetie, everything okay?
I wanted to get ahead on lunches.
Sure. Let me help you up.
Guess I got carried away.
Maybe a little.
Let's go see Docter Fine.
This is just a blip, okay?
Nothing to worry about.
I'll wrap up the, uh, sandwiches
And then we'll go.
[ 2. Everything Else ]
Mozart was crazy
Flat fucking crazy
Bad shit, I hear
But his music's not crazy
It's balanced, it's nimble
It's crystalline clear
There's harmony, logic
You listen to these
You don't hear his doubts
Or his debts or disease
You scan through the score
And put fingers on keys
And you play
And everything else goes away
Everything else goes away
And you play 'til it's perfect
You play 'til you ache
You play 'til the strings
Or your fingernails break
So you'll rock that recital
And get into Yale
So you won't feel so sick
And you won't look so pale
'Cause you've got your full ride
And your early admit
So you're done with this school
And with all of this shit
And you graduate early
You're gone as of May
And there's nothing
Your paranoid parents can say
And you know that
It's just a sonata away
And you play
And everything else goes away
Everything else goes away
Everything...
Sounds good.
I still have this practice room
For seven and a half minutes.
Yeah. I mean, I know, I just like to listen.
I'm Henry.
Natalie.
Yeah. I mean, I know.
It's a little creepy that you know.
We've gone to school together
For, like, six years.
I sit behind you in,
Like, four classes.
Also creepy.
You're in here a lot.
Before school and after.
Right. Seven minutes.
You give up way too easily.
Umm, you're kind of a confusing person.
You should meet my mother.
[ 3. Who's Crazy?/
My Psychopharmacologist and I ]
The pink ones are taken with food,
But not with the white ones.
The white ones are taken
With the round yellow ones
But not the triangle yellow ones.
The triangle yellow ones are taken
With the oblong green one -
With food, but not with the pink ones.
If a train is leaving New York at 1:20
And a train is leaving Saint Petersburg
At the same time
Going backwards...
Who's crazy,
The husband or wife?
Who's crazy
To live their whole life
Believing that somehow things aren't
As bizarre as they are?
Who's crazy,
The one who can't cope,
Or maybe
The one who'll still hope?
The one who sees doctors
Or the one who just waits in the car?
And I was a wild twenty-five
And I loved a wife so alive
But now I believe I would settle
For one who can drive
The round blue ones with food
But not with the oblong white ones.
The white ones with the round yellow ones
But not the trapezoidal green ones.
Split the green ones into thirds
With a tiny chisel...
My psychopharmacologist and I
It's like an odd romance
Intense and very intimate
We do our dance
My psychopharmacologist and I
Call it a lover's game
He knows my deepest secrets
I know his name
And though he'll never hold me
He'll always take my calls
It's truly like
He told me
Without a little lift
The ballerina falls
Goodman, Diana.
Bipolar depressive with delusional episodes.
Sixteen year history of medication,
Adjustment after one week.
I've got less anxiety,
But I have headaches, blurry vision,
And I can't feel my toes.
So, we'll try again
And eventually we'll get it right.
Not a very exact science, is it?
Zoloft and Paxil and Buspar and Xanax,
Depacon, Chronaphin, Ambien, Prozac
Ativan calms me when I see the bills
These are a few of my favorite pills
Oh! Thank you, doctor.
Valium is my favorite color.
How'd you know?
It's just that, the thing with jazz...
How do you know you got it right.
It's just making shit up.
Which is also known as the act of creation.
Oh, you're one of those
Pretentious stoner types.
That's totally unfair.
I'm not pretentious.
I'm definitely not classical.
It's so rigid and structured.
There's no room for improvisation.
You have to play the notes on the page
Yeah, and what did Mozart know anyway?
He should've just smoked a bowl
And jammed on "Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star."
Yeah, let's do that!
Goodman, Diana:
Second adjustment after three weeks.
Delusions less frequent,
But depressive state worse.
I'm nauseous and I'm constipated;
I've completely lost my appetite
And gained six pounds,
Which, you know, is just not fair.
May cause the following side effects,
One or more -
Dizziness, drowsiness,
Sexual dysfunction,
Headaches and tremors, nightmares and seizures,
Constipation, nervous laughter, palpitations,
Anxiousness, anger,
Exhaustion, insomnia, irritability,
Nausea, vomiting
Odd and alarming sexual feelings
Oh, and one last thing -
Use may be fatal.
Goodman, Diana:
Third adjustment after five weeks.
Reports continue: mild anxiety
And some lingering depression.
I now can't feel my fingers or my toes.
I sweat profusely for no reason.
I have wasted, like, weeks of practice
With you here improvising.
Oscar Peterson was classically trained.
Beethoven did cocaine.
Miles Davis went to Juilliard.
Mozart wrote poems about farts.
Fortunately, I have absolutely
No desire for sex.
Although, whether that's the medicine
Or the marriage is anybody's guess.
I'm sure it's the medicine.
Oh, thank you.
That's very sweet,
But my husband's waiting in the car.
Who's crazy,
The one who's half gone
Or maybe
The one who holds on
Remembering when she was twenty
And brilliant and bold
And I was so young and so dumb
And now I am old
And she was wicked and wired
And though he'll never hold me
The sex was simply inspired
He'll always take my calls
Now there's no sex, she's depressed
It's truly like he told me
And me, I'm just tired, tired, tired, tired
Without a little lift the ballerina falls
Who's crazy
My psychopharmacologist
The one who's uncured
and I...
Or maybe the one who's implored
He's at every sight I lie
The one who has treatment,
Without you I'd die
Or the one who just deals with the pain
My psychopharmacologist and I...
They say love is blind...
But believe me, love is insane.
Goodman, Diana: Seven weeks.
I don't feel like myself.
I mean, I don't feel anything.
Hmm. Patient stable.
Your mom is,
Like, in the next room.
She's in denial.
It's totally convenient.
Dude, it's therapeutic!
Right.
It's medical marijuana to treat your ADD.
Totally. Huh?
I don't put anything into my mouth
That's on fire.
I guess that's a good rule.
Look, I can't do this!
Not with my life.
I'm, like, one fuck-up from disaster.
Your life is not a disaster.
The environment is a disaster.
Sprint is a disaster.
You're stoned.
[ 4. Perfect for You ]
Our planet is poisoned
The oceans, the air
Around and beneath
And above you
Umm, Henry, that's true
And I totally care
I'm trying to tell you I love you
What?!
The world is at war
Filled with death and disease
We dance on the edge
Of destruction
The globe's getting warmer
By deadly degrees
And this is one
Fucked up seduction
This planet is pretty much broken
Beyond all repair
But one thing is working
If you're standing there
Perfect for you,
I could be perfect for you
I might be lazy, a loner,
A bit of a stoner - it's true
But I might be perfect for you,
I'll make myself perfect, perfect for
You square all the corners,
I straighten the curves
You've got some nerve, Henry
And I'm just all nerve
But even if everything else
Turns to dirt
We'll be the one thing
In this world that won't hurt
I can't fix what's fucked up
But one thing I know I can do
I can be perfect for you
Perfect for you
Nice house.
Can I come in?
Oh, no.
Okay.
Are you spying on your own daughter?
When did she get a boyfriend?
How did I miss this?
Well, you kind of miss a lot.
Do you think they're in love?
Who knows? They're young.
They're horny.
It happens.
Marry me!
What?
Marry me.
Let's have a family.
I know we're too young,
But we're not.
I'm almost 22,
And how do you know
This isn't a sign
Saying we belong together?
How do you know it's not a sign
Saying "get new rubbers"?
Because I know it's not.
I love you... and this baby!
Dan. This is crazy.
Maybe it is.
[ 5. I Miss the Mountains ]
There was a time when I flew higher
Was a time the wild girl running free
Would be me
Now I see her feel the fire
Now I know she needs me there to share
I'm nowhere
All these blank and tranquil years
Seems they've dried up all my tears
And while she runs free and fast
Seems my wild days are past
But I miss the mountains
I miss the dizzy heights
All the manic, magic days
And the dark, depressing nights
I miss the mountains
I miss the highs and lows
All the climbing, all the falling
All the while the wild wind blows
Stinging you with snow
And soaking you with rain
I miss the mountains
I miss the pain
Mountains make you crazy
Here it's safe and sound
My mind is somewhere hazy
My feet are on the ground
Everything is balanced here
And on an even keel
Everything is perfect
Nothing's real
And I miss the mountains
I miss lowly climb
Wandering through the wilderness
And spending all my time
Where the air is clear
And cuts you like a knife
I miss the mountains
I, I miss the mountains
I miss my life
Are you sure about this, Mom?
Do you think it's a bad idea?
I think it's a great idea.
I think you're brave.
What will your father think?
Nothing. He doesn't know.
[ 6. It's Gonna Be Good. ]
It's gonna be good
Good, good
G-O-O-D, good
It's gonna be good
Uh-huh
Mmm-mmm
Two weeks and its all working
Just the way I knew it would
And I don't sit and work
Just waiting
For the phone to ring
Ring
It's a good, good, good, good thing
Ring,
Ring
Hello? Oh! Hi, sweetie!
Everything's great here -
Fantastic!
I disinfected the entire house,
Rewired the computer
And did some decoupage.
Okay, bye-bye.
Hmm... next, I think I'll retile the roof.
Its gonna great
Great
Fucking great
The sex is still amazing
And we don't stay up that late
It's almost been a month
Oooo
And she's happy as a clam
Happy as a clam
Do I look great?
I am!
I'd invite you in,
But it's too soon.
We've been going out
For nine weeks and three days.
Don't I get to meet your family?
You keep count?
You're so the girl.
And no.
Natalie.
And this must be Harry.
It's Henry.
Pleasure to finally meet you.
Come in. Why don't you come in
And join us for dinner?
Umm, Dad, Henry can't really stay.
He's got... uh...
It's gonna be good
Homework!
Surgery!
We'll sit right down together
Like a happy family should
Rabies!
We'll eat and talk and laugh and joke
My pride my brood and me
It's gonna be good you'll see
We'll smile and chat
And just like that
It'll all me all okay
Its gonna be great
Its gonna be gonna be gonna be
Great that way
Its gonna be good
Its gonna good
We'll sit right down together
Like a happy family should
And eat and talk and laugh
And joke my family and me
Its gonna be good gonna be good
Gonna be gonna be gonna be
Gonna be gonna be
Good good good good good
Gonna be good, gonna be good
Gonna be good you'll see.
Okay, it's someone's birthday!
Whose birthday is it?
My brother's.
I didn't know you had a brother.
I don't.
He died before I was born.
[ 7. He's Not Here. ]
What? What is it?
He's not here
Love, I know you know
Do you feel he's still real?
Love, it's just not so
Why is it you still believe?
Do you dream or do you grieve?
You've got to let him go
He's been dead all these years
No, my love, he's not here.
This is fucked.
Language.
Fuck this!
It was wonderful to meet you both.
What about the new meds?
We have the happiest
Septic tank on the block.
Jesus, Di...
They were working.
They weren't really.
We'll get a new round.
We'll call Doctor Fine...
NO!
Diana, look, I know this is hard.
[ 8. You Don't Know/I Am the One]
Do you know? Really?
What exactly do you know?
I know that you're hurting.
I'm hurting, too.
Do you wake up in the morning
And need help to lift your head?
Do you read obituaries
And feel jealous of the dead?
It's like living on a cliff-side
Not knowing when you'll dive
Do you know, do you know
What it's like to die alive?
When a world that once had color
Fades to white and grey and black
When tomorrow terrifies you
But you'll die if you look back
You don't know
I know you don't know
You say that you're hurting
It sure doesn't show
You don't know
It lays me so low
When you say "let go"
And I say "you don't know"
The sensation that you're screaming
But you never make a sound
Or the feeling that you're falling
But you never hit the ground
It just keeps on rushing at you
Day by day by day by day
You don't know, you don't know
What it's like to live that way
Like a refugee, a fugitive
Forever on the run
If it gets me it will kill me
But I don't know what I've done
Can you tell me
What it is you're afraid of?
Why I'm afraid it's me?
Can I touch you?
We've been fine for so long now
How can something go wrong
That I can't see?
Cause I'm holding on
And I won't let go
I just thought
You should know
I am the one who knows you
I am the one who cares
I am the one who's always been there
I am the one who's helped you
And if you think that
I just don't give a damn
Then you just don't know
Who I am
Could you leave me?
Hey Dad, it's me
Could you let me go under?
Why can't you see?
Will you watch as I drown and wonder why?
And wonder why
Are you bleeding?
Are you waiting?
Are you wishing?
Are you wanting all that she can't give?
Are you bruised?
Are you broken?
Are you hurting?
Are you healing?
Are you hoping for a life to live?
Does it help you to know
Well, so am I?
Well, so am I!
Tell me what to do
Look at me
Tell me who to be
So I can see what you see
And you'll see
I am the one who holds you
I am
I am the one who'll stay
I am the one who won't walk away
I won't walk away
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I am the one who'll hear you
I am
And now you tell me
That I won't give a damn
You do give a damn
But I know you know who I am
Who I am
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
That's who I am
I am
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
That's who I am
I am
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
That's who I am
'Cause I'm holding on
You say you hurt like me
And I won't let go
You say that you know
Yeah, I though you should know
You don't know
I am the one who knows you
I know you don't know
I am the one who cares
You say that you're hurting
I am the one who's always been there
I know it ain't so
Yeah, yeah, yeah
You don't know
I am the one who needs you
Why don't you just go?
And now you think that I just
Please go
Don't give a damn
And I'm saying
Then you just don't know who I am
You don't know
Who I am
You just don't know who I am
When she gets like this,
She's useless.
She can't use the phone,
Can't drive.
I bet she's got great pills.
I mean, not that I'd go there.
That shit's inorganic.
And totally ineffective, apparently.
I'm old-school - dying breed.
All the preppies and the jocks
Are raiding their parents' medicine cabinets
And popping Xanex and snorting Adderall.
Really?
But me.
I'm the master of
Making a pipe out of an apple.
Yeah, you're the McGiver of pot.
You promise this'll help?
No.
Why?
[ 9. Superboy and the Invisible Girl. ]
Superboy and the Invisible Girl
Son of steel and daughter of air
He's a hero, a lover, a prince
She's not there
Superboy and the Invisible Girl
Everything a kid oughtta be
He's immortal, forever alive
Then there's me
I wish I could fly
And magically appear and disappear
I'd fly far away from here
Superboy and the Invisible Girl
He's the one you wish would appear
He's your hero, forever your son
He's not here
I am here
You know that's not true
You're our little pride and joy
Our perfect plan
You know I love you
I love you as much as I can
Take a look at the invisible girl
Here she is, clear as the day
Please look closely and find her before
She fades away
Superboy and the invisible girl
Son of steel and daughter of air
He's a hero, a lover, a prince
She's not there
Let's not get discouraged.
We'll find you a doctor
Who'll treat you without the drugs.
There's someone out there for you.
In the depression chat rooms,
They say it's like dating.
You have to keep going
Until you find the right match.
They have depression chat rooms?
And this doctor's supposed to be fantastic -
A real rock star.
Three different women at work
Gave me his name.
Three women at work know I'm nuts?
Uh.
Ah!
Diana, this way, please.
YEAH!
What did you just say?
I said "welcome."
Have a seat.
It's nice to meet you.
Let's get it on now, baby!
Excuse me, what?
I said, "Let's get started."
Are you nervous, Diana?
I am a little.
A bit out of breath.
Tingly, actually.
Now you go.
Well, let's start by getting to
Know each other a bit.
Psychotherapy and medication
Work best in tandem,
But we can try the first along
And see how far we get.
Why don't you tell me...
Baby, what's your history?
Where'd you go
And who'd you see? Yeah!
My history? Well...
Um... I was diagnosed bi-polar...
Wow... sixteen years ago.
Only, it turned out "bi-polar"
Didn't totally cover it.
Well, often the best that we can do
Is put names on collections of symptoms.
It's possible bi-polar
Has more in common
With schizophrenia than depression.
When I was young,
My mother called me "high-spirited".
She would know.
She was so "high-spirited"
They banned her from the PTA.
Well, sometimes there's
A pre-disposition to illness,
But actual onset is only triggered
By some traumatic event.
I never know what to say
When I have to go over all of this.
It starts to sound like some story
I tell about some other person entirely.
Why don't you tell me about
The last time that you truly felt happy.
Oh.
Were you happy when you got married?
I thought I was.
There's a difference between being happy
And just thinking you're happy?
Most people who think they're happy
Just haven't thought about it enough.
Most people who think
They're happy are actually just stupid.
I see.
Were you happy
When your son was born?
My son?
[ 10. I'm Alive. ]
Tell me about him.
About my son?
Why is he still around?
Who is he? What is he?
I am what you want me to be
And I'm your worst fear,
You'll find it in me
Come closer, come closer
Where does he come from even?
I am more than memory,
I am what might be
I am mystery
You know me
So show me
When I appear
It's not so clear
If I'm a simple spirit
Or I'm flesh and blood
But I'm alive, I'm alive,
I am so alive
And I feed on the fear
That's behind your eyes
And I need you to need me,
It's no surprise
I'm alive, so alive
I'm alive
Four times a week?
That's a lot, isn't it?
That's what the doctor recommended.
This is never going to get better, is it?
He's never going away.
I don't know, Natalie.
This is one of those moments
When you could just be a typical parent
And lie and say "yes".
Yes.
Thanks.
That's comforting.
I am flame and I am fire
I am destruction, decay, and desire
I'll hurt you
You know, Natalie,
I'll heal you
It's not all about your comfort.
I'm your wish, your dream come true
And I am your darkest nightmare too
I've shown you
It's about helping your mother.
I own you
As always!
And though you made me,
You can't change me
I'm the perfect stranger
Who knows you too well
And I'm alive, I'm alive
I am so alive
And I'll tell you the truth
If you let me try
You're alive, I'm alive,
And I'll show you why
I'm alive, so alive
I'm alive
Xanex.
What the hell!
I'm alive
I'm right behind you
You say forget
But I'll remind you
You can try to hide
But you know that I will find you
'Cause if you won't grieve me,
You won't leave me behind
Oh, oh, oh
You say he's eighteen now.
Isn't that when kids move out?
Isn't it time to let him go?
No, no, no
I'm alive, I'm alive,
I am so alive
If you climb on my back
Then we both can fly
If you try to deny me,
I'll never die
I'm alive, so alive
I'm alive
Yeah, yeah
It's been four weeks,
And I'd like to try something new today.
Sometimes when these stories are hard to tell,
Hypnosis can be helpful.
[ 11. Make Up Your Mind/Catch Me I'm Falling. ]
Oh, I don't think I could be hypnotized.
I mean, it's fine.
It's just... I'm not the type.
Put your feet on the floor.
Put your hands in your lap...
And breathe.
Walk with me
Go all the way down
Down a long flight of stairs
Stairs.
Go step by step into
The darkness down there
Should we turn on a light?
You know, with the stairs?
Walk with me
Down a hall
A hall that you know
At the end there's a door
It's a door that
You've never laid eyes on before
Open the door
Can you hear me, Diana?
Yes.
Are you nervous?
No.
Good. Now...
Make up your mind
To explore yourself
Make up your mind,
You have stories to tell
We'll search in your past
For what sorrows may last
Then make up your mind
To be well
Di, you come home
From these sessions in tears.
Is this helping or... Di? Di?
We were both undergrads - architecture.
The baby wasn't planned,
Neither was the marriage.
I had always expected to be too busy,
But when the baby came,
It all seemed to make sense until... until...
Until?
He's not here
Love, I know
You know
Make up your mind
That you're strong enough
Make up your mind,
Let the truth be revealed
Admit what you've lost
And live with the cost
At times it does hurt
To be healed
Catch me, I'm falling
In our first session,
You told me...
Catch me, I'm falling
... that talking through your history...
Faster than anyone should
Catch me, I'm falling
... feels like it's about someone else.
Please hear me calling
Make it about you.
Catch me, I'm falling for good
Hey, I'm not supposed to be backstage,
But ... for luck.
Did you see my parents out there?
Um, are you okay?
I'm fine.
My dad said they'd both be here.
Then I'm sure they will be.
Will they?
We had Natalie to...
And I know she knows.
I couldn't hold her in the hospital.
Where the hell are they?
I couldn't let myself hold her.
That's the first time
You've mentioned Natalie
In weeks of therapy.
Goddammit!
She's not there!
Make up your mind,
You want clarity
Take what you know
And then make it make sense
Just face what you fear
And soon it comes clear
The visions are
Just your defense
Umm, thank you for coming.
Natalie Goodman.
Let's try to understand
What this is doing to you...
And your family.
Fuck.
Your grief for your son.
Your distance from Natalie.
I'm sorry.
I just... the thing is,
I... you know what the problem
With classical is?
It's so rigid and structured.
You have to play the notes on the page!
There's no room for improvisation!
Oh, no...
Take a look
Catch me I'm falling
Make up your mind to be free at last
Take a look
Falling
Make up your mind to be fully alive
Look
Falling
Embrace what's inside,
Look
Falling
Replace what has died
Look
Falling
Make up your mind you'll survive
Catch me, I'm falling
Unresolved loss can lead to depression.
And fear of loss to anxiety.
Flying head-first into fate
Catch me, I'm falling
The more you hold to
Something you've lost,
Please hear me calling
The more you fear losing it.
Catch me before it's too late
Depression, anxiety...
Depression, anxiety -
Catch me before it's too late
One gives rise to the other.
Catch me, I'm falling
It becomes a cycle.
Wouldn't you like to
Be free from all of that, finally?
Wouldn't you like to go home
And clear out his room,
Maybe spend some time with your daughter
And let your son go at last?
Uh, should we go?
Yes.
Mom.
Yes, I would.
This is good, Di.
It's a good step.
[ 12. I Dreamed a Dance. ]
I saw you light the ballroom
With your sparkling eyes so blue
Graceful as an angel's wing
I dreamed a dance with you
You whispered slyly, softly
You told me you would be true
We spun around a thousand stars
I dreamed a dance with you
I know the night is dying dear
I know the day will dawn
The dancers may disappear
Still the dance goes on
And on
I'll wake alone tomorrow
The dream of our dance is through
But now until forever love
I'll live to dance with you
I'll dream my love
I'll live my love
And I'll die to dance with...
[ 13. There's a World. ]
There's a world,
There's a world I know
A place we can go
Where the pain will go away
There's a world
Where the sun shines each day
There's a world,
There's a world out there
I'll show you just where
And in time I know you'll see
There's a world
Where we can be free
Come with me
Goodman, Diana.
Discovered unconscious at home.
There's a world where we can be free
Multiple razor wounds to wrists and forearms.
Self-inflicted.
Come with me
Saline, sutures, gauze, IV antibiotics.
Isolated, sedated and restrained.
Damnit. ECT is indicated.
Wow. I mean, they still do that?
We do. Yes.
It's the standard in cases like this.
She's got a long history of
Drug therapy and resistance.
She's acutely suicidal.
It's really our best option.
Well, that's kind of terrifying.
It's not.
The electricity involved is barely enough
To light a one-hundred-watt bulb.
Oh. If it's just a hundred-watt bulb.
It's safer than crossing the street,
And the short-term success rate
Is over eighty percent.
I thought she was better.
Sometimes, patients recover
Just enough strength to follow through
On suicidal impulses,
But not enough strength to resist them.
Well, that seems very... fucked.
Yes. Legally we need her consent.
Hospital policy is we need yours, too.
I don't think she's gonna go for this.
Mr. Goodman, we can administer the ECT,
And you can bring her home in ten days
Or we can keep her sedated
For fortyeight hours, discharge her
And wait for her to try again.
Look, go home. Take the night.
Talk to her in the morning.
[ 14. I've Been. ]
Standing in this room,
Well, I wonder what comes now
I know I have to help her
But hell if I know how
And all the times that I've been told
The way her illness goes
The truth of it is
No one really knows
And every day this act we act
Gets more and more absurd
And all my fears just sit inside me,
Screaming to be heard
I know they won't, though,
Not a single word
I was here
At her side
When she called,
When she cried.
How could she leave me
On my own?
Will it work,
This cure?
There's no way
To be sure
But I'm weary to the bone
And whenever she goes flying
I keep my feet right
On the ground
Oh now I need a lift
And there's no one around
Hey...
Oh...
I...
Know...
And I've never had to face the world
Without her at my side
Now I'm strolling right beside her
As the black hole opens wide
Mine is just
A slower suicide
I've been here
For the show
Every high,
Every low
But it's the worst
We've ever known
She's been hurt
And how
But I can't give up now
'Cause I've never been alone
I could never be alone
Dad, why didn't you take me with you?
You know, we don't see
Much of you these days.
Is this Henry a good influence?
Like, compared to what?
Okay, that's fair.
The after-effects are minimal.
You'll feel a bit like
You have a hangover.
Mom, don't let them do this.
It causes brain damage.
Your mother's in for
A new treatment. ECT.
Okay... L, M, N, O, P.
What is that? I don't know.
Electro-convulsive therapy.
Shock therapy.
A minority of patients report
Some memory loss,
But it's usually not much memory.
How can you know
How much memory you've lost
If you've lost it?
You're kidding, right?
Dad, that's bullshit!
Language.
Patients have said it's like
Becoming a new person.
It's bullshit!
She trusts you!
Natalie!
[ 15. Didn't I See This Movie?. ]
Didn't I see this movie,
With McMurphy and the nurse?
That hospital was heavy,
But this cuckoo's nest is worse.
Isn't this the one where
In the end the good guys fry?
Didn't I see this movie,
And didn't I cry?
Didn't I cry?
The modern procedure's clean and simple...
Hundreds of thousands of patients
Receive it every year.
What makes you think
I'd lose my mind for you?
I'm no sociopath,
I'm no Sylvia Plath
I ain't no Francis Farmer,
I don't fight for you
So stay out of my brain
I'm no princess of pain
Didn't I see this movie,
Where the doctor looked like you
Where the patient got impatient
And said, "Sorry, doc, I'm through?"
I know where this is going,
And I know what you're about
'Cause I have seen this movie
And I walked out
I walked out
I'm walking...
[ 16. A Light in the Dark ]
One light shines in the drive
One single sign that our house is alive
Our house, our own
So why do I live there alone?
Tell me why I wait through the night
And why do I leave on the light
You know, I know
Our house was a home long ago
Take this chance cause it may be our last
To be free, to let go of the past
And to try to be husband and wife
To let love never die or to just live our lives
Take my hand and let me take your heart
Keep you far from what keeps us apart
Let us start with
A light in the dark
Night falls I stare at the walls
I stare at these walls
I wake and wander the halls
I get lost in these halls
And I ache to the bone
It's like nothing I've known
I can't get through this alone
Take this chance and we'll make a new start
Somewhere far from what keeps us apart
And I swear that
Somewhere in the night
There's a light
A light in the dark
ACT II
Come on! This is my favorite club!
Let's go!
Hey, isn't three clubs
A little much for a Tuesday night...
Wednesday morning?
Oh, come on.
They're playing my favorite song!
They're all your favorite song.
What are you on?
Adderall, Xanex, a Valium,
And Robitussen.
When did you become
A bad influence on me?
Hey, I am under stress.
My mom is in a hospital
Being electrocuted.
Good morning, Diana.
It's good to see you.
Seriously. She gets it,
Like, everyday for two weeks.
I can't even deal with it.
I'd never let them fuck
With my brain like that.
No, you're strictly a "do-it-yourselfer!"
This is your anesthesiologist;
Just breathe normally,
Relax, and count backward from one hundred,
And before you reach one
You'll be asleep.
When you wake up,
You may feel some muscle stiffness,
OK? Here we go.
[ 17. Wish I Were Here ]
In an instant lightning flashes
And the burst might leave me blind
When the bolt of lightning crashes
And it burns right through my mind
It's like someone drained my brain out
Set my frozen mind to thaw
Let the lethargy and pain out
While I stood and watched in awe
I am riding on the brightest buzz
I am worlds away from who I was
And they told me
It would change me
Though they don't know how it does
I have lived a life of clouds and grey
But this is crystal clear
Wish I were here
I imagine it's remarkable
Exuberant, austere
Wish I were here
It's euphoria,
It's anger
It's the winter wind, it's fire
And it kills my deepest hunger
As it fills me with desire
I'm the light and heat of every sun
I'm a bullet from a magic gun
And I'm trying
To enjoy it
But I'm missing all the fun
I am missing all the fun
Am I feeling
What I think I'm feeling?
The hope, the heat,
The fear
Wish I were here
Is this someone else's head trick?
Do I just disappear?
Wish I were here
Sweetheart, what are you doing
In my electricity?
It's always about you, isn't it?
I'm Robo-tripping!
I can't feel my legs.
I don't want you doing drugs.
That's persuasive, coming from
The Pfizer Woman of the Year.
You're the one who's hallucinating.
It's my treatment.
It's a miracle.
Everything's different now.
I know what you mean.
Plug me in and turn me on
And flip the switch;
I'm good as gone
It slits my skin
And trips my brain
I feel the burn,
But I don't feel the pain
Is my brain reborn or is it wrecked
In freedom or in fear?
Wish I were here
Have I blown my mind forever?
Is cloudy my new clear?
Wish I were here
Wish I were...
Natalie! Natalie! Damn.
This is, like, the fifth night in a row
That I've had to come find you
At some random club.
Diana?
Dan.
Your two weeks are up.
It's time to go home.
Home? But...
Shh... don't talk. Relax.
Okay, you can go.
I'm, like, seventy percent
Less messed up now.
Seriously, my dad's going to
Be home any minute.
He's bringing my mom
From the hospital this morning.
You don't want to be here.
Will you call me?
Just go.
Can I hide my stupid hunger?
Fake some confidence and cheer?
Wish I were here
We're here!
Hey. Wow... you look great.
Oh. Well, thank you. And who are you?
Who am I?
Diana, this is Natalie.
Your daughter.
Oh. Of course.
And this is our house?
[ 18. Song of Forgetting. ]
Diana, don't you...
You don't remember any of this?
I should, right?
This house and all these rooms
Last Christmas or last year
Out back the dogwood blooms
Do I really live here?
The paint, the walls
All this glass and wood
You don't recall?
How I wish I could
Our house on Walton Way
The house with the red door
Our trip to San Tropez
The whole week a downpour
My first few steps
And my first lost tooth
What, nothing yet?
To tell the truth
Sing a song of forgetting
A song of the way things were not
Sing of what's lost to you
Of times that you never knew
Sing of not remembering when
Of memories that go
Unremembered and then
Sing a song of forgetting again
That day our child was born
Our baby girl's first cry
That gray and drizzly morn
I've never felt so high
The day we met
And we shared two beers
Then?
I forget.
But that's nineteen years
That Doctor Mitchell said that
There might be some memory loss.
Doctor Madden.
Well, see... there you go.
What a lovely cure!
It's a medical miracle
With a mind so pure
That she doesn't know anything
It's there,
I'm sure
'Cause memories don't die
Why?
They don't die
They die!
Why?
Sing a song of forgetting
A song of the way things were not
Things were not
Sing of what's lost to you
What's lost to you
And times that you never knew
What's lost to you, you never knew
Sing of not remembering when
Of memories that go
Unremembered and then
Sing a song of forgetting
Again
[ 19. Hey #1 ]
Hey
I've missed you these days
I thought you might call
It's been weeks
I've been crazed
Hey, hey
Have you been on the scene?
'Cause you look like a mess
Thanks, I guess
Are you clean?
Wow, coming from you
I don't do what you do
Okay, how did it start?
But you took it too far
Oh, I took it too far?
Hey, hey
Henry, don't!
Are we over?
Don't do this to me
Don't say that we're over
Don't you want us to be?
No, I want who I knew
She's somewhere in you
Hey, say
Will you come to this dance?
It's some spring formal dance
It's March first and it's cheese
But it's fun and it's free
I don't do dances
Do this dance with me
Goodbye, Henry
Natalie, Natalie! Wait up!
This much loss is rare,
But it has been reported.
It may be partly psychedelic.
At times like this,
The mind tends to repress memories,
But they're still there...
Somewhere.
They tend to return in fits and sparks.
But it's been two weeks.
[ 20. Seconds and Years. ]
A little loss of memory is normal
And helpful in forgetting all her fears
I couldn't give a flying fuck
What's normal
We haven't had
A normal day in years
Diana, are things becoming clearer
With the treatment?
Well, yes.
Is life less cloudy than it was before?
Yes.
Do you still feel your head
Is filled with concrete?
No.
And you're not a scary
Rock star anymore
Okay. Great.
But what about her memory?
The memories are there somewhere
Find some pictures you can share
Keepsakes of the life
That's there behind her
Should I bring up the subject of...
Yes.
But keep it light at first
That's best
Careful that she's
Not distressed
When the time's right
Tell the rest
Remind her
You'll find her
[ 21. Better Than Before. ]
So let's start with something small
Something personal and pretty
I bet you'll know these shiny things
They must be tacky trinkets from,
I guess, Atlantic City?
No, actually, Di
They're our wedding rings
It's going well.
Here's a flower from our wedding
It was such a sight to see
And the ceremony everything
We'd hoped
Umm, Dad...
Well, that's how I remember it
So that's how it'll be
It was raining
It was Portland
You eloped
I mean, Portland.
It's an open book to write here
It's a life we can restore
We can get back
What we had and maybe more
Maybe get us back
To better than before
Umm, missing a few pictures here,
Aren't you, Dad?
Didn't the doctor say...
The doctor said at the right time.
Oh. Well, then...
Here's the year
We drove the west
We hit the highway
In the Honda
And I took pictures
Everywhere we went
We saw the Painted Desert
The Grand Canyon and Aunt Rhonda
And Nat learned
What her middle finger meant
Here's the first house
That we owned
On Walton Way,
We loved that place
Then we built this one on land
That we both chose
And here's a pic of all of us
With smiles on every face
And the photo-shopping
Hardly even shows
We're standing by a lake
With all these ducks
And who's this little chubby girl?
That's Natalie
This sucks
Nat.
Gonna get us back to normal
Gonna get us back to good
Gonna get back
What we had and maybe more
Gonna get us back to good times
And forget the things we should
Gonna get us back
To better than before
Get things back
All right, fine.
Here's the headline in the paper
When you freaked out at the market
Here's the house on Walton Way
After the fire
Here's the damage to the Honda
When you showed me how to park it
Did we crush somebody's cat
Beneath the tire?
Yes, ours.
Here's Dad at my recital
And we're wondering
Where you are
I remember this
I made it to the school
Wait, you remember?
It was the year of too much Lithium
I hid out in the car
Yes.
And your swim meet just last year
I'm in the pool
So you are.
You're getting it
You've got it, Di
Hooray!
Your life has kind of sucked, I think
You've got it
Yay, hooray!
Hooray!
Gonna get back what I lost here
Gonna find out who I was
Gonna open up the gates
And let it pour
And if memory makes things better
Well, memory always does
Gonna get us back
To better than before
Make everything much better than
Won't anything be better than before?
I guess it must be better than before
Better than before
[ 22. Aftershocks. ]
They've managed to get rid of me
Return me to the grave
ECT, electric chair
We shock who we can't save
They've cleared you of my memory
And many more as well
You may have wanted some of them
But who can ever tell?
Your brain waves are more regular
The chemistry more pure
The headaches and the nausea will pass
You'll endure
Your son is gone forever, though
Of that the doctor's sure
The memories will wane
The aftershocks remain
You wonder which is worse
The symptom or the cure
Di, honey,
You've been at this for days.
There's something missing, Dan.
It's like it's tugging at me.
I can almost see it.
Come to bed.
If the memories are meant
To come back, they will.
Oh. Sorry, Ms. Goodman.
I just needed to talk to Natalie
About some homework.
I know it's late.
She's not answering her phone...
Is everything all right?
Henry.
Yes.
You remind me of someone.
How old are you?
Seventeen. Why?
I don't know. Natalie's in her room.
They've managed to get rid of me
I'm gone without a trace
But sear the soul and leave scar
No treatment can erase
They've cut away the cancer
But forgot to fill the hole
They moved me from your memory
I'm still there in your soul
Your life goes back to normal now
Or so they all believe
Your heart is in your chest again
Not hanging from your sleeve
They've driven out the demons
And they've earned you this reprieve
The memories are gone
The aftershocks live on
But with nothing to remember
Is there nothing left to grieve?
With nothing to remember...
[ 23. Hey #2 ]
Hey
So tomorrow's the dance
It's annoying, I know
But let's go
Not a chance
Let me know you again
Not right now
Okay, when?
Say wait and I'll wait
It's already too late
There's no way it's too late
Hey, hey
There's no way
Will you listen?
I stayed by your side
Just shut up and listen
Why do I get denied?
You remind me of me
And how fucked up I can be
Okay, hey
Let's start over clean slate
I'll come by here at eight
If you show
Then we'll go
If you don't
Well, we'll see
You just don't give up
So don't give up on me
Goodbye, Henry
[ 24. You Don't Know (Reprise). ]
It's been four weeks
Since the treatment
And my mind is still a mess
And what's left to be remembered
Well, it's anybody's guess
'Cause my past is like the weather
It will come and it will go
I don't know, even know
What it is that I don't know
I'm some Christopher Columbus
Sailing out into my mind
With no map of where I'm going
Or of what I've left behind
I don't know the things I don't know
I'm sure something's missing
I wish it would show
I don't know, you say take it slow
I do, but how I do, I don't know
Are you talking with your husband?
Well, he hasn't much to say
Is he helping you remember?
I remember that's his way
Does the puzzle come together
Piece my piece and row by row?
I don't know, I don't know
Where the fucking pieces go
'Cause I don't how this started
So, I won't know when it's done
Have you talked of your depression,
Your delusions and your son?
My what?
Your husband didn't...
I think you two should talk more.
We should talk more?
That's it?
I don't even remember
Marrying this man, its not like I'm not
Some sexually frustrated soccer mom.
Interestingly, the underlying challenges
Are similar.I'll see you next week.
But...
Next week.
What...?
What are you doing?
What is this?
Where did you get that?
It's nothing -
An old music box.
[ 25. How Could I Ever Forget?. ]
We played it for the baby.
Sometimes it helped him sleep.
Diana.
Him. We did have a boy.
Diana, you shouldn't...
We were still living downtown
This is not a good idea.
My black coat thrown
Over my blue nightgown
You drove too fast
The lights of the city flew past
Please... don't...
How could I ever forget?
Outside the morning was cool and wet
He had such chills
But still, he lay there so still
Just eighteen months old
So cold
We ran him inside
Lost, worrying, wondering
That hospital room, that gloom
How could I ever forget?
Screaming at doctors
Alarmed, upset
God, I was so upset
They said to wait
Diana, don't
They never said we were too late
You think this will help, but it won't
But I was a child
So many years ago
Raising a child
So much we could not know
Those weeks full of joy
Then a moment of dread
Someone simply said,
"Your child is..."
How could I ever forget?
This was the moment my life was set
My life was set
That day that I lost you
It's clear as the day we met
How could I ever forget?
Why would you want to remember
The things that hurt you?
I want to remember everything, Dan.
How did he die?
He was sick.
With what?
Why wasn't he treated?
What was wrong?
Something the doctors all missed
The clinic, the ER, each specialist
They said, "Babies cry,
Allergies, gas, who knows why?"
And I was a child
Raising a child
We stayed up all night
Those nights you slept at his side
But still he just cried
And cried
He was a baby when he died,
But I remember him much older.
No. He was a baby.
We should call Doctor Madden.
[ 26. It's Gonna Be Good (Reprise). ]
Why should we call Doctor Madden?
I'm just trying to make sense of this.
God... what was his name?
I don't remember ever hearing
You say his name.
Why is that?
What was his name?
Tell me.
It's gonna be fine
We'll go back to the doctors
'Cause we caught it just in time
We'll take the pills,
We'll pay the bills
We'll do more ECT
His name... our son...
It's gonna be good, you'll see
What was his name?
It's gonna be good
Good, good, good, good
Name, name, name, name
Good, good, good
What was his name?
What was his name
Jesus! Dad!
Natalie...
[ 27. Why Stay?/A Promise ]
Why stay?
So steadfast and stolid
And stoic and solid
For day
After every day
Why stay?
Why not simply give in
And get on with living
'Cause everyone knows you tried
But somehow,
Something died on the way
So tell me why you stay
Why stay?
Enduring and coping
And hurting and hoping
For day
After fucking day
Why stay?
Why not simply end it
We'd all comprehend it
And most of the world
Would say it,
he's better off that way
To be free and maybe so is she
A promise a boy says forever
A boy says whatever may come
Will come through
And who can know how
When all I know now to be true
Is this promise that I made to you
A question a boy wonders whether
Should I stay together the way that they stay
For year after year for
Love or fear either way
That's the promise
That I made that day
Here's what I say
To the girl who was
Burning so brightly
Like the light from Orion above
And still I will search
For her nightly
If you see her, please send her my love
And the boy was a boy for all seasons
That boy is long lost to me now
And the man has forgotten his reasons
But the man still remembers his vow
A promise a man says forever
A man says I'll never regret or let you
The promise I made to stay and I stay true
Knowing one day we'd remember that joy
You'd remember that girl
I'd remember that boy 'til we do
The promise I made I'll make it brand new
The promise that I made to you
[ 28. I'm Alive (Reprise). ]
I am more than memory
I am what might be
I am mystery
Come closer
Dan...
Diana, there's nothing there.
I am old as time
I'm forever young
I am every song
That will stay unsung
I'll find you
Oh, no.
Goddamnit!
Remind you
Natalie!
Di!
Come back here!
Until you name me
You can't tame me
This is one old game
I can play so well
I'm alive, I'm alive
I am so alive
The medicine failed
And the doctors lied
I'm alive, I'm alive
I am death-defied
I'm alive, so alive.
I'm alive!
I can't go to your dance.
I have to take my mom to the doctor.
I'll drive.
No!
I'm alive
Let me help.
You can't. Just go!
Diana.
I'm alive!
Look, I'll try to come later, okay?
I'll wait for you!
I'm alive
[ 29. The Break. ]
They told me that the wiring
Was somehow all misfiring
And screwing up
The signals in my brain
And then they told me chemistry,
The juice and not the circuitry
Was mixing up
And making me insane
What happens when the burn has healed,
But the skin has not re-grown?
What happens when the cast,
At last, comes off,
And then you find the break
Was always in another bone?
Relapse is very common, Diana.
It's upsetting that
The delusional episodes have returned,
But it's not entirely unexpected.
They tried a million meds and
They strapped me to their beds and
They shrugged and told me
that's the way it goes
But finally you hit it
I asked you just what did it
You shrugged and said
That no one really knows
What happens if the medicine
Wasn't really in control?
What happens if the cut, the burn,
The break was never in my brain,
Or in my blood,
But in my soul?
What happens if the cut, the burn,
The break was never in my brain,
Or in my blood,
But in my soul?
[ 30. Make Up Your Mind/Catch Me I'm Falling (Reprise). ]
Make up your mind
This is clarity
Clarity that you did not
Have before
The treatment is strong
But last only so long
Its maybe your mind's
Needing more
Let's say that's not that.
The ECT is powerful.
It gave you your life back,
But the effects fade
And additional treatments
Are almost always needed.
That wasn't on the form.
Make up your mind
That you'll try again
There are moments of light
But one things that's sure
Is that there is no cure
But that doesn't mean
We don't fight
Catch me I'm falling
We'll return to the talk therapy.
Sinking and sprawling
There's more work to do.
Maybe I'll let myself fall
Watch me I'm falling
We may need to look at...
Maybe the falling
... a new drug regimen.
Isn't so bad after all
Make up your mind to be free
Watch me I'm falling
Watch me I'm flying
Make up your mind
Somehow surviving
Make up your
Diana! You have a chronic illness.
Like diabetes or hypertension.
If you leave it untreated,
It could be catastrophic.
I understand.
But there has to be another way.
Stay with me, try again
Don't walk out on treatment
Don't lose what you've won
You've struggled for years
But you've only begun
My first psychiatrist told me that,
According to the manual,
Grief that continues past four months
Is pathological and should be medicated.
Four months.
For the life of my child...
Who makes these decisions?
It's a guide, Diana.
Nothing more.
Yes. Nothing more.
Stay with me
Try again
Is medicine magic?
You know that it's not
You know it's not perfect
But it's what we've got
It's all that we've got
Goodbye,
Doctor Madden.
[ 31. Maybe (Next to Normal). ]
What'd he say?
He said I could do more ECT
Or go back on the meds.
And what are you gonna do?
I'm going to take you to your dance.
Mom...
It's time for you to start
Thinking of your own happiness.
It's not happiness.
It's Henry.
You love him.
Mom, you can't just walk out
On your doctor.
Maybe I've lost it at last
Maybe my last lucid moment has past
I'm dancing with death, I suppose
But really, who knows?
Could be I'm crazy to go
They say you should stay
With the devil you know
But when life needs a change
And the one devil won't
You fly to the devil you don't
So... what?
You're just going to wing it?
Maybe I'm tired of the game
Of coming up short of the rules,
Of the shame
And maybe you feel that way, too
I see me in you
A girl full of anger and hope
A girl with a mother
Who just couldn't cope
A girl who felt caught
And thought no one could see
But maybe one day she'll be free
It's so lovely that you're sharing
No, really, I'm all ears
But where has all this caring been
For sixteen years?
For all those years I prayed
That you'd go away for good
Half the time afraid that you really would
When I thought you might be dying
I cried for all we'd never be
But there'll be no more crying
Not for me
Things will get better, you'll see
You'll see
Not for me
You'll see, you'll see
You'll see
Maybe we can't be okay
But maybe we're tough
And we'll try anyway
We'll live with what's real
Let go of what's past
And maybe I'll see you at last
I don't believe you.
Seventeen years ago when...
Your brother died of
An intestinal obstruction,
He was eight months old.
The doctors missed it,
And your father
And I didn't know anything.
We were kids,
Not much older than you.
I'm so sorry we never
Talked about that.
We wanted to give you a normal life,
But I realize I have no clue what that is.
I don't need a life that's normal
That's way too far away
But something next to normal
Would be okay
Yes, something next to normal
That's the thing I'd like to try
Close enough to normal
To get by
We'll get by
Okay.
Now, go to your dance.
[ 32. Hey #3/Perfect For You (Reprise). ]
Hey...
You look like a star
A vision in blue
Oh, I do?
And you are!
Hey, you came...
Well, I said that I might
I thought we were through
Me and you
Not tonight
Will your mom be okay?
Well, she might be
Someday
But for now it's all fine?
She's still on my mind
Can you leave it behind?
Hey!
Stay, let's see this thing through
Am I crazy?
I might end up crazy
I'll be here for you
You say that right here
But then give it a year
Or ten years or a life
I could end up your wife
Sitting staring at walls
Throwing shit down the stairs
Freaking out at the store
Running nude down the street
Bleeding out in the bath
Shhh...
Perfect for you
I will be perfect for you
So you could go crazy
Or I could go crazy
It's true
Sometimes life is insane
But crazy,
I know I can do
Cause crazy is perfect
And fucked up is perfect
So I will be perfect
Perfect
Perfect for you
[ 33. So Anyway. ]
So anyway, I'm leaving
I thought you'd like to know
You're faithful come what may
But clearly, I can't stay
We'd both go mad that way
So here I go
And anyway, I'm leaving
I guess that you can see
I'll try this on my own
A life I've never known
I'll face the dread alone
But I'll be free
With you always beside me
To catch me when I fall
I'd never get to know
The feel of solid ground at all
With you always believing
That we can still come through
It makes me feel the fool
To know that it's not true
What doctors call dysfunction
We try to call romance
And true, it's quite a trick to tell
The dancers from the dance
But rather than the chance take me
I'll take the chance
I'll take a chance on leaving
It's that or stay and die
I loved you once and though
You love me still
I know it's time for me to fly
I loved you once and though
I love you still
I know it's time for me to go
And so,
Goodbye
[ 34. I Am the One (Reprise). ]
I am the one who loved you
I am the one who stayed
I am the one
And you walked away
I am the one waited
And now you act like
You just don't give a damn
Like you've never knew who I am
I am the one who knows you
I am
I am the one you feel
I am the one who's always been here
I've always been here
I am
I am the one who'll hear you
I know you told her
That I'm not worth a damn
But I know you know who I am
No...
I know you know who I am
Why can't you just
Leave me alone?
I know you know who I am
Why didn't you go with her?
Cause I'm holding on
Let me go
And I won't let go
And I want you to know
You don't know
I am the one who held you
I am the one who cried
I am the one who watched while you died
I am the one who loves you
I tried pretending that I don't give a damn
But you've always known who I am
Gabe. Gabriel.
Hi, Dad.
Dad. What the hell.
Why are the lights off?
Where's Mom?
She's, uh... she's...
Gone.
Yes.
[ 35. Light/Finale. ]
Oh. So, it's just me and you.
For now.
Yes.
Okay.
We need some light
First of all, we need some light
You can't sit here in the dark
And all alone, it's a sorry sight
It's just you and me
We'll live, you'll see
Night after night
We'd sit and wait
For the morning light
But we've waited far too long
For all that's wrong
To be made right
Day after day
Wishing all our cares away
Trying to fight the things we feel
But some hurts never heal
Some ghosts are never gone
But we go on
We still go on
And you find some way to survive
And you find out
You don't have to be happy at all
To be happy you're alive
Do you know where she went?
Have you heard from her?
She's staying with my grandparents.
Do they actually exist?
Yes.
That's good, right?
Well, going home has never really
Been a solution to my problems.
That's what you have me for.
Seriously?
You're, like, number three
On my list of issues.
List?
You keep a list?
But you're my favorite problem.
Well, that's all I ask.
Day after day
Give me clouds and rain and grey
Give me pain
If that's what's real
It's the price we pay to feel
Price we pay to feel
The price of love is loss
But still we pay
We love anyway
I know you can't tell me
If you're still treating her.
I just... I wonder if she's okay.
I think she's working on it.
Do you think she'll come home?
It's hard to know.
Right.
Dan, would you like me to recommend
Someone for you to talk to?
No, no. I, uh... yes, I would.
Thank you.
And when the night has finally gone
And when we see the new day dawn
We'll wonder how
We wondered for so long, so blind
The wasted world we thought we knew
The light will make it look brand new
So let it
Let it
Let it shine
Shine
Day after day
We'll find the will to find our way
Knowing that the darkest skies
Will someday see the sun
When our long night is done
There will be light
When we open up our lives
Sons and daughters, husbands, wives
Can fight that fight
There will be light
THE END