Central Partnership
Central Partnership presents
Halt!
A Kolibri Studio production
Sergei KOLTAKOV
Get them out!
Sergei GOROBCHENKO
One, two, three, one, two, three!
Yelena LYADOVA
Anatoliy BELIY
Viktoria ISAKOVA
Alexander GOLUBEV
Pavel DEREVYANKO
In a Yury Moroz film
THE BROTHERS KARAMAZOV
Based on the novel
by F.M. Dostoyevsky
Screenplay:
Alexander CHERVINSKY
Director of photography:
Nikolai IVASIV R.G.C.
Artistic directors:
Yekaterina KOZHEVNIKOVA, Marat KIM
Halt!
Composer:
Henri LOLASHVILI
New Russia State Symphonic Orchestra
Conductor: Yury BASHMET
Sound director:
Marina NIGMATULINA
Make-up:
Marina FIRSOVA, Olga UIKOLAEVA
Forward march!
Move!
Part Three
Thank you very much.
I'll be waiting for your advise
how to find Lyagavy.
The main question is:
if I re-register to him this grove
and all illegally taken Chermashnya,
will Mr. Informer give me
three thousand in advance?
How can I know that?
Why do you call him Lyagavy?
His name is Gorstkin.
He takes offend
when somebody calls him Lyagavy.
He's drunk.
Has been drinking all day long.
What should I do now?
I have very important
things to talk about with him.
I need to come back tonight.
I have to wake him up.
You have to wait.
He is out of form.
God!
I need to wake him up now.
You can't imagine
how desperate I am.
He won't be able to talk tonight.
I have nothing to do but waiting.
I'll start just when he wakes up.
I'll pay for the candle,
you won't forget Dmitri Karamazov.
Good bye, I wish you to be
fully satisfied.
This is so stupid.
Disgracefully.
What an absurd!
My whole life depends on him,
and he is snoring here.
This is Snegiryov!
Beat him!
What do you think you're doing?
Get out off here!
'll manage with them alone.
Why do you throw stones in me?
Monk in silk trousers!
Very well, I am going,
I don't want to tease you.
I heard how they tease you.
I don't want to. Good bye.
Aren't you ashamed?
What are you doing?
What have I done to you?
I'm sorry, I fell asleep.
I'm lieutenant Dmitri Karamazov.
You probably heard that I'm
an old man Karamazov's son.
Whom you're buying the grove from.
You're lying.
Why are you saying that?
You know Fyodor Pavlovitch, don't you?
I don't know Fyodor Pavlovitch.
You are buying the grove from my father.
I'm ready to give you the rights
to the whole Chermashnya.
And I'm ready to sign the papers now.
Only for three thousand.
You're lying.
This is not a joke.
You are a dyer.
I am Dmitri Karamazov.
And I came to you
with a profitable offer.
Talking about that grove.
Three thousand only.
No, you are a dyer.
You contracted with me.
And you are a scoundrel.
I assure you, Mr. Lyagavy,. .
Why do you call me that?
I'm not Lyagavy for you.
I am Gorstkin! Gorstkin!
- Do you understand that?
- I know you are Gorstkin.
I am Gorstkin.
God, what have I done?
- You are Gorstkin?
- Yes, I am Gorstkin.
And you are a dyer.
Scum.
He warned me. Gorstkin.
I am Gorstkin.
This is for overnight stay.
My God, what despair!
What death all round!
Alexey Fyodorovitch, I was expecting you.
We have Ekaterina Ivanovna
and your brother here.
Not that horrible one.
Ivan Fyodorovitch is here.
He is speaking with her.
He is speaking with her
as if his heart is breaking.
Alexey Fyodorovitch,
why is Lisa in hysterics now?
Once she heard you come,
she is hysterics.
You are in hysterics, not me.
I didn't know he was coming.
What do you mean you didn't know.
Yulee told you Alexey Fyodorovitch has come.
She was on the watch.
Dear mother, this is not funny at all.
But if you want
to improve the situation,
and you want to say something
very clever,
say to this mister,
to Alexey Fyodorovitch,
that by coming here
after what happened yesterday,
he proved his stupidity.
And he doesn't pay attention
to the fact that everyone is laughing at him.
Lisa!
I'll finally resort to strong measures!
Who is laughing at him?
Everyone needs him.
Alexey Fyodorovitch, I am so upset.
Her sickness, her whims,
and Dr. Gerzen can't understand
anything, and Ekaterina Ivanovna's tragedy,
this is so terrible!
Excuse me, give me please some cloth.
I injured my hand and it hurts.
Here
My God! What a wound!
A wound? Why didn't you say
anything about it?
He could've blooded till death.
Yulya, get some water.
We need to water the wound.
You need to put your hand
into cold water, so it won't hurt.
Mommy, hurry. Find some water and a bowl.
We need to send for a doctor.
Your doctor will not
understand anything again.
Where is that Yulya with water?
- Yulya, hurry!
- Mommy, please, go get it yourself.
Hurry, or I will die.
Mommy, bring some lint,
and that turbid liquid for cuts.
I don't remember its name.
It's in your bedroom, in the right closet.
I will bring it right away.
Don't be so loud.
Look how firmly Alexey Fyodorovitch
bears his suffering.
Where did you manage
to injure yourself?
Yulya, bring a clean handkerchief.
Now quickly give my letter back.
I don't have it with me.
It's not truth. I knew
you'd say that. It's in your pocket.
Give it to me right now.
I left it there.
Then bring it to me today.
It was a joke.
Do you hear me?
I repented this joke.
Did you laugh much at me?
Not at all.
Why not?
Because I believed your letter.
- You are insulting me.
- No, I am not.
Once I finished reading,
I realized this is the way it will be.
The monastic elder ordered to leave
the monastery and to get married.
I realized there is no
better wife than you.
When we come of age
we will definitely get married.
I will love you.
I'm a freak.
They carry me on a chair.
I will carry you.
But I am sure
you'll get better by that time.
You are insane.
What nonsense you
made out of that joke!
Here is mommy.
Mom, what took you so long?
You are always late!
Yulya has brought a handkerchief already.
Lise, my head aches
because of your shouts.
I remembered the name of that liquid.
It's called lead water.
Mommy, can you imagine,
he had a fight with boys in the street.
And one boy bit his finger.
Can he marry after that?
Because, can you imagine,
mommy, he wants to marry me.
Isn't it funny?
What do you mean marry?
It's not appropriate for you.
That boy can be rabid.
Mom, there are no rabid boys.
They can be, Lise.
Maybe this is stupid.
But your boy was bitten by a dog, wasn't he?
So he became a rabid boy.
And he bit Alexey Fyodorovitch.
Aren't you afraid of it yourself?
Stop it, Lise.
Maybe I shouldn't have said
about the rabid boy.
But you shouldn't say that.
Alexey Fyodorovitch, Ekaterina Ivanovna
found out that you are here,
and she is waiting for you.
Mom, tell her he can't see her.
He is in pain now.
No I am not. I can go.
You really can?
- Mom, he is a monster.
- Lise!
I will come to you after that
and we will talk as long as you want.
- Mom, take him away!
- Lise, you are going mad!
Let's go, Alexey Fyodorovitch,
I'm afraid of her.
I don't want to anticipate,
but you will see anything by yourself.
The most fantastic comedy
is happening there.
Ekaterina Ivanovna loves
your brother Ivan Fyodorovitch,
but she makes us believe
she loves your brother Dmitri Fyodorovitch.
That is terrible!
Hello, Alexey Fyodorovitch.
Ivan Fyodorovitch,
please stay just for one minute.
I want to hear
Alexey Fyodorovitch's opinion.
Alexey Fyodorovitch, yesterday
you were a witness of that horror.
That is why I trust you.
Well, I don't know now
if I love Dmitri Fyodorovitch.
He became pitiful for me,
but that's a bad sign.
No, of course you don't love him.
Wait, I haven't said
what I have decided last night.
My decision is:
even if he marries that bitch,
I will never leave him.
I will be faithful to him
whole my life.
In spite of what I bore yesterday.
And when he becomes
miserable with her,
and that will happen for sure,
he will come to me.
He will see a friend in me.
He will see a loving sister.
He will see a faithful person in me.
I will become means of his happiness.
A tool... How to say that?
I will be an engine for his happiness.
And that will be for all his life.
That is my decision.
And Ivan Fyodorovitch approves that.
No, I just expressed my thoughts.
Your life will be full of suffering.
But with the lapse if time
it will become softer.
And the rest of those feelings
will satisfy you most of all.
My God, this is so wrong.
Why don't you say something,
Alexey Fyodorovitch?
Well, tomorrow I will have to go
to Moscow and leave you for a long time.
Tomorrow to Moscow? But...
I am so happy.
Not because you are leaving.
You will tell aunt Iogasha my situation.
All my horror.
You are indispensable for me.
I am going to write a letter.
What about Alexey Fyodorovitch's
opinion. You wanted to hear that badly.
I didn't forget.
Why are you so hostile to me?
I am listening to you,
Alexey Fyodorovitch.
I haven't thought about it.
I couldn't imagine that.
What?
He is going to Moscow,
and you said you were happy.
You said that on purpose,
like you played it in a theatre.
I know I shouldn't say that,
but I will say.
You don't love my brother Dmitri
at the first place.
And maybe Dmitri doesn't love you either.
He just honors you.
I don't know how dare I.
But I must say the truth
because nobody wants to say it here.
What truth?
Invite Dmitri here.
Let him take your hand
and after that Ivan's hand.
And ask him to link your hands.
You torture Ivan
only because you love him.
But you don't love Dmitri,
you just convinced yourself in that.
You are a little prat!
You are mistaken, my dear Alyosha.
Ekaterina Ivanovna has never loved me.
She always knew I loved her.
Even though I have never
said a word about my love.
She knew that,
but she didn't love me.
She kept me for continuous vengeance.
She took vengeance on me
for all insults she had from Dmitri.
From their first meeting.
Ekaterina Ivanovna,
you really love him.
You love him for insulting you.
If he reformed, you'd give him up at once.
You need him so as to contemplate
continually your heroic fidelity
and to reproach him for infidelity.
And it all comes from your pride.
I don't want your hand.
You have tortured me too deliberately for me
to be able to forgive you at this moment.
I shall forgive you later,
but now I don't want your hand.
I don't need the reward.
You did nothing wrong.
You were perfect.
This is my fault. I started it.
You saw that by yourself.
That was a laceration.
Mom, why was he acting like an angel?
I have a serious request for you,
Alexey Fyodorovitch.
Your brother Dmitri offended a man.
He was angry,
but that offence was serious.
The name of that man is Snegiryov.
I'd like to ask you to visit him
and delicately give him this.
Two hundred roubles.
He will accept it for sure.
I mean to persuade him to accept it.
You are so excellent and kind.
This is from me.
Not from Dmitri.
Find him. He lives in Lake Street
in the house of a woman called Kalmikov.
Do it please.
Do it.
Now I am tired. Good bye.
Tears is a good sign.
This is wonderful, Alexey Fyodorovitch.
Hurry up with that assignment.
And come back quicker.
Liza, don't delay him here.
No way. Not anymore.
Speak through the door now.
How have you come to be an angel?
For an awful piece of stupidity, Lise!
Goodbye!
It's a monk come to beg for the monastery.
A nice place to come to!
No, Varvara Nikolaevna, you are wrong.
Wrong guess.
I came to discuss one business.
What business?
Daddy, he came to complain of me.
I bit his finger.
So it is you whose finger he bit?
Yes, me.
He was throwing
stones with other schoolboys.
There were six of them against him alone.
I went up to him,
and he threw a stone at me.
I asked him what I had done to him.
And then he rushed at me
and bit my finger badly.
I'll thrash him.
At once - this minute!
But I am not complaining at all,
I am simply telling you.
Besides, he seems to be ill.
Do you suppose I'd thrash him?
That I'd take my Ilyusha
and thrash him for your satisfaction?
No, sir.
Instead of thrashing Ilyusha,
I'll chop off my four fingers
with this knife here before your eyes.
I should think four fingers would be enough
to satisfy your thirst for vengeance.
You won't ask for the fifth one too?
I think I understand it all now.
He attacked me
as the brother of your assailant.
I understand it.
My brother regrets his action.
He will ask
your forgiveness if you wish it.
After pulling out my beard, you mean,
he will ask my forgiveness?
He will do anything you like.
So if I were to ask his highness
to go down on his knees
before me in that very tavern,
he would do it?'
Yes.
Touched me to tears
and pierced me to the heart!
So leave off playing the fool!
Did you hear that?
Allow me to introduce...
Daddy, stop it! Some idiot comes in,
and you put us to shame!
You see that?
That's her character.
Now let me present you to my wife,
Arina Petrovna.
Get up, mister Karamazov. You
must stand up to be introduced to a lady.
It's not the Karamazov, mamma.
It's his brother.
Hello. Sit down, Mr. Tchernomazov.
Karamazov. Karamazov.
We are of humble origin.
Father.
Sit down. Why has he pulled you up?
My legs are swollen like
barrels, and I am shriveled up myself.
When we were with the army,
we used to have many such guests.
I don't mean to make any
comparisons; everyone to their taste.
The deacon's wife
used to come then and say,
Alexandr Alexandrovitch
is a man of the noblest heart,
but Nastasya Petrovna,'
she would say, 'is of the brood of hell.'
'Well,' I said, 'that's a matter
of taste; but you are a little spitfire.'
'And you want keeping
in your place;' says she.
'You black sword,' said I,
'who asked you to teach me?'
'But my breath,' says she,
'is clean, and yours is unclean.'
And ever since then I had it in my mind.
Not long ago I was sitting here
as I am now,
when I saw that very general
come in who came here for Easter,
and I asked him :
'Your Excellency,' said I,
'can a lady's breath be unpleasant?'
'Yes,' he answered ; 'you ought to open
a windowpane or open the door,
for the air is not fresh here.'
'I won't spoil the air,' said I,
'I'll order some slippers and go away.'
My darlings, don't blame
your own mother!
There's only Ilyusha who comes
home from school and loves me.
Nikolay Ilyitch,
how is it I can't please you?
Forgive your own mother -
forgive a poor lonely creature!
Why has my breath
become unpleasant to you?
Mamma, my dear, give over!
Father, how can you - with him!
There, you see, you hear?
Do give over fooling, showing off your
silly antics which never lead to anything!
Your anger
is quite just this time, Varvara Nikolaevna,
and I'll make haste to satisfy you.
Come, put on your cap,
Alexey Fyodorovitch, and I'll put on mine.
We will go out.
Let's go, Alexey Fyodorovitch.
I have a word to say to you in earnest,
but not within these walls.
Come along, Alexey Fyodorovitch,
we must make an end.
Let's go.
Your brother dragged me out of
the tavern into the market place.
At that moment the boys were coming
out of school, and with them Ilyusha.
As soon as he saw me
in such a state he rushed up to me.
'Father,' he cried, 'father! '
He caught hold of me,
hugged me, tried to pull me away,
crying to your brother,
'Let go, let go, it's my father, forgive him! '
Yes, he actually cried 'forgive him.'
He clutched at that hand,
that very hand, and kissed it.
I remember his little face at that moment.
I haven't forgotten it and I never shall!
No, I will never forgive your brother.
It was not only you
whom he insulted.
He has insulted his betrothed, too,
a noble-hearted girl.
She commissioned me at once - just now -
to bring you this help from her.
Two hundred roubles.
From her, as from a sister.
Two hundred roubles?
You must take them.
Unless all men
are to be enemies on earth!
You have a generous heart.
You must see that.
Two hundred roubles! I haven't seen
so much money for the last four years!
And she says she is a sister.
And is that the truth?
I swear that all I told you is the truth.
Two hundred roubles
mean a lot to me.
I can look after mamma and Nina,
my hunchback angel daughter.
Yes, yes, of course.
Katerina Ivanovna
will send you as much more as you need.
And I have money too, take what you want,
as you would
from a brother, from a friend,
you can give it back later.
Wouldn't you like me
to show you a little trick I know?
What trick?
A pretty trick.
Look.
Do you see, do you see?
Look there!
So much for your money!
What should I say to my boy if I
took money from you for our shame?
Why have you come?
To find out how you are.
You need not have troubled.
But I knew you'd
come poking in directly.
Red's better.
It's just like the hospital in a white one.
No, red's better.
Ivan's gone out.
He is doing his utmost
to carry off Mitya's betrothed.
That's what he is staying here for.
Surely he did not tell you so?
Yes, he did, three weeks ago.
You don't suppose he too came
to murder me, do you?
What do you mean?
Why do you say such things?
He must have had some object in coming.
He doesn't ask for money, it's true,
but yet he won't get
a farthing from me.
Because, my dear Alexey Fyodorovitch,
I want to pass for one
for another twenty years.
As I get older, you know,
I shan't be a pretty object.
The wenches won't come to me of their
own accord, so I shall want my money.
So I am saving up for myself.
For I mean to go on in
my sins to the end.
For sin is sweet.
All abuse it, but all men live in it.
Only others do it on the sly.
And I openly.
And your paradise is not to my taste.
Even if it exists.
I believe that I fall asleep
and don't wake up again.
And that's all.
You can pray for my soul if you like.
And if you don't
want to, don't, damn you!
That's my philosophy.
And I'll marry Grushenka
in a minute if I want to.
For if you've money, you have only
to want a thing and you can have it.
How cross you are!
It's because of yesterday.
You had better lie down.
There! You say that,
and I am not angry with you.
But if Ivan said it,
I should be angry with him.
Won't you have a drop of brandy?
Take some cold coffee and I'll pour...
No, thank you.
I'll take that roll with me if I may.
And you'd better
not have brandy, either.
You are quite right, it irritates
my nerves instead of soothing them.
Only one little glass.
I'll get it out of the cupboard.
You see you are in a better humour now.
I love you even without the brandy.
But with scoundrels I am a scoundrel.
I am an ill-natured man.
You are not ill-natured, but distorted.
Look what I wanted to ask you.
If I were to hand
Mitya over a thousand or maybe two now,
would he leave?
Forever. Without Grushenka.
If you would give
him three thousand, perhaps he...
No! That's nonsense!
You needn't ask him now, no need!
I've changed my mind.
I want my money myself.
I'll crush him
like a beetle without it.
You know how I crush
them at nights?
And it cracks.
And your Mitya will crack.
Because you love him,
I can see that.
You can go. There's nothing
for you to do here to-day.
What's that for?
We shall see each other again.
Or do you think we shan't?
Not at all, I didn't mean anything.
You can go.
I did not mean anything either.
THE BROTHERS KARAMAZOV
End of Part Three