What's the matter?
Nothing
Are you sure?
Do you want some medicine?
Thank You
Sir, please fasten your seat belt
Would you be going home immediately?
Of course
Hope to see them as soon as we land
Why didn't you request them to receive you?
Oh, just want to give them a surprise
How far is it from the airport to my home?
Not far, it takes less than 20 minutes
Hong Kong is a small place
Very much unlike Canada...
where it takes an hour to go anywhere
Young master!
Where's Dad?
He has gone to a ball
He asked me to come and pick you up
He will be back a little later
Dad's always busy. I rarely get to see him
We'll drop Miss Kei off first
Hong Kong is so busy even at night
Well, that's Hong Kong
How long will it take to my home?
Quite soon
Headache again?
Are you alright?
Maybe I am not used to it
Who could it be? It's really late
It's late, you better return home
It's okay, I'll walk you up
- Po-erh - Daddy
It's you!
Uncle
I'm Michael, Michael Cho
I am Po-erh's classmate, we...
See you tomorrow
Okay. Goodbye, uncle
Thank you
You're welcome.
- See you - Bye
You came back all of a sudden,
does your auntie know about it?
Had she known, she wouldn't have allowed
All my classmates go for holidays every year
Only I used to be left out. So boring!
I've graduated this year
This year? So soon, huh!
Go and greet mummy
Guess who is here?
Mommy
Come sit here and talk to your mother
I'll get some tea.
Let me do it, you stay with your daughter
Was it a long flight?
Yeah
You're in university, isn't it?
I graduated.
I wanna call uncle Cheung
He doesn't know I am back
Okay
Where's the phone?
Telephone... over there
Have some tea
Thanks
Mommy
You have some rest
What is it? Why're you hiding in here?
Your daughter's back. Why not come on out?
What're you afraid of?
Nothing. There's nothing to fear
She is your own daughter
Hey, come on
Okay, see you tomorrow. Bye
You must be tired. Go to bed early
Have an early morning tea with daddy tomorrow
Tomorrow I'm meeting uncle Cheung
What's up?
Nothing
Daddy, I want to look at the room I lived in
Alright
Po-erh, why don't you turn on the light?
She...
What?
Nothing
You sleep here tonight
Goodnight
Why does she stay in my room?
I don't like her to use my stuff
She takes my bed, where should I sleep then?
Mommy! I don't like her!
Don't... don't push me
Help... help!
Mommy
Sorry
Oh, it's alright
Has daddy left for the office?
I'll get it
She...
Good morning!
Uncle Cheung
Hey, how come you're back so suddenly?
Come on in
Take a seat
Uncle never lets you down. I came over...
to meet you as soon as I got your call
How's your auntie?
She is fine.
What's the matter?
God knows what's happening to my head
Always seem to have this strange headache
You think too much
No, I'll get used to it
You think I ought to have it checked?
I better attend the kitchen
How could it be?
What?
It seems mom isn't happy with my return
Oh, come on!
Do you have time later?
I'll take you to my place to have a look
There's nothing wrong with my niece
Too studious. Could be a nervous breakdown
Of late she's been complaining of pains
Have you given her a check-up?
Yes, I've seen her grow up
I know her family quite well
The Mrs. Kei I mentioned to you before
She's her daughter
I visit her in Canada almost every year
Ask her to meet me in a couple of days
Let me check my schedule
Take a seat
lt'd be best if she can make it today
Tell her to come over at 3 o'clock
Okay, thank you
- Alright then - Bye
What should we do?
What is it? Po-erh asked me this morning
Aren't you happy with her coming back?
Yes, I really didn't want her to return
Couldn't even sleep well last night.
Persuade her to go back to Canada
Relax. She's here just for her holidays
You two are meeting after so long
Take her somewhere for fun and enjoyment
Why don't you understand?
She can't stay back
She cannot stay and live here
Do you remember...
why I sent her to Canada?
Why aren't you all willing to believe me?
You would trust me...
when something untoward happens, is it?
Ching-yi
Do you remember, as a child she always...
fell down the stairs for no reason at all;
or even get seriously ill
You go to fetch it
You forgot that when she was four,
she had gone to chase the ball
and almost got knocked down by a car
These things always happen to children
No, it's because of Bei-erh
I saw it myself
She pushed Po-erh everytime
for winning toys
Ching-yi, not again!
I thought you are getting better...
with your mental illness
Who knew it'd strike again after seeing your daughter
Actually, she's been around all these years
Hence I don't even keep Po-erh's photo
You think I don't like to visit Po-erh
But we never go
Anyway, I'm here. Everything will be fine
She'd better leave soon
Don't cry
With time she will forget it all.
We've already forgotten it for so long
Seeing you so flustered,
She will doubt about it all the more
I knew you'd come looking for him
If he could ask Po-erh to return to Canada
I feared she'd overhear so I didn't speak to you
You are not happy with her return
I don't know what's on your mind
Principal Cheung
Please don't spoil my relationship with my daughter
You misunderstand me
No, I don't
For the past twenty odd years,
You've stayed with her more than we have
You go to Canada several times a year
The silly girl assumes you're really fond of her
What do you mean?
What do I mean!
Po-erh is a medical miracle
But it's all for yourself
You just want to complete the medical report
Let me tell you
Don't consider that since my daughter's back
You can drop by every now and then
Excuse me. I've a lunch appointment with a friend
Should you drive that fast?
After seeing the doctor...
Come over for dinner. My parents wanna meet you
No.
Hey, why do you avoid me...
every time?
You wished to come back, I accompanied you
I didn't ask you to
Yes. You didn't
Come to my place for dinner?
Told you I didn't want to
If you don't promise then I won't drive
Why do you always act like that?
Don't be so childish, okay?
Bonnie, I am sincere
However you ought to watch your temper
Honestly, I'm being quite accommodating
I know it's quite hard on you
But I didn't ask you to do that
I just want to be with you
Is there anything wrong with that?
Quiet! My car is broke down
Hey, move your car!
Boy, driving Rolls Royce is not a big deal
Go to hell
Are you sure you can drive?
Please start the car
Then you've got to promise me
Do what you like
- Bonnie - Look out!
I'm sorry
Are you alright?
What's wrong with you?
You almost killed her by driving that fast
Are you blind?
Stop arguing. I'm alright. Get in
Would've sued him if you hadn't stopped me
Are you coming with me to the doctor?
It's hard to believe that...
driving in Hong Kong would be that crazy!
Then you aren't a Hong Kong-ite, is it? Move on
You really need to see this kind of doctor?
Are you okay?
I'm nervous. I would chop people at any time
Principal Cheung asked me to come
I made an appointment for 3 p. M
Miss Kei, please come on in
Take a seat
Okay
Doctor Poon
Okay, bye-bye
Take a seat
Would you like a candy?
On diet?
What's the time now?
3:15 p. M
I'm sitting for an exam. Perhaps I won't succeed
You too?
Hi. I'm not late today, is it?
Doctor has a patient right now, you need to wait
No problem!
What time is it?
I don't know
Why do you drive a motorbike?
Why?
No traffic jam and it could be parked anywhere
You haven't been on one before?
My nervousness- could it turn to dementia?
Won't be that serious.
But last night I can swear I saw a little girl
Perhaps it was just an illusion
Oh no, my perception was real
What do you feel wrong?
I asked uncle to recommend me a specialist
To get a second opinion, sort of
Uncle Cheung said I'm fine. It's just my mind
Okay, come here at 10 a. M tomorrow
- Wendy - Bonnie!
How come you're back in Hong Kong?
Why not? My parents are here
Last year your auntie didn't allow you
How did she agree this year?
God, she's so strict. How did you manage?
You know how old am I this year?
Can't even make my own decisions?
Miss Li
Doctor Poon!
Ask Mr Wong to come.
I'm in a hurry, may I jam in?
But I made an appointment for 3.30 p. M
Dear, let me first!
Bonnie, don't forget to call me!
Who is she?
She was my classmate in Canada
She came back without graduating
We're old friends
She's quite a rightful girl, but a bit naughty
And meeting handsome boys she goes gaga
What's wrong?
Yes! Yes!
It's painful. My stomach!
Nurse Li...
I've never met a shy doctor like you
There you go crazy again!
Don't be angry. I will come to see you often.
What's wrong with you, Miss Chu?
I am tense and always miss you
My heart is beating fast,
just like it would jump out.
That Wendy, does she have a mental disorder?
Don't say like that...
Why else would she come to see a shrink!
The doctor is a neurosurgeon
Whatever!
What good can such a doctor be?
You know, in Canada...
I can easily hire a couple of them for you
Michael
What?
I didn't ask you to pay the bill, did I?
Why on earth do you differentiate
Everything of mine is yours too
Let me make it clear, we're just friends
Don't do anything for me, don't interfere in my life
All I'm saying is, I just care about you
I'd never come to such third-rate doctors
Even then I come along with you
If you like to argue on streets...
you just go ahead
Where are you going? My car is over there
Where are you going?
I need some breathing space
Michael, I can't stand you anymore.
How many times a day you have got mad?
Ms Kei
Doctor Poon. You're leaving
Could you drop me off?
Sure. My bike is right ahead
Please don't! It's dangerous on a bike
Relax, it's alright if she holds me tight
Bonnie... l'll call you tonight
Principal Cheung said that all along...
you've been with your aunt in Canada
Also that you're here just for a few days
You know him very well?
Why are you still here?
Bonnie went off with some friends
I feel totally lost
She has left you behind?
No way
I accompanied her to the doctor. We're quite close
You wouldn't understand
Where are you going right now?
I don't know, it's a bit early for dinner...
Maybe get the car first
You have got a car? That's cool!
Give me a ride
Ok. Where do you want to go?
Didn't you say it's a bit early for dinner?
How about we go shopping at Stanley
I hear there're some real good jeans shops there
Alright then, we'll keep driving around
Come on
It's really your car? Have you borrowed it?
Borrowed? You lend me one then
It's cool with a boyfriend having such a car
That's right
Not many boys would be as lucky as me
I am the only child, you know
I can easily have many cars like these
I will inherit all the business from my father
Oh boy, Bonnie sure is lucky to know you
Of course
Riding in a convertible is such fun!
Sit down! You sit down
I want to fly
Are you crazy? The car is moving
Why're you scared? The road is ours
Why did you move to the back seat?
Don't play with my hair
Stop playing
Don't play. Please sit down immediately
Stop. What are you doing?
Let me drive, okay?
Stop it. Sit down
What's wrong with you? You're such a bother
Don't be that serious. I was just kidding
You call that ' kidding '?
Give me a try
Stop, otherwise you get out of my car
I won't ever date you
I'm friend of Po-erh.
You are her boyfriend
I can't date you, can I?
I just wanted to test you
Sit properly
C'mon, start the car. Should I drive, huh?
Come on
I won't go back to Canada.
Is it alright, daddy?
Okay
Then I'll tidy up the room tomorrow
Oh, no!
Don't touch anything in the baby room
Never
I'd say that bed is not more than four feet
How can you expect our daughter to sleep there?
What would you do staying back in Hong Kong?
Think about how much your aunt would miss you
I'd rather you call auntie and ask her
I just ask, who is my mom; you or her?
Po-erh!
I was just a few years old when you sent me there
You've hardly given a thought to me all these years
Sometimes I doubt if I am your daughter!
Po-erh!
Okay. If you don't like me...
I would move out tomorrow
Po-erh!
No more. Just this bag left, Mr. Janitor
And to say being abroad all these years
Nothing you've learnt, but making fun of your dad
I love you, I just love you!
Right, I'd like to invite you all for a dinner together
Great! We'll go to your father's...
- Bamboo restaurant - That's it
Okay then
I have an appointment tonight
lt'd be fun; you both are invited
Right
Is it a boy or girl?
Whatever! None of your business
Who is he?
Your boyfriend?
Poon Chi-ching.
- He? - Him?
Who is he?
Please
Uncle Cheung
Come sit here
You're naughty
Going home with someone you've hardly known!
It's his idea to bring you here on your birthday
Happy Birthday!
What is it?
Open it and see
Thank you, Uncle Cheung
What do you think?
It's really pretty
Do you like it?
Of course. I'll put it on right now
Just a small gift. Happy Birthday
Thank you
Let me get you some drink
This wasn't my idea, I swear
No...
Put this on
Thanks
Without doubt, your house is haunted
Now you're really scaring me
Who is scaring you!
My driver said your place used to be a burial ground
Don't say it!
You're more likely to see a ghost if you're scared
What?
I've heard that if your forehead looks black...
You will see a ghost sooner or later
What is it? Where?
Here! Bad luck is here!
Where?
Right here
I can't see
Right here. You see
Sorry, I've to go first
I got a little sick. I am leaving too
I'll drop you off
No need. Bye
Goodbye
You stay with Miss Chu for a while
Actually we both are headed the same way
Where do we go afterwards?
Do you really feel sick?
Couldn't you feel that...
Wendy's got a crush on Michael?
I just brought romance to a happy ending
Isn't it for both of them and yourself?
Why? Why?
What are you doing?
I've known you for two years, and he?
Michael, I told you before
What is it?
Think you can woo her just because you're a doctor
What is it that I'm not good at?
Be mature. Okay?
We will never be together
But he?
You totally don't understand.
Oh, I told him to take her home first
- Oh yeah? - Yes
- Is it? - Yes
- Yes? - Yes
Don't be upset. Revenge is the key
Daddy, Mommy
Come, let me introduce
My daddy, mommy
And he is doctor Poon Chi-ching
How are you?
Uncle, Auntie
Where are you going?
- For a movie - For tea
Yes. We'll be back soon
Sit for a while
Tonight we'll have dinner together
We have to leave, see you
Bye bye
Daddy, mommy
Who is she?
She's your sister, died from meningoencephalitis
Hello
Doctor Poon
It's you, what's up?
Doctor Poon. Hurry over to my place
God knows why Po-erh is feeling depressed and sick
She is not willing to see any doctor either
lt'd be wonderful if you can come immediately
Ask her to talk to me
She doesn't want to. She won't speak to you either
Okay. You come over right away
Alright, you stay with her
As soon as possible. Bye
Bye Bye
I just feel it's not a good idea
What's wrong with it?
Don't you wanna take revenge?
You have called him and he is coming
What should I do?
Hide yourself in the kitchen first
I've never done it before
What's there to be scared of? Go into the room!
Hi!
Where is Po-erh?
Come in first
Sit down
Where is Po-erh? How is she?
What would you like to drink?
Nothing. Is she gone?
You seems nervous
Bet you wouldn't be here that fast had it been for me
If Po-erh is not here, I'd better leave
I've got things to do
She is inside the room, come along
Come on
Where is Po-erh? She is not here?
What Po-erh? Do you know how much I miss you?
Miss Chu
Miss Chu, don't play with me
No, I'm serious
Miss Chu
You know I love you. I love you very much
You're crazy! Stop doing that
Day and night I think of you
Stop it
So this is how you see your patients!
No one would believe you anymore
I'm warning you, keep away from my girlfriend
I will show her these pictures
I'm sure she'll detest you hereafter
You...
Me? It's my house
I can do anything I want
You're naive. To think she'd trust you two!
Well? Is my idea good enough?
I don't see any reason to get scared
I hate her
I want her to jump down the roof by herself
Bei-erh. Bei-erh...
Don't do it. Come out. She is your sister
Don't. Let me out
Bei-erh. Don't do it. Bei-erh
Let me out please
Why are you yelling inside?
I can't open the door
Can't open the door
Quick, follow me
Po-erh is on the roof. Something will happen.
Let's go
What? Po-erh is on the roof?
Po-erh. Po-erh...
Po-erh, what are you doing?
Po-erh...
Don't go further, Po-erh!
Po-erh!
Po-erh...
Po-erh
Uncle and auntie. What has happened with Po-erh?
Chi-ching...
Po-erh has been there for long...
Why would she be that careless?
I don't know why she would go on the roof
How is Po-erh?
It's alright. It's just a minor injury
It's lucky there was something as the cushion
Could she leave the hospital tonight?
Not yet. She needs observation
I'll stay with her then
No need. She's fine and you should go have a rest
Principal Cheung said it's ok
You don't understand that
It's all my fault
Because of me she has this sleepwalking illness
Let's go home and talk it over
No. I'm not going home. Let me be here
If you wish you can go back home yourself
Which room is she in?
Nurse, bring her to room 108
I've got to go
Principal Cheung, I have something to ask you
I want to see Po-erh's medical history
Her case is getting more serious
If you really want to help her
Please let me have her medical history
Sorry, without the consent of her parents
I can't give it to you
You know her mother has been to the phrenitis hospital
For the betterment of Po-erh and her mother
I suggest you mind your own business
Since you knew she has sleepwalking disorder
Why don't you take her to see a brain specialist?
It's all her own imagination
You're not cheating her but wish to keep it from me
It's late. Let's talk about it some other time
What exactly are you trying to hide?
Tell me, principal Cheung!
You're fortunate enough to be saved last time
I won't let you go
I'll let you know how it feels like to die unjustly
Help!
What's the matter?
Ghost.
Where is it?
She was staring at me on the bed
No. Po-erh
I am not staying here. I must leave
This place is haunted. I don't want to stay here
I've got to move out
I've to return home...
She is staring at me
I don't want to stay here, Mom
You two shared one brain
Without surgery, both of you would have died
Why did they hide it from me all this time?
It's all for you. They don't want to affect you
Don't be upset. I understand your feeling
I looked at her and she looked...
It seemed as if she really hates me
It's real...
She kept staring at me...
Calm down. It's your illusion
There just aren't any ghosts in this world
You listen to me. No
She is unfortunate,
but she is not the sufferer
Your mother suffers the most
She went crazy after giving birth to siamese twins
Later she had to be admitted to the phrenitis hospital
You have to forgive your mom. Only you can help
Where is Po-erh?
Chi-ching has brought her out
Chi-ching has seen Po-erh's medical history
What?
How could you let him get away with it?
This is all just because I trust you
You don't need to say this
Where is Bei-erh?
It's your great work!
Bei-erh
Ching-yi, you've just got one daughter
Po-erh is your only daughter
She is living with you. Don't think too much
No!
Give me back my Bei-erh
I have two daughters
Bei-erh...
Bei-erh is in this house
Get out, you get out.
You killed my daughter...
and made my wife get a serious phrenitis
And what're you going to do now?
Not enough for me?
I don't understand your words
You don't
If you weren't sure in the past you should've stayed away
I won't let you kill my daughter
I had told you that...
the chance of the surgery is 50%
If you didn't sign the paper, I won't...
I should've known better
Yes. I admit that the surgery failed
But if it was a success,
one of them would've surely turned out insane
I would rather have an idiot daughter...
instead of pushing my wife into pain
I suggest you to take her away from this house
Don't let her live in the past
I am not leaving!
Bei-erh will be alone if I left
I will not go. You get out. And you
You leave. I don't want to see you
Both of you, get out
Ching-yi! Go and rest
Get out
Listen to me. Ching-yi
Ching-yi!
Leave me alone. Get off
Let her bite
Release
Ching-yi
Let her rest on the sofa
Send her to hospital immediately
Why did you punch her so hard?
Hadn't I done that she'd have bitten you to death
You always hit your wife
Nothing is good when you're here
No brake!
Watch out...
Why the car can't stop?
It's Principal Cheung's car
Go to have a look.
- Uncle Cheung - Principal Cheung
Be careful
Daddy
Uncle
Daddy...
- Uncle... - Daddy...
Quick!
- Mommy - Auntie
What's wrong? Mommy
Auntie
Do you recognise me? I'm Michael
You father must hate me a lot
He didn't come just because he is busy
He will never forgive me
We've to go out for a while
Auntie, take some rest. Don't think too much
Wake me up if your father comes
I've got lots to tell him. Don't forget
I haven't seen principal for all day long, why?
You get some sleep. We'll soon be back with you
Mommy, I will stay with you
Don't cry
They are so unlucky
Lower your voice. Auntie might hear
Wendy and I will stay with you...
and you won't be afraid of the dark
It is an accident. A person can't live two lives
Don't be so upset
Let's go
Eat something. Don't keep silent all day
You have to eat something
We'll go sailing tomorrow
My brother'll lend me a yacht. We'll have lots of seafood
Daddy
Let's talk tomorrow
How about we go to a disco tonight!
I don't feel like. You two go together
Hello
Thank you. Kei Po-erh
- Doctor Poon? - Yes
Don't bother me
She doesn't want... No... She...
Stop calling her anymore
I'm here. You're not needed
Hello
Go out for a while
No
I'm downstairs
Then it's okay
I'm going out for some time. I'll return soon
Where are you going?
Sit here first
It's late at night. I'll accompany you
No need
Damn it. It makes me sick
Could you tell me why?
I came back from Canada with her
I accompany her no matter where she goes
Also went with her to see such a doctor
However she isn't willing to come home once for dinner
What? You like to bring others home for dinner?
She has no time for a drive,
no time for a dance
No no and no for all day
A boyfriend like me,
what's wrong?
I can stand. I can wait
Even for my own dad I don't show such patience
Don't be angry. Who the hell asked you to do all that?
You don't know. Po-erh is conservative
She is...
What?
Have some wine, I've got lots to tell you
Here
Sorry
Why is it so difficult for you to face the truth?
What happened to your dad and uncle is an accident
Don't try to blame yourself
This way it's likely you'll go crazy
Get real, Po-erh. This is 20th century
There simply aren't any ghosts
It's all your imagination
There is no ghost in the world. Listen to me
I already explained to you your mystery
Why a surgery for Siamese twins...
would have such impact on you?
Face the truth
It's just that you don't accept the reality
I've seen her with my own eyes more than once
I always feel that she is hovering around me
Yes, her death is indeed unfair;
since she died, not me
But now, haven't I lost everything?
This is fate. How could you fight against it?
It's not fate. It's human
Had they made a different decision...
Daddy and uncle Cheung won't be dead
Nothing would have happened...
if I'd never have come back to Hong Kong
Po-erh, calm down
I am your doctor. Let me help you
How would you help me?
Yours is illusion. Mine is truth
What is the different between illusion and reality?
Po-erh
Anyway, you can't help me
Doctor, doctor...
Does a doctor always make correct decision?
Are you saying a doctor can't be wrong, huh?
Yes. I was saved by the operation,
but how about my sister?
She is gone and it's not fair
There isn't anything such as 'fair' in this world
I'd say don't dwell on it too much
It's easier said than done
Presently my father and uncle are dead
It's not related to you
You asked me out...
just to tell me not to think too much
I don't need your comfort
I just need you to trust me
Ok. You come to my clinic tomorrow
and I'll give you a body check
Bullshit!
Po-erh!
It seems someone is back home
Huh, someone's back home?
Hurry, put on the clothes
Where're my clothes?
Be quick, put this on
Hey, this isn't mine
Whatever!
Quick. Where is my sweater?
I... she is
Goodnight
Bonnie...
Do you want some food?
Wendy and I, actually...
Where are you going?
Michael. Michael!
Michael, what are you doing?
Help, help me!
Michael, let go of her
Damn, how could I have killed him!
What shall we do?
Who are you calling?
The police!
No, I'll be totally finished
Let's call doctor Poon
Nobody? Come on!
Now what? C'mon, hurry up. Answer the phone
At this late an hour!
Why're your hands so cold? Sit down
I'll get you some hot tea
Po-erh! What are you doing?
Po-erh... what are you doing?
Po-erh, are you mad?
Po-erh, don't!
Po-erh
What are you doing? No
Po-erh, are you crazy?
Po-erh
No...
You're not Po-erh. Who are you?
I can't get through
What then?
Never mind, let's just go there
Go over to his place?
Never mind, let's just go
Doctor Poon
The door is open. Let's go in
What a mess!
Doctor Poon?
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
What's wrong? Doctor Poon
Wendy...
Bonnie
Help!
Wendy...
Po-erh, why would I be like this?
What's wrong with her? Tell me
What happened here? Please tell me
Tell me...
Chi-ching...
Mommy, come play with me
Daddy and uncle Cheung are not good at playing
Where is your father and sister?
Mommy, come and stay with me!
Ok...
But you've to promise not to hurt your sister
Po-erh. You better leave
America, Canada or wherever
You've to come along as well
I'll book the tickets
I'm afraid mom wouldn't want to leave
You must convince her
Mommy, we must leave this place
Leave? We can't escape
If you don't leave, then I'll stay here too
You'd better go as soon as possible
Mommy, I'm really scared!
Well, let's get our luggage packed
Great. I'll go to take the flight tickets now
Wait for my call. Don't forget your passports
I'll go and complete the discharge formalities
Without delay we've to get moving
I know
Po-erh
What is it, mom?
I know you're reluctant to leave Hong Kong
But in Canada, I'll be there...
as well as auntie to keep you company, isn't it?
Then you'd better pack up quickly
It's almost time for the flight
And you too, hurry up
Bei-erh. Show up, dear. Mommy has to leave
Let me see you once again
You blame mommy, isn't it? Please show up
Bei-erh. You come out now, honey
It isn't that mommy doesn't love you
You've grown up. You don't need me anymore
Bei-erh. Come to me
Mommy, you don't like me anymore...
Mommy, you don't like me
But I won't let you go. You said you'll be with me
You always favor Po-erh. I'm also your daughter
Mommy! Mommy
Hey, where's auntie? It's getting late!
The flight is about to depart
Where're the passports? What's wrong?
I have even got the plane tickets
Doctor Poon!
Chi-ching...