Hi,Mike
Are you studying again?
Do you realize how depressing that is to come home to?
As depressing as coming home to an empty lasagna tray?
Touch? michael.
It's just a reminder of the fact that I have no social life out here.
I'm having  the worst dry spell ever.
My dry spell's lasted 20 years, but go on.
I mean, in new york, if you see a pretty girl, you can just walk right up to her, you know?
But here, they're all in cars. They go whipping past me at, like, a million miles an hour.
You know, like today, I saw this pretty girl driving toward me,
so I make a u-turn ,and get a ticket for 800 bucks!
$800 for a u-turn?
Yeah.
We may have been on a freeway at the time, but...
I just wish I had a regular place where I could go and meet women
Well, you could go to bars.
No, I'm getting too old for that.
Plus, I'm not great at telling whether or not they're gay bars before I go in.
Oh, by the way, if ramon calls, I am not here
影音工作室
YYETS小组
英文字幕:Johnsonh
中文字幕: skier_man   paulyang
时间轴制作: Requiem
校对: skier_man   小鬼神
Joey 104
Enjoy！
Hey
Joey, come here .Look at this.
The world is a freakin' joke
Cargo pants are five minutes ago? The world is a freakin' joke!
No, the thing about the celebrity hairstylist.
I went to cosmetology school with that girl
She burned way more hair than I did, and I burned some hair.
And now I have to read about her living the glamorous life, and rubbing elbows with celebrities.
That should be me.
You cut my hair. I'm on tv
No offense
but you're only slightly more famous than my client who shot her husband.
Hello, giant plate of sandwiches
Joey, listen...
oh, hey, michael. Didn't even see you there.
Hands off.
These are for my book club tonight
A book club here,
in my own home?
God, it's like I'm living at the playboy mansion.
Stay away from the sandwiches. Watch him, mom.
I can't believe this.
It's so upsetting when people with less talent than you are more successful.
Yeah, like that dog from my beer commercial.
Couldn't catch a frisbee on cue. Works all the time.
You should ask your agent to hook me up.
She has lots of famous clients that need to get their hair done
Just show her my portfolio. I am sure she will be impressed
Well, I can show it to her, but I'm not so sure she'll be impressed.
All the hairstyles are modeled by michael-- even the women'S
So?
So,that dorothy hamill haircut with the heavy makeup?
We're lucky he's not burying bodies in the backyard.
Joey
what are you doing here?
Why aren't you out there getting work?
Uh, I didn't have any auditions today.
Oh, sure, put it all on me
What's that?
Oh, it's a portfolio of hairstyles.
what?
Oh! Who's the model?
Oh, I'd like to keep that little piece of chicken in my pocket and snack on him all day
Uh, that's my nephew.
Oh, we can see who has the looks in your family
Anyway,
my sister is a hairdresser
that's her portfolio I was hoping maybe you could show it to some of your clients.
Oh, absolutely.
Hi, halle berry?
My client has a sister who's a barber.
Could she do your hair for the oscars?
What did she say?
Joey,
I'm not here to do you personal favors.
Let me explain how this agent thing works.
First you become famous, and then
I'll kiss your ass.
But until then, let's keep it strictly professional.
Okay.
Sorry. I understand.
Leave the pictures of the boy toy.
Well, hello.
Are you here for book club?
I am now.
What did you think of this week's book?
I... found it extremely fictional
Uh, joey, joey, can I just talk to you for one second?
Uh, yeah.
Sorry.
What are you doing?
You didn't tell me there were pretty ladies in the nerd club.
You got to let me in.
Look, I don't know.
Hey, come on, michael.
You can't keep me out of a room full of women.
If I was in charge of a room full of boring stuff, I'd let you in.
This isn't one of those book clubs where people come to mingle, all right?
It's a place to discuss literature, not pick up girls.
Oh, my god, jane's here. Jane.
Hi, michael. I brought an ice cream cake.
That's great. It's great to see you.
Uh, great book, huh?
So great. It was little slow at the beginning,
but great overall.Did you think it was great?
The cake is cold. My hands are getting numb.
Not a place to pick up girls ,huh?
What, jane? No way. No, are you kidding?
No, I would never...
great, great, g-great, great, g-g-great, great, great, g-g-g-g-great, great
all right.
I love her so much.
So, so, ask her out.
No, book club has a strict no-datingule, and I'm the president.
She's my vice-president. The scandal would tear our administration apart.
Michael, you have to seize this moment.
he love between two nerds is a rare and fragileT thing.
I want to. I can't go against the rules
without a motion being passed.
So, I'll make a motion.
You're not a member. There's an approval process.
Well, I motion you suspend it on account of me
being the sole payer of rent for the book club's headquarters.
I second the motion. The motion is passed.
I motion for a presidential exemption to the no-dating rule.
I second the motion; the motion is passed.
I motion that you and me eat that entire ice cream cake right now!
Motion denied!
Mr. Chairman, you're out of order!
Great book club tonight.
Lively discussion,
and I got five phone numbers.
Yeah, the girls were crazy about you.
What's your secret?
There's no trick.
Women just want to be listened to.
So, when they talk, I pretend to listen and go like this.
Hey, so, how'd it go with jane?Did you ask her out?
No, I want to wait till next week's meeting so I can set the mood.
So, I picked a romantic book, and I asked her to come over right
before to help me write out the discussion questions.
Nice, nice. What's the book?
Jane austen's pride and prejudice.
It's a tale of manners and courtship set in 19th century rural england.
I hope you enjoy reading that.
Joey,
if you're going to be in this book club, you have to read the book.
The whole notion of... stop that!
Stop it!
Hey, guys.
Hi, mom.
So, is your agent going to send me any clients?
Uh, no. Actually, bobbie's been very busy, so I don't know if you should expect a call.
Your agent?
She did call.
Really?
Yeah, it was weird. She called me her little chicken nugget, then made a bunch of slurping noises.
That's just showbiz talk
I can't believe you don't know anyone famous.
If you hadn't turned down that hit show you'd have so many connections that could help me right now.
Yeah, that's what I regret most about that decision.
hey, I'm sorry to bug you, but, uh, did you get some of my mail by mistake?
I didn't get my people magazine and the post office said they delivered it today.
Gina, weren't you reading that earlier?
What's the problem? I'm not good enough to steal your magazine?
Alex, I think it's upstairs. Have a seat.
No, that's okay. You don't have to leave us alone.
So, tell me, do you...?
This isn't a social hour. What famous people
you know?
Oh. Well, um, my college friend jessica
is married to a big-time movie producer.
So, does she wear really expensive gowns and get her hair all done up and go to big premieres?
Yeah, all the time. She goes to one every week.
Oh, you're lying to impress me.
No, I'm not lying. She's a really good friend of mine.
Yeah, right. I'd like to see you ask her to let me do her hair for her next premiere.
All right, I will.
Wait, what just happened?
I'm really good, I swear. I just need a chance.
If you call her and set it up, I'll be nice to you.
For how long?
Name your terms.
Two weeks.
Done.
I should have said three.
Now you're down to one.
oh
Hey.
Hello.
Tonight at book club, don't have diane sit next to maureen.
Why?
I may be dating both of them exclusively.
oh, my god, that's jane.
All right, I'll get out of your hair until book club startsI'll be in my room reading the book
and listening to some soft rock hits of the '70s
Can you believe someone threw this out?
Hi.
Whoa! Uh, come in. I'm sorry. You just, you look great.
Thanks. You look... I don't know.
I can't see without my glasses.
I probably shouldn't have driven here.
So, uh...
did you enjoy the book?
Oh, yeah.
It's pretty romantic.
Very.
So, I wanted to ask you...
Don't mind me! Just grabbing a snack.Reading makes me hungry
I'm sorry. He'S... um, so...
just call me angel of the morning, angel
just touch my cheek before you leave...
so, I was, I was just thinking that maybe we could...
loosen up the rules of book club.
Oh, okay.
Like maybe we could strike the no-dating rule from the bylaws?
Oh, yes, let's do that!
Okay. Consider it stricken.
Okay, great. So, we can date people in book club?
Yes, we can.
So, what's up with your uncle?
I'm sorry?
Do you think he would go out with me?
He mentioned he was single last time, and I was hoping you could say something for me
I'm going to go read in the courtyard!
Give you two some privacy.
Four down, 371 to go.
Hey.
I just wanted to tell you guys to be sure to watch tv tonight.
I just did alex's frand she's going to be on the red carpet.iend's hair for a premiere,
Oh, how did it go?
Oh, I was a little nervous at first. She's a very fancy lady.
She was drinking martinis, and sitting with her legs crossed.
But then I got into it, and instinct just took over.
I did this beautiful old hollywood style up-do.
Congratulations. All right!
I'm gonna go tell michael.
No, no, no no, no, no, no. He's in there with a girl.
Okay, he's in there with a girl, and you're reading books?
What is this, freaky friday?
All right. I guess I'll go tell blondie how it went.
Uh, call her alex. You promised you were gonna be nice.
Yeah, only one more day of that, and some stuff is gonna happen.
five minutes left. I got to buckle down.
Hey, little snail!
Hi, joey.
Diane. Maureen. Uh, you two know each other?
Oh, yeah, we're good friends.
I did not know that.
Come on in.
Hi, joey.
What's up?
listen, michael, I didn't exactly finish the book, okay? So, don't call on me.
You're unbelievable.
What?
Come here.
What's the matter?Did you ask jane out?
No, I didn't ask her out, 'cause she wants to go out with you!
Oh, dude, I'm so sorry. Ob-obviously, I would never...
you totally screwed this up for me!
But I didn't mean to. I barely said two words to her.
You didn't have to. You came to last week's meeting with your game face on,looking to score, and it worked, all right?
You're like a big blob of sex, and you...
you oozed your charm all over the girl I like.
I am not a sex blob. Okay?
And this is not my fault! Look, I'm sorry if she likes me, but I didn't do anything wrong.
I should never have let you in.
Uh, should we get started?
Come, joey,let's go talk about the book we all read.Yes.
Okay, nothing past page four.
Hey, I wanted to call and tell you what a great time...
uh, book club is starting, everybody. Book club! Hee-hee. Book club.
Okay, so, who wants to start?
I thought...
joey, what did you think of pride and prejudice?
Let's hear it. What were some of the central themes?
Uh... uh, well, pride was one.
Mm. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And, of course, prejudice, which is wrong.
Uh, uh-huh. And what did you think of darcy?
She was good.
Darcy's a man.
But not in the modern sense
Is that what you're saying, joey?
Uh, yes, it is. Yes, it is, maureen. Thank you.
that's interesting.
That's very interesting.
Look, he didn't read the book! The only reason he's here is to pick up women!
Now, in the interest of maintaining the integrity of book club
,I motion that we kick joey out. Who seconds?
Come on! He didn't read theook.
Neither did I.
Me, neither.
I saw the movie.
There was a movie?!
Did-did anyone here read the book?
You put too muchressure on us, michael. A book a week?
It's just really gotten very stressful.
How is reading stressful?!
Reading is fun!
It's fun!
OK,Let's not turn to a hostage situation
If you want me to leave, I will.
No!
Okay, you know what? I'm-I'm just gonna go.
okay, it's almost time for the big premiere. I made popcorn.
Nice place.
Oh. Who's the knockout in the tiara?
Oh, that's my sister nancy. She was queen of the rose parade.
Hmm. You're cute,  but maybe you shouldn't stand next to her in family pictures
Yeah, that's what my mom says.
Yeah, I really appreciate you helping me out. I mean, I know I mess with you sometimes,
but it's just for fun.
Oh, yeah. That is fun.
So, this is actually kind of nice. Being friendly.
Maybe we could keep it up a little longer than a week.
Mm. I physically can'T.
Oh. Oh, my god, it's on!
Oh. Mmm-mmm. Look at george clooney. I would wear him down to a nub.
Yeah, I would... have bunches of sex with him.
Oh, my god, i think that's jessica's husband getting out of the limo!
Oh, my god, this is exciting! Oh, there she is!
O Oh, wow.
She actually looks really good.
Uh, uh, not that I'm surprised.I mean, when I said "actually," I didn't mean that...
what?
What's wrong?
Sh-she took it down.
What?!
That wasn't the style I gave her. Sh-she must have taken it out in the limo.
Sh... she hated it.
I can't believe this.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I knew when I walked in there,  I was out of my league,
but I spent two hours trying to fake it.
Oh, no.
Um, there, there.
I can't believe I ever thought I could do this.
I just don't fit in with rich people.They look down on me. They always have,and they always will.
With their grammar and their leg-crossing, and...
hey,
don't be saying that, girlfriend.
Okay, look, I grew up with money, and I don't look down on you.
If anything, I envy you.
Oh, come on.
It's true.
I wish I were as strong and as confident as you.
And if it were me, I'd be more than happy to have you do my hair.
Really?
You mean that?
Absolutely.
So, can we do it right now?
Now?
Oh, now seems so soon.
Look, michael, it's joey. I know you're mad,
but I hope you come home soon so we can talk about how you're feeling and work this out.
And also, if you get a chance to pick up some tacos or something on your way home
that would be great.
hey.
Look, uh,
I know you're upset because jane liked me, all right?
But I hope you know, I would never come between you and a girl, all right?
And I really did not mean for that to happen.
Oh, I know you didn'T.
That... that's the problem.
What?
It'S... it's gonna happen whether yotry or not
you know? Any time I actually get a girl and bring her home she'll take one look at you, and she'll forget I'm even here.
Hey, come on, give yourself some credit.
Michael, you have so many gifts that I don't have.
You're really smart.
People respect your opinion about stuff. That's a great thing.
Maybe, you know?
I'd still rather have your gifts
Yeah, me, too.
Hey, but believe me
you are on your way to big things
Okay, because you're only gonna get better with girls and stuff
but I'll always suck at math.
You know? In, like, five years, you are gonna be a force to be reckoned with.
Yeah?
And in five years
you'll be 40.
You got a lot of your mother in you, don't you?
Okay, ladies and gentlemen, modeling an original gina tribbiani hairstyle called the nice 'n nasty...
I give you alex garrett.
Whoa! Now that's a neighbor.
come on. Get your camera.I want to get some pictures.
You look so different. I-I can't believe you own an outfit that slutty.
Hey, that's mine. I wear that to church.
You're very nice to be such a good sport.
Can I tell you something?
I love it.
I feel like julia roberts in pretty woman.
Oh. You know she was a hooker, right?
Yes. I have to go look at myself in the mirror again.
Joey,I've got a great news
did I get that commerical?
No, I bought a horse.
Joey,come on I gotta get to school
OH,hi,I'm Michael
Have a seat
Joey I completely forgot
There's a 重播的支票 in the accounting department
Why don't you go and grab it
All right I'll be right back
So, Michael
How do you feel full frontal nudity
I'm not an actor
Oh,yes,I know