有 很 多 人 问...
天 下 最 美 的 地 方 在 哪 里 ?
天 下 最 美 的 地 方 是 移 花 宫
有 很 多 人 问...
天 下 武 功 最 高 的 女 孩 子 是 谁 ?
江 湖 上 武 功 最 高 的 女 孩 子 是
移 花 宫 主
现 在 移 花 宫 正 在 欢 宴
天 下 第 一 才 子 江 枫
因 为 她 爱 上 了 他...
不 幸 的 是 江 枫 看 中 的
却 是 她 的 贴 身 侍 婢 花 月 奴
两 个 人 偷 偷 的 相 爱
在 花 前 月 下 , 卿 卿 我 我
不 幸 这 件 事 很 快 给 移 花 宫 主 知 道
所 以 他 们 被 逼 着 偷 偷 的 离 开 移 花 宫
躲 在 万 花 崖 上 , 而 且 生 了 两 个 孩 子
日 子 倒 过 得 非 常 非 常 幸 福
可 惜 好 景 不 常
江 枫 给 他 的 管 家 江 琴 出 卖 了
移 花 宫 主 十 分 愤 怒
马 上 到 万 花 崖 , 杀 死 两 个 人
但 是 人 虽 死 , 恨 却 未 消
移 花 宫 主 , 看 着 他 们 的 两 个 孩 子
想 出 一 个 天 下 最 毒 的 毒 计
她 趁 着 江 南 大 侠 燕 南 天
还 不 知 道 江 枫 有 两 个 孩 子 之 前
命 人 把 其 中 一 个 儿 子
叫 人 送 给 江 枫 的 义 兄 燕 南 天
并 且 告 诉 他 出 卖 江 枫 的 江 琴
逃 到 了 恶 人 谷
燕 南 天 知 道 了 , 马 上 就 赶 去
"神剑大侠燕南天之灵位"
想 杀 我 , 人 呢 ?
人 在 这 里
我 早 就 说 过 天 下 第 一 神 剑 燕 南 天
绝 不 是 好 对 付 的
你 来 这 儿 干 什 么 ?
我 来 找 出 卖 我 义 弟 的 江 琴
快 点 把 他 交 出 来
否 则 我 燕 某 今 天 就 踏 平 你 们 恶 人 谷
好 大 的 口 气
走
"江枫之灵位"
义 弟 ...
我 们 早 就 想 过
在 江 湖 上 能 伤 燕 南 天 的
只 有 他 最 好 的 朋 友 江 枫
果 然 , 连 死 去 的 江 枫
也 能 点 中 了 你 的 如 泉 穴 , 插 了 两 刀
你 是 谁 ?
我 是 色 中 饿 鬼 , 白 开 心
我 是 半 人 半 鬼 的 阴 九 幽
我 是 半 女 半 男 的 屠 娇 娇
唉 哟 , 你 好 棒
那 你 一 定 是 专 吃 人 肉 的 李 大 嘴
那 又 怎 样 ?
跟 笑 里 藏 刀 的 哈 哈 儿
燕 南 天 , 江 琴 骗 你 来
就 是 要 我 们 把 你 杀 掉
你 怎 么 有 三 只 手 ?
那 只 不 过 是 我 吃 剩 的 一 只 人 手
哈 哈 儿 , 接 著
恶 人 谷 里 面 的 人 , 不 是 好 惹 的
把 他 杀 了
住 手
万 春 流 ...
把 他 交 给 我
为 什 么 ?
他 伤 成 这 个 样 子 , 你 们 不 动 手
他 也 活 不 到 明 天
如 果 你 们 把 他 交 给 我
对 你 们 都 有 好 处
什 么 好 处 呀 ?
你 们 抓 我 来
无 非 是 替 你 们 医 治 奇 难 杂 症
如 果 你 们 将 他 交 给 我
让 我 作 为 试 验 草 药 之 用
不 是 对 各 位 都 有 好 处 吗 ?
老 大
这 条 漏 网 之 鱼 , 怎 么 办 ?
什 么 怎 么 办 , 当 然 是 我 吃 , 拿 来
慢
老 大 , 你 常 说 世 上 恶 人 太 少
把 这 条 鱼 儿
教 成 天 下 间 最 恶 毒 的 人 , 怎 么 样 ?
嗯 , 这 主 意 好 新 鲜
扎 马 要 低 一 点
还 不 到 两 个 时 辰 , 想 偷 懒 呀
叔 叔 , 我 好 累 呀
哦 , 你 累 了
哦
叔 叔 , 好 疼 呀
什 么 , 你 好 疼 ?
是 呀 , 好 疼 呀 , 叔 叔
疼 不 疼 ?
好 疼 …
要 学 打 人 , 先 要 捱 得 疼
不 准 哭 , 要 笑
我 好 辛 苦 , 笑 不 出 来
你 笑 不 出 来 也 要 笑
笑 , 笑 得 多 一 点
对 了 … 笑 得 甜 一 点
这 样 笑
你 长 大 了 要 记 着
你 以 后 在 敌 人 最 开 心 的 时 候
出 手 杀 人 是 最 适 合 的 啦
握 紧 拳 头
握 紧 拳 头 , 还 有 走 近 人 的 身 边
就 先 发 制 人
里 面 有 条 狗 , 你 进 去 杀 了 给 我 吃
天 下 事 就 是 这 样
不 是 他 死 , 就 是 你 亡 , 进 去
去
多 喝 点 … 对
发 财 … 五 个 三 …
喝 …
你 有 狗 肉 吃 , 不 要 吃 我 了
小 鱼 儿
来 啰
什 么 事 ? 又 要 杀 狗 了 ?
简 单 呢 , 十 条 还 是 二 十 条 啊 ?
杀 狗 用 不 着 刀 , 用 这 棵 草 就 可 以 了
李 叔 叔 , 烧 水
啊 …
老 … 老 … 老 虎 , 老 虎
唉
够 坚 固 了 吧 ?
当 然 坚 固 , 不 然 老 虎 跑 出 来 了
怎 么 办 ?
李 叔 叔 , 放 了 我 吧
小 鱼 儿 , 记 住 白 叔 叔 的 话
当 自 己 处 于 下 风 的 时 候
千 万 别 求 人 , 去
走
进 去
锁 上
唉 …
等 一 等
干 什 么 ?
这 房 子 有 很 多 栏 杆 松 了
我 怕 老 虎 会 跑 出 来 吃 你 们 呢
啊 …
不 会 吧 ?
进 去 看 看
好
诶
你 干 什 么 ?
没 什 么 , 请 …
哼
啊 … 啊
请 你 们 三 个 人 自 己 去 喂 老 虎 吧
钥 匙 在 我 这 儿
啊 … 你 …
你 要 打 人 , 先 得 捱 疼
哎 哟
哎 呀
哈 哈 …
都 是 你 , 当 初 你 还 怕 不 够 坚 固
行 了 , 别 啰 唆 了 , 快 想 办 法
唉 …
不 要 …
啊 …
哦 …
哟 …
啊 …
不 敢 , 不 敢 了 ...
小 鱼 儿 , 你 …
这 个 网 我 做 好 了
我 已 经 等 你 两 个 月 了
哎 哟
快 … 快 …
哎 哟 …
快 拉 我 一 把 …
啊 …
快 拉 我 上 去 哟
哎 哟 …
啊 … 哎 哟
好 小 子
哎 哟 …
这 叫 做 袋 里 有 乾 坤
啊 …
哈 哈 …
我 要 吃 人 了
哎 哟 …
嘿 …
下 次 不 敢 了 , 你 饶 了 我 吧
哼 ！我 看 你 还 能 逃 到 哪 里 去
千 万 别 过 来 …
别 过 来
啊 …
快 放 我 出 来
你 想 找 死 呀 ？
李 叔 叔
这 个 桶 是 屠 伯 伯 用 来 洗 脚 的 水
味 道 还 不 错 吧
好 臭 , 你 快 点 放 我 出 来
好 臭 呀
快 放 我 出 来
李 叔 叔 , 烧 熟 了 , 你 自 个 儿 吃 自 己
这 叫 做 不 是 你 死 , 就 是 我 亡
再 见 了
好 热 , 小 鱼 儿
快 拉 我 出 来
嘿 … 还 不 能 上 来 呀 , 要 不 要 我 来 帮 手 呀 ?
哎 呀 …
哎 哟 …
来 …
小 鱼 儿 , 我 求 求 你
你 放 了 我 吧
这 个 机 关 叫 过 桥 抽 板
我 已 经 做 了 三 天 了
三 天 了 , 我 求 求 你 …
白 叔 叔 , 你 不 是 说 过 吗 ?
当 人 处 于 下 风 的 时 候
千 万 不 要 求 人 ，呐
唉 ，小 鱼 儿 ，唉 …
唉
我 小 的 时 候 , 你 不 是 常 常 让 我 笑 吗 ?
笑
笑 甜 一 点
哈 哈 …
就 是 这 样
你 想 不 想 出 去 ?
我 想 …
你 真 的 想 , 我 有 办 法
我 把 老 虎 放 出 来
你 不 想 出 来 都 不 行
老 虎 , 你 不 要 放 … !
救 命 呀 ! 不 要 放 呀 !
怎 么 小 鱼 儿 , 你 又 受 伤 了 ?
不 , 我 已 经 把 他 们 治 服 了
我 要 走 了
啊 , 你 走 呀 ?
要 不 要 跟 我 一 块 走 ?
不 , 我 好 几 次 想 走
可 是 为 了 给 他 们 医 怪 病
都 被 抓 了 回 来 , 还 是 不 要 连 累 你 吧
再 说 , 你 燕 叔 叔 的 病
我 也 医 得 差 不 多 了
我 真 希 望 能 把 他 医 好
你 以 前 偷 偷 跟 我 讲 我 爹 的 事
是 不 是 真 的 ?
都 是 真 的
这 些 碎 银 子 是 给 你 留 在 路 上 用 的
你 这 次 下 山 , 一 定 要 找 两 个 人 报 仇
第 一 个 是 你 爹 的 管 家 江 琴
那 另 外 一 个 是 谁 ?
素 玉 谷 的 移 花 宫 主
花 无 缺
孩 儿 花 无 缺 在
小 心 啦
现 在 你 武 功 差 不 多
时 候 也 差 不 多 , 你 可 以 下 山 了
还 记 得 为 什 么 要 下 山 吗 ?
当 然 知 道 啦 , 你 要 我 去 杀 一 个 人
为 什 么 要 杀 他 ?
我 根 本 不 需 要 知 道
姑 姑 要 我 做 的 事 , 我 一 定 要 做
姑 姑 要 我 杀 的 人 , 我 一 定 要 杀
这 个 人 叫 什 么 名 字 ?
江 小 鱼
啊 …
打 死 你 …
唉
为 什 么 要 打 人 呢 ?
来
干 什 么 ?
哎 哟 …
你 是 什 么 人 ?
你 管 我 是 什 么 人 呐 ?
你 为 什 么 打 小 孩 ?
他 们 弄 我 的 羊 , 我 当 然 要 打 他 们
我 打 他 们 , 关 你 什 么 事 ?
怎 么 不 关 我 的 事 , 他 们 是 我 弟 弟 啊
什 么 ? 他 们 是 你 弟 弟
那 连 你 也 该 打
小 兔 崽 子
什 么 ?
打 你 王 八 蛋 的 , 去 死 吧
多 管 闲 事
臭 小 子 , 快 给 我 滚
好 , 我 记 住 了 , 你 们 欺 负 人
你 们 欺 负 我
走 … 有 什 么 好 看 ?
好 便 宜 … 买 点 …
哈 哈 …
买 地 毯 呐 …
老 板 , 我 就 买 这 个 , 你 给 我 包 起 来
好 , 给 你 包 起 来 啊
快 ，好
客 官 给 你 包 好 了 , 谢 谢 你
好 的 , 好 的
慢 走
老 板 , 你 们 有 没 有 贵 重 的 瓷 器 ?
有 , 里 面 请
好
你 看 这 个 怎 么 样 呀 ?
贵 重 吗 ?
贵 重 , 这 是 先 朝 皇 帝 用 过 的
真 的 , 没 错 呀
啊 …
你 怎 么 把 他 打 烂 了 ?
诶，你 放 心 , 现 在 关 内 的 瓷 器
要 破 烂 才 值 钱
他 们 用 来 冒 充 几 千 年 的 古 董 来 卖 ，啊
现 在 这 几 块 破 瓦 , 我 一 定 发 达 了
这 些 银 子 给 你 , 我 发 达 了
我 发 达 了
哈 …
啊，这 么 多 银 子
难 道 现 在 关 内 真 是
打 烂 的 瓷 器 才 值 钱
让 我 打 烂 他
诶
哎
这 个 值 钱
那 个 也 值 钱
哈 …
我 的 银 子 呢，怎 么 不 见 了 ?
你 放 在 哪 儿 ?
刚 才 还 挂 在 身 上
现 在 不 见 了
赶 快 找 呀
找 找 呀
没 有 呀
找 找 看 吧
没 有
老 伯 … 你 是 不 是 遗 失 了 银 包 ?
是 呀
你 的 银 包 是 不 是 金 色 的 ?
对 …
卖 古 董 的 老 板 给 偷 去 了
是 , 快 去 找 他
快 点 去
原 来 真 的 是 他 偷 了 我 的 银 包
你 胡 说 , 这 些 银 子 是 一 个
买 破 烂 瓷 器 的 人 给 我 的
你 是 不 是 老 糊 涂 了
人 家 会 拿 这 么 多 银 子
买 一 个 破 烂 瓷 器
是 呀
信 不 信 由 你
现 在 破 烂 瓷 器 才 值 钱
你 看 我 都 打 烂 了 这 么 多
我 看 他 是 疯 了 , 疯 了
揍 他 …
你 们 干 什 么 ? 打 人 呀
打 呀
兄 弟
好 , 打 呀
你 的 玩 意 也 不 错 呀
又 是 你 ?
让 开
你 们 有 没 有 看 见
一 个 穿 白 衣 服 的 少 年 呀 ?
没 有
喂 , 我 在 这 里
你 要 找 我 , 跟 我 来
追
你 们 找 我 有 什 么 事 呀 ?
我 们 想 要 你 身 上 的 一 张 纸
好 呀
你 们 想 拿 我 身 上 的 东 西 , 过 来 呀
上
好
怎 么 样 , 你 还 要 不 要 我 身 上 的 东 西 ?
我 们 要
毛 家 兄 弟
不 错
凭 我 们 毛 家 兄 弟
配 不 配 拿 你 身 上 的 东 西 ?
不 配
你 们 也 不 配
绿 衣 仙 女
不 错 , 是 我
等 我 收 拾 好 他 们
再 回 来 拿 你 的 东 西
走
奇 怪
你 这 是 干 什 么 , 我 救 了 你 的 命
你 这 样 谢 我 呀 ?
对 不 起
谢 谢 你
你 敢 在 她 手 上 救 我
你 胆 子 可 不 小 呀
她 是 谁 呀 ?
她 就 是 江 湖 上 出 名 的 绿 衣 仙 女
出 道 才 一 年 多
江 湖 上 最 少 有 五 、 六 十 个 武 林 高 手
败 在 她 手 里
管 她 什 么 红 衣 仙 女 , 绿 衣 仙 女 的
碰 到 我 小 鱼 儿 , 算 她 倒 霉
把 身 上 东 西 拿 给 我 看 看
什 么 东 西 ?
就 是 他 们 不 要 命 抢 的 那 个 东 西 呀
啊 , 那 个 东 西 不 在 我 身 上
不 在 你 身 上 ?
You can at least tell me what it is
A treasure map
I don't want such things
I have treasures everywhere
Why waste my energy?
So thirsty
Great, there's a well out there
Here is a bowl I'll
get you some water
You wouldn't run away, would you?
Why would I?
The water is nice
What are you doing?
I just saw a rut
You said you were thirsty,
why aren't you drinking?
I fear the water might be poisoned
If it were,
I would die first Right
So sweet
Oh no
The water is poisoned It's not
But I drugged your bowl of water
Why?
Because I'm going somewhere you can't
I'm fainting, why?
Of course
You drunk your own drug
What?
When I threw the brunch
I switched the bowl
I tell you frankly
I knew this trick since I was two
What... do you want?
Nothing
Just to get from
you the treasure map
This fool...
why is he sleeping here?
Who's this?
Who is this?
You don't know him
I don't know him at all
Strange, why is he sleeping here?
Fool, he is not asleep
He's been drugged
Drugged?
Get me Cl bucket of water Yes
You...
Am I very old?
No, miss
You're not to cull me miss
Why are you still standing there
like cl dummy?
Get some water, go
Hitting people indiscriminately
How come there isn't any?
Water's here...
Sorry...
Why have you numbed my pressure point?
What do you think I would do?
For someone as ugly as you, say,
even if you strip
I would have no interest
I struck your pressure point
to take revenge
Who are you?
Why should I tell you?
I'll never forget you
That's good
I'll leave you another sweet memory
You...
Your pressure point...
will automatically resume normal
in 4 hours,
you must remember me
Fondly remembering the day
we were happy that year...
Don't ever lei me see you again
Hey, you...
You're awake
What did you do 10 me?
Nothing much, I took off your clothes
and searched all over
I searched everywhere What?
You searched everywhere?
Yes
Why didn't you tell
me you're u girl?
Had you told me
I would not have stripped your clothes
Had I not stripped your clothes
I would not have...
Would not have what?
You know, though I'm young
I'm essentially cl
man That's why...
That's why what?
That's why I made cl mistake
What's done is done, it's meaningless
even you kill me
You might as well just marry me
I'd rather marry u pile of logs
What did you say?
You're us skinny as a log, if I marry you
wouldn't I be sleeping with CI log?
You want to die?
What do you want?
Do you want to kill me or marry me?
Who is marrying you?
So you have Cl man already
Heavens
It's my first time and I've
got second-hand goods
What rotten luck
You heartless basic: rd
You second-hand item
You've cheated my feelings
and want to kill me too?
Shut up I swear 10 the Heavens
I have never met CI man
as heartless as you
Just my damn luck
Wait, before you die hear me out
You want 10 say something?
Yes
I swear to the Heavens
I have never touched
a woman including you
Then... you didn't...
Though I know you would be disappointed
I really didn't
But my clothes...
Your clothes were indeed stripped
for you said something about
a treasure map
Right
My shoes?
I threw them away, they smelled
Where did you throw them?
Into the sea
The middle of the sea,
they can't be found anymore
Damn, you'll be the death of me
Why? I didn't do that thing
Did you know the map was in my shoes?
That piece of stinking,
yellow rotten paper?
What? Rotten paper? Over these ten years
many have used different
tricks 10 get it
Then the Green Fairy you mentioned
was also after this?
Not really
She is Miss Mu Yung Ching from
the Mu Yung family
The owner of the map
was her mother's childhood friend
Some say her mother's lover
She's come to get the map and
return it 10 its rightful owner
Who's that?
Yin Nun Tien
So the treasure belongs to uncle Yin
It's not yours, why do you want it?
I want to exchange it
for my father's life
Who's your father?
I um Tieh Sin Nun
My father is one of the Ten Villains,
Tieh Chin
Ten Villains? Where are they?
Villains' Valley,
naturally Who says so?
A renowned martial artist
You've been fooled, I'm Jiang Xiuo Yu
from Villains' Valley
Your father is not there
What proof do you have?
None
I speak the truth
and need no proof
Alright... I'll tell you frankly
I took your map, it's here
Take it and find your father
if you don't believe me
Where are you going?
To find the person who has cheated me
You should take this with you
if you're leaving
If someone knows I had the treasure mop
I'll be in trouble
I'll swallow it
Then I'll eviscerate you 10 get it
Don't move
Your kung fu is very good
May I ask what school...
Have you heard of Villains' Valley?
You're related to my grand teacher,
cannibal Li Da Jue?
Happens to be my teacher
Then how is my teacher
the smiling dagger Ha Ha Er
related 10 you?
My iunior brother
One big family...
Greetings, senior uncle...
Quick Yes
Quick... Yes...
So tiring 10 ride in a sedan for so long
So itchy...
Scratch it... Scratch... Yes
So fragrant
Here's the food
Uncle, please eat Okay
Wipe my feet clean
Yes
Help me put on the shoes
Uncle, is this okay?
Yes
Why aren't you eating?
You go first Good etiquette...
Have some wine
Feels good
Wash your face Good
Have some tea Good boy
Why aren't you eating?
It's finished We'll eat later
I have some business, I have to go out
wait for me here
Okay... take cure
I only have gold on me,
do you have any silver?
Yes...
Enough?
Yes... pay you buck later No need
You would be thirsty on the road
have another sip of tea for the road
Alright
I've found the treasure at lust
Strange, why um I dizzy the whole clay?
It's still early, why have
so many people died?
You'll dead soon too
You've come too, did you kill them?
No, we only want to kill you
We have been looking for the treasure
Having seen you swallow the map
We disguised as Li's students
and wait upon you
Do you know who I um?
Who are you?
We are the last two of the ten Villains
the "money maniac" Au Yeung Ding
I'm Au Yeung Don. I've to see money
before my eyes open
So, it's senior uncle,
that makes things easy
We can simply divide the treasure
into 3 parts
What, three parts?
Do you remember
the tea you drank before you went off
It's been drugged
Damn... I am dizzy the whole day
Don't procrastinate, go and kill
Right... before the three of us die
take cl lust look at the treasure
we'll not gel
We three must die. Why?
You don't know
I know you two aren't good characters
so I put in some slow-working poison
in the food
Poison?
If you don't believe me, that's fine
we'll meet in hell anyway
You're lying, if you've put in poison
why aren't we dead?
Is it noon now?
Yes Put your hand
on your fifth rib
Don't tell me, there's u slight pain
Give me the antidote
Give me the antidote, quick
I um confused, how can I remember?
Give him the antidote Yes
Your antidote is effective
Where's our antidote...
With me Look for it
No
Give me some
I'm the big brother, I should eat more
I'm your iunior, I should have it too
Give it here...
I need more Give it to me
None left
The pain seems 10 be gone
It's alright
Naturally,
it's noon your blood circulation
is just at your fifth rib
that's why when you pressed there
you felt numb
Noon has passed and the pain
should be gone
You have not poisoned me
You only cheated us to relieve you
from our drug
Wrong again, I've poisoned you
Give it to me
The antidote you fought over was made by
Yin Jiuo You, one of the ten Villains
The Eight-step Killer
I don't believe
you lying bastard
One two three four five six
You've walked 6
steps Two more left
I don't believe you
Brother...
Never mind him, you have seven steps left
I'll kill you before I die
Don't come near, you have only
5 more steps
Four, five, six, seven, eight
Ten Villains
The three swords of Jin Ning
Black crow
Blood-sucking Red But
These people died by your hands
Indeed cl young hero
I am chief of the security bureau
of 1he18 counties
With super human strength
and fist of iron to conquer
Invincible golden sword,
the hero Chiu Chuen Hui
Thirty one words in your name
that's over doing it a bit
People around give me face
Your name sir...
I am the king of swords
and the father of blades
King of kings, who conquer all
I um invincible all around
the famous Jiung Xiclo Yu
My name has thirty five characters
four more than you
It does not appear I
have heard your name
You must have storied your career recently
Go ask your teacher He'll know
Right,
he's bound 10 know Attack...
510p
Stop, please, everyone
Hero Chiu,
my greetings Thank you
whY did you fight?
They've come for the treasure
and started fighting at the foot
of the hill
I have the map... So do we...
It is rumored there is only
one treasure map
how come there are so many?
There is something wrong
You mean...
The treasure might be inside
Come in with me to take u look
Right,
let's take a look Alright...
Let's go
This is where each leader
of the Er Mei School resides
It doesn't seem right for us
to enter like this
Why?
This is a trespass
and if Er Mei knew about this
they cure sure to come after us
If the man with the false map
has tricked you here
so you and Er Mei would kill each other
wouldn't you have fallen into that trap?
Exactly...
Who do: res to
trespass this sucroscmci ground?
Attack...
What are you doing?
Trespassers will be killed
Don't fight, you don't know
who has come today
Who is he?
He is Hero Jiang with 35 characters
to his name
His kung fu is excellent
He brought us in here I...
You...
So you're the muster mind
Is it true you know different kinds
of kung fu?
Yes Why then are you
unable to fight off
a few ordinary guys?
You haven't seen the real thing
So close
It's a close shave
I bite you
Sorry, this is the decree of Er Mei School
I cannot show any mercy
Why has Er Mei
endeavored to kill today?
Who are you?
How dare you trespass
the sucroscmci ground of Er Mei
I go anywhere I want
Yi Hua kung fu
That's right, Ah Yeuk, Chao Kuk, retreat
Yes
Have you also come from
the Yi Hucu Palace cut the Soo Yue Valley
Yi Huu Palace
That's right, I am Hua Mu Juet
of Yi Hua Palace
Er Mei & Yi Hua Palace
aren't connected whatsoever
Why have you insulted us
by trespassing the sacrosanct ground
I have been secluded for CI number of years
and don't know the rules
I heard many heroes
have come here
and I wanted to find out
the whereabouts of a person
hence my intrusion, please forgive me
I um leaving
Wait, the decree holds,
respussers must die
You cannot leave
The what can I do?
Unless I um not the chief
and I don't have the order in my hands
It isn't anymore
Now, can I live?
You bully
Not really, I was only saving my life
and yours too
I don't need your help
Return the order immediately
Do you want to grub it from me?
To get near your enemy
you must strike first
I do: re not
Old Chiu I'm dead Old Chiu...
Don't worry you're not dead yet
I've thought about it
I've killed many men today
See all those corpses outside
So I don't wcmi to use weapons again
but I'd like to make cl bet with you
On what?
I'll use three moves I've learnt
If you can do them, you win
If you can't, return Er Mei's order
Well?
Right, I'd like to know
if there is anything
I cannot learn
Rig hi, let's sic: rt
You must smile before you kill
First, the Golden snake stick out tongue
No, this is like cl hungry cur after shit
Going after shit
Second, Nimble cut catches rut
No, it's the Monkey going up CI tree
Monkey going up CI tree
Hungry cur after shit,
and Monkey going up CI tree
I've seen them I am confident
I can learn them
What's the last move?
Master Huq remember
uncle Bui's words
when in a disadvantageous position
don't ask for help
I have one more move,
I'm sure you can't learn that
This is culled Dog taking CI pee
Feels good
Hucl Mu Juei, it's your turn
Take off your punts
Alright, your intention is friendly
in any event
I can't learn this move, you win
Thanks...
Priest
Heroes
we've been fooled regarding the treasure
With the order in my hand
I um the leader of Er Mei
I announce I won't
kill you Please leave
Quick In Cl moment I
won't be Er Mei's chief
Quick
Go quickly...
Let's retreat to the outside
Priest Shun Sek, take it
Now we're outside the forbidden ground
the order is returned to you
You can get on with
your business Good bye
Wait
Still want to fight?
No... Young hero, you not only
preserved Er Mei's reputation
but also avoided cl bloody bottle
I'll never forget this favour
Please leave your name so I could
repay you one day
Right, I always do such things
Forget it, my name has
thirty five characters and it's too long
Just remember I have two fishes on me
Hey, let's go
Priest,
sorry for what happened just now
Let's go
He saved us...
Wow, I never realised behind Er Mei
there is such cl beautiful place
It's really beautiful
Right Sorry for just now
May I know your name?
My real name is Jiang Xiuo Yu
What? You're Xiao Yu Erh?
Do you know me?
Yes, I have come all the way
to look for you
So you need help from me
Just tell me how I could help
Strange, though this is the first time
I see you
I like you Yes, I like you too
How can I help you, tell me
I'm not here 10 ask for help
but 10 kill you
What? To kill me?
I don't even know you,
why would you want 10 kill me?
I don't know either
I only know someone has asked me
to kill you
Who?
Princess of the Yi Hucu Palace
Oh, so I understand now
She killed my father
I was looking for her too
I'm afraid you won't have the chance
So, your kung fu is not bad
even I cannot defeat you
You've given me leeway
Don't... come near
Do you want to kill me with
your own hands?
Yes, I have to follow my orders
If you don't kill me with
your own hands then
the princess of the Yi Hua Palace
would not be happy
Why couldn't I kill you with my own hands?
BECGUSG GS soon GS YOU IHOVG
I'll iump down the cliff
and you won't be able to kill me
with your own hands
Well? I don't think you can kill me today
Let's arrange for another day
Jiung Xiao Yu...
Jiung Xiclo Yu
Help me, young fellow will you?
Okay
Thanks Where's your home?
Right here
Hey, what place is this?
A man's paradise
One doesn't have to do anything here
One can play the happiest game
What would that be?
You really don't know?
You wouldn't know such things
How would you serve the emperor tonight?
Your highness
How's my palace?
Your highness Good
What?
That's her
Why have you brought me here?
What are doing?
Haven't you heard that among
the ten Villains
one doesn't live in Villain's Valley
Siuo Mi Mi?
What? The ten Villains again?
Why are there so many villains
in this world?
I always bump into them
But this villain is different from
the rest
It's your romantic fortune that
you've bumped into me
What are you doing?
'COO
I must have it now
What do you want?
I?
I want your virginity
Jumped into the water
They are fighting
You still want to run?
Come,
men Yes Take off his pants Yes
Don't be in such cl hurry Why?
I... have a habit, I do nothing
before I eat anything
That's easy
Have more
Eat this
Who are those people in the cage?
They are new
mistresses Mistresses?
Then I'm your mistress foo No
You are my queen
I'll make you happy every day from now on
eighteen times each day
We'll love each other 10 death
Your highness
What do we do with these mistresses?
As usual Get rid of them
Yes, your highness
Quick... go Go
That kid has an
evil look Who is he?
Of all the men I know, he is the most
useless, just like half a girl
The first night he came here
I sent him away
What's that place you sent him to?
It's reserved for men I've finished with
Sooner or later, I...
This is our wedding night
& you're still...
asking about this & that.
Makes me so anxious
Come,
men Yes Lower the curtain Yes
Go out at once all of you
Where are you going?
I want it now...
Big trouble
Your highness, we have big trouble
Many martial artists are
marching towards our palace What?
Come, men
Yes
Come here, quick
Give me your arms
This is a love lock, watch him
don't lei him get away
Go
Quick...
What? A trap? Where are you going?
Give it back
Why? This secret creed isn't yours
Where are you going?
Let me go...
What are you doing with all that rope?
Are you fleeing for your life or not?
It's so high, how could we iump?
What do you want now?
We'll lower ourselves down from here
It's too tall to lower us down
There are 2 ways out of here
one's been blocked by their trap
so if we want 10 flee
we need to be lowered quickly down
So you fooled them by saying
someone's looking for her
You've planned this escape all along
Right, but I never expected you
would be with me
Who cure you after all?
Why are you taking all that stuff?
I was there for a year because
of the secret manual
I didn't expect that when everything
is ready
I'd bump into you
Hey, who are you?
Don't you know me?
I am the famous martial artist
with thirty five characters to my name
Everyone looks upon me as CI king
Open it
Hey What are you doing?
This is the famous love lock
Normal swords cannot even scratch it
What do we do? I'm tied to you for life
Don't worry I have a
sharp sword at home
Looks like you have 10 follow me home
Thank you
You're welcome...
I haven't yet thanked you
for saving Yu Long's life
You're mistaken, without him
I could not have escaped
Right
I can go now
Young hero, my home is large
and my father is hospitable
Why don't you stay at my place
for a few days
Not cl bud idea
besides I have no where to go
Sir, this might... not be foo convenient
No, you're too kind
the pleasure is ours
Yu Long
See to it young hero is put up
in the guest room
Yes... Please...
Pulling thread
Lethal Flying Kick
Sleep walk Kwun Lun Dan
So I practised kung fu in my sleep
Yu Long, where is the secret creed?
Here
Why is there only half of it?
That's because when I got it
I was with Jiang Xiao Yu
Then the other half must be with him
That's why I used every trick
to lure him to my home
Lei dud think of a way to deal with him
Should we kill him to get
the creed back immediately?
No need. In another 2 days
it's my 50th birthday
Let's deal with him after that
l1 looks like Jiang Nun Hero
is not a good person
Yin Nun Tien treasure map
So he made all the fake maps
Then he is the culprit behind cull this
So it's even more difficult to
separate the good
from the bad outside Villains' Valley
Could it be him who
cheated Tieh Sin Nun?
Congratulations hero Jiang,
many happy returns
Thank you...
Hero Jiang, do you remember me?
Miss, you are...
I am the one who paid for
your treasure map
to save my father, my name's Tieh Sin Nun
But when I saw you last time
you dressed up like a mun
Someone told me however
my dad's not in the Villains' Valley
You're lying What?
Did you hear that?
This lady is culling me a liar
Miss, hero Jiang is one of the
richest men around
and highly charitable
He has done cl lot of good
Someone like hero
Jiang would never lie
That's right...
Don't believe him... he is CI villain
Jiung Xiao Yu, hero Jiung
So you've come too?
Not only that, but I've discovered
cl big secret
Gentlemen, on Er Mei
Didn't we suspect someone was
setting us up with CI fake map?
Right Now I've found
out who he is Who?
It's him Him...
Jiang, you foul-mouthed villain,
you dare frame me
where's your proof?
Of course I have proof
Come on Hold this
Hold this... This treasure map
It's difficult 10 get
Jiang Xiuo Yu, who gave you these maps
to set me up?
What? Set you up?
Of course,
they were on you Right...
Everyone saw this
My father couldn't have given them 10 you
Right, hero Jiang is
right He's right...
This map was taken from your study
Who saw that?
Nobody Then how
could you say that?
I have no quarrel with you
why do you want 10 set me up?
Who are you two?
I know
The Green Fairy
I am lute
Congratulations hero Jiang,
many happy returns
Thank you...
What? ls Miss Mu Yung friends with them?
No, it's the opposite
I want to seek revenge in this place today
What is this all about?
He is cl villain
who would practically do anything
I swore I would kill him
if I saw him again
So he is a villain who cheated you
Alright, everyone...
Now everything is clear
I never expected that someone like me
who has never created any enemy
would be set up
by such Cl villain
Yu Long, give me my sword
He is a great liar
Regardless of which
I will get rid of this evil being
Jicmg Xiuo Yu, you meddle too much
in others' affairs
510p
We of the Jiang family
never let other people down
If it were not for the grudge
which Miss Mu Yung bears
I could let him go free
I'll hand him over 10 you
I already said
if I saw you again, I would kill you
Sorry, you can't kill him
Huu Mu Juet
He is Hua Mu Juet of Yi Huu Palace
This is a present for
hero Jiung Nun's birthday
from the princess of the Yi Hucu Palace
Thank you...
Best wishes 10 you on your special day
Master Hua, you know them too?
Yes, I have looked everywhere for him
Who is he?
Why do you stop me from killing him?
Sorry, that's because I want to
kill him personally
Strange, everyone I meet today
wants to kill me
I never expected that coming to
the birthday feast
I'd see you here
There are no cliffs for you
to iump off this time
You are CI strange person
Every time when someone tries 10 kill me
you come to the rescue
Then afterwards you try to kill me
but you never tell me why
I don't understand either because
I don't know myself
What's going on?
Hurry... put on the lights
Put on the lights... Hurry
Hurry, put on the
lights What's going on?
I don't know either
Put on the lights Don't"
Put on the lights... Hurry...
Where are Xiuo Yu Erh and Tieh Sin Nun?
Xiclo Yu Erh's gone
I'll go find him Wait
Did you conspire with Xiao Yu Erh?
Once you appear, he's gone
I never lie
Wait for me here, I'll go find him
Go
Let's go
Where we they gone'?
It's you
If it were not for the seven of us
how could we put out the fire
and save you out from
all these people simultaneously?
I've rescued Xiao Yu Erh
Who... who is he?
Tieh Sin Nun, how come it's you?
Who are they?
Oh, my little emperor
you are flirting with women
Siuo Mi Mi, don't be ieulous
Lei him tell us where the treasure
was hidden
Yin Nun Tien will be here any minute
by then, you and I would be killed
What? Hus Uncle Yin recuperated?
We wouldn't have been forced
lo leave Villains' Valley
if his wound were not healed
Uncle Yin has recovered
Big brother, I think you'd better
listen to my words
Lei me kill him and eat him
and get the map from
his stomach Bullshit
Alright, you have two options
Either you take us to look for
the treasure
or let Li eat you
Lei them enioy her
Laugh, laugh louder
Don't move
Xiclo Yu Erh, what do you think?
You'd rather she died
or take us to look for the treasure?
Don't kill her
She is pregnant with my child
You two have...
You know
You just have to let her go
& I'll lead you to treasure
Deal. As long as you take us there,
we'll let her go
Thank God
Let's us talk in private before
we separate
Wife, my poor wife Hey,
what are you doing?
After my death take
good cure of my son
He is the only descendant from
three generations
As soon as Uncle Yin arrives
come immediately to Er Mei to rescue me
Got that?
Yes
You've got that
You've to bear this in mind Yes
I'm going
We are now going
We hope that we can be there before dawn
Let's go
Remember that
Is it here?
Yes...
It's here
What's going on?
Where's the treasure?
Xiclo Yu Erh, don't play tricks anymore
Speak
Where's the treasure? Speak
I... I don't know either
I've got it, this treasure was
very peculiar
When the sun comes out
the sunbeam will fall on
the place where the treasure lies
Then we have to wait till dawn
Of course otherwise I won't know
where it's been hidden
Is he telling the truth?
We have no choice but to believe him
He has exhausted his bug of tricks
Let's wait for one to two hours
Uncle Yin, you have to come to rescue me
before dawn
I wonder if he is telling the truth
They must be discussing about
how to kill me before dawn
It's cl pity that I'll die here
The tomb of the greatest hero
Jiung Xiao Yu
What do you want?
This is called pre-empiive attack
Guess it's too much dividing
buried treasure in 7 parts
What's going on?
Don't blame me, you've said earlier
either you live or I die
Bui Hui Sin, you are going to die
We've been together for so many years
You are too ruthless to be CI human being
We are not human beings anyway
Don't move
See where you can hide?
Why's that? Have we not agreed already?
But Bai Hui Sin and I have agreed
even earlier
It's unexpected that you two...
We are not human beings either
Hey, fatty, do you want us to kill you
or will you kill yourself, come out
I beg you...
Please... don't kill me
Don't kill me, I'll give up the treasure
Please... Please... lei me go
Please...
You...
One is prone to fail
at the time when one is complacent
with one's success
You might have forgotten that
the Smiling Dagger has 3 poisonous spears
Siuo Mi Mi, kill him for me
If I want to kill him, I wouldn't be here
It's me who has asked him to kill you
Ha Ha Er, your poisonous spears work
Sure, this is my last move
of course, it must work
Siao Mi Mi, after you've got the treasure
is it true that you'll never leave me?
Of course, I love you forever
I knew that your secret weapon is lethal
I haven't been shot by
your poisonous spear
You... you two...
We two are the real partners
Can't imagine after being together
for so many years
you are now killing each other
Mind your own business
See, the moon is going down west
and the sun will soon be rising
If you still can't find the treasure
you too have to die No.
He won't die here
Yin Nan Tien That's
right, it's me
Uncle Yin
Xiao Yu Erh, are you alright?
My kung fu is so good, of course
I'm alright
He's called Xiao Yu Erh
That's right, he's the son of
your sworn brother
Xiao Yu Erh
Why have you brought them here?
Someone in the martial arts world
has made up some fake maps
saying that you've hidden treasure here
There's no such thing at all
The treasures I had, belonged to
your father &
had been taken by your dud's
housekeeper Hung Chin
Who made all these fake maps?
Jiung Bei He the hypocrite
What? Jiang again
Hero Jiang
Miss Mu Yung, how are you?
Fine
Any news from Muster Hun'?
Not yet Do you feel lonely
waiting here all by yourself
for Muster Huu
You... I admire you very much
You must be dreaming
Your kung fu is good
But it's still no better than mine
Your kung fu is not bud
Muster Huu, please stop...
Bastard,
you've made us lose face
Master Hua,
I apologize Senior I apologize
Senior, you... I
I have already shot the Jin Sze needle
into your pressure point
Once you move
the needle will follow the flow of
your blood
Within 7 steps, it will get into
your liver's veins
and you will start laughing
In no more than an hour
you will die of laughing
Jiung Bei He, you are so ruthless
Miss Mu Yung, it's been rumored that
Yin Nan Tien
has returned to the martial arts world,
I have a grudge against him
so I must take you
away as hostage
Because you are the daughter of
Yin Nan Tien's mistress
Having you with me
will make him more scrupulous
Let's go
Still want to fight?
Have you forgotten that
you cannot survive 7 steps?
Muster Huu, my pressure point
has been numbed
and I cannot move, you can't save me
You'd better wait until we've all gone
and think of a way 10 save yourself
Hua Mu Juet, do you really
want to die by laughing?
Muster Huu, please
Please don't move the last step
Don't worry, everyone has one life
Even the I'lUCI Mu
Juei is no exception
Master Hua...
Dad, we don't have much time
we'd better kill Huu Mu Juei
Take Mu Yung Ching away
If we kill Huu Mu Juei
I'm just afraid that the
Yi Hua Palace Princess will...
Don't worry, we can...
blame it on Yin Nun Tien
Good idea, let's go
Huu Mu Juet, the only good thing I do
in my whole life
is to allow you cm easy death
Muster Huu
Xiuo Yu Erh That's
right, it's me
Huu Mu Juei, go on laughing
Muster Huu
How do you feel?
You shouldn't have beaten me all the time
Dad, you handle him first
I'll take cure of Hua Mu Juei
Don't be afraid, you've stopped laughing
Yin Nan Tien That's
right, it's me
It's quite unexpected that after 18 years
we meet again
Uncle Yin, do you know him?
Yes, he's Jiang Chin, the one
who took away your
family treasure and betrayed your dud
No wonder you've made
so many fake mops so that
martial artists will fight against
each other, while
you can divert other people's
attention simultaneously
hoping no one'd know where
the treasure has been hidden
Give me back my father's treasure
Jicmg Chin, don't try 10 escape
Dad, take me with you...
He doesn't deserve to be a father
How's he?
He's been wounded by the Jin Sze needle
Only by your internal power
can it be forced out
Xiao Yu Erh, release her pressure point
It's none of my business
Uncle Yin asked me to do it,
don't blame me for this
Thank you
How's he doing?
Thanks for saving my life
Don't mention it...
Alright, you've your life back
Xiuo Yu Erh, who is he anyway?
He's Hua Mu Juet of the Yi Hua Palace
What? He's from the Yi Hua Palace?
Uncle Yin, don't kill him
Why? Your father was killed by them
But he's saved my life twice
Unfortunately, he has to kill me
though he's saved me
Why do you have to kill him?
I also wish to know
We from the Yi Hucu Palace
have to obey orders of
the Yi Huu Palace Princess
It's her again; I'm just going to find her
Alright,
I'll lei you go but tell her that
at tomorrow noon
Xiao Yu Erh and I will wait for her
at the Man Huu Wood
You'd better ask her
why she wants 10 kill Xiuo Yu Erh
What? You want 10 know why
Yes, I've also heard that people
from Yi Hua Palace
has killed his father, is this true?
Hua Mu Juet, you've grown up in this place
you should know the rules of
the Yi Huu Palace
There's no such thing as should
or should not
the only thing matters is
whether I like it or not
But I can't kill the one who saved my life
He's the one who saved your life?
I killed his father. If you don't kill him
...he will kill me!
Huq Mu Juet, do you really want to
know why
I asked you to kill Jiqng Xiclo Yu?
Alright,
I'll tell you after he dies
A Miss Tieh would like to see you
Miss Tieh, what's your business
here cut this late hour?
I am here to kill you
There are two cups here
One of them has poison
If you choose the one with poison
you'll be the one to die
otherwise... it will be me
Why should I choose?
Are you afraid?
Don't you have confidence?
Do you fight only if
you feel confident?
If you fight
only if you know that you will win
then this is not Cl
duel this is murder
Why are you willing
to fight for Xiuo Yu Erh?
You love him?
Xiuo Yu Erh is more fortunate than I um
There's still one person in this world
who is willing to die for him
Regardless of whether this wine
is poisoned
it's your own choice
This is a fair duel
Yes, I believe so
Wait
You can't drink this wine
Why?
It's poisoned
This is meant 10 be a duel to the death
Even if it's poisoned, no one can blame me
I blame you for putting poison
in both drinks
You can deceive others with this trick
but not me
No matter which one he chooses,
he is going 10 die
If I did this it was
in order to save you
I don't appreciate it
you use such dirty tricks to save me
Get lost
XiCIO Yu Erh, why aren't you convinced that
I um willing to die for you?
Why didn't you check to see whether
there's poison in both drinks
before you threw her out?
Do you really believe that
there're so many good people
in this world?
Yes I do
H's weird; she is willing to die for me
but I culled her CI liar
She wanted to poison you
but you are still putting in
good words for her
There's no explanation for everything
and I don't know why we've to have cl duel
Like you, I don't know either
You're leaving?
We have to meet for the lost time tomorrow
People tell the truth
at the last hour before their death
or do things they've always wanted
Tieh Sin Nan is willing to die
with Xiuo Yu Erh
because she loves him
Xiao Yu Erh doesn't want you to die
because he loves you
You still don't know why
you have to kill him
Still that same old story
I hope I don't have to fight with
Xiclo Yu Erh tomorrow
But you... why?
Because of you
I'm afraid that you might get hurt
in the duel tomorrow
The duel starts at noon,
why are you here so early?
I couldn't sleep, what about you?
I haven't slept either
It's strange that ever since
I left Villains' Valley
I've been very happy
But in the last couple of days,
I've changed
There are so many things that
I don't understand
Why do I like you?
Why do I have to fight you?
I know
Because he is Hucl Mu Juei
and you are Xiao Yu Erh, you two live
for today's duel
So you are the princess of
the Yi Huu Palace
who wants him to kill me
Huu Mu Juet, kill him
Princess
You've been brought up by me.
C'mon, draw your sword
Jiung Xiclo Yu, I was brought up by her
I must listen to her
Now you know why you have to kill me
Princess said she'll tell me after you die
Xiao Yu Erh You... Xiao Yu Erh
Xiao Yu Erh
XiCIO Yu Erh...
Why didn't you wait for me?
Yin Nun Tien
You've killed him
Uncle Yin, forgive me
I um from the Yi Hucl Palace
I must listen to the princess of
the Yi Huu Palace
What? You again
Princess, you can tell me now
why I have to kill
Xiao Yu Erh Of course
Retreat Yes
Why did you ask them to retreat?
For the reputation of the Yi Hua Palace
I can only tell you about this
it cannot be passed on
to the martial arts world
What is it?
Eighteen years ago
I fell in love with the
number one scholar Jiang Fung
but he eloped with
my maid Huu Yuei Lao
and hid in the Man Hucl Cliff,
and bore 2 children
Later they were betrayed by Hung Chin
To fake revenge for this, I killed both
and separated the two brothers
I brought up one, and gave one
10 Yin Nun Tien
so that when they grow up,
they'll fight against each other
Only by this can I have my revenge
and get rid of my hatred for your family
What? Xiclo Yu Erh is my little brother
You are such a ruthless woman
Hucl Mu Juei, it's your turn
because after I've told the truth
even if you don't kill me, I will kill you
It's you
Huu Mu Juet
He's Jicmg Chin, the housekeeper,
who betrayed your Dad
Your father was killed by him
Now you understand why I have to tell you
the secret of 18 years ago
because I know that Jiung Chin and I
will definitely kill you today
Last night, I took Uncle “Ian's potion
so I could stop my
pulse Only by doing this
will you tell the truth and
lure Jiang Chin here
Xiclo Yu Erh. Watch out her Yi Hucl kung fu
Don't touch her body
She is old and ugly
I believe no man wants to touch her
Jiang Chin, you'd pay for what you did
You ruthless villain, where can you hide?
You old bitch, you are so ruthless
how can you crown yourself
with such pretty name
as the princess of the Yi I'lUCI Palace
You should call yourself an evil old hag
You must be tired of living
No matter what
I will have you stub my chest
Huu Mu Juet
Xiao Yu Erh
Uncle Wan, what is it?
I've examined these 2 cups
One is with poison and one is without
Last night Tieh really risked her life
to save me
Xiao Yu Erh
She is now at the lakeside
You'd better clean up yourself
get changed before
you go 10 her Okay
What are you doing here?
Nothing much, I just want to tell you that
I'm so sorry that I took off
all your clothes that day
and made a mistake
What?
Besides, you are not some
second-hand commodity
You are so bad...