You're late, you think I got nothing better
你迟到了，你觉得我除了整晚坐在这里等
to do than sit around and wait all night?
没有别的事可做吗？
Hey, sorry, snake,
嘿，对不起，蛇，
I just wanna make sure I wasn't followed.
我只是想确保我没有被跟踪
Shut up, let me see the stuff.
闭嘴，让我看看东西
Right, I see where you're coming from.
好的，我明白你的意思了
Check this out.
看一下这个。
Top grade, I can make a killin' on this.
最好的，我可以为此杀人
How much more can you get me?
你还能给我多少？
As much as you want, babe.
你要多少都行，宝贝
I got a new source, unlimited.
我有一个新的来源，无限的
Don't call me babe,
别叫我宝贝
I told you about that before, I hate it.
我之前告诉过你，我讨厌这样
Gotcha, no problem.
明白了，没问题
I remember you telling me that before.
我记得你以前告诉过我
What the hell is that?
这他妈到底是什么？
Are you sure you weren't followed?
您确定没有被跟踪吗？
I'm positive.
我肯定
I'll take care of this.
我来处理
All right, what do you want?
好吧，你想要什么？
I'm lookin' to party.
我在寻找派对
Yeah, well there's no party here
这里没有派对
so why don't you just beat it.
所以你为什么不滚蛋
Well, that's too bad,maybe we could start our own.
好吧，那太糟糕了，也许我们可以自己开始
Hey, get her to shut that thing off, will ya?
嘿，让她把那东西关掉，好吗？
You wanna wake up the whole neighborhood?
你想叫醒整个街区吗？
Hey, baby, would you mind
嘿，宝贝，你介意
finishing your aerobics elsewhere?
去别的地方做你的有氧运动吗？
We're trying to conduct a little business here.
我们想在这里做点小生意
What kinda business, big boy?
什么事，大男孩？
None of your business.
不关你的事
So why don't you just move on.
所以你为什么不离开
I said I was lookin' to party.
我说过我要参加派对
Yeah, well it looks like you got an early start on it.
是的，看来您早早开始了
Why don't you just get back in your car
你为什么不回到你的车里
and take that portable disco with you.
带上那个便携式迪斯科舞厅
Listen, I got money with me.
听着，我有钱
So if you just tell me where I can find the party,
所以，如果您告诉我在哪里可以找到派对
I'll be on my way.
我就会走了
She's got money.
她有钱
What the hell?
我勒个去？
Shut up, what kinda money you talkin' about?
闭嘴，你在说什么钱？
I ain't talkin' about change for the parking meter.
我说的不是停车计时器的零钱
Yeah, there's a party here,
是的，这里有一个派对，
we just sorta forgot to buy the streamers.
我们只是有点忘了买彩带
Screw the streamers,show me what you got.
去他的彩带，给我看看你有什么
Ooh, I knew you could help me out.
哦，我就知道你可以帮我
Yeah, I just might let you party with me.
是啊，我可能会让你和我一起去派对
There's just one little thing.
只是有一件小事
What's that, sweetness?
什么事，甜心？
You're busted, get your hands up now!
你被捕了，把手举起来
You gotta be kidding.
你开玩笑的吧
J huh
j got a pistol in my pocket
j and baby, you can cock it
j put your finger on the trigger
j feel it getting bigger
j move a little closer
j let me stick it
in your holster
j let's do it
j shoot my bullet
j got a pistol in my pocket
j and baby, you can cock it
j it's got a 12 inch length
j and you can make it plank
j blow me away, just
give it a yank
j let's do it
j shoot my bullet
j when you roll up in my Levi's
j you can feel my Colt, yeah, 45
j got a pistol in my pocket.
J and baby, you can cock it
j it's straight from undercover
j but don't show it mother
j looking for a sexy way
j to blow my ammunition
j let's do it
j bite my bullet
j well, you better
start strippin'
j or you're gonna get
in the way of love
Hurry!
快点！
Good morning, students.
早上好，同学们
Good morning, miss Devonshire.
早上好，德文郡小姐
I see we're all here bright and early today.
我知道我们今天都很早就到了
Let me just take our roll call and,
让我来点名
yes, Holly.
霍莉
I'd like to say that the drug bust,
我想说缉毒行动
which I took on single-handedly last night,
我昨晚单枪匹马搞定了
went off without any flaws.
没有任何瑕疵
But we've never studied their set-up and operation.
但是我们从来没有研究过他们的组织和运作
We don't even know who their main supplier is.
我们甚至不知道他们的主要供应商是谁
Well, since my father is the chief of police,
好吧，既然我父亲是警察局长，
he did give me all the inside information
他确实把他发现的所有内幕消息
that he had uncovered.
都告诉了我
He thought that maybe if I had the case all to myself
他想，如果我一个人处理这个案子的话
I could pick up some extra credit in the class.
也许我可以在班上获得一些额外的学分
I've warned you about this before, Holly.
霍莉，我之前已经警告过你
What if something had gone wrong
如果出了什么差错
and your life would have been in danger?
你的生命有危险怎么办？
Daddy had every surrounding block manned by patrol cars,
爸爸在每个街区都有巡逻车，
if I had let out one little scream
如果我发出一声尖叫
the entire area would have been crawling
整个区域会在几秒钟内
with black and whites in seconds.
被黑人和白人警察包围
Sounds like an expensive operation
听起来要抓住一个毒贩
to catch one drug dealer.
花费不菲啊
You know, that's what daddy said,
爸爸就是这么说的
but after I talked it over with him,
但是我跟他讲完之后
he didn't seem to mind.
他似乎并不介意
Hm, I'll remember that next time
嗯，下次我需要向他要钱的时候
I need to ask him for any expenditures.
我会记得的
Oh, and I do have a full copy
对了，我还有一份昨晚的
of the report from last night.
完整报告
Watch where you're going!
走路看着点！
Why don't you say it a little louder,
你为什么不大声点说
I'm sure there's a few people here
我确定这里有人
that didn't notice we came in late.
都没注意到我们来晚了
You're late.
你迟到了
See what I mean.
明白我的意思了
I don't suppose any of you
我不认为你们中的任何人
have excuses for your tardiness.
有迟到的借口
Class started without us?
没等我们就开始上课了？
I've heard that one before.
我以前听过这句话
And you?
你呢？
No comment.
无可奉告
You three are going to need
你们三个
to show more interest in this class.
要对这门课表现出更多的兴趣
Showing up late is hardly any way
迟到可不是什么好事
of going about getting your place on the force.
并不能让你在警队里占有一席之地
Don't most vice arrests take place at night?
大多数逮捕罪犯不是在晚上进行的吗？
How is getting up early in the morning gonna do any good
当这个城市里所有的下流人都睡着了的时候
when all the low-life in this city is asleep?
早起又有什么好处呢？
Not all the low-life.
不是所有的下层人士
Vice is a 24-hour a day job.
犯罪是一天24小时的工作
While you were sleeping last night,
当你昨晚睡觉的时候
Holly managed to pull off an arrest all on her own.
霍莉自己成功逮捕了一个人
That brings her arrest quota
所以她的逮捕名额
to the highest of anyone in the classroom.
是全班最高的
Big deal, if I had an entire police force
有什么大不了的，如果我有一整支警察队伍
at my Beck and call,
听候差遣
I'd have the highest arrest quota also.
我的逮捕人数也是最多的
Dream on.
继续做梦
Just shut up already.
闭嘴吧
Girls, please, we have other things at hand today.
姑娘们，拜托，我们今天还有别的事要做
Now you all realize that graduation
现在你们都意识到毕业
is just a few weeks away.
只有几个星期了
And each of you must make 10 arrests in order
你们每个人必须逮捕10个人
to get a position on the force.
才能在警队中占有一席之地
My father says that my badge
我父亲说我的警徽
and uniform are already waiting for me.
和制服已经在等我了
Well, that's fine for you,
好吧，这对你来说很好
but let's see what everyone else can do
但是让我们看看其他人
before graduation day comes around.
在毕业前能做些什么
Now, would anyone like to tell us
现在，有人愿意告诉我们
where we left off in our last lecture?
上节课讲到哪里了吗？
Yes, Dwayne?
德韦恩？
We were about to watch some x-rated videos
我们正要看一些x级的视频
so we could study the craft in which they're made.
所以我们可以研究它们的制造工艺
No, I'm sorry, that's not it.
不，抱歉，不是这样的
We were about to study how to disarm an assailant.
我们正要学习如何解除攻击者的武装
Close enough.
接近了
Shawnee, Dwayne, would you come up here, please?
肖尼，德韦恩，你能上来吗？
Now, Dwayne, you be the assailant.
现在，德韦恩，你就是攻击者
Take this gun and act threatening.
拿着这把枪并且威胁
Your money or your life.
要钱还是要命
Now, what would you do in your defense?
现在，你会怎么做？
No, no, no, that's hard,
不，不，不，那很难
hardly the way to do it.
很难做到这一点
I'll show you the proper method
我会告诉你正确的方法
and put your clothes back on!
穿上你的衣服！
Man has several pressure points on his body.
人身上有好几个压迫点
One of these being the groin.
其中之一就是腹股沟
A kick to this area will easily make him
对这个区域的一次踢击，会让他很容易地
release his grip on any object.
放松对任何物体的抓握
Any questions?
有什么问题吗？
Yes, do you think that each of us could try that?
是的，你觉得我们每个人都可以试试吗？
Certainly, line up, all of you.
当然，排队，你们所有人
You can each have a chance to practice.
你们每个人都有机会练习
Very good, next.
很好，下一个
No, not quite, go to the end of the line and try again.
不，不完全是，走到最后再试一次
We'll do this all day until each of you gets it right.
我们会这样做一整天，直到你们每个人都做对了
Very good.
非常好
Yes, keep the line moving.
保持队伍前进
Good, excellent,very good, very good.
好，非常好，非常好
No, try again, very good, that's right.
不，再试一次，很好，就这样
Excellent, knees up, good.
很好，膝盖抬起来，很好
Very good!
很好！
Miss Devonshire.
德文郡小姐
Yes, sir?
什么事？
I was wondering if you could spare a moment
我在想你能不能抽出一点时间
of my daughter's time.
和我女儿谈谈
I need her to make a positive identification
我要她确认
of the dealer she arrested last night.
昨晚逮捕的毒贩的身份
Certainly, line them up, daddy.
当然，排队，爸爸
Scum.
人渣
Pig.
猪
Bitch.
婊子
You're gonna pay.
你要付出代价
You ruined our operation,I oughta ring your neck!
你毁了我们的行动，我应该勒你的脖子
Which one is it, daddy?
是哪一个，爸爸？
The two on the left.
左边那两个
Maybe I just need a closer look.
也许我只是需要靠近点看
Those are the guys, right there.
就是那些人，就在那里
Daddy, you let them get away!
爸爸，你让他们逃走了！
After all my hard work!
在我辛苦工作之后！
Don't you worry,pumpkin, we'll find them.
别担心，小南瓜，我们会找到他们的
Honestly, does she really think
老实说，她真的认为
we're ever gonna chase anybody over one of these things?
我们会因为这些东西，去追上任何人吗？
Faster, stop holding up the line!
快点，别挡着队伍！
This is even stupider than the last one.
这比上一次还要愚蠢
Really, it works for me.
真的，对我很有用
All right, Dwayne,one more stunt like that
好吧，德韦恩，再耍一次这样的花招
and we'll try the disarm the assailant trick again.
我们再试试解除攻击者的武器
How does that sound to you?
你觉得怎么样？
No, thanks.
不，谢谢
Remember, always make your opponent submit.
记住，一定要让你的对手屈服
And begin!
开始吧！
Very good, next.
很好，下一个
And begin.
开始
Dwayne, at least make it look convincing.
德韦恩，至少让它看起来有说服力
Much better, next!
好多了，下一个！
And begin.
开始
Really, I wish miss Devonshire would have given me
真的，我真希望德文郡小姐能给我
a partner who was somewhat of a challenge.
一个有点挑战性的搭档
Look, isn't that your father?
看，那不是你爸爸吗？
Where?
在哪？
Now, after you fire the warning shot,
现在，在你开了警告枪之后，
the actual shot you fire next is the one that counts.
你下一枪的实际射击才是最重要的
I prefer to aim for between the eyes.
我更喜欢瞄准两眼之间
Really?
真的？
Yes, really.
是的，真的
Now, shawnee, you have six shots here.
肖尼，你有六发子弹
Let's see if you can make them count.
让我们看看你能不能让它们有价值
And try and keep your clothes on.
尽量穿好衣服
Sorry.
很抱歉
Go on, keep trying.
继续，继续努力
Keep trying, you'll eventually hit a target.
继续努力，你最终会击中目标的
Sorry, mister.
对不起，先生
I wonder if she got him between the eyes.
我想知道她是不是从两眼之间射中了他
Go on, you only have one shot left.
继续，你只剩一次机会了
One out of six, at least it's better than last time.
六个中有一个，至少比上次好
And now, let's continue our studies
现在，让我们用更安全的方法
with something much safer.
继续学习
Ooh!
Miss Devonshire, I didn't know
德文郡小姐，我不知道
you sold makeup in your spare time.
你在业余时间卖化妆品
Hey, I could use some new nail Polish.
嘿，我需要一些新的指甲油
Silence, you imbeciles!
安静，你们这些白痴！
I'm not selling this makeup,
我不卖这个化妆品
this is a demonstration of what you may need
这是一个示范，你可能需要什么
when you go undercover.
当你去卧底
Really, I never seem to find a use for it.
真的，我好像从来没有找到它的用处
Frequently you may have to pose
在卧底的时候
as prostitutes when undercover.
你经常要扮成妓女
I'm going to show you how they wear their makeup
我将向你们展示她们是如何化妆的
so that you can learn.
这样你就可以学习到了
Didi, shawnee, come up here, please.
迪迪，肖尼，请上来
Miss Devonshire, wouldn't it be more beneficial to us
德文郡小姐，如果你能在女孩身上试试
if you tried it on girls
不是对我们更有好处吗？
who weren't so cheap looking to begin with?
他们本来不就是那么便宜的人吗？
No, Holly, that will be enough.
不，霍莉，够了
Now remember, time is everything.
记住，时间就是一切
No pimp is going to wait an hour
没有哪个皮条客会等一个小时
for his whore to put on her face.
让他的婊子给她脸上化妆
Didi, I want you to take this stopwatch and time me.
迪迪，我要你拿着这块秒表给我计时
Now, watch carefully, here I go.
现在，仔细看，我开始了
21 seconds!
21秒！
Now, let's see what she looks like.
现在，让我们看看她长什么样
Ooh!
Now, shawnee, let's see if you've learned anything.
现在，肖尼，让我们看看你是否学到了什么
Let's see what you can do for didi
让我们看看你能为迪迪做些什么
in the same amount of time.
在同样的时间里
And begin.
开始
19 seconds, a new record.
19秒，一个新的记录
Well, let's see what you've done.
好吧，让我们看看你做了什么
Didi, it's you.
迪迪，是你
And, class dismissed.
下课了
This just goes to prove something
这只是为了证明一些事情
I've suspected for some time.
我已经怀疑了一段时间了
What's that?
是什么？
Only a witch could put on make-up this quickly.
只有女巫能这么快化妆
You know, you two really surprise me.
你知道，你们两个真的让我很惊讶
What do you mean?
什么意思？
I thought that I was the only one in class
我以为我是班上唯一一个
who took the time to go out undercover every night.
每晚都花时间出去卧底的人
I had no idea that we shared the same interests.
我不知道我们有共同的兴趣
Holly, you might be going out undercover,
霍莉，你可能是去做卧底，
but we're just going out to have some fun.
但我们只是出去找点乐子
I should have known.
我早该知道的
Isn't there anything in life that's important to you?
难道生活中就没有对你重要的事情吗？
Do you just wanna have fun all the time?
你只想一直玩得开心吗？
Give it a rest, school's out.
休息一下，放学了
No, you just name one important cause
不，你只要说出一个
you have ever fought for!
你为之奋斗过的重要事业！
We once petitioned for the legalization
我们曾经请求合法化
and the decriminalization of a, nevermind!
和非犯罪化，无所谓！
Forget I asked.
当我没问
You're right, Holly,
你说得对，霍莉
we're gonna give that some serious thought
我们会认真考虑的
and when we think of what we can do,
当我们想到我们能做什么的时候
you'll be the first to know.
你会是第一个知道的
Well, I'm glad that you see it my way.
I do.
I don't understand it, daddy.
I have been out here for over three hours
and no one has even come up to me.
Keep at it, pumpkin, we'll get 'em.
Honey, we are going out tonight.
Yes!
You look really good.
Did you say something?
No.
Hey, are you all right?
What happened to you?
Leave me alone!
Let us help you.
How can you help me?
We're cops.
Are you sure you're cops?
Well, sometimes we're not even sure ourselves.
We're still in the academy but we can help you.
Just tell us what happened to you.
My name is cherry pop,
I ran away from home when I was 15
with a name like cherry pop, no wonder.
No, that's not my real name.
I recently tried to get out of the porno business,
I released my own exercise video.
"Boning up with cherry pop."
But the people I made the pornos for didn't like it,
they said stop making these tapes.
Who did this to you?
Was it one of the actors?
No, not the actors,
the director hired someone to do this to me.
And now I'll never work again!
Why don't you just come down to the station with us
and file a statement
and testify to put these people away.
No, I'm afraid of them, I can't testify!
They'll come after me, they'll kill me!
No, no!
Wait, we wanna help youl!
I hate to admit it,
but Holly might be right about something for once.
What do you mean?
We have to grow up already.
We can't just waste away the rest of our lives.
Yes, girls?
We're going undercover to investigate
phony roller derby matches.
Well, I hope those weeks of practice come in handy.
And we're gonna try and shut down a Mexican donkey show.
There goes my weekend.
Miss Devonshire, we heard about a porno operation
that hires underage girls.
We'd like to take a crack at it.
Girls, be serious.
No, we mean it.
I know the location of the company
and the people in charge there.
Very well then,
I'll give you some equipment you can use for your cover.
All right!
What's that?
It's your cover.
I'll just type your name on this phony resume
and you'll be all set.
There, just stick a picture of yourself on the back.
Thank you, miss Devonshire.
And remember, in order to make an arrest,
you need to obtain solid evidence.
You need to catch everyone in the act.
Yes, I understand.
There is one other thing you can use.
It looks like a whore's purse.
But look inside.
It is a whore's purse.
No, no no, look at this.
It looks like a lipstick.
It may look like a lipstick but watch.
Simulated gun fire,now, watch this.
Wow!
What's that?
It's a portable radio,
but combined with these earrings,
it's also a receiver and transmitter.
You can talk into this earring for help
and listen from this one.
Your backup agent can wear the headphones
and come to your aid.
These are very expensive devices, just be careful.
Any questions?
Does it come in any other colors?
This is the place.
Thanks for coming along, Dwayne.
Yeah.
Well, how do I look?
On!
That good, huh?
Remember, this case is important to me.
I'm not just doing it for our quota.
Hey, don't worry,
with this transmitter we can hear everything that goes on.
Good luck.
God.
Here.
Oh, 9:30.
9:30.
Can I help you?
Word's out on the street you're looking for a new actress.
Great, get on your back and let's see what we can do.
Hey, listen, any work I do is considered a day's paycheck.
So unless you're willing to start me on payroll right now,
you just better keep your clothes on.
You're a pro, ar en' Ty a?
I'm not just off the bus from Omaha.
Listen, I was just kidding about the first part.
Really?
This is great, all we need is some solid evidence now.
Do you think she should have gone on the couch with him?
Shh!
I brought my resume with me,
it'll show you what I do best.
Quite impressive.
Well, I like what I do and I do it well.
Is there anything you wouldn't consider doing in a film?
Well, I don't do any animal acts.
Really?
It says here that you've done quite a few in your picture
"if I could talk to the animals."
Looks like you made it with half the zoo.
Uh, well, that was one of my earlier films.
Animal acts!
Who gave her that resume?
Miss Devonshire gave it to her.
I think she should've read it first.
Uh, I also don't do any s&m.
Are you sure?
According to this you enjoy it,
you've done everything imaginable in your picture,
"beat me in St. Louie."
That was a long time ago, I, uh,
I'm looking for a new image now.
Are you sure you want to do a picture like ours,
I mean it's only straight sex.
Sounds fine to me.
Wow, who's that?
What about your fans,
what if they don't like your new image?
Chucky, just in time.
Yeah, time for what?
I'd like you to meet the actress
who's auditioning lead opposite of you in our next film.
Chucky long, meet didi fluffer.
Hello.
Didi might be replacing the actress
that you usually work with.
Um, what happened to the other actress?
Oh, we had to get rid of her because she turned 19.
I never thought she passed 18.
Hey, Chucky, since you're here,
why don't you read a scene with didi.
Yeah, how 'bout it?
I don't know, I've got a full schedule today.
I've got an appointment at my tanning salon
and then there's my facial.
Why don't you make time?
J well, if you only live in it
j everybody else will too
j set on out to this Mark
this thing's only 12 pages long.
Our films aren't about dialogue, you should know that.
Oh, yeah, right.
All right, why don't you go ahead
and start reading from the scene on page three.
Baby, it's been a long, hard day
and I'm looking for some relief.
It looks like you came to the right place.
Some things were just meant to be.
J for as long as I need
j come and purify the disease
brilliant, you got the part!
Oh, great, I'll do it for free.
What did you say?
I said we'll discuss my fee.
9:45.
Yeah, and I gotta get out of here,
unless you want me to change my stage name to Lily white.
Ooh, 9:45.
I'll see you on your back.
Congratulations,you got the part.
I love this job.
I wish I knew what slut this resume belonged to.
Sowould I, I'd like to meet her.
No.
If you like it now,you're gonna love it later.
If you like it now, you're gonna love it later.
If you like it now, you're gonna.
How you doing?
Um, I'm a little nervous,
it's been a while since
I've done one of these.
There's too many people in here,
I think I'm gonna
go in the next room
and read a few lines by myself.
Where did she go?
She said she was nervous.
She had to go in the next
room and do a few lines.
Understandable.
If you like it now,
you're gonna love it later.
If you like it now, you're
gonna love it later.
I found a book that covers
all their illegal operations.
Good, see if you can lift
it without anyone noticing.
No, he might look there.
They're waiting
for you on the set.
Right.
Noon.
Don't we have enough
evidence to take them yet?
No, not yet, we have to
catch everyone in the act.
Is it, if you like it now,
you're gonna love it later.
Oris it, if you like it
now, you're gonna love it...
Didi, I want you to meet
Desiree, our director.
Pleased to meet you.
Likewise, and you
probably never worked
for a woman director before.
I think it might be
a little different
than what you're used to.
Sex films used to be about women
on their knees in
a peep show booth.
Well, things aren't
like that anymore.
My films have a story,
all the women in my films
play powerful characters
that choose their sex partners.
You understand?
Yes.
Good, now take your places.
Oh, and Chucky.
Yeah?
In the scene,
I'd like you to degrade
her as much as possible.
Okay, everybody, places!
I wish we could
make our move already.
You wanna hear the latest
tape from severe tire damage?
Severe tire damage?
They're my favorite
group, put it on.
Turn it up.
Woo!
Okay, you two know
what to do, right?
Yeah, we got it.
"Chafed raw",
scene one, take one.
Action.
Who is it?
I wanna rape you until
you're split in two.
No, no cut!
Didi, you're supposed
to be frightened of him.
You're not supposed
to so goddamn anxious
you rip the door off the hinges.
Sorry.
Take it from where you left off.
"Chafed raw",
scene one, take two.
Action.
I said action, didi,
didn't you hear me?
Yeah, I just wanted to make
sure everybody else did, too.
I forgot something my
doctor told me to do.
Her doctor?
Hey, you never told me she
had any medical problems.
She never told
me anything either.
Uh, no, no, it's about my back.
My doctor said that I should
just stay off my feet.
I mean on my feet!
Didi, are you having
some sort of trouble today?
She'll be all right, won't you?
I'm ready for my
close-up, Mr. demille.
Take it from where you left off.
You shouldn't open
the door to strangers.
I'm gonna have to
teach you a lesson.
I wish he'd degrade her more.
I heard from one of our
sources that some vice ring
might try to crack
down on our operation.
You think it might
be somebody in here?
Do you think it might be
one of the crew members?
We've worked with this crew
before, we can trust them.
What about the new actress?
Are you kidding?
Wait a minute!
We forgot about didi.
I think we're a little late.
A little late?
All right, cut.
Freeze, you're under arrest!
Sorry we're late.
You lied to us, you never
had sex with any zoo animals.
Of course not, you fool.
I'm appalled at the
way you betrayed me.
You're no sister.
Desiree, as a director,
you have a lot to learn
about a woman's needs.
A vice cop?
I feel used and violated.
Shut up, Chucky.
Yeah, well I faked
my orgasm for you.
Shut up, I might be able
to Grant you full immunity.
All right, everybody outside.
Come on!
You're coming with me.
Didi, there's something
I've got to ask you.
Sure, what is it?
Was it good?
Huh, the best!
Oops, I forgot something.
Come on, put
your hands up, come on.
Put your hands up.
What are we doing at your place?
You'll see.
Well, what're
you gonna do to me now?
Time to get back to work!
All right, scene two, take one!
You've got to be kidding.
Ooh, oh, Chucky, scene
one, take two, take three!
Wait, I need some rest.
Scene two, take one!
Scene five, six, seven!
Oh, scene two, three, four!
Oh, okay.
Oh.
After today I bet
we're finally gonna get
the kind of respect we
deserve around here.
Oh, don't look now,
but here comes Holly.
Good, she can be
the first to hear.
Holly, you know you're not
supposed to come to school
in the clothes your boyfriend
makes you dress up in.
For your information, didi,
while you were sleeping
in this morning,
I was busy breaking up a high
school narcotics operation.
Is that so?
How many arrests did you make?
Four.
Ha, while you were
busting freshmen,
we made twice as many arrests
cracking a porno operation.
A porno operation?
How did you hear about that?
I have my sources, too.
Really, what sources?
You'll find out,
just watch and see who's going
to be teacher's pet today.
In fact, here she comes now.
Miss Devonshire,
would you like to hear
about the arrests that
I made this morning?
I got two high school
seniors for dealing drugs
and another two for
writing obscenities
on the bathroom wall.
Later, Holly.
Didi, I got a
report this morning.
It had something on it
that was so unbelievable
I had to hear it
from you myself.
What is it?
You infiltrated that porno
ring yesterday, didn't you?
Yes.
Well, here's what I'm
having trouble with.
It says that before
you made the arrest,
you had sex with a male lead
in front of the entire crew.
Now is that true?
Well, yeah.
How could you be so stupid,
don't you realize we can't
put these people away
until we get a conviction?
How is your testimony
going look in court
when it comes out that
you performed a sex act
before you made the arrest?
Well, I don't know.
It's worthless,
you might as well let
these people go right now.
No jury is going to convict
them based on your testimony.
Miss Devonshire, I don't think
you can blame didi
entirely for this,
we're also to blame.
Yeah, we were
late making arrests.
She had the choice between
blowing her cover or blowing...
Shawnee, that will be enough!
You three are a disgrace
to the entire academy.
Go on, didi, tell us
how you were going to
be teacher's pet today.
Shut up, Holly.
No, go on,
I only had to do a few
cheers for my cover,
what did you have to do?
You're right, Holly,
I should have left
the case for you,
you make a much better
whore than anyone in class.
Ooh!
Girls, break it up!
This is against academy rules.
Watch out for the tires!
Girls, girls, break it up!
Cheap trash!
Spoiled brat!
That will be enough!
Didi, shawnee, Dwayne, I have
a special assignment for you.
You three realize that
since you can't get
a conviction on this case,
I can't count it against
your quota of 10 arrests.
That's not fair,
we made the arrests.
But since tomorrow
is graduation,
I'll give you one last
chance to make your quota.
But you have to do it
completely by the book.
There is a prostitution
ring working the inner city.
If you crack it, make the
arrests, and close them down,
you will be allowed to graduate
tomorrow with the others,
that's the deal.
You have 18 hours, good luck.
Miss Devonshire, I
couldn't help overhearing,
my father's been working
on the inner city ring
for quite some time now.
It's one of the queen
bee's operations,
every time he sends an
officer out on the job,
they never come back.
He's lost five already.
Yes, I know.
I better let that group
in the porno movie go.
We can't keep them
here any longer.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Well, speak up.
I heard on the street
that you arrested some
people making a porno movie.
It's true, I was just
about to let them go.
Because of a
technicality though,
we can't get a
conviction against them.
That won't be necessary,
I'm willing to
testify against them.
This book will
back up everything
I have to say against them.
I don't know how we're gonna
pull this thing off in time.
Graduation's tomorrow morning!
Don't worry, we have all night.
Look, there's one now.
Let's get to it.
Remember, you gotta
get her to say a price
before you can arrest her.
Right.
Watch this.
Hi, there, what's your name?
Hi, my name's tinsel.
That's a pretty name.
Oh, thank you.
I just happened to notice
you were standing
here all by yourself
and I thought maybe you
could use some company.
Oh, that's generous of
you, I like that type.
Why don't you give me an idea
on how generous I need to be.
Well, why don't you tell me.
I asked you first.
Hi, how ya doing?
He's doing fine and I'm busy,
so why don't you
find your own block.
Listen, whatever
she's charging you,
I'll do the same and throw
in a continental breakfast.
What?
Continental breakfast?
That's right, I'll
make it all by myself.
Hey, look, what are
you lookin' for tonight,
a good time or short order cook?
What comes with this breakfast?
Eggs, muffins, and
fresh squeezed juice.
Oh, this is ridiculous.
I'll make 'em any
way you like 'em,
hard-boiled, scrambled,
or over-easy.
Hey, look, honey,
I'm sorry your waitress
job laid you off,
but this is my block.
Enterprise is the American way.
Which one of us?
All right, I'll throw
in a dozen donuts.
Mm, glazed?
Huh, whatever
she's charging you,
I'll do it for 10 dollars less.
Why now that's
hitting below the belt.
Well, how much are you?
Well, I'm usually 40 bucks,
but I'll make an exception
and do it for 30.
What do you think of that?
Okay, we're vice cops.
You're under arrest.
What?
I don't know how to cook
any of those things either.
Oh, you stinkin' piece
of trash, you tricked me.
You'll never get away with it.
Save it for the judge.
How'd it go?
Beautiful, we did
everything by the book.
Hey, you're just
wasting your time.
I'll be back out on the streets
before you even get a chance
to get around the block.
By the time you get out you'll
be too old to do phone sex.
You watch what
you're saying, you...
Get in there!
Hey, look, there's another one.
Let's see how fast
we can bust this one.
You working tonight or
just watching the stars?
The only time I watch the
stars is when I'm on my back.
That's a good position.
Watch out, sparkle, it's a trap.
Hey, keep it to yourself.
You ready to go
gaze at some stars?
I couldn't help overhearing,
I have a telescope at my place.
Why don't you come
home with me instead.
What the hell is this?
I've never seen you here before.
That's because when you're good,
you don't spend much
time out on the streets.
Yeah, well, you don't
know who you're talkin' to.
What'll it be, I'd love to
see the big Dipper tonight.
Well, what kind of
telescope do you have?
Hey, screw this.
Hey, I'm $40, do
you want it or not?
Yeah, I want it.
You're under arrest!
Hey, you tricked me.
Honey, you must be good
because you're not gonna
be spending much time out
on the street either.
Uh, no!
Ow, ow, hey, ow, ow!
Oh, tinsel, they got you, too?
Oh.
Join the party.
Nice.
Cheap floozies.
They're like scum.
Two-bit con artists.
Shut up back there!
Oh!
This is easier than
I thought it would be.
What we need to do is
to start picking
them up in quantity.
How do we do that?
Well, this one at a
time stuff's all right,
but I'm sure there's a
whole group of people
somewhere all in one place.
All we need to do is find
them and make one big arrest.
That's great if
we can find them.
We will, come on, let's go.
Look, there it is,
a laundromat posing
as a front for prostitution.
Oh, no, they found it!
I think I need a
special cover for this.
Hello, girls, I'm
looking to party.
I have a lot of money, here!
How much are we talkin' about?
I am looking for good prices.
You can have us all for $150.
Up against the wall, spread 'em.
Say what?
Look, here he comes.
Ow!
Get in there.
Sparkle, tinsel?
Save the reunion for later.
We're half-way there.
What about the Johns?
You have to go to the bathroom?
No, now that the
laundromat is empty,
didi and I can take over and
arrest some of their customers.
Yeah, we can make
our quota right here.
Get to it.
Yeah!
Girls, it's okay
of you wanna struggle
and try to get loose,
I like to watch.
Pervert!
What do we do now?
Look like we mean business.
Oh, I'm just looking for change.
I think you came
to the right place.
So what are you doing?
My laundry.
Aren't you supposed to take off
all your clothes
before you wash 'em?
Sometimes, but I like
to do two things at once.
Really?
So what brings you here?
A hot rinse, a fast tumble,
or something on the
more delicate side?
Gee, I don't know,
what'll this get me?
Ooh, that will get me
to wash all my clothes.
So can we go in one
of the rooms in back?
Sounds like you've
been here before.
I think the back's
a little crowded,
why don't we just
do it right here?
Right here, in
front of everybody?
Don't worry, we'll have privacy.
A laundry bag?
There's plenty of room, look.
Now why don't you just join me.
All right.
Here, you put it in place
while I get to work, huh?
Hey, what are you doing?
You're under arrest, bozo!
This, this is entrapment.
Huh, yeah and it
worked real well.
I'll check the back to
see if we got 'em all.
Good, I'll take him outside.
Open up the back,
I got another one.
That was fast.
She's got a tire iron!
Uh, Dwayne, help, Dwayne!
I'm trying.
Help, Dwayne!
Get her, get her.
Hey, get the keys
to these damn things.
I got 'em, I got 'em!
Let's take them
back to our warehouse
around the corner, we'll
take care of them there.
You're tampering
with police business.
You can't get away with this.
Just shut it up already!
Oh, call a tow truck.
Welcome to a theater
that's been closed for 50 years.
Hello?
Oh, Chuck, we were in
the middle of an arrest
and something went wrong,
they've got shawnee and Dwayne.
I need your help to save them.
Oh, yeah, how am
I supposed to help?
You left me
handcuffed to the bed.
I left you the key
under the telephone,
I thought you'd find it by now.
When the lights go down,
the body count goes up.
Great, thanks a lot,
now I'll see if I can
walk after last night.
Chucky, please
don't let me down.
They took them to a warehouse
near cahuenga and lankershim.
Meet me there as
soon as you can.
Okay, okay, goodbye.
I mean, right now.
Help, help,
help, help!
You can yell all you want
'cause there ain't
nobody around to hear ya.
Oh, Chucky,
I'm so glad you're here.
You know, I don't know
why I'm doing this for you.
There's something
I wanted to tell you.
What is it?
Well, this is kind
of awkward for me.
Even though I only
find you attractive
on a strictly physical level
and I could never take you
home to meet my parents,
I still think I love you.
I sorta feel the
same way about you.
There's one other thing.
What?
I lied to you before, I
didn't fake my orgasm for you.
I kinda figured that
one out on my own.
Come on, let's go.
Follow me.
Okay, this way.
The queen bee will see you now.
Now just be quiet and wait.
So you're the two that thought
that you could
crack my crime ring?
But you didn't expect to run up
against the queen
bee, now did you?
Who?
The queen bee.
Are we supposed to know you?
The queen bee,
the one who runs all
these inner city drug
and prostitution rings.
Don't recognize the name.
I thought you
said they were cops.
Well, that's what I thought.
Miss bee, we're
not police officers,
we're students at
the vice academy.
The academy, the academy?
These people are rookies.
Your people cost
me a thousand dollars
and I'm gonna take
it out of your hide.
And from what I can see
now, you're about 950 short.
Didn't you realize
that our police force
has already sent out
five undercover agents
to pose as hookers in my ring.
We captured all five and we
haven't heard from them since.
What happened to them?
Well, we sent them overseas.
We sold them into white slavery.
They don't bother me anymore
and soon you'll join
them, very soon.
What about me?
What about you?
Oh, we have a special
assignment for you.
We need someone to watch
over all of those girls.
That's something I think
you could do quite well.
Watch a group of girls,
that doesn't sound so bad,
I might even enjoy it.
I doubt that,
because first we're
going to castrate you.
Help, somebody help us!
Scream all you want,
no one can help you now.
You can't capture
that entire group,
you might as well
call the police now
before we get caught also.
You heard what she'd do to us,
there are some things a man
won't sacrifice, no matter what.
Chucky, it's no time to talk
about major surgery,
I have a plan.
A plan, right.
I still have a few
tricks left up my sleeve,
just trust me.
Okay, now I want you to
make a tape recording
of you sounding like a police
officer arresting everybody.
Now go on, try it.
This is the police chief,
you're all under arrest.
No, no, no, make it
sound more convincing.
Use the voice that you
use in your movies.
This is the police chief,
you're all under arrest.
Put your hands in the air,
you have the right
to remain silent,
don't move or we'll shoot.
We have the building surrounded.
Anything you say can and
will be used against you
in a court of law.
Don't try to escape, we're
sending for backup units.
That was great, where'd
you learn to say all that?
Oh, I've been
arrested a few times.
Hmm, hurry, we got to
get back to where we were
before the tape starts.
Oh, get those shipping
crates over here, will you?
And don't forget to punch
some holes in them this time
so they don't suffocate
like the last group.
This is the police chief,
you're all under arrest.
What the hell is that?
It's a trick, queen bee.
Yeah, pack these two up.
Put your hands in the air,
don't move or we'll shoot.
It is a trick, they wouldn't
shoot with two hostages.
This is no time
to fix your make-up.
Sh!
Oh my god, I forgot,
they're rookies,
they'll shoot at anything.
We have the place surrounded,
you have the right
to remain silent.
What do we do now, queen bee?
This place is a
honeycomb of mazes,
they'll never catch
us, follow me.
Don't try to escape,
we're sending backup units.
Listen to that!
Which way now?
This way, b-girls.
Didi, how'd you find us?
Never mind, we have to catch
them before they get away.
What's he doing here?
He was the only one I
could call to help us.
What's he done so far?
Don't move or we'll shoot.
Good work.
Hurry, we have to get them
before they find their way out.
I thought you said this
place was a maze of honeycombs.
I am the queen bee
not the maze keeper!
This must be the way out.
Hurry, girls.
Faster, b-girls, faster!
Hey, how did you get untied?
It's a professional secret.
Oh, yeah, well, what
kind of professional secret
have you got for this?
(Gun clicking
Dwayne, Dwayne!
Dwayne, the pressure point!
I thought we were gonna
do everything by the book.
We are, I'm just
using a different book.
Follow me.
Chucky long, it's you!
Oh, mr, long, I'm
your biggest fan.
You can have it for free.
You like it kinky?
Does the queen
bee sleep on her back?
Now, wait here while
we catch the others.
Damn you!
This is the last
time I ever spend
a quarter to see
one of your films!
What the hell happened to you?
Sparkle, how did
you get handcuffed?
Oh, never mind, it was
just a brief infatuation.
Come on, come on, come on!
What happened to you?
I don't know, when
that girl took off her blouse,
it had an effect on me like
I never experienced before.
Oh, really?
Well, we'll have to
discuss it, later!
This must be the way out.
Something's wrong!
Go!
Didi!
Yeah!
Oh, great we got them!
Oh, Chucky, we couldn't
have done it without you!
Hey, wait, what time is it?
It's after seven in the morning!
Hurry, we're gonna
miss graduation.
Come on!
Go!
Congratulations on
your commencement.
Graduating the vice
academy is an honor
that only we can
bestow upon you.
Soon you will be
working hand in hand
as proud members of
the police force.
Cleaning up our streets
of all the sleaze,
slime, and filth,
that make our academy strong.
And now, police chief Wells
would like to say a few words.
Thank you very much
for those very kind
words, miss Devonshire.
You said them just the
way I had them written.
I'm especially proud
of my daughter Holly,
and all of you for that matter.
Faster, didi, faster!
Of the glorious graduates...
Miss Devonshire, wait!
What in the world?
You can't start
graduation without us!
How dare you interrupt
my father's speech.
Shut up, you'll wanna see this.
I don't believe it.
The queen bee,
my own police force
hasn't been able
to bring her in.
Yes, I know, we
got them to confess
to where they had
all of your agents
that they'd previously captured.
This is the greatest sting
operation I've ever seen.
Better than anything my own
police officers have ever done,
better than anything my
own daughter is capable of.
Daddy, how could you?
Oh, but, pumpkin...
Don't touch Mel
Princess.
Just leave me alone.
A-ha, just as I thought!
What?
There are only nine
people in the Van,
their quota was 10 and
they failed to meet it.
But...
You know as well as I
that they can't be
allowed to graduate.
But surely you can make
an exception in this case.
The queen bee
should count double.
Literally.
We do things by
the book around here.
The requirement was 10 and
they failed to meet it.
I'm afraid she's right,
the requirement is 10.
I'm very sorry.
You forgot to
count me, it is 10.
Chucky, what are you doing?
Be quiet, I owe you.
Why aren't you in the
back with the rest of them?
They let me in front on
account of good behavior.
Chucky, how can
I ever repay you?
Post my bail.
It looks like you
three are graduating.
Please reconsider,
this one can't even
keep her clothes on.
This is the most arrests
we've had at one time
since we booked that
group in the porno movie.
We were the ones who
brought in that group.
But since miss Devonshire said
that we couldn't convict 'em,
it wouldn't count
against our quota.
What are you talking about?
We had a witness come
in here yesterday.
We've got a conviction
that's good enough
to put the whole group
away for some time.
What?
Oh, didn't I mention that?
Hi, you guys.
- Cherry pop!
- Hi, cherry!
We have good news,
we're graduating!
I have good news, too,
my exercise video
just went platinum!
- Get outta town!
- God.
Oh, let me see now, our
arrest quota is actually 20,
that's the highest in
the academy's history,
do you know what that means?
Congratulations on
a job well done.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
How's it feel
watching us graduate
when there's nothing
you can do about it?
Let's hear it for
our valedictorians!
So, is there really money
in making exercise videos?
Are you kidding,
at this rate I'll be able
to retire at 18.
This could be the new career
move I've been looking for.
Hmm, "pump it up with Chucky
long," got a nice ring to it.
Come, miss Devonshire, we
have a trip to make downtown.
You know, I have
to give you credit
for your class this semester.
I'm sure your
three prized pupils
will work very well
side by side with you.
You don't mean it.
Of course I do,
I think their best
place on the force
will be working
right along side you.
Shut up back there!
I mean, sure, they'll
make great partners.
J huh
j got a pistol in my pocket
j and baby, you can cock it
j put your finger on the trigger
j feel it getting bigger
j move a little closer
j let me stick it
in your holster
j let's do it
j shoot my bullet
j got a pistol in my pocket
j and baby, you can cock it
j it's got a 12 inch length
j and you can make it plank
j blow me away, just
give me a yank
j let's do it
j shoot my bullet
j when you roll up in my Levi's
j you can feel my Colt, yeah, 45
j got a pistol in my pocket
j and baby, you can cock it
j it's straight from undercover
j but don't show it mother
j lookin' for a sexy way
to blow my ammunition
j let's do it
j bite my bullet
j well, you better
start stripping
j or you're gonna get
in the way of love
J huh
j got a pistol in my pocket
j and baby, you can cock it
j I'm a gun fanatic
j feel my automatic
j grab my love rocket
j and then feel my body rocking
j let's do it
j bite my bullet
j now I've got you in my sight
j and I'm gonna hear the full cry tonight