There are many schools of
martial arts in our country.
One of which is the Southern style.
Besides Hung, Lau, Choy and
Li, Mok styles,
it also includes a popular style
called Wing Chun Kuen.
Legend has it that Wing Chun Kuen
was founded by a Shaolin Abbess Ng Mui.
She imparted her skills to a girl,
Yim Wing Chun.
Hence the name Wing Chun Kuen.
Yim imparted her skills
to her husband Leung Bok Chau.
Leung taught Wong Wah Bo.
Wong taught Leung Jan.
Leung Jan's family owned a pharmacy,
Hang Sang Tong, in FoShan.
He was a proficient herbalist
and qualified in bone manipulation.
Leung Jan is a kind and helpful man.
He's very respected in the village.
The villagers called him Master Jan.
FoShan has another kind and
rigteous man called Chan Wah.
He's brave and would stand
against any injustice.
He would help anyone in trouble.
There are many Kung Fu experts in FoShan.
Each has their own training school.
Competition to get into
these schools was strong.
Chan Wah has always been
interested in Kung Fu.
He first learnt Kung Fu on his own.
He later became a student of Leung Jan.
He is to become the fifth generation
Wing Chun Master.
Wah was working as
a cashier at Mok Kei Bank.
He's known as Cashier Wah.
My fellow villagers,
Fatty's stall is now open...
Please buy something.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we've fresh rice dumplings.
Every one is specially made.
Please try one.
lt's very tasty.
Come on, please buy one.
Hey! Tall one....
No, Uncle.
Rice dumpling, look carefully before buying.
Don't you like rice dumplings? OK...
This is a special rice dumpling,
good with either sugar or salt.
This is really special, it tastes wonderful.
Marvellous.
Hey!
- Hey Fatty! l'm looking for a restaurant.
- What?
Are you deaf?
Where's the restaurant?
Straight from here,
then turn left and left and left.
Left and left and left again.
When you see Ah Sao, you're there.
- Fatty!
- Good morning, buying dumplings?
- Wait.
- l've something to tell you.
What? Someone in your family died?
Nonsense, it's your family.
All my family members have died.
l'm the only survivor.
Fatty, someone has been talking about you.
Who's that?
Spittle Mun.
Spittle Mun? l don't know him.
What did he say?
He said that Wing Chun Kuen is good
but what you learnt is crap.
Everyone in FoShan
from three to 83 years old
knows that l am a student of Leung Jan.
- Really?
- How old is Spittle Mun?
He's 84.
No wonder.
What's so good about Wing Chun?
l'm good at Horse Groin Clamps.
The Sifu of my Sifu was practising
Horse Groin Clamps under a big tree.
Suddenly there was a thunderstorm.
A bolt of lightning felled the tree.
The Sifu of my Sifu didn't move an inch.
Such is the power of Horse Groin Clamps.
- That's impressive.
- How is he now?
He got struck by lightning and died.
lt's true, l was told.
Spittle Mun said that
your Horse Groin Clamps isn't that good.
lf l'm in the stance,
ten of you can't move me.
- Really?
- He's boasting.
lf you can handle the power of my palm,
l'll be impressed.
Who do you think you are? Let's try.
Let's bet then, if l can move you with
my palm, you give me all your dumplings.
lf you can't?
Then l'll buy all your dumplings.
- Good.
- Let's do it.
- You're not to move once you're ready.
- OK.
Hey! Mister, stop it. No! No!
Mister!
Why are you taking my dumplings?
l'm not taking your dumplings,
l'm claiming them. You've lost the bet.
Are you denying it?
- l...
- l want to thank you.
- Rice dumplings...
- Savoury dumplings...
Rice dumplings, savoury dumplings,
sweet dumplings...
How many?
Please come inside.
Please be seated.
Master, be seated.
Damn, the table is too small for seven of us.
We'll sit there, follow me.
Master, l'm sorry but
this table has been reserved.
Reserved? By who?
Master Jan, this is his regular table.
Master Jan? Never heard of him. Sit.
Master...
Master Jan.
Third Uncle, look at them.
lt's nothing to do with you.
So you're Master Jan.
Yes, what can l do for you?
Who is this girl?
She's my niece.
She's taken my seat,
what are you doing about it?
l apologise.
Kam Fung, stand up and
give your seat back to him.
Bitch, trying to make fun of me?
Stop it!
We've just arrived and
you're already in trouble.
lt's not a time to fight.
Gentleman, please tell me,
where is the Mok Kei Bank?
Those bullies must have
taken advantage of you again.
Cashier Wah, you can help someone poor.
Can you cure someone stupid?
l don't think so.
l want a change of career.
l'll sell watermelons next.
Why? You make a loss
whenever you sell something.
Even if people don't cheat you,
you end up eating all your stock.
Why don't you give me some advice?
What business should l do?
There's a job that you won't be cheated in
and you won't eat anything.
- Fatty, not selling dumplings any more?
- l have a new career.
New career? What are you selling now?
Can it be eaten?
You're clearing shit now?
lf l don't change my career,
you'll cheat me again.
Boss, we thought you were dead.
We're surprised to see you here.
There's one more thing
that you'll never guess.
l've opened a bank here
using the money we made together.
We've been doing good business.
We've made twice as much now.
Let's split the money.
lron Fist, you really are a pea-brain.
Because of Mok Kei Bank
l am a respectable man in this village.
Boss, respectability doesn't buy food.
But l can use it as a springboard.
What do you have in mind?
l want to control FoShan.
There's still a bill in my pocket.
No wonder l couldn't balance the account.
lf l become the Village Head here,
you guys will have nothing to worry about.
Aren't you afraid of other contenders?
There's only one person in this village
who could compete with me.
- Who's he?
- Leung Jan.
lf we want to kill the current Village Head,
it's easy.
We just have to make it
look like an accident.
l've already got a plan.
Who's that?
Rushing around like a blind chicken?
Master Yao, l've something important
to tell the Village Head.
What makes you think that
the Village Head doesn't need to sleep?
What's the matter?
- Really?
- Yes.
l didn't know that Boss Mok was like that.
l hope you have not told anyone about this.
l haven't.
Good!
This is an important matter,
you have to tell the Village Head personally.
But you can't do it in his house.
Let's meet at the Mountain Pavilion
early in the morning.
l'll come with the Village Head.
Cashier Wah, it was your misfortune
to have bumped into me.
This must be the worst day of your life.
What do you mean?
lt means that you have shit luck.
Luck of a lump of shit.
l don't know what are you talking about.
- Where's the Village Head?
- The Village Head.
My job is done.
Brother Wah, what happened?
Where is he?
- Search inside.
- OK.
What happened to him?
l don't know, ask him when he's conscious.
- You want Cashier Wah to come to us?
- Yes.
Cashier Wah is a loyal family man.
lf something happens to his mother,
he'll definitely come to us.
Remember, this time don't let him escape.
You have a good rest.
Fatty, go to my house and
tell my mother not to worry about me.
OK, l'll do it now.
What happened?
l'm not sure, but l heard that Cashier Wah's
mother was killed by bandits last night.
Where's Cashier Wah?
l don't know.
l've sent someone to the Mok Kei Bank
for him but he didn't go to work.
- Put more men on the case, find him.
- OK.
Fatty, how is my mum?
She's very well.
Did she tell you anything?
She said...
She said you shouldn't rush to see her.
Fatty, besides my mum,
did you see anyone else?
Yes, l saw the Village Head.
- ln my house?
- No, l saw him walking past.
- Fatty, l have another favour to ask you.
- What?
Tell the Village Head that
someone is trying to kill him.
Ask him to be careful.
- ls it true?
- Yes.
Fatty.
Tell the Village Head personally,
don't let anyone know about it.
Fatty, any women bathing inside?
Why can't l see it?
- lnside? Nothing there.
- Nothing?
lf there's nothing there,
what are you peeping at?
Nothing.
- lf there's nothing to see, get out of here.
- All right.
What are you looking at, bum?
Hey! Village Head.
- What is it?
- l've something to tell you.
l'm busy, what is it?
- Someone wants to kill you.
- What?
Someone is trying to kill you,
you must be careful.
Watch what you say.
Who wants to kill the village head?
- l don't know.
- Then what are you on about?
Nonsense.
Trust me for once, l'm not lying.
Who told you that?
Someone, but l can't tell you his name.
You are talking nonsense.
Me? Talking nonsense? l don't think so.
Stupid Fatty, l told you to get lost.
What are you doing here?
- Nothing, nothing.
- Get lost then.
- OK, l'm going.
- Scram.
- Why the leg?
- l'm sorry.
Looking for trouble?
l'll kill you... l'll kill you!
- What are you doing?
- Cramps.
Much better now.
Where has he gone?
The next time l see you, you'll be dead.
Fatty was telling the truth.
Village Head!
Serving The People
Why isn't he here yet?
We're very busy.
My fellow villagers, we've tried our best
to find the Village Head.
This meeting can't happen without him.
According to our constitution, if the
Village Head fails to attend without reason,
we have the right to choose another head.
Before we have more news
from the Village Head,
l recommend that all his duties
fall to the boss of Mok Kei Bank.
How about that?
- Good, good, good.
- l agree.
Cashier Wah, where are you going?
To see my mum.
You can't show yourself yet.
l'll be careful.
l'll return as soon as l see her.
- You won't recognise her.
- What do you mean?
Your mum is dead.
Fatty, say that again.
l'm not lying.
l saw the undertakers carrying her out.
lt can't be true!
Don't go! lf those seven guys see you,
they won't let you go.
They killed my mother. l want revenge.
Listen to me.
They did it to lure you out.
You will fall for their trick if you go.
l must avenge my mother's death.
You're not their match,
they are too strong for you.
lf you want revenge, go beg my Sifu.
Beg Master Jan.
Cashier Wah is at Master Jan's.
Yes, l just found out.
l never expected Leung Jan to get involved.
lt doesn't look like it.
lf Leung Jan wanted to get involved,
he would do something.
Anyway, Leung Jan is a nuisance to us.
Let's show him who's in charge.
Master Jan.
Master Jan, l've not eaten for two days.
Thank you.
l'm sorry, l'm sorry.
Good morning, Master Jan.
What a coincidence. Please, join me.
- l'll do it myself.
- Fine.
Please have some tea.
Master Jan, we are here specially for you.
What can l do for you?
A simple task, give us our man.
Your man?
Cashier Wah is of no use to you.
You two have misunderstood.
l haven't sheltered Cashier Wah.
He's just another of my patients.
l've no intention of getting involved
between you and him.
Until he's fully recovered,
he'll remain in my establishment.
That's my responsibility.
Trade him with your own life then.
Stop it!
Who are you?
How dare you start trouble here?
These guys obey you.
You can't be good.
Master Jan, how did you
get mixed up with these people?
l must have offended them
when l was much younger.
- Ah Mao!
- Yes.
l'll pay for the damage.
You don't have to.
Thank you, Master Jan.
- Boss Mok, l have to go now.
- Please.
Herbs Encyclopaedia
Cashier Wah, l don't know what
dispute you have with those people.
And l don't wish to know.
Since you've fully recovered,
you can go now.
Master Jan, why won't you adopt me?
You want me to adopt you
as my student only for revenge.
To learn Kung Fu for revenge
is against the principle.
- Master Jan, those are bad people.
- Enough.
To settle any dispute,
one party has to give in first.
That's the only way to avoid bloodshed.
Cashier Wah, you can go now,
l won't take you as my student.
- Sifu.
Thank you.
Sifu, is Cashier Wah
still kneeling in the study?
- Third Uncle...
- How many times have l told you?
No talking when you are eating.
Sifu, l know.
No talking when l'm eating.
Come on, please take a seat first.
Don't choke yourself.
Fatty, your idea didn't work.
lf l kneel any longer, l'll be paralysed.
Sifu is a very conservative man.
What should l do now?
Should l kneel or should l go?
What next?
l'm thinking about it.
Third Uncle, have some tea, please.
Kam Fung, has Cashier Wah left?
No, but he's found another Sifu.
Another Sifu?
- Sifu's here, get ready.
- OK.
Kneel down, kneel down.
Little Sifu, have some tea, please.
Fatty, what are you doing?
Since you rejected him as a student,
l've decided to teach him myself.
Now he is to call me Sifu.
- Student.
- Here.
- On your feet.
- Yes.
l'll teach you some basics.
Little Sifu, why are you not
using your hands?
- This is the Handless style.
- What stance is this?
This is the Two Gangsters stance.
Push your bum forward.
What's the function of this.
Wing Chun practitioners' way
of healing piles.
ls this Wing Chun style?
Why do you care? Just do what l say.
ln Wing Chun, our hand
has to look like Snake or Crane...
Why is your Crane slanted?
This is the Slanted Crane from Wing Chun.
Hand block.
Left block, right block, big block.
Last block, done.
Why are you keeping
the blocks in your pocket?
We have so many blocks,
where else can you keep them?
That makes sense.
ln Wing Chun, we go over the bridge,
not under it. Show me your hand.
- What if there's no bridge?
- No bridge?
Build one yourself, stupid.
Build a bridge?
How do l do that?
What does this look like?
- A bridge.
- Yes, it's more like a bridge than a tunnel.
Do you understand now?
Let's have a sparring match.
We'll see whose style is better.
But l warn you that Wing Chun
is unbeatable, you can't touch me.
This is Cultivating Hand.
This is Twisted Hand. The next is...
Little Sifu, what's the next move?
Back arch... lt hurts!
Watch out again.
- Sifu...
- You are a disgrace to Wing Chun.
Here, come on.
He will adopt you as his student.
Quick, serve Sifu some tea.
Sifu.
Abbess Ng Mui developed Wing Chun
after witnessing a snake and a crane fight.
She later refined it to three routines.
The first routine is Little ldeas.
Why is it called Little ldeas?
Sifu doubts that we will learn
the whole system of Wing Chun,
so he won't teach us Big Thoughts,
he will only give us Little ldeas.
Hence the term Little ldeas.
Stay focused!
Hey! We've learnt this before.
- Let's practise somewhere else.
- Good idea.
Searching the Bridge.
Darting Fingers.
Our moves come from the heart,
our strength from the ground.
The Six in One Move is from your
ankle,
knee,
waist,
shoulder,
elbow and wrist.
Strength from the six points
merge to form the Six in One Move.
The weakest part is your fist.
Other parts, like your palm,
elbow and shoulder,
could be attacked and defended.
The fist has three points.
Two points are here, watch.
The palm has three angles.
Palm should be flexible.
Hand can be snake or crane.
The form resembles a chicken,
the force resembles a cat.
The energy should be
directed at the enemy.
Expend your energy only when necessary.
l'm teaching you the most fundamental
technique of Wing Chun, Separate Hand.
Attack me.
This is Deadly Slap.
Dispersing Attack.
Winged Arm Darting Punch.
Controlling Arm.
Subdue Head, Rattle Tail.
Divert the attack, Linking Fast Palms.
Come again.
Cultivating Hand.
This is the Fiery Dragon.
Follow me.
Show me two fingers.
When l let go, catch it.
Pick it up.
Let's try again.
Do you know why you can't catch it?
Your eyes see it and alert the brain
before signalling your fingers to catch -
all this takes too long.
That's why in Wing Chun
there's a technique called Sticky Hand.
Sticky Hand trains the sensitivity
of your hand.
lt also allows you
to apply force appropriately.
Do you understand?
- Fatty.
- Yes, Sifu.
Practise with him.
Just now you are using lmpetus Power.
lmpetus Power combined with
Directional Power
will result in a momentous explosive force.
This is the power of combined force.
Sifu, what if the enemy uses his legs?
You try.
Use your arms to block high kicks.
Use your legs to negate the low kicks.
Do you understand?
Vengeance
Cashier Wah, l'll teach you
the secrets of Wing Chun,
l hope that you'll pass it on.
Sifu, l won't disappoint you.
Block it.
You must use the fastest time
and the shortest contact
to get these two dummies
back to their place.
Sifu.
You can't even control two dummies.
lf l were your third enemy,
you would be dead.
Start from the top.
With your skill you can defeat
more than two dummies.
Your problem is that you can't concentrate.
When you enter this dummy corridor
you only have one thing in mind.
Vengeance
Fatty has improved so much.
He's been scoring.
Sifu, he's...
Every martial art practitioner
has weaknesses.
Even someone who has mastered
the lnvincible Armour technique.
The most common weak points are,
the eyes and the groin.
To attack the weak points
is not an easy task.
The human body
has 108 basic pressure points.
The lnvincible Armour
technique won't change this.
The points are consistently
around the same area.
The lnvincible Armour
is not hurt by a normal punch.
But would be hurt by an impetus punch.
As long as you disturb his energy flow,
you have a chance to attack his weak points.
The weakest points with
the biggest surface area are
the feet and the side of the feet.
Now, l'll teach you the Wing Chun
Six and a Half points Pole.
First point, Twins on a Flute.
Second point, Falling Sky.
Third point, Deadly Ground.
Fourth Point, Monkey Stealing Peach.
Left Block, Right Bloom.
Beauty Rowing a Raft, only half a point.
Put together it becomes
Six and a Half points Pole.
The most difficult parts of this technique
are stabbing and dispersing.
lt's about the way you disperse
your energy to the tip of the pole.
The pole has elasticity.
Our aim is to combine its elasticity
with our applied force effectively.
Now, l want you to crush this olive stone.
You didn't combine
all your energy effectively.
You are only able to push the stone aside.
Try again.
Sifu.
Practice makes perfect.
No pain, no gain.
You should know the philosophy.
Don't worry.
Pick up all the olive stones now.
Try again.
Don't stop.
Sifu, l'm...
Your target is never stationary.
lf you respond only to your opponent's move,
it's already too late.
You have to reach the stage
when you hit whatever you see.
Try again.
l'm not worried about Cashier Wah.
lt's Leung Jan that l'm wary of.
- Master Jan won't compete with you.
- l know.
But he's sheltering Cashier Wah.
He might cause a problem in the future.
Master Jan is not a simple man.
- Mister Yao, everyone has a habit.
- That's true.
- Habits mean weaknesses.
- True.
He might be very skilful but he's still human.
Master Jan.
What's happening?
We are having renovations done,
please sit upstairs.
Master Jan, please be seated.
Master Jan.
l'm very hungry.
You...
l've not offended you
so why are you attacking me?
Killing you will get rid of
a pain in my backside.
Third Uncle, Third Uncle!
Stop it.
You will die together now.
- Junior, even Sifu lost to them.
- What should we do?
- Go with Cashier Wah.
- And you?
l'll take care of myself.
He's escaped.
Stupid Fatty,
not happy with the way you died?
lt's Fatty.
- What have you found out.
- What happened?
Mok has become the Village Head.
- He's taken over the village office?
- Yes.
Where are his accomplices?
Let me think.
l know.
We'll have to attack them separately.
Kam Fung.
Use the Eight Slashing Knife
to counter Tiger's Long Spear.
Fatty, use your Sticky Hand
to counter Thunder's technique.
l'll use my Six and a Half Point Pole
against lron Fist.
Let's do it tonight.
l have to go.
- No don't go.
- lt's getting late.
- l'll come tomorrow night.
- Master.
Please come again.
Thunder.
You!
l'm Tiger, Thunder wouldn't visit
such a place.
Shit. l've got the names mixed up.
l'm in big trouble.
Bamboo.
Bamboo forest.
Kam Fung, help me. He's here.
lt's no use. Get ready to see your dead Sifu.
Your hand got stuck to mine.
Sifu...
Why did you die so easily?
Are you really dead?
l'm talking to you. Are you dead?
You're really dead.
lf l see you down below,
l'll kill you again and again.
Stupid Fatty mixed up the names.
l wonder how Fatty is doing?
What's happening?
We have intruders.
You two take care of them.
l'll go and get Boss Mok.
Kam Fung, why couldn't you last longer?
l give up.
Does Boss Mok know Kung Fu?
You're asking me?
How should l know?
l think l can take on the Fatty.
You.
Yes.
Come on.
Stupid Fatty, went for my weaker leg.
No, l'll do it myself.
Praying mantis.
Left, right, left, die.
- What's wrong?
- Cramps.
Much better.
Where is he?
Why is your head so hard?
There's a plate on top.
Should have kept you guessing.
l'll pretend l don't know.
Take that.
- Why can't you feel that?
- That's my numb and useless leg.
- Are you going to let me through?
- Yes, of course.
Smart move.
Let me down!
Do you like it?
l have a child and a wife, let me go!
Let me down!
Stupid Fatty.
Thank you.
Thanks a lot.
You peed yourself.
l know.
This is Praying Mantis Grip.
This is Fat Bird Pecking.
Fatty, are you all right?
l'm all right. Let's beat him together.
- How?
- l'll take his blows, you hit him.
- OK.
- l'm willing to die.
Hit his head.
Don't worry about me. Kill him.
l'm falling.
Fatty, are you all right?
- Can you stand?
- l'm not dead yet.
- Can you walk?
- No, you had better...
You want me to carry you?
No, l'll crawl out of here.
Let's go, then.