Ruby, have a drink with me.
Spare my assistant. I'll drink with you.
Pour.
- Finish this. - Finish this...
What about the apartment?
I'll buy it. No problem.
Nobody, nobody but you.
Andrew, where are you?
Why didn't you tell me you're not coming?
Now I have to do this all alone.
They brought devilish alcohol because of you.
My stomach is about to bleed.
Is this a set up?
What are you babbling about?
Your wife?
I can't hear...
Even the shoes suck when you're out of luck
Hold it...
Tonight someone has to strip.
Quiet down...
Today, we're all gathered here,
because the handsome and charming Zhu Tian
from our precinct
will kiss his bachelor days goodbye.
He found himself a wife.
Dong, you're too fussy. Just cut the spiel.
I want to sing this song.
Dong, get with the times. This song is out.
This is the wrong key.
This version is different.
You two go ahead. I can't sing this song.
Good, I'm sober.
You didn't have to do this.
What did you say?
You think women can only climb onto a bed?
Not me. I'll make a name for myself.
You go go go
Keep an eye on that moron.
N-A-E-L-C.
Miss.
Why is there a seedling here?
Are you drunk, Miss?
You're a little lamb in a men's world.
What room are you in? I'll take you back.
Take me back. Why am I left here?
What's this doing in my hand?
Police.
Don't get any ideas.
A cop? Great, you better take me back.
What room are you in?
I don't know, they ditched me.
Take me home, officer.
Miss...
You smell good.
What room are you in?
Where have you been?
Mr Ko. No. I just order some snacks for you guys
seems you are so hungry.
I am not hungry, just thirsty.
Let's play a game. If I win,
you must buy a flat from me.
No problem. I'll buy.
Let's play a game.
Let's go back inside.
- Come on. - OK.
Look at all those holes on your vest.
Inside and out, they're the living proof
of your bachelorhood.
We're all married,
you should be next.
I have to go.
Come on, not when we're all here.
Stay. It's hard setting up this gathering.
No, I need to catch the last train.
I can't spend more than I should.
You're great,
saving each penny for your bro.
Ping, Dong is a lifesaver.
He needs to look after Zhencong. Let him go.
Well...
Don't drink and drive.
- All right. Have a safe ride home. - Have fun.
Xiaole, don't be late next morning.
I know.
Bye.
Bye
Miss.
Why didn't you catch me, you stupid?
Are you OK?
It hurts.
Come on.
Miss.
Are you OK?
Little lamb.
Are you drunk?
Miss.
Take me home.
I must go home, Miss.
I want you to carry me home.
I have to go home myself.
I have to go home too.
Where do you live?
I live...
Where's your friend?
My friend?
You're right...where is he?
Last year, I was alone in Beijing,
I was almost frozen...
under a big clock.
I sang
"Happy Birthday" to myself.
"Happy Birthday" to myself...
It's snowing.
No, it's not. You're drunk.
It is really snowing.
Look.
Where's the switch?
Welcome home.
Take it easy.
I'll put your purse over here.
It's dangerous to drink like this.
A girl shouldn't drink like this.
You smell good.
Ouch.
I don't want to be alone.
Don't go back to your wife.
Stay here with me.
"Alcohol is bad. I paid $27 for the cab."
You're Lion King, You're just as professional...
as Yao Ming.
Stop playing, you'll wake the neighbors. Don't be late for work.
I want one.
OK...Lion King needs to break for lunch.
Come on.
Go home...It's lunchtime.
Come, let's eat.
I ate already.
You did? With whom?
Stay here.
I can't. There's a car in front.
If it doesn't move, I can't.
Miss, is this your car?
Move it, you're holding up traffic.
Where else am I supposed to park?
What are you looking at?
Put this in the car.
Remember me at the karaoke the other night?
I know you.
You bit me.
Alcohol is bad. I paid $27 for the cab.
You remember the fare, but what about me?
What's your name? I remember you.
Fang Zhendong.
Show some respect and move the car.
People are getting impatient.
All right, I respect you. Take this.
I'll buy you coffee some day.
Li Peiru.
Fang Zhendong.
A toast to Guiping's prosperous business.
Thanks, Zhong.
Good business.
Thanks.
What is it? You hurt yourself?
Nothing, just a bit numb.
Drink up, it's good for your circulation.
What's your hurry back to Tianjin? Your wife?
Do I look pussy whipped to you?
Both my in-laws are not in good health.
I need to be back sooner to look after them.
Anyway, I've already sold my flat...
in Beijing.
That's a good idea.
In a few more years, I'll sell mine too
and take Zhencong to an outlying village.
I have an old house in Mentougou,
remember we went there last year?
I think it's quite suitable for Zhencong.
Let me know if you need it.
Enough about your bro. What about yourself?
There's a better solution.
Get a wife. She'll take care of you both.
Grandma said I was a lifesaver.
It's my job to look after my kid brother.
Drink up.
The truth of the matter is...
you're not only...
your brother's savior.
Girls are waiting to be rescued by you.
Fang Zhendong. What a coincidence.
It's you?
You're alone?
Where's your wife?
I don't have one. That's why I'm alone.
A nice, independent man.
What did you buy?
Ingredients to make dumplings.
Dumplings?
What's your phone number?
13552881838
OK.
All these are for dumplings?
Yes.
I'm in a hurry. Let me borrow them.
No way.
I beg you. Please.
You know how to make them?
That's why I asked for your number.
Wait for my call. I'll buy you coffee next time.
Fang Zhendong.
Relax, I won't take advantage of you.
It's OK as long as you'll pay me back.
Fang Zhendong.
Hello, Miss Li.
How do you know it's me?
Only you call me Fang Zhendong.
What are you doing right now?
Making dumplings.
Perfect. Can you send them over?
Why should I?
Because you're a cop, you're here to serve.
You must save me.
Cops don't save anyone with dumplings.
You're not an ordinary cop.
I'm here all by my lonesome,
you must come over and save me.
You want me to save you?
Please? Fang Zhendong.
Alright...don't cry.
Hurry, Fang Zhendong. Come on in.
Look.
You're from Hong Kong? You're very capable.
I'm not very capable. I'm simply brilliant.
Right...brilliant.
You summoned me here to watch
how you brilliantly ravage the dumplings?
Show me...
how to make genuine local dumplings.
Your wrapping...
shouldn't be too thick.
You must not put too much stuffing.
You're amazing, Fang Zhendong.
You're a true lifesaver.
Smell that?
No. I made coffee for you.
Thanks. I thought you were talking about me.
Do you cook?
No.
You cook for your girlfriend?
No. You're making...
your boyfriend dumplings?
No, you are.
Me? Why don't you eat out?
I must do something special.
A girl from Hong Kong
makes Beijing dumplings for her boyfriend.
That's so romantic.
If I do it, it will be me romancing him.
No, do you understand?
All Hong Kong cooking shows are like this:
"I made this because we're pressed for time."
Everyone wants ready-made, not the process.
That's because he's married.
You told me when you were drunk.
I was drunk?
I'm a cop, I have a still trap.
Thank you.
He's early.
Put this on.
Andrew.
Thanks. Is the john fixed?
Yes.
Thank you.
It's all right.
I made you dumplings.
I can do better than that.
I remember the 1 994...
World Cup final.
BraZil Vs...
Italy.
In the U.S.A.
Brazil Vs Italy.
I remember my ex just left me,
and you made me watch the World Cup with you.
Dong, get your facts straight.
She left because you watched the World Cup
or you watched it...
because she left you?
Fang Zhendong. Where are you?
Our worry is uncalled for.
All right.
Miss Li. Are you all right?
No lights?
You blew a fuse? No air-con?
- No power. - This is supposed to be a 5-star home.
You're drunk again?
There's nothing to drink but alcohol.
You can't do this.
Get the manager to fix it.
Miss Li,
you should call your boyfriend.
My boyfriend?
Yes.
He doesn't want me. He's with his wife.
Miss Li.
Lie down.
Cover up.
You have anything thicker?
Little lamb.
- Miss Li. - Why are you so nice to me?
Why did you come over when I called?
I'm not a little lamb, Miss Li.
Little lamb.
Miss Li.
You always come over
I'm not a little lamb, Miss Li.
when I call.
Miss Li, I'm Fang Zhendong.
Miss Li.
Let me see your heart.
Why even you don't want me?
I'm all alone.
Hold me.
I'm cold.
I'm tired.
Are you all right?
Did I invite you over?
Of course.
We're going to have a baby then.
We slept...
in the same bed.
Get up.
What is your make-up doing in the freezer?
For women,
this is more important than water.
Miss Li, I must go home.
I must make breakfast for my kid brother.
That's so sweet.
What do you mean by little lamb?
What little lamb?
You call me that when you're drunk.
That's gibberish.
Want me to make you breakfast?
Yes.
Your ginger tea.
Eat.
Breakfast is ready.
Your brother is an artist.
I'm sorry. I must go look for my brother.
What?
Zhencong.
You're not working today. Why are you here?
Is everything all right?
He's your kid brother?
- Have you eaten? - How cute.
Hello.
So cute.
Are you cold?
I'm fine.
I'll help you.
Good.
Zhencong, let's go home.
Let's go.
Yours?
So you're actually a handsome man.
Hot dumplings.
Come here.
Let's eat.
Try it.
Slowly...it's hot.
Put this on.
So many awards.
I work hard because I can't do anything else.
Serving the people.
You have a nice home.
You call this nice?
My ex...
took everything when she left,
including the wedding picture on the wall.
You have a 5-star home. I have no star.
Your ex?
When did you get married?
1 999,
not for very long. She left 9 years ago.
I hope you'll sleep well.
How long have you been seeing her?
Dating.
3 years, in 1 996.
Few men remember things like that.
We both like A-Mei then.
She was a hit.
My ex sang "Crushed by the One I Love."
She said I clapped the loudest.
Then I sang Chen Xing's "Don't be Lonely."
She said she was moved when I sang it to her.
Moved? I'll have to hear this.
It's your smell.
No way. I always put it out...
in the sun.
Here.
Nobody ever says it smells.
Right?
Get some sleep.
Good night.
Your call cannot be connected.
Hello.
How are you, nice to meet you.
Turn left at the next intersection,
turn right at the next light...
- and go straight. - Thanks.
- Don't mention it. - Thanks.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Chief, you haven't submitted your reports.
What reports?
The daily reports.
No way. I hand them in on time every day.
But they didn't receive it.
Who told you?
We come here at 4:30 every day.
I turn it in at 5:30. It cannot be.
But you haven't turned it in for 3 days.
Fang Zhendong.
Get in, Zhencong.
Aren't you tired of wearing that?
I'm only tired of not wearing them.
Can you do me a favor?
Like what?
Follow my boyfriend.
No.
He put all my money on a flat.
I can't afford a private investigator.
I can't abuse my power, understand?
You're supposed to serve the people.
I can't mix business with pleasure.
Please?
Forget it.
What do you want to know?
I want to know if there's another woman.
His wife is a woman.
She's his past.
Other women will be his future.
Even if I'll find out he has another woman,
I can only tell you "No," understand?
It's all right, I'm fine.
You're bleeding.
It's all right.
Wait a minute.
- It's all right. - I'm sorry.
Let's go.
Dong.
Xiaowan.
Having a good time?
Zhencong.
I made soup.
Xiaowan.
Spare me that guy's things. I'm no trash can.
You're so petty.
I better go then.
It's all right.
Chief, did you hand it in?
Mind your business. I'm serious.
Fang Zhendong.
What is it?
One piece of luggage.
Ruby.
What are you doing, Peiru? Are you craZy?
Peiru.
Watch it.
Forget it, Andrew.
I want my money back.
What money?
My commission from selling each flat.
I already gave you $20K...
for your credit cards.
My commission is over $1 00K.
Says who?
Ruby did most of the work.
You're from Hong Kong. You can't be serious?
Get up.
How can you say that?
I'm fine. I can still manage...
without men or money.
What?
Why did you move back?
The creep took my 5-star home.
I was at your office.
I was fired.
Why?
It happens. Layoffs after the new year.
When the stock market falls, people split up.
I consulted a fortune teller.
He told me to put these here for good luck.
Get me the salt.
Inside this cupboard?
Yes.
Pour it in.
All of it.
Put this on the east west side.
I'll have luck and health.
Why are you here?
I made dumplings.
Nuke them...
if you're hungry.
I have to go.
Throw these out for me.
You don't want this?
Earth to earth, dust to dust.
It's all right. You can call me.
Tear this down, my work station over here.
The pantry over here.
Coffee, red wine, mixer...
Over here,
Heaven and Earth Real Estate Co.
How much is the rent?
Around $280K in total.
That's almost $300K.
Just $280K.
I already got a discount.
$300K is a lot.
You should re-consider.
- What do you mean? - Nothing.
- You don't think I can do this? - I don't mean that.
I came to Beijing by myself.
I won't be here
if I'm scared.
I'll get a loan from the bank.
Miss Li.
If you had...
told me about Andrew earlier,
I could have made Ruby leave him.
None of this would have happened.
Miss Li.
I don't blame you, OK?
I know what I have to do.
"Final notice."
I'm glad you're here.
I don't know how to deal with Xiaowan's Mom.
Dong.
Zhencong, the green onions...
Here they are.
Here.
Go.
I'm here because of this, Mr Fang.
"Mom, Zhencong wants me to marry him."
We're poor and my daughter is a mute,
but...
I won't marry her off casually.
I must make sure she's happy.
I know,
my brother has communication issues.
He can't even take care of himself,
Iet alone take care of someone else.
He has no business getting married.
But please believe me.
As his brother, I'll look after them both.
Please re-consider.
- You're mistaken, Mr Fang. - No.
I know...
you don't want Xiaowan to suffer.
No.
Look.
I trust he will be good to her. Look.
Look at the details...she looks so pretty.
Xiaowan knows...
Zhencong will make her happy.
She says she's not mute...
in Zhencong's world.
She's unique.
Chicken.
- Xiaowan, Zhencong usually... - Dong.
- Auntie. - Dong.
I made sweet & sour spareribs...
for the guests.
- I brought them over. - That's enough.
Help yourselves.
Thank you.
- So happy. - Cheers.
Cheers.
No bottoms up.
The food is getting cold.
- Let me get you a helping. - A toast to Xiaowan's Mom.
Must be tough for you.
Thank you.
So happy.
No bottoms up.
Half...
Cheers.
Miss Li, are you all right?
So happy.
Are you all right?
So much happiness in this world.
Mother's love, brotherly love.
Enough love to get married. I've seen them all.
I thought they had gone extinct.
Did you see Xiaowan's Mom?
When you said you'd take care of Zhencong,
did you see how happy she looked?
Yes.
You know then how much she loves Xiaowan.
You cried.
I did not.
Yes, you did.
Yes, you did. Tears rolled down your face.
It's obvious you cried.
OK, I cried...
It's all right. Take it easy.
Everyone was crying
and everyone was happy.
Miss Li.
Everyone but me.
My Mom is a bitch when she wants money.
What am I to her?
An ATM machine.
You look after your kid brother,
but everyone in my family is selfish.
You had too much to drink.
Miss Li.
Next time don't drink so much.
I did not.
Men always make me
drink a lot.
I used to be a hairstylist.
Right.
Hairstylists are cool.
But with no money? Cool my ass.
Right.
I'm not...
I'm not hungry for money.
I just don't want to be like my parents.
They bought a flat...
before they retired.
Now the family is stuck with the mortgage.
I have to give them $5,000 a month,
and I still have 9 more years to go.
9 years later,
I'll be 40 years old.
Right. Miss Li.
You will be fine...
just too much alcohol.
I want a man who won't make me pay mortgage.
I don't mind if he's married.
But he only wants my money,
not me.
It's all right. I'll go to Taiwan alone...
to Shanghai, to Beijing,
I don't care.
Stop it,
Miss Li.
- I'm tired. - Don't say it
Don't say it anymore, Miss Li.
Whenever you need me, I'll be there.
Miss Li.
Nobody would hire me for the last 6 months.
Even a mute is wanted but not me.
Miss Li.
Sorry,
but we don't approve of your business.
We have reviewed your file.
If you were in Hong Kong,
we would have approved your application,
but not here.
It's high risk for us as you're new at this.
Here's the kids' room. Get a feel for it.
- Not bad. - Think about it.
We have to go, Mr Fang. You'll hear from me.
Well?
If you want it, you must hurry.
I can't guarantee I can hold it.
I like it.
The price...
Negotiable. Let's talk back in the office.
- I'm sure you'll be happy. - All right.
You don't have to sell it.
Zhencong needs the money to get married.
You should think it over.
Maybe she'll find a job.
Then she won't need to borrow from you.
Zhencong will get his share.
I'm only loaning her my share.
"Alcohol is bad for you...best of luck to you."
Renovation starts on the 1st.
The carpenters arrive on the 2nd,
electricians on the 5th,
bricklayers from the 6th to the 1 0th.
They must clear out on the 1 1th,
because the furniture is here on the 12th.
Cleaning from the...
14th to the 16th,
worship ceremony on the 17th,
and we're open for business on the 18th.
Have some coffee.
Thanks.
You don't want any?
What's wrong?
She wants to borrow $20K more?
That's $300K altogether.
The price she paid for getting dumped.
You're not responsible for her.
It's not about responsibility.
I'm in love with her.
It's true.
I like to hear her
call me Fang Zhendong.
Fang Zhendong.
What are you doing?
What is going on?
You said nothing during the renovation.
Now you're starting trouble.
I don't know what happened before.
But this ceiling is...
against regulations.
Miss Li,
your wiring is illegal.
I can't be held responsible for accidents.
How would I know there's a problem?
I need to open for business tomorrow.
What do you expect me to do?
What is it?
Fang Zhendong. They're tearing down the shop.
Talk to them.
What's the problem?
The sprinkler and the wiring.
Can we put in an extra pipe over here?
No, you must tear it down.
Don't talk to them. Talk to their boss.
I had a contract.
I must open for business.
Let me talk to your boss.
Your wiring is against regulations.
Fang Zhendong, you're a cop.
Tell them to get the hell out.
This is not Hong Kong. You must obey the law.
Is there another solution?
Can we put in something? Take a look.
Her power supply is very problematic.
Uncle Dong.
Zhencong. Xiaowan.
Dong.
Wear this even if you're not wearing suits.
I know you're busy, so I bought them for you.
I'll make dinner.
Zhencong, is Dong all right?
He's all right.
Zhencong, the oil and vinegar...
Dong.
It's all right.
You...
I'll make dinner...
the oil...
The scanner shows blood stasis in your brain,
and you have sustained an injury.
Were you in an accident?
A few years ago when I caught a criminal.
The stasis is pressing against your nerves
and is affecting your memory.
Doctor, does he need surgery?
No, that's too risky. We'll try something more conventional.
What will happen?
Hard to say. Maybe nothing.
Or maybe you'll forget everything.
Xiaole, you're a real jerk.
What?
I said you're a jerk. Got it?
You betrayed your mentor.
I did nothing wrong. I told the truth.
He also told me, I must report every mistake.
He did use the patrol car to help his girl.
Shut up.
This is the precinct, not the cadet school.
You're not the prefect. Don't be a snitch.
You'll soon be the team leader too, you'll...
Stop it.
This is ridiculous.
Chief.
Xiaole.
You did the right thing. You learned from me.
I...
Shut up.
Dong, let's talk to the boss.
Everyone makes mistakes.
You can't say that, Zhu Tian.
You shouldn't try to cover it up.
One must own up to one's mistakes.
I've been a cop for over 1 0 years.
As an honest cop,
even when I'm not in uniform,
I'm still a cop, right?
"Only a bass guitar is left"
"listening to my heart."
"I miss you"
"in this empty room."
"My dreams have left me."
"I'm lost when I wake up."
"I keep searching"
"in this gloomy world."
Salute.
"I'm like a pathetic joke"
"holding onto thin air."
"Perhaps I should have given up,"
"given up meaningless courage."
"I should not hope for anything."
"I should not believe in miracles,"
"but go on living without any expectations."
"Nothing can be resolved."
"Why talk about the future? "
"I can't let go"
"my love for you."
"The silent guitar"
"is answering me quietly."
"I talk to myself"
"when it's raining in my heart."
The number you have dialed has been disconnected.
"I'm like a pathetic joke"
"holding onto thin air."
"Perhaps I should have given up,"
"given up meaningless courage."
"I should not hope for anything."
"I should not believe in miracles,"
"but go on living without any expectations."
"Nothing can be resolved."
"Why talk about the future? "
"I can't let go"
"my love for you."
"The silent guitar"
"is answering me quietly."
"I talk to myself"
"when it's raining in my heart."
Those of you tuning in,
are you aware of
someone around...
who gives you positive energy?
He may not be much of a talker,
nor is he very capable.
Swing hard. You understand?
Who is she?
My sister. Don't mind her.
Swing hard.
Dee is getting married.
You know his girlfriend lives here.
I'm not going to mind your business.
I have to pick up my daughter from school.
But tonight, I'll make an exception.
I'm willing to give John 20 seconds
to say something important.
Move in with me, my jewelry will be yours.
Fried rice noodles with soy sauce.
- Plain? - Yes.
- $1 more for take out. - OK.
Thanks, Mom.
That's right.
No need.
Something moving needs not be earth shaking.
Something simple can be just as sweet.
Nancy said she hadn't received a hand-written letter
in over 1 0 years.
Today, she got one in the mail.
As she read it word by word,
she felt as if her friend was talking to her in person.
Because she remembered every word by heart.
"Don't be Lonely Fang Zhendong"
What is it, Sis?
Give me $1 00K. I'll move out tomorrow.
Forget the previous payments but I won't chip in anymore.
I'll transfer it to you tomorrow.
Is Zhendong home?
He moved.
Don't wait here anymore.
Let me repeat:
I don't know where he is.
What is it, Miss Li?
I'm looking for Fang Zhendong.
He's gone.
Where to?
I don't know.
You should.
You worked with him for so long.
That's just your assumption.
I'm his friend.
Then you should know where he is.
Miss Li, what you want from me
is beyond my call of duty, understand?
Why won't you help me?
I'm here to make a report.
About what?
Fang Zhendong is missing. Find him.
How are you related?
I'm his girlfriend.
Occupation?
You want 3 bedrooms?
Facing the sun, right?
There's a studio flat in...
Chaoyang District.
Is Miss Li Peiru here?
Please wait.
Hello, I'm Li Peiru.
You're looking for Fang Zhendong?
Yes, I am.
When he moved, he left your things with me.
He said you'd come back for them.
Zhendong has cerebrovascular dementia.
He won't be able to look after himself,
Iet alone look after you.
He'll be increasingly dependent on others.
He's no longer the Zhendong you know.
If you leave him after you see him,
you shouldn't see him at all.
Will you tell him you love him?
I must let you off here, Miss.
- Straight ahead? - Yes, just go straight.
Thank you.
Where does Fang Zhendong live?
Go straight and make a turn.
Thank you.
Xiaowan.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Is it hard looking after them both?
"They're both trying very hard. We're OK."
What about you? Are you scared?
"Being with the one I love, I'm not scared."
No need.
Want some cabbage?
Fang Zhendong.
What are you going to cook?
Why did you come back?
I said I wouldn't take advantage from you.
Go home.
I'm hungry. Can you serve me lunch first?
Go home after you finish eating.
Have some tea. Careful, it's hot.
Tell me about your condition.
I thought you wanted me to leave.
Maybe you can scare me off.
It's nothing. I'm becoming forgetful.
The doctor said it's a type of dementia.
Will you forget I owe you $300K?
Forget how much I hurt you?
Forget you promised you'd look after me?
Did I?
I know I should leave, given your condition.
I tried, but I couldn't.
I missed you all the time.
What should I do?
You're going to forget me anyway.
Now is all we have, right?
Why am I inside your glove?
Because you're cold.
I'm cold? Thanks for taking care of me.
You came back when I can't take care of you.
You have suffered enough.
You don't need a burden like me.
Eventually I'll have nothing.
Do you know even if I die tomorrow,
I'll have no regrets today because I see you.
The first time I saw you,
I already had no regrets after you kissed me.
I did?
It's probably her.
- Yes. - Maybe it was her?
I don't think I did.
Ouch.
Congratulations. I didn't expect a girl from Hong Kong
to be so loyal.
A real loyal girl.
Morning.
What are you doing?
I'm eating. What about you?
I want dumplings tonight.
Let's go.
You already fed the fish.
"Twice a day (morning and night)."
Starting today,
I'll remember how nice Zhendong is to me.
He won't forget.
I'll write it down for him.
Stop.
Wait, there are 1 3 of you.
there are 1 3 of you.
No, just 12.
I counted. I'm sure it's 1 3.
Can you count?
Quiet. We made a mistake.
Please go in.
Is Dong picking you up?
You need to lock up?
You have to go?
I'll wait outside.
All right, goodbye. Take it easy.
Next stop : North Jinsong Bridge.
Please use the back door, swipe your card when you alight.
I need to get off.
I need to get off. Open the door.
Open up.
There you are.
You've been waiting for me?
I knew you'd be here.
Your hands are cold.
I have a personal heater.
I don't need you here.
You sent me an angel.
You're going to be a father.
You don't like that?
No, I...
I didn't know you're willing to bear my baby.
Why not?
You know what I mean.
I don't.
I'm wearing you out.
I don't know what you mean.
I don't know what to say.
You know I'm not good with words.
Then I'll say it for you.
Thank you.
Thank you for letting me in your life.
What did you say?
I'm hungry.
Let's eat...go get them.
The food is ready.
Zhencong, bring the rice.
Hurry up, Zhencong.
Just 20 more minutes.
Sit down.
Get in there. Move.
For the little one, Mom feels empty inside.
When Dad is not happy,
Mom feels even worse.
You're inside me.
You feel my heart pounding
every time I see your Dad?
I never wanted to be a mother,
but Dad makes me...
proud to be a mother.
What is it?
I lost $400.
You don't have to work?
I...
Why are you following me? Go home.
Go away.
Be careful.
Dong.
I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
Go away.
Dong.
He's worried. He wants to protect you.
Him?
He's worried about the money you're carrying.
How does he know? You told him?
You take care of us three.
Are we after your money?
He can't protect me.
Hold me... I'm scared.
You pushed me away.
You must remember me. Don't abandon me.
What if I give you...
a hard time every day?
Xiaowan said being with the one you love,
there's nothing to be afraid of.
Her heart is strong.
Just like her Dad.
Come on in. Drop by anytime.
Why did you bring all these?
My wife's friend owns a shop.
Everything is at cost.
Where's Peiru?
Inside...she's cooking.
Hello.
- We're here to bum a meal. - You bought so much.
You're too kind.
Don't mention it.
Here...
- Sit down. - Sit down.
Auntie. Xiaowan. Zhencong.
Come.
Auntie, let me help you.
No...you're here to eat.
Then I'll wait.
You're so happy.
We got married before you did,
and we still don't have children.
Just live with it.
White wine or beer?
Anything.
I'll get it.
Thanks.
Auntie, you're such a good cook.
Then you should eat more.
- Definitely. - Zhu Tian.
Let's drink this.
Come. No problem.
Have you decided on a name?
Yes.
What is it?
One word.
One word?
It's...
Stop guessing.
Ming. As in to engrave on one's mind.
Right.
- Fang Ming. - Fang Ming.
Good name.
- Sounds good. - Not bad?
Pour the wine.
You'll have an amazing baby.
Sit down.
Thanks.
Here we go...
You should sit down, Auntie.
Sit down and eat.
I was transferred in 1 994.
I was in my 20s then, about your age,
but more capable than you.
You don't believe me?
Ask Guiping. Shen Guiping,
you don't know him?
He knows, where is Guiping?
Tell him to come over.
Guiping and I were on beat every day,
3 hours a day, and finished by 16:30.
We made a big circle from north of Sanlitun.
I wrote and handed in the reports at 17:00.
Guiping has gone to Tianjin.
Cut the crap.
You're new?
What do you know?
You're picking on me. You look down on me?
Why are you always picking on me?
Listen, I'd risk my life when I work.
I risk my life...
When I arrested that fugitive in 1995,
I ran 3 blocks after that bastard.
In order to get away,
that bastard pushed a kid out on the street.
He was almost run over by a car.
I was wounded when I saved the kid's life.
I spent 3 days in the hospital.
When I got home, my brother...
didn't speak to me for 3 months.
He was scared.
He'd have nothing...
if I were dead.
You know what? I can't die.
And you?
You guys look down on me.
You all look down on me.
I know, it's just a job.
Because my marriage failed? I didn't care.
My ex ran off with another man. I didn't care.
I slaved on my job...
for over 1 0 years.
I was never promoted. I didn't care either.
Know why I'm still alive?
My wife is having a baby,
my baby.
I can't give her a better life,
I...Iisten...
In order to let my baby...
grow up healthily,
I must come back to work. I need to work.
I want to come back and be a good cop,
OK?
Calm down, Dong.
Fang Zhendong.
Are you all right?
I'm fine. Zhu Tian brought me along.
He said you need a physical before you come back to work.
A physical?
Yes, Zhu Tian went for a physical.
That's the regulation.
Right, let's go.
The police is responsible for the public.
You must stay healthy, right?
Your wife is absolutely right.
Are you scared to go?
No...I don't know.
You don't know? Let's go now,
you can come back to work tomorrow.
Good.
I'll go with you.
Let me carry that.
Slow down. Why did you run?
- I'm sorry. - Dong.
Slow down.
You're up early.
I'm disturbing you?
I was chatting with my father.
Your father?
He makes musical instruments. He's reticent.
I talk to him through music.
We were just chatting.
What did you talk about?
I sang him a song.
Now I remember the lyrics I used to forget.
I'll sing it to you.
Fang Zhendong.
He's coming.
Fang Ming is on his way.
The baby's head didn't turn.
Should we save the mother
or the baby?
The mother. Save my wife, thanks.
Don't cry.
Fang Ming.
3 spoonfuls.
Wipe it, slowly.
Are you hungry, baby?
Let's check if we need to change the diaper.
The baby is hungry.
Wait. How much did you put in?
3 spoonfuls.
You think I screwed up?
Do it yourself.
Zhencong.
What are you doing?
Stop. Police.
Stop.
Dong.
What happened? Where's your brother?
We have a tough road ahead.
I can't go on without you.
Without you, I can't smile.
The baby needs to know how amazing you are.
I still have a burden even without you.
I can't go on without you.
Remember
you promised me
you'd come to me whenever I called your name?
Fang Zhendong.
You said you're a lifesaver.
Here's a damsel in distress.
Wake up.
Thanks.
You haven't rested for 3 nights.
Are you OK?
You're running a fever. Let's go see the doc.
I'm all right.
I'll be right back.
Mr Fang, your wife is sick. I'm taking her to see the doctor.
Let's go.
I'll be back.
Slowly...
Mrs Fang.
Doctor.
What's your name? I remember you.
Fang Zhendong.
Relax. I won't take advantage of you.
You can pay me back later.
It's all right, Miss Li.
Whenever you need me, I'll be there.
Fang Zhendong.
What are you going to cook?
I'm hungry. Can you serve me lunch first?
You've been waiting for me?
I knew you'd be here.
You sent me an angel.
Fang Zhendong.
I'm sorry to make you worry.
You tied me over.
Don't cry.
The baby's name is Fang Ming. As in engraving on one's mind.
Tell her this name is for Mom.
So Dad would remember Mom.