Now after the last video, I really didn't like how the painting was going so I wanted to tweak around the colors a little bit.
I've got it to this far, but if I apply the final look to this painting right now, we can see that the characters are very dark.
And they're a little bit too dark actually.
So I'm going to press work mode again and adjust my colors.
To adjust my colors, I'm going to press control U, which will bring up hue and saturation.
And from here, I'm going to make the cowboys lighter.
I'm going to make sure that I'm going to make these cowboys lighter than the background as well.
This way they'll feel like they're in the spotlight.
And then when I'm done, when I'm done all four cowboys, I'm going to go up to my actions and make sure that I have my folder selected.
And I'm going to press the finished look button and press play.
And now this is looking much better, so I continue on with this.
And let's go back into our work mode and start colorizing the rest of the elements.
So I'm going to start off with this tall guy again.
And the first thing I want to do is I want to find which layer he's on over here.
So he's on layer number 8.
So having layer number 8 selected, I'm going to control click on layer 8.
And then I'm going to go down to the new layer button, click on that to create a new layer just above layer 8 and just underneath layer 7.
So that I don't end up painting on top of the cowboy on layer 7.
Now a couple of things that go through my head as I'm painting all the different elements for this cowboy is what will it look like as a finished look?
I want to take into consideration the fact that the colors will change.
The colors will get richer, they'll get more saturated.
So therefore the colors that I choose will be a lot less saturated just to compensate for what I feel is going to happen once I press the finished look button.
This is something that you can actually develop a sense for.
Just over time and practice, you'll develop a sense for what the color will end up looking like after you do all the treatment onto it.
Now as you can see with this technique, it is combinable with the first lesson.
And you're going to find the same similarities in all the classes. They're all combinable, all these different techniques.
So by the end of it, you would have learned so many different techniques that are all combinable to any kind of style.
And you're going to find that your possibilities of making digital painting will be endless.
The main thing is you want to be able to really understand every lesson.
And that can be best done through practice and just playing these videos over and over and following them step by step.
That's the best way to get as much from these videos as possible.
Now remember, if your selection is really bothering you and you don't want to see that, then all you need to do is press Ctrl H to hide it.
The thing about this is a lot of people will tend to forget that they've hidden a selection.
So when it's about time to start painting outside of this selection, they think that their pen doesn't work or something, and they don't know what to do.
If this ever happens to you when you start painting on a layer and you know that it's visible and the opacity has been turned up on this layer,
if nothing is showing up, the best thing to do is to press Ctrl D, and that will deselect everything.
Then try to see if you can paint.
Most often than not, that will solve your problem.
At one point or another, you might be thinking to yourself, now why do I need to set this folder to this certain setting,
and why do I need to duplicate it and set the top layer to overlay, the bottom layer to color?
What is the deal with all this stuff?
If I just paint with a lot more color, then I won't have to compensate for the color changing more saturated when you apply all the finished treatment to it.
Well, that's because the final look that we see after we click the Finish Look mode is a combination of things.
It's only because there's a certain specific combination of certain settings that will give us this final look.
You would not be able to achieve this look with just having, say, a color mode or an overlay mode.
It's only because of these two things combined that we can achieve this final look.
Now why is it that we have to always revert back to a work mode?
Why can't we just continue to paint having the folder set to color or overlay?
Why do we need to set it to normal and then knock down opacity to 80%?
Well, that's because when the folder is set to, say, color mode, it's hard to see exactly where you're painting things.
It's hard to see exactly where you're painting them to.
If you have the folder set to normal with 80% opacity, then not only do you get a clear idea of exactly where you're painting,
but you also get a very clear idea of the drawing underneath and where that is.
Now if you're not liking the colors that are coming out at this point,
here's a little checklist that you can do to try and correct this problem and help you pick out some better colors.
The number one thing that I'll think about first is, is it too saturated or is it not saturated enough?
The next thing that I'll think about is, I'll ask myself, is this the right darkness?
Does it need to be brighter? Does it need to be darker?
And the last thing that I'll ask myself is, is this the right hue?
And adjust accordingly in your hue and saturation window.
Something else that might help is if you open up a secondary window.
You could do this by going up to Window, Arrange, New Window.
And this has opened up a duplicate window of this document.
We can shrink this one down so that we can always keep an eye on what we're doing to the painting as a whole in the smaller window,
as well as paint up close in the larger window so that we make sure that we're painting nice and accurately.
It's the same way that we set up in our first lesson, visualizing through darkness.
So for your assignment, I want you to follow this video as accurately as possible through all the different steps.
You might not have to pick the same colors. You could feel free to go and explore all sorts of different color schemes.
But the procedure in how you apply these colors, this is what I want you to really pay attention to and do them exactly how it's done in the video.