Okay, so now that we've gone through all of the technical stuff, now it's time to apply it to some real situations.
Okay, so can you please open up the file called bigfoot.jpg?
Now here's the situation. You've drawn your initial sketch for your painting, and you've scanned it in.
You can see that there's little eraser bits here, there's a little bit of texture over here, and there's a lot of red that we don't want either.
The red was what I used for my initial rough.
Okay, I choose red because, and a lot of people they'll use blue, but I just tend to use red because I find that it's much easier, much cleaner to get out of in Photoshop.
Blue, a lot of times it'll turn out that the computer will pick it up as black.
So with red it's much easier to get out of Photoshop.
So what you need to do is open up your channels window. If you can't see it, just go up to window, channels, and from here we're going to click off all these little eyeballs, all the visibility except for the red channel.
And what that's going to do is it's going to get rid of all the red.
Okay, and once you've gotten rid of all the red, what I want you to do is delete these unwanted channels.
Just leave the one channel with the visibility in there.
Okay, and from here we're going to change the image mode, so we're going to go up to image mode and change it to grayscale.
And now from grayscale we're going to change it to RGB.
Now why did we need to do all that?
Well, if we just go back into history a little bit, if I want to change the mode of this image to RGB, I go up here and you can't even select it.
What you need to do is change it to grayscale first and then it will give you the option to change it to RGB.
Okay, so now we've gotten rid of all the red.
Now it's time to just clean up some of these little bits in here.
So what I'm doing is I'm using a solid brush, just a normal default brush, 100% opacity and 20% flow, but we can make the flow even higher just to make sure that a good amount of white paint is coming out.
And with this white we're going to just zoom right into the picture and paint over all the little specks on our image, all the little unwanted specks.
So I've just zoomed right in so I can see everything in detail.
I'm zoomed in at 100% opacity.
Okay, so the top corner over here, all that paper texture, I'm just going to enlarge my brush and just paint right on top of it to erase that as well.
Now this will happen to you quite often as well where your initial sketch is still pretty light even though you might have used a black pencil.
So for this all we need to do is go up to Image, Adjustments, Auto Contrast.
Auto Contrast, this will make all the values in your image have extra contrast in there.
Now if this is too dark for you, which I feel it is for me, what I'm going to do is I'm just going to undo that and copy the background layer.
And we're going to do auto contrast to this copy.
Okay, so we can either go up to Image, Adjustments, Auto Contrast, or we can press Alt Shift Control L.
So on a Mac that would be Alt Shift Command L.
And from here we can just turn down the opacity until we have something that we like.
Okay, once we have something that we like we can merge these two together by pressing Control E.
And now we have prepared our line drawing ready for painting.