关注左岸电影微信公众号：film-zone
"Boundaries of...
"propriety...
"vigorously assaulted...
"... propriety were... "
"The boundaries of propriety were vigorously assaulted.
"The boundaries of propriety were vigorously assaulted as was only right
"but not quite breached as was also right.
"Nevertheless
"she was not pleased."
- What is it? - Jane.
Oh.
Jane!
Oh dear me.
That girl needs a husband.
And who's good enough? Nobody.
I blame you for that.
Being too much the model of perfection.
I've shared your bed for 32 years
and perfection is something I have not encountered.
Yet.
No. Stop it. Mr Austen it's Sunday! Stop no it's...
The utmost of a woman's character is expressed in the duties of daughter
sister and eventually wife and mother.
It is secured by soft attraction virtuous
love and quiet in the early morning.
If a woman happens to have a particular superiority
for example a profound mind it is best kept a profound secret.
Humour is liked more but wit? No.
It is the most treacherous talent of them all.
Now George old fellow you know you have to stay.
- Jenny! - George George.
Hurry along Jane! We'll be late!
When Her Ladyship calls we must obey.
Come along Jane.
Lady Gresham may I introduce my niece Comtesse De Feuillide
and Mr Fowle Cassandra's fiance.
- Comtesse? Then you presume to be French? - By marriage.
Monsieur le Comte is not here to pay his respects?
A prior engagement ma'am
Monsieur le Comte was obliged to pay his respects to Madame le Guillotine.
Oh!
I see your nephew is with us again.
Mr Wisley.
Wisley is indispensable to my happiness.
Well do sit down.
Mr Fowle and Cassandra are only recently engaged.
When shall you marry?
- Not for some time Your Ladyship. - Why not?
I'm also engaged to go to the West Indies
with Lord Craven's expedition against the French as chaplain.
- What has Craven offered you? - I've hopes of a parish on my return.
How much is it worth?
Enough to marry on in a modest way.
Mr Wisley did you know the Basingstoke assemblies resume?
Very soon I believe.
- Jane does enjoy a ball. - Wisley can't abide them.
But sir
a ball is an indispensable blessing to the juvenile part of the neighbourhood.
Everything agreeable in the way of talking and sitting down together
all managed with the utmost decorum.
An amiable man could not object.
Then I find I'm converted.
Displayed like a brood mare.
- Mr Wisley is a highly eligible young gentleman. - Oh Mother!
- You know our situation Jane. - Oh!
And he is Lady Gresham's favourite nephew and heir.
One day he shall inherit this.
Excellent prospects!
- His small fortune will not buy me. - What will buy you cousin?
More wary in the world Mr Lefroy.
You can pay me for that later.
- Huzzah! Huzzah! - Come on Mr Lefroy.
Come on man hit him!
Lefroy!
- Glass of wine with you sir? - Madam.
- Displaying to advantage I see Lefroy. - Like the sword Austen.
How long before you have to get back to the sticks?
A day.
So soon?
Doghouse debts but one must cut some sort of a figure even in the militia.
Especially when condemned to a parsonage my friend.
Yes.
Still who is this sour - faced little virgin?
Your pardon ma'am.
Mr Tom Lefroy may I present Mr John Warren?
Joining me in Hampshire my father is preparing us both for holy orders.
I understand you've visited Hampshire Mr Lefroy.
Last year.
- Long visit was it? - Very long Mr Warren. Almost three hours.
Mr Austen you're devilishly handsome. A kiss a kiss.
Oops!
So Tom where should we go? Vauxhall Gardens?
Been there.
Lefroy there's a Tahitian Love Fest on at White's.
Seen it.
- Crockford's? - Crockford's? Done that.
Or did it do me?
Wh - wh - wh - what is a Tahitian Love Fest?
Warren!
I humbly beg your pardon sir.
Theft of one pig is a crime heinous to be sure but two pigs...
Two pigs is a violent assault on the very
sanctity of private property itself.
Excuse me.
You and your kind are a canker on the body social.
And cankers are cut out.
Transportation for life. Next.
- Why are you here in London sir? - To learn the law.
- Which has no other end but what? - The preservation of the rights of property.
- Against? - The mob.
Therefore order is kept because we have...
- A standing army? - Good manners sir and prudence.
- Do you know that word? Prudence? - Yes.
Consider myself.
I was born rich certainly but I remain rich by virtue of exceptional conduct.
I have shown restraint.
Your mother my sister became poor because she did not...
She married my father because she loved him.
Yes and that's why you have so many brothers and sisters back there in...
- Limerick. - Mmm.
If you hope I say hope...
If you aspire to inherit my property
you must prove yourself more worthy.
But what do we find? We find dissipation
wild enough to glut the imaginings of a Hottentot braggadocio.
Wild companions gambling
running around St James's like a neck - or - nothing young blood of the fancy.
- What kind of lawyer will that make? - Typical.
Humour?
Well you're going to need that because I'm teaching you a lesson.
I'm sending you to stay with your other relations the Lefroys.
- Uncle they live in the country. - Deep in the country.
- Jane? - Mmm?
Can you?
Thank you.
I think you two quite the prettiest sisters in England.
Mr Fowle will be enchanted.
San Domingo is half a world away.
He'll forget me.
Impossible. Look at the memory you're giving him tonight.
Cassie.
His heart will stop at the very sight of you or he doesn't deserve to live.
And yes I'm aware of the contradiction embodied in that sentence.
Is it?
- Jane! - Henry!
You look wonderful.
Well hello John. It's very good to see you.
- Nice to see you. - Oh John!
George!
Leave your brother alone.
Jane! Jane? Have you heard? My father's nephew is staying with us.
From London.
- He is a... - A brilliant young lawyer.
- Lucy please. - With a reputation.
For lateness?
Hat off George. Hat off Father's ready.
- Thank you John. - Please.
The family is always moving in great ways and small.
Firstly the small. Henry is back from Oxford with his degree
- thank goodness. - Well done.
And our friend John my new student. Then the great.
Cassandra who is forsaking us for her brother Edward and his family at the coast
whilst Robert voyages to the West Indies with Lord Craven's expedition.
And then together they can embark on that most great
and most serious journey of life.
Miss Austen I understand you will be favouring us with a reading?
- Do Jane. - Do.
- Oh please Miss Jane. - Oh yes Jane do.
Please Jane.
"Advice from a young lady on the engagement of her beloved sister Cassandra
"to a Fowle."
"His addresses were offered in a manner violent enough to be flattering.
"The boundaries of propriety were vigorously assaulted as was only right
"but not quite breached as was also right.
"Nevertheless she was... "
And may I introduce my young nephew Mr Thomas Lefroy?
Oh.
And he's more than welcome. Join us sir join us.
Green velvet coat. Vastly fashionable.
You'll find this vastly amusing.
"His addresses were...
"The boundaries of propriety were vigorously assaulted
"as was only right but not quite breached as was also right.
"Nevertheless she was not pleased.
"Her taste was refined her sentiments noble her person lovely her figure elegant."
Good God there's writing on both sides of those pages.
Shh. Damn it man.
"'It was only yesterday I repelled Lord Graham and his six million
"'which would have lasted me almost a twelvemonth
"'with economies... '
"'greater than all the jewels in India an adoring heart."'
God!
"'And pray madam what am I to expect in return? '
"'Expect? Well you may expect to have me pleased from time to time."'
Is this who I am?
"And a sweet gentle pleading innocent
"delicate sympathetic loyal"
"untutored adoring female heart."
The end.
- Bravo Jane. - Well done Jane.
Bravo.
Well done.
She speaks so well.
Well excessively charming I thought.
Well accomplished enough perhaps
but a metropolitan mind may be less susceptible to extended juvenile self - regard.
Well thank you. We're both very proud.
# In airy dreams #
# absent love to see #
# Dear you oh to think #
# On thee #
Careful there old fellow.
Fine piece Mr Lefroy.
Handled a gun before have you Tom?
- Mmm. - Tom!
Jesus!
- Tom. - Uncle?
Why not try a walk?
There's some very fine country round about. Very fine.
A walk.
Miss!
Miss! Miss!
Miss! Miss I...
Miss?
- Miss... - Austen.
Mr Lefroy.
Yes I know but I am alone.
- Except for me. - Exactly.
Oh come!
What rules of conduct apply in this rural situation?
We have been introduced have we not?
What value is there in an introduction when you cannot even remember my name?
Indeed can barely stay awake in my presence.
Madam.
These scruples must seem very provincial to a gentleman with such elevated airs
but I do not devise these rules. I am merely obliged to obey them.
I have been told there is much to see upon a walk
but all I've detected so far is a general tendency to green above and brown below.
Yes well others have detected more. It is celebrated.
- There's even a book about Selborne Wood. - Oh.
A novel perhaps?
Novels?
Being poor insipid things read by mere women even God forbid written by mere women?
I see we're talking of your reading.
As if the writing of women did not display the greatest powers of mind
knowledge of human nature the liveliest effusions of wit and humour
and the best - chosen language imaginable?
- Was I deficient in rapture? - In consciousness.
It was...
It was accomplished.
It was ironic.
- And you're sure I've not offended you? - Not at all.
My lords ladies and gentlemen the Grand Vizier's Flight.
- May I have the honour? - How kind cousin.
- Miss Austen. - Mr Wisley.
May I have the pleasure of this next dance?
- Oh no we're so late. - Take care.
Oh thank you Tom.
- Hurry. - Lucy.
Oh!
I am mortified.
I practised but it won't stick.
What a lovely pair they make.
Ah Sister.
- What do you make of Mr Lefroy? - We're honoured by his presence.
You think?
He does with his preening prancing Irish - cum - Bond - Street airs.
Jane.
Well I call it very high indeed refusing to dance when there are so few gentleman.
- Henry are all your friends so disagreeable? - Jane.
Where exactly in Ireland does he come from anyway?
Limerick Miss Austen.
I would regard it as a mark of extreme favour
if you would stoop to honour me with this next dance.
Being the first to dance with me madam I feel it only fair to inform you
that you carry the standard for Hampshire hospitality.
Ah then your country reputation depends on my report.
This by the way is called a country dance after the French contredanse.
Not because it is exhibited at an uncouth rural assembly
with glutinous pies
execrable Madeira
and truly anarchic dancing.
You judge the company severely madam.
- I was describing what you'd be thinking. - Allow me to think for myself.
Gives me leave to do the same sir and come to a different conclusion.
- Will you give so much to a woman? - It must depend on the woman
and what she thinks of me.
But you are above being pleased.
And I think that you miss what was it?
- Austen. Mr? - Lefroy.
I think that you Miss Austen consider yourself a cut above the company.
Me?
You ma'am
secretly.
How many times did you stand up with that gentleman Jane?
- Was it twice? - Twice would have been partial.
- Thrice would have been absolutely... - Flagrant.
Careful Jane Lucy is right. Mr Lefroy does have a reputation.
Presumably as the most disagreeable...
"... insolent arrogant impudent
"insufferable impertinent of men."
Too many adjectives.
What is she trying to say?
On your toes gentlemen. No singles.
Bowler's end bowler's end.
- Again! - Run for more.
I never feel more French than when I watch cricket.
- Out. - Not out.
- No? - No.
Is he out?
I begin to suspect you're flirting with my brother cousin.
Flirting is a woman's trade. One must keep in practice.
You're gone.
Well played Tom.
We're depending on you.
Oh it's Mr Warren's... turn.
Best of luck!
John Warren!
Good luck Mr Warren.
John never was very good though.
Easy!
Run Warren run!
- Quickly hurry! - Run!
Jolly good show!
Watch.
- You're out. - Yah!
- You're gone Mr Warren. - Oh dear.
Prodigious Tom prodigious.
Thank you Warren. On your way.
Same again Tom.
- Well done Mr Warren. - Bad ball. It's a terrible wicket.
I hope you're not too disappointed Miss Austen.
Four more to win Wisley.
- Who's next? - Come on!
- She can't... - Jane!
What on earth are you going to do?
- Irrepressible. - she can.
Move in!
Go easy Tom.
Be gentle Lefroy!
Run Jane run!
- Move! - Run!
Only four more to win.
Bowler's end! Move yourself you lout!
- One more! - Quickly!
Go go go!
Not out.
Bad luck Lefroy.
See?
She was so good.
- You've played this game before? - No choice you see. She was raised by brothers.
Time for a swim I think.
Well played Henry.
I dedicate our victory to La Comtesse de Feuillide.
- Now there's a decent bit of river over the hill. - Oh yes?
Careful!
Come on let's go!
Wait!
- Not this time Lefroy. - Huh?
You think not?
Down boy.
- Father have you seen Tom? - No Lucy I've not.
Besotted. Natural enough at 15.
Love and sense are enemies at any age.
- Mrs Lefroy may I explore your library? - Of course.
Lucy would marry him tomorrow and what a terrible husband he would make.
I suppose you mean his reputation. Experience can recommend a man.
- Miss Austen. - Oh Mr Lefroy.
- And reading. - Yes.
I've been looking through your book of the wood. Mr White's Natural History.
Oh.
- Well how do you like it? - I cannot get on. It is too disturbing.
- Disturbing? - Mmm.
Take this observation.
"Swifts on a fine morning in May flying this way that way
"sailing around at a great height perfectly happily. Then...
"Then one leaps onto the back of another grasps tightly
"and forgetting to fly they both sink down"
"and down in a great dying fall"
"fathom after fathom until the female utters... "
Yes?
"... the female utters a loud piercing cry
"of ecstasy."
Is this conduct commonplace in the natural history of Hampshire?
Your ignorance is understandable since you lack... What shall we call it?
The history?
Propriety commands me to ignorance.
Condemns you to it and your writing to the status of female accomplishment.
If you wish to practise the art of fiction to be the equal of a masculine author
experience is vital.
I see.
And what qualifies you to offer this advice?
I know more of the world.
A great deal more I gather.
Enough to know that your horizons must be... widened
by an extraordinary young man.
By a very dangerous young man
one who has no doubt infected the hearts of many a young...
- Young woman with the soft corruption... - Read this
and you will understand.
"When the philosopher heard that the fortress of virtue had already been subdued
"he began to give a large scope to his desires.
"His appetite was not of that squeamish kind which cannot feed on a dainty
- "because another... " - "Another has tasted it."
- He's not tasting this dainty. - What dear?
"... nor had her face much appearance of beauty.
"But her clothes being torn from all the upper part of her body... "
"... her breasts which were well formed and extremely white
"attracted the eyes of her deliverer and for a few moments they stood silent... "
"... and gazing at each other."
I have read your book.
- I have read your book and disapprove. - Of course you do.
But of what? The scenes? Characters? The prose?
No all good.
- The morality? - Flawed.
Well of course it is. But why?
Vice leads to difficulty virtue to reward. Bad characters come to bad ends.
Exactly. But in life bad characters often thrive. Take yourself.
And a novel must show how the world truly is
how characters genuinely think how events actually occur.
A novel should somehow reveal the true source of our actions.
What of my hero's feelings?
Well it seems to me sir that your hero's very vigorous feelings
caused him and everyone connected with him a great deal of trouble.
Ah well if the book has troubled you...
- Oh but an orphan must know trouble. - What sort of trouble?
All sorts of trouble.
Laverton Fair. Vastly entertaining. Monstrous good idea Jane.
Yes Miss Austen not exactly your usual society I'd say.
Show a little imagination Mr Lefroy.
Trouble here enough.
And freedom the freedom of men.
Do not you envy it?
But I have the intense pleasure of observing it so closely.
Ah.
Now there's a fool to go to it with a professional.
- You know about this of course. - Of course.
Yes a vastly fashionable pastime in London.
Beating a man to a pulp. What are you doing?
Mr Lefroy stop!
Make way!
- Stop! - Let us see how you fare against me sir.
Coming through.
Five shillings on the gent. Who will take it? You sir? That's the ticket.
Have that.
Thank you.
Go on hit him!
Come on Lefroy hit him man!
Tom you must stop.
Come on Lefroy!
Up sir.
Tom!
Lucy.
- That's twice he's done that to me. - You spend money like water.
I'm afraid it's damn low water with me.
- I'm afraid I'm short sir. - Take it.
How embarrassing.
Yeh!
Mr Lefroy? Mr Lefroy? Mr Lefroy?
Was I deficient in propriety?
Why did you do that?
Couldn't waste all those expensive boxing lessons.
Forgive me if I suspect in you a sense of justice.
I am a lawyer. Justice plays no part in the law.
Is that what you believe?
I believe it. I must.
I beg your leave.
- Her heart is stirred. - It's a summer squall.
Mr Lefroy will soon be gone.
And Mr Wisley will still be waiting I hope.
- The man's a booby. - Oh he will grow out of that.
And she could fix him with very little trouble.
You could persuade her.
To sacrifice her happiness?
Jane should have not the man who offers the best price but the man she wants.
Oh Mr Austen.
Must we have this conversation day in and day out?
We'll end up in the gutter if we carry on like this.
Jenny! Mr Austen!
Where are you?
So kind of you to return the call.
- Will you take a dish of tea ma'am? - Green tea?
- Brown Your Ladyship. - Then no.
Where is your youngest daughter?
She's visiting the poor ma'am.
Jane? Jane!
At last. Lady Gresham and Mr Wisley have come to call.
Where have you been?
Ma'am. Sir.
Well perhaps... Perhaps the young people would like to take a walk?
I see there's a pretty little wilderness at the side of the house.
Excuse me.
Jane?
- What is she doing? - Writing.
Can anything be done about it?
Miss Austen you may know
that I have known you
for some considerable time during my visits to Steventon.
The garden is so affecting in this season.
Indeed.
- The impression you have given me has always... - The flowers particularly.
What I'm trying to say is that I...
I have a respectable property of 2000 a year
in addition to even greater expectations as Lady Gresham's heir
- to which it may be indelicate to refer. - Oh indelicate yes.
It's yours. If we marry all of it yours.
Mr Wisley...
Your offer is most sincere I can see and
gentlemanlike and it honours me truly.
But for all you are and all you offer I...
Yes.
Sometimes affection is a shy flower that takes time to blossom.
Lying to tradesmen mending scratching scraping.
Endlessly endlessly making do!
I understand that our circumstances are difficult ma'am.
- There is no money for you. - Surely something could be done.
What we can put by must go to your brothers. You will have nothing unless you marry.
Well then I will have nothing. For I will not marry without affection like my mother!
And now I have to dig my own damn potatoes!
Would you rather be a poor old maid? Ridiculous despised the butt of jokes?
The legitimate sport of any village lout with a stone and an impudent tongue?
Affection is desirable.
Money is absolutely indispensable.
I could live by my...
Your what?
- I could live by my... - Pen?
Let's knock that notion on the head once and for all.
What's this?
Trouble amongst my women?
Come
take hands and there's an end.
- Where are you going? Miss! - To feed the pigs ma'am.
He could give you a splendid home.
- A comfortable life. - Father.
Consider.
This is likely to be your best offer.
Wisley?
It is true so far he has not impressed...
- A booby. - He should grow out of that.
Nothing destroys spirit
like poverty.
I saw Queen Marie Antoinette wear something the same at a ball once.
Am I making a show? I am I know.
What trouble we take to make them like us when we like them.
Henry?
- Eliza my brother is much younger than you. - And poorer.
He knows that I care for him sincerely.
I know that he is handsome...
And the handsome young men must have something to live on as well as the plain.
You encourage him to take you for money?
- Men do. - That does not make it honourable.
Well I'm a sensible woman.
I thank God I am not by your description.
If you were you might have ascertained that your Irish friend has no money not a penny
and could not be expected to marry without it.
Consider that at the ball tonight.
In any event he'll be gone tomorrow back to Bond Street where he can do no more harm.
Good evening Miss Austen.
Yes yes.
Miss Jane Austen.
Pleasure.
We're very honoured to be here at your aunt's ball.
You dance with passion.
No sensible woman would demonstrate passion if the purpose were to attract a husband.
- As opposed to a lover? - Hmm.
Rest easy Mr Lefroy.
- I have no expectation on either account. - I did not mean to offend or hurt...
Oh no no of course not. Excuse me I'm just over warm.
Pardon me.
- Ah Miss Austen. - Excuse me.
This is unbearable. My father is pressing for an early ordination
while my own inclination is to the scarlet of a captaincy in His Majesty's regulars.
But I do not have the money to purchase one.
I do.
- Well that of course is impossible. - Oh Henry do not disguise yourself not to me.
The scarlet will suit you very well.
Miss Austen? There you are.
Miss Austen I cannot believe I am obliged to have this conversation.
Your Ladyship?
Mr Wisley's mother my own dear sister died young.
I have no children of my own.
I hope you never come to understand the pain of that condition.
Let us simply say my nephew's wishes are close to my heart
however extraordinary they may be.
Well
your health seems robust.
You have the usual accomplishments.
Your person is agreeable.
But when a young woman such as yourself receives the addresses
from a gentleman such as my nephew it is her duty to accept at once.
But what do we find?
- Independent thought? - Exactly.
My nephew Miss Austen condescends far indeed
in offering to the daughter of an obscure and impecunious clergyman.
Impecunious? Your Ladyship is mistaken.
I am never mistaken.
Your father is in grave financial difficulties.
But all is not lost.
He has a daughter upon whom fortune has smiled.
Mr Wisley is a good opportunity for Jane.
She should accept him at once.
Do not you think?
- Lucy let us take some refreshments. - What? Mother.
I have learned of Mr Wisley's marriage proposal.
My congratulations.
Is there an alternative for a well - educated young woman of small fortune?
How can you have him?
Even with his thousands and his houses
how can you of all people dispose of yourself without affection?
How can I dispose of myself with it?
You are leaving tomorrow.
- Did I do that well? - Very very well.
I wanted just once to do it well.
I have no money no property
I am entirely dependent upon that bizarre old lunatic my uncle.
I cannot yet offer marriage. But you must know what I feel.
Jane I'm yours.
Gah I'm yours. I'm yours heart and soul.
Much good that is.
Let me decide that.
What will we do?
What we must.
"My dearest Cassandra my heart has wings.
"Doubts and deliberations are ended.
"Soon I shall escape the attentions of that great lady and her scintillating nephew.
"Eliza Henry and I will join you at the coast
"but we are obliged to break our journey in London.
"Tom has cleverly secured an invitation to stay with his uncle the judge.
"Let us hope we can convince him of my eligibility.
"Please destroy this disgraceful letter
"the moment you have recovered from your astonishment.
"Yours affectionately and in haste Jane."
Tom! Our guests have arrived.
Decorum.
Countess.
Sir.
- Welcome... - Madame le Comtesse.
Madame le Comtesse.
Seldom too seldom my house receives the presence of nobility.
And of course its friends. Please.
Your stay is short. There's not a moment to lose.
My nephew has devised a plan of metropolitan amusement.
Pleasure is as you would say Madame his forte.
Ah is it?
Which battle was it Tom?
Villers - en - Cauchies.
Very good. Thousands slain. Served those Frenchies out.
Oh. Saving your presence ma'am.
Be not afraid of abusing the Jacobins on my account Judge.
- They guillotined my husband. - Oh savages. Beasts.
- And his property? - Confiscated.
A disaster.
Of course by then much of my wealth was portable so...
Yes portable property is happiness in a pocketbook.
Do I detect you in irony?
It is my considered opinion that irony is insult with a smiling face.
Indeed.
No.
No?
No irony is the bringing together of contradictory truths
to make out of the contradiction a new truth with a laugh or a smile
and I confess that a truth must come with one or the other
or I account it as false and a denial of the very nature of humanity itself.
My cousin is a writer.
- Of what? - Jane?
Novels.
A young woman of family?
Yes uncle and tomorrow we go and visit another Mrs Radcliffe.
She keeps herself to herself almost a recluse but I know her husband through the law.
- Who? - The authoress Mrs Radcliffe.
- As writing is her profession. - Her what?
500 uncle for the last novel The Mysteries of Udolpho.
- And 800 I believe for her next. - The Italian.
Above 1000?
The times the times.
You live so quietly.
And yet your novels are filled with romance danger terror.
Everything my life is not.
Apparently.
Of what do you wish to write?
Of the heart.
Do you know it?
Not all of it.
In time you will.
But even if that fails that's what the imagination is for.
Your imagination has brought you independence.
At a cost to myself and to my husband.
Poor William.
To have a wife who has a mind is considered not quite proper.
To have a wife with a literary reputation nothing short of scandalous.
But it must be possible?
- To live as both wife and author? - Oh.
I think so.
Though never easy.
Could I really have this?
What precisely?
You.
Me how?
- This life with you. - Yes.
Lefroy.
- Hush. The judge. - The man's like a rampant dog.
He will be generous. I'm sure of it.
- You'll speak with him? - Tomorrow I promise.
I really must say good night.
- Good night. - Good night.
- Miss Austen? - Yes?
Good night.
You know I think my mother is right. A husband and the sooner the better.
Five girls of little fortune.
"... sensibly and as warmly as a man violently in love can be supposed to do."
"Mr Wickham was the happy man towards whom almost every female eye was turned.
"... partial prejudiced absurd.
"Watch for the first appearance of Pemberley Woods.
"The happiness which this reply produced...
"It will not do. My feelings will not be repressed."
- Good morning sir. - Good morning?
- Has the world turned topsy? - Sir?
I trust the countess is enjoying her visit?
- I gather she is sir. I... - Fine woman very fine woman.
Indeed.
- I'd hoped to discuss a certain matter. - Your allowance is beyond negotiation.
Now that you have had the opportunity to become acquainted with Miss Austen yourself
I am sure you will find as I do that she is a remarkable young woman.
- This is an outrage! - Lf you will allow me to speak sir.
There is no need. This letter makes it absolutely clear.
Letter?
Now I know what you were at down in Hampshire.
- It is from Steventon. - Is it true
that you have practiced upon me with this chit?
I wished you to know the young lady.
I wished to introduce her to your affections discreetly.
Aye! Blind me with the rich widow and then
insinuate that penniless little husband-hunter!
- Moderation sir I beg you! - That ironical little authoress.
I wished you to know her for yourself.
I was certain her merit would speak for her.
- Consider sir my happiness is in your hands. - Happiness?
Damn it nephew
I had rather you were a whore - mongering blackguard with a chance of reform
than a love - sick whelp sunk in a bad marriage.
My uncle has refused to give his consent.
- The letter has done its work. - Who sent it?
Lady Gresham?
Or her nephew.
They think that they can do what they like with us but I will not accept this.
We have no choice.
Of course we do.
I...
I depend entirely upon...
Upon your uncle.
Mmm.
And I depend on you.
So what will you do?
What I must.
I have a duty to my family Jane. I must think of them as well as...
Tom...
Is that... Is that all you have to say to me?
Goodbye Mr Lefroy.
The sentence of this court is that you be taken to the place whence you came
and thence to a place of execution
and that you be there hanged by the neck until you are dead.
May the Lord have mercy on your soul.
Next.
He has behaved so ill to you Jane.
Perhaps soon we can return home to Steventon.
Is there any news of Robert?
He has arrived in San Domingo at last.
Good.
Glass of wine with you sir?
Yes.
Yes a toast from one member of the profession to another.
I'm sorry to have been so disobliging in the past.
Mr Wisley?
So the infamous Mrs Radcliffe.
Was she really as gothic as her novels?
Not in externals
but her inner landscape is quite picturesque I suspect.
True of us all.
There's a message for Reverend Austen.
- Message for Reverend Austen. - Thank you.
Uncle?
What is it?
It seemed he died very soon after landing in San Domingo.
My God he was hardly there.
What was the disease?
Yellow fever. Lord Craven he wrote.
He said that if he had known he was engaged to be married
he would never have taken him.
Jane there's something else.
Mr Lefroy Tom.
What?
I would keep this from you if I could.
He's here visiting Mrs Lefroy and I...
He is engaged.
So soon?
A letter?
No.
It's something I began in London.
It is the tale of a young woman.
Two young women.
Better than their circumstances.
So many are.
And two young gentlemen who receive
much better than their deserts as so very many do.
Mmm.
How does the story begin?
- Badly. - And then?
It gets worse.
With I hope some humour.
How does it end?
They both make triumphant happy endings.
Brilliant marriages?
Incandescent marriages
to very rich men.
You asked me a question.
I am ready to give you an answer. But there is one matter to be settled.
I cannot make you out Mr Wisley.
At times you are
the most gentlemanlike man I know and yet you would...
"Yet". What a sad word.
And yet you write yourself most tellingly to great effect.
- I'm speaking of course of your letter. - What letter?
Was your aunt the correspondent on your behalf?
What matter?
One way or another passion makes fools of us all.
I hope in time passion may regain your better opinion.
The emotion is absurd.
When you consider the sex to whom it is often directed
indistinguishable from folly.
I thank you for the honour of your proposal. I accept. Good day.
George George.
Mr Wisley is... He's an honourable man.
You'll always have a place with me.
Miss Austen.
Mr Lefroy.
Sir.
I believe I must congratulate you Mr Lefroy.
And you've come to visit an old friend at such a time. How considerate.
I have come
to offer an explanation belatedly
for my conduct. I cannot think how to describe it.
Tell me about your lady Mr Lefroy.
From where does she come?
She's from County Wexford.
Your own country. Excellent.
What was it that won her? Your manner smiles and pleasing address?
No no not at all.
No had I really experienced that emotion I should at present detest
the very sight of him.
And you are mistaken.
I'm even impartial towards the gloriously endowed Miss Wexford...
I cannot do this.
And so you would marry Wisley?
Please?
If there is a shred of truth or justice inside of you
- you cannot marry him. - Oh no Mr Lefroy.
Justice by your own admission you know little of truth even less.
Jane I have tried. I have tried and I cannot live this lie.
Can you?
Jane can you?
What value will there be in life if we are not together?
Run away with me.
An elopement?
That is exactly what I propose.
We'll post to London by Friday be in Scotland and man and wife.
- Leave everything? - Everything.
It is the only way we can be together.
You'll lose everything.
Family place. For what?
A lifetime of drudgery on a pittance?
A child every year and no means to lighten the load?
- How will you write Jane? - I do not know.
But happiness is within my grasp and I cannot help myself.
There is no sense in this.
If you could have your Robert back even like this
would you do it?
- Please conceal my departure as long as possible. - Wait.
Here.
Take these. Now go quickly.
Come. If we hurry we can still make the morning coach.
You are sure?
Be careful.
- Is it coming? - Not yet.
Take my hand. All right?
Hurry. I can hear it approaching.
Here it is.
Whoa.
Two to London. We'll settle at first rest.
- Yes? - Right you are sir.
Hampshire your home county.
It was.
Stuck. Everybody out ladies and gentlemen please.
- We need to lighten the load. - No let me let me.
I shall require you gentlemen to give me a hand put your shoulders into it.
Now sir if you can push on the coach itself. Excuse me sir. Young gentleman?
- Yes yes. - You on the other side sir thank you.
- Young gentleman please come along. - All right.
Mind helping us? Thank you.
Right all together now then sirs please?
One two
and a three and push!
Come on.
"Dear Tom.
"How timely was the arrival of the money you sent."
One two and three!
"It was so very much appreciated by your father and I.
"You're so kind to share your uncle's allowance.
"Indeed I do not dare think how we would survive without it."
Well done. Thank you sirs.
All right ladies and gentlemen back on the coach as soon as you can thank you.
We are ready.
- Worried? - No.
- Is it the loss of your reputation? - No.
The loss of yours.
- I do not... - Please sir come along the coach is departing.
Come.
Changing horses. Twenty minutes only.
House of office at the back of the inn. All down quick as you like.
How many brothers and sisters do you have in Limerick Tom?
Enough. Why?
What are the names of your brothers and sisters?
They...
On whom do they depend?
Your reputation is destroyed.
Your profligacy is a beautiful sham.
- I can earn money. - It will not be enough.
I will rise.
With a High Court Judge as your enemy? And a penniless wife?
God knows how many mouths depending on you?
My sweet sweet friend you will sink and we will all sink with you.
- I will... - Hampshire Flyer.
Hampshire Flyer's leaving in five minutes.
No! No Jane.
I will never give you up.
- Tom... - Don't speak or think.
Just love me. Do you love me?
Yes.
But if our love destroys your family it will destroy itself.
- No. - Yes.
In a long slow degradation of guilt and regret and blame.
That is nonsense.
Truth.
Made from contradiction.
But it must come with a smile.
Or else I shall count it as false and we shall have had no love at all.
Please.
Goodbye.
Typical bloody runaway. "Will I won't I? "
Miss. Miss.
All right off you go.
Hello?
- Where is everyone? - Looking for you Miss. Looking everywhere.
- Thank you Jenny. - Mr Warren.
Your family tried to keep the matter from the servants but...
Where is that blackguard Lefroy? My God if Henry finds him he'll kill him.
He won't find him.
If he does he won't kill him.
There's no need.
What happened?
Nothing happened.
I see. I see.
Jane
I may have less personal charm than Lefroy.
Superficial charm to some eyes.
To others it is mere affectation but I...
- I have no hopes. - Hopes?
You cannot begin to imagine.
Thank you for the great honour of your offer
but are there no other women in Hampshire?
It was you who wrote the judge.
You must consider how much I have always loved you.
Well?
You came back to us.
Leave it.
Mr Austen I must inform you that I shall not attend service today.
- Not in the presence of this young woman. - Indeed...
- If I must speak plainly... - Aunt.
I believe your youngest daughter has been on a journey.
- Her Ladyship considers travel a crime? - Unsanctioned travel.
Furthermore be aware that my nephew has withdrawn his addresses
to someone without family fortune importance
and fatally tainted by suspicion.
- Oh she has family madam. - Indeed she has.
Importance may depend upon other matters than Your Ladyship can conceive.
As to fortune a young woman might depend upon herself.
An interesting notion Miss Austen.
Oblige me a walk along the river to enlarge upon the topic.
Wisley?
I am sorry if my conduct has disappointed you Mr Wisley.
It seems you cannot bring yourself to marry without affection.
Or even with it.
I respect you for that and share your opinion. Neither can I.
I'd always hoped to win your love in time
but I am vain enough to want to be loved for myself rather than my money.
Do we part as friends?
We do.
- So you will live... - By my pen. Yes.
Will all your stories have happy endings?
My characters will have
after a little bit of trouble
all that they desire.
The good do not always come to good ends.
It is a truth universally acknowledged.
"... that a single man in possession of a good fortune
"must be in want of a wife."
"However little known the feelings or views of such a man may be
"on his first entering a neighbourhood
"this truth is so well fixed in the minds of the surrounding families
"that he is considered as the rightful property of some one or other of their daughters.
"'My dear Mr Bennet ' said his lady to him one day
"'Have you heard that Netherfield Park is let at last? '
"Mr Bennet replied that he had not.
"'But it is ' returned she... "
Is it Miss Austen? The Miss Austen?
No Madam. That courtesy according to the customs of precedence
belongs to my elder sister.
Miss Jane Austen the authoress of Pride and Prejudice?
My sister wishes to remain anonymous but your kind regard is much appreciated.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Please come through.
I shall never forgive Henry for this.
Yes you will. We always forgive him for everything.
Jane an old friend.
Late as ever.
Madame le Comtesse Miss Austen.
Mr Lefroy.
Please allow me to introduce to you
your most avid of admirers my daughter Miss Lefroy.
Miss Austen what a pleasure to meet you.
Will you read for us this evening?
Ah well you see my sister never reads.
Otherwise how else is she supposed to remain anonymous?
- But... - Jane.
I will make an exception
if my new friend wishes it.
Come sit by me.
She is lovely Tom.
"She began now to comprehend
"that he was exactly the man who in disposition and talents
"would most suit her.
"His understanding and temper though unlike her own
"would have answered all her wishes.
"It was an union that must have been to the advantage of both.
"By her ease and liveliness
"his mind might have been softened his manners improved
"and from his judgment information and knowledge of the world
"she must have received benefit of greater importance.
"But no such happy marriage could now teach the admiring multitude
"what connubial felicity really was."
关注左岸电影微信公众号：film-zone