赵成钢制作
Created time 13.02.24 16:44:18
白色区是乘客上落专用区 The white zone is for loading and unloading of passengers only,
不准停在红色区 There is no stopping in the red zone,
你好，请收下醒悟教的花朵 Hello. Take this flower from the Religious Consciousness Church.
-可否捐献？ -不了，但谢谢你的花 - Would you care to make a donation? - No, but thank you anyway.
红色区是乘客上落专用区 The red zone is for loading and unloading of passengers only,
不准停在白色区 There is no stopping in the white zone,
白色区才是乘客上落专用区 No, The white zone is for loading and unloading,
不准停在红色区才对 There's no stopping in the red zone,
红色区一直是乘客上落专用区 The red zone's always been for loading and unloading,
不准停留的一直是白色区 There's never stopping in a white zone,
别告诉我哪区是上落区 Don't tell me which zone is for stopping and which is for loading,
别又再说那些白色区废话了 Listen, Betty, don't start up with your white zone shit again,
你好，请收下醒悟教的花朵 Hello. Take this flower from the Religious Consciousness Church.
-可否捐献？ -不，我们在办公室已捐献了 - Would you like to make a donation? - No, thanks. We gave at the office.
请把金属物件放在盘上 Would you put all your metal objects into this dish, please?
白色区是不许停下的 There'sjust no stopping in a white zone,
你别装蒜了 Really, Vernon, why pretend?
你在说什么大家心知肚明 We both know what you're talking about,
你想我坠胎 You want me to have an abortion,
只要小心行事，这是最佳方法 lt's the only sensible thing to do, lf it's done properly,
基本上并不危险 therapeutically, there's no danger involved,
的士！ Taxi!
我很快回来 l'll be back in a minute.
先生，请收下醒悟教的花朵 Hello, sir, take this flower from the Religious Consciousness Church.
你可否… Would you care...
-莱利，铲车呢？ -铲车？ - Hey, Larry, where's the forklift? - Forklift?
在那边，行李装机旁 lt's over there by the baggage loader.
小心！ Look out!
-绮莲 -泰德！ - Elaine. - Ted!
我早了回家，看到你的便条 l came home early and found your note.
你大概是想我稍后才看到 我得和你谈谈 l guess you meant for me to read it later. l've got to talk to you.
我不想再说了 l don't want to go over it any more.
我知道很多事是日积月累的 Things haven't been right for a long time,
但一定会有所改变 就像开始时那样 but it'll be different, like in the beginning.
请有点耐性，我会想办法 Just be patient and l'll work things out.
我一直都很有耐性 并尝试去帮助你 l have been patient and l've tried to help,
但你甚至不让我这样做 but you wouldn't even let me do that.
你对我已没有感觉？ Don't you feel anything for me any more?
令爱情长久，要有很多因素 lt takes so many things to make love last.
最重要是彼此尊重 Most of all, it takes respect.
我不能与我不尊重的人生活 l can't live with a man l don't respect!
真惹人讨厌 What a pisser.
（小说）
（非小说）
（怪诞材料）
（现代精子）
欧机长，请接听白色电话 Captain Oveur, white courtesy phone,
欧家伦机长，请听白色电话 Captain Clarence Oveur, white courtesy phone,
不，白色电话才对 No, the white phone!
我是欧机长 This is Captain Oveur.
美奥诊所找你 One moment for your call from the Mayo Clinic,
欧机长，请听白色电话 Captain Oveur, white courtesy phone,
-我已在接听 -谢谢 - l've got it! - Thank you,
请接来 Go ahead with your call,
我是美奥诊所的布医生 This is Dr Brody at the Mayo Clinic,
在你往芝加哥的航机上 有一名乘客 There's a passenger on your Chicago flight,
一个叫戴莉莎的小女孩 是前往明尼阿波利斯的 a little girl named Lisa Davis, en route to Minneapolis.
她正排期接受心脏移植手术 She's scheduled for a heart transplant.
告诉她母亲我们找到捐赠者 Tell her mother we found a donor.
心脏已准备好移植 The heart is ready for surgery,
手术得在六小时内进行 We must have the recipient on the operating table within six hours,
确保她要躺着 Make sure she's kept in a reclined position,
并一直接受静脉注射 and that a continuous watch is kept on her lV.
她保持冷静是很重要的 lt's very important she remain calm,,,
对不起，我是接线生 Excuse me, this is the operator,
韩先生急电，在第五线 l have an emergency call on line five from a Mr Hamm,
替我接进来 Give me Hamm on five, hold the Mayo.
你明晚会回来 到时我们共进晚餐好好谈谈 You'll be back tomorrow night. We'll have dinner. We'll talk things over.
我不会回来 我要求调往阿特兰大 l won't be back. l've requested the Atlanta run.
绮莲，我保证我可以改变 Elaine... l promise l can change.
那么为何你不接受李路易 在波音公司给你的工作？ Then why didn't you take the job that Louie Netz offered you at Boeing?
战后我无法走近飞机 l haven't been able to get near a plane since the war.
加上我的战时记录 他们不会聘用我的 And they wouldn't hire me because of my war record.
战时记录？只有你才在意 War record? You're the only one keeping that alive.
其他人都不当这是一回事 For everyone else, it's ancient history.
-你以为我会相信？ -那是事实 - You expect me to believe that? - lt's the truth.
最丢人的是你战后的记录 What's hurt you the most is your record since the war -
往不同城市，做不同工作 different cities, different jobs -
完全显示了你不可以承担责任 and not one of them shows you can accept any real responsibility.
-绮莲，再给我一次… -太迟了 - Elaine, just give me one more... - lt's too late, Ted.
当我返回芝加哥 When l get back to Chicago,
我要重新生活，抱歉 l'm going to start my life all over again. l'm sorry.
请收下醒悟教的花朵 Excuse me, take this flower from the Church of Religious...
你好 Hi! Well, good evening.
行了，跟着他们 There you go. Just follow them to the back.
有没有盐湖城那风暴消息？ Any word on that storm lifting over Salt Lake, Clarence?
没有 No, not likely, Victor.
我刚看过四点至十二点的 地区报告 l just reviewed the area report for 1600 hours through 2400.
有一道冷锋在达科他上 There's an occluded front stalled over the Dakotas,
一直伸展至犹他 backed up all the way to Utah.
若移至大湖区，就会很大雾 lf she decides to push over the Great Lakes, it could get plenty soupy.
走南路绕过图沙又如何？ What about that southern route around Tulsa?
我已查看过了 l double-checked the terminal forecast,
天气同样恶劣 and the wind's aloft and lFR ceilings all the way.
如何恶劣？ Where do they top out?
二万英尺高空满布密云 一万八千英尺高空更有冰雹 Light scattered cover at 20,000, icing around 18.
-似乎丹佛的天气最好 -是的 - Looks like over Denver is best. - Denver it is.
抱歉 Sorry, Clarence.
最新报告显示由盐湖城至林肯 都很大雾 Latest report shows everything's socked in from Salt Lake to Lincoln.
罗渣，欢迎你 Hi, Roger. Glad to have you aboard.
伟达，这是梅罗渣，白伟达 Victor, this is Roger Murdock. Victor Basta.
-你好吗？ -幸会 - How do you do? - Nice to meet you.
我正跟伟达说 我看过四点至十二点的… l was telling Victor l reviewed the area report
地区报告 for 1600 hours through 2400.
有一道冷锋在达科他上 There's an occluded front stalled over the Dakotas.
（美国新闻 选举影响）
行了，谢谢 There you go. Thank you.
请问狄绮莲在这班机上吗？ ls Elaine Dickinson on this flight?
所有机员都登机了，让我看看 The whole flight crew has boarded. Let me see.
对，她在机上 Oh, yes. She is on board.
我想要一张往芝加哥的机票 没有行李 l'd like one ticket to Chicago. No baggage.
-吸烟抑或不吸烟？ -吸烟 - Smoking or non-smoking? - Smoking, please.
这里，祝旅程愉快 There. Have a nice trip.
史泰德，这是红队长四号 Striker, this is Red Leader Four,
主要目标被大雾遮盖 Primary target covered by fog,
你要决定继续进行 Decision to proceed is yours,
是你决定… The decision is yours,,,
是你… is yours,,, is yours,,,
那白人该远离我妻子
否则我会揍他
对，他不该这样做
我认识一个处境相同的人
结果他后悔莫及
别那么天真了，雅瑟
我们每人都有道德选择
早睡早起
令人健康、富足和聪明
说得真好！
（请勿吸烟）
（扣紧安全带）
很紧张？ Nervous?
是的 Yes.
第一次？ First time?
不，已很多次 No. l've been nervous lots of times.
我们快起飞了 我替你扣好安全带吧 Hi. We'll be taking off real soon, so l better fasten you in tight.
劳驾，妈妈，我很兴奋 Thank you. Oh, Mother, this is so exciting!
我知道，但你得休息 l know, but remember, you must get some rest.
你放松点吧！ 飞机起飞后我会再回来 That's good advice. You relax, and l'll be back after we take off.
谢谢你 Thank you.
-我会很想念你 -我也是 - l'm going to miss you so much. - l'm going to miss you, too.
答应我写信给我 Promise you'll write?
每天都会 Every day.
阿标！ Bill!
快登机吧 Better get on board, son.
所有乘客登机 All aboard!
209号班机叫地面指挥 我们准备起程 209er to ground control. We're ready to taxi.
-再见，阿标 -再见，宝贝 - Goodbye, Bill! - Goodbye, darling!
我爱你 l love you, darling!
209号班机 请使用第19号跑道 209er, taxi to runway19er,
再见，宝贝 Goodbye, darling!
你一到步 就要拍照并立即寄给我 Have your picture taken the minute you get there and send me one.
好的，拿着 OK. Here, hurry.
这是你的手表，你不该给我 你会用得着的 lt's your watch. You shouldn't. You're going to need this.
不要紧，已坏掉 lt's all right. lt doesn't work.
-阿标 -再见，宝贝 - Bill! - Goodbye, darling!
阿标！ Bill!
阿标，我会整天戴着它 Bill! Bill! l'll keep it with me all the time.
-209号班机，可以起飞 -收到 - Flight 209er- clear for takeoff, - Roger.
-洛杉矶离开频道是123.9 -收到 - L departure frequency 1 23,9er, - Roger.
-请给航向指示 -什么？ - Request vector. Over. - What?
209号班机，可以起飞了 Flight 209er, clear for vector 324,
-我们可以起飞了 -收到 - We have clearance, Clarence. - Roger, Roger.
伟达，航向指示是什么？ What's our vector, Victor?
-我想要无线电指示 -我是欧家伦 - l want radio clearance, Over, - That's Clarence Oveur, Over,
-收到 -什么？ - Roger, - Huh?
-收到？ -谁？ - Roger, Over, - Huh? Who?
先生，你没事吧？ Do you feel all right, sir?
我很久没有乘搭飞机了 Oh, l haven't flown for a long time.
各位好，我是欧机长 Good evening. This is Captain Oveur speaking.
我们今晚会在 三万六千英尺上空飞行 We'll be cruising at 36,000 feet this evening,,,
（男孩生活）
（修女生活）
放松，好好享受今次旅程 Relax and enjoy your flight,
想看点什么吗？ Would you like something to read?
有没有轻松一些的？ Do you have anything light?
“著名犹太运动巨星” 册子如何？ How about this leaflet, ''Famous Jewish Sports Legends''?
好的，劳驾 Yes. Thank you.
-泰德，你为何会在这里？ -我得和你谈谈 - Ted! What are you doing here? - l've got to talk to you.
你不该上机，我现在没时间 You shouldn't have come. l don't have time now.
-小姐？ -失陪 - Stewardess? - Excuse me.
难怪你不开心，她很可爱 No wonder you're upset. She's lovely.
身材又好 And a darling figure.
肌肤充满弹性，丰乳纤腿 Supple, pouting breasts, firm thighs.
可惜你俩合不来 lt's a shame you two don't get along.
我知道 Yes, l know.
以前并不是这样的 Things used to be different.
我记得我们首次相遇的情形 l remember when we first met.
是战时的事 lt was during the war.
我加入空军 驻守巴巴利海岸的杜林比 l was in the air force, stationed in Drambuie, off the Barbary Coast.
经常往马金巴酒吧 l used to hang out at the Magumba Bar,
那是一处品流复杂的地方 lt was a rough place, The seediest dive on the wharf,
三山五[的人都聚集在那儿 populated with every reject and cut-throat from Bombay to Calcutta,
比底特律还要差 lt was worse than Detroit,
那儿的气氛也不好 The mood in the place was ugly,
拳头要够硬才可以往那里 You wouldn't be there unless you knew how to use your fists,
几乎每晚都会发生打斗 Afight broke out almost every night,
我并非往那里找情人 只想喝几杯 l didn't go there that night to fall in love, l just wanted a couple of drinks,
突然之间，我看到她 And suddenly, there she was,
我完全被她俘虏，像遭电击 l was captivated, entranced, lt hit me like a thunderboit,
我得叫这厮捏我 以确保自己不是在做梦 l had to ask this guy to pinch me to make sure l wasn't dreaming,
我害怕上前认识她 l was afraid to approach her,
但那晚，我们注定相识 but that night, fate was on my side,
我们谈天、说笑和跳舞 We laughed, we talked, we danced,
我不想那晚结束，现在亦然 l never wanted it to end. l guess l still don't.
我说够了，希望没把你闷坏 Enough about me. l hope this hasn't been boring for you.
但每当说起绮莲，我都很投入 浑然忘记了时间 But whenever l talk about Elaine, l get so carried away. l lose all track of time.
想要晚餐吗？ Would you like to order dinner?
-祖儿吃牛扒，我们则吃鱼 -我何时可以参观驾驶舱？ - Joey will have steak. We'll have fish. - When can l see the cockpit?
机师现在很忙 The pilots are probably too busy flying the plane for that.
真气人！ Aw, gee whizz!
我跟机长说，且看能否安排 l'll talk to the captain and see what l can arrange.
太好了！ Gee, that'd be swell!
想吃晚餐吗？ Would you care to order your dinners?
我想吃牛扒
我要鱼
我刚巧经过 Excuse me, l happened to be passing.
你要咖啡吗？ l thought you might like some coffee.
你真有心，谢谢 That's very nice of you. Thank you.
-坐吧 -谢谢 - Won't you sit down? - Thank you.
-加奶吗？ -不，我喝黑咖啡的 - Cream? - No, l take it black.
像我的男人一样 Like my men.
泰德，我实在太快乐了 Ted, l never knew l could be so happy.
这几个月简直是神仙生活 These past few months have been wonderful.
不如明天我们去吃海鲜 Tomorrow, why don't we drive to that little seafood place and...
-怎么了？ -我接到命令 - What's the matter? - My orders came through.
我的部队要明天出发 My squadron ships out tomorrow.
我们要在六点钟 轰炸戴基利的补给站 We're bombing the storage depots at Daiquiri at 1800 hours.
我们由北面进袭 低于他们的雷达 We're coming in from the north, below their radar.
-你何时回来？ -我不能说，是机密 - When will you be back?. - l can't tell you that. lt's classified.
泰德，万事小心，我很担心 Oh, Ted, please be careful. l worry about you so much.
我爱你，绮莲 l love you, Elaine.
我爱你 l love you.
209号班机，这是丹佛控制塔 Flight 209er, this is Denver flight control,
前面天气并不稳定 请上升至四万二千英尺 You're approaching rough weather, Please climb to 42,000 feet,
-收到 -有访客到 - Roger, Denver. - We have a visitor.
你好 Hello.
欧机长、梅先生、白先生 这是夏祖儿 Captain Oveur, Mr Murdock, and Mr Basta, this is Joey Hammen.
-祖儿，你好 -过来 - Hi, Joey. - Come up here.
这是送给访客的，想要吗？ This is for special visitors. Would you like to have it?
-实在谢谢你 -别客气，到过驾驶舱没有？ - Thank you. Thanks a lot. - Sure. Ever been in a cockpit?
没有，我从没乘搭过飞机 No, l've never been up in a plane before.
你见过成年男性裸体吗？ Have you ever seen a grown man naked?
-该看看天气吗？ -不，你负责吧 - Shall l check the weather? - No, why don't you take care of it?
祖儿，你有否到过体操馆？ Joey, do you ever hang around the gymnasium?
-我们还是回去吧 -不，祖儿可以多留一会 - We'd better get back. - No, Joey can stay for a while.
-真的？ -只要你不碍事便行 - Could l? - OK, if you don't get in the way.
209号班机叫丹佛控制塔 我们升至四万二千英尺上空前进 Flight 209er to Denver, climbing to cruise at 42,000.
我们到林肯上空时会再报到 We'll report again over Lincoln. Over and out.
慢着，我认得你，你是渣巴 Wait a minute, l know you. You're Kareem Abdul Jabbar.
效力洛杉矶湖人队的 You play basketball for the Los Angeles Lakers.
抱歉，你认错人了 Sorry, you have me confused with someone else.
我叫梅罗渣，是副机师 My name's Roger Murdock. l'm the co-pilot.
你是渣巴，我看过你比赛 我爸买了季票 You are Kareem! l've seen you play. My dad's got season tickets.
你该返回座位，对吗？家伦 You should go back to your seat now. Right, Clarence?
不，他没骚扰任何人 让他留下 No, he's not bothering anyone. Let him stay here.
好，但记着，我叫做梅罗渣 All right, but just remember my name is Roger Murdock.
是个机师 l'm an airline pilot.
我觉得你是最出色的球员 l think you're the greatest,
但爸说你在防守方面做得不够 but my dad says you don't work hard enough on defence.
他经常说你甚至不回防 And he says lots of times you don't even run downcourt.
在季后赛时才偶尔回防 And you don't try, except during the play-offs.
我有回防的！ The hell l don't!
自从我在大学开始 已不断听到这种废话 Listen, kid, l've been hearing that crap ever since l was at UCLA.
我每晚都尽力比赛 l'm out there busting my buns every night.
叫你老爹把裁判员带来球场 Tell your old man to drag Walton and Lanier
要他们上落跑48分钟吧 up and down the court for 48 minutes.
祖儿 喜欢关于格斗者电影吗？ Joey... Do you like movies about gladiators?
绮莲，请听我说 Elaine, just hear me out.
我知道我们之间问题存在已久 但一切将有改变 Things haven't been right for a long time, but it'll be different,
就像开始时那样，记得吗？ like in the beginning, remember?
我记得一切 l remember everything.
我只有回忆 All l have is memories.
记得最深刻的是晚上一起时 Mostly, l remember the nights we were together.
我记得你怎样拥抱我 l remember how you used to hold me,
我怎样坐在你的面上摆动 how l used to sit on your face and wriggle, and...
然后我们会一起看日出 afterwards, how we'd watch till the sun came up.
当太阳升起时 When it did, it was almost like...
就像那新的一天是为我们而设 like each new day was created only for us.
我一直就想这样 That's the way l've always wanted it to be.
可惜事与愿违 But it won't be.
你一直活在过去！ Not as long as you insist on living in the past!
泰德，你飞得太低了！ You're too low, Ted!
（美军精神病院有茂醇）
你的脑袋又愚弄你了 The mind plays tricks on you.
他今天看来很高兴吧 He looks so happy today, doesn't he?
你今天看来很高兴 You look so happy today.
罗拔，放他们下来，不痛的 OK, Robert, slip them down. This won't hurt much.
总部今天有电报给你 You got a telegram from headquarters today.
总部？什么来的？ Headquarters? What is it?
即将军聚首的巨型建筑物 算了 A big building where generals meet, but that's not important.
那次突击的事，他们不怪责你 They've cleared you of any blame for what happened on that raid.
-这岂非好消息？ -是吗？ - lsn't that good news? - ls it?
由于我的过失，有六人死亡 Because of my mistake, six men didn't return from that raid.
是七个，薛中尉今早逝世 Seven. Lieutenant Zip died this morning.
但沉医生说你一周后可以出院 这不是好消息吗？ But Dr Sandler says you'll be out in a week. lsn't that wonderful?
但愿我能这样跟薛佐治说 l wish l could say the same for George Zip.
耐心一点吧！ 没有人预期你会立即忘记此事 Be patient, Ted. Nobody expects you to get over this immediately.
史，可否歇一歇？我很累 Hey, Striker, how about a break?. l'm getting tired.
好的，休息五分钟吧 Yeah, all right. Take five.
谢谢你 Thanks.
我为我们找到新房子 有砖造的火炉 l found a wonderful apartment for us. lt has a brick fireplace
睡房也很特别，天花板有镜子 and a cute bedroom with mirrors on the ceiling and...
红队长，我要下去了！ Red Leader, l'm going down!
姬上尉以为自己是机师 仍在打仗 Captain Geline. He thinks he's a pilot, still fighting the war.
我找到隧道了，这边 l've found the tunnel, Johnson! lt's this way!
二十五元一根烟太贵了！ $25 for a cigarette is too much!
-他怎么了？ -他是胡中尉 - What's his problem? - lt's Lieutenant Hurwitz.
严重弹震症 以为自己是雄性人鱼 Severe shell shock. He thinks he's Ethel Merman.
战争实在可怕 War is hell.
先生，吃晚餐前想喝杯咖啡吗 Excuse me, sir. Would you like some coffee before dinner?
不用了，谢谢 No. No, thank you.
-要多一杯吗？ -好的，但占不要了 - Would you like another cup? - l will, but Jim won't.
我想要多杯咖啡 l think l will have another cup of coffee.
占在家从来不会多要一杯咖啡 Jim never has a second cup of coffee at home,
-修女 -什么事？ - Excuse me, Sister. - Yes?
-机上有一名病重的小女孩 -她真可怜 - There's a little girl on board who's ill. - Oh, yes, l saw. Poor child.
我想借你的结他去令她开心点 Could l borrow your guitar? l thought l'd cheer her up.
-好的 -谢谢你 - Of course. - Thank you.
-你好 -你好 - Hi. - Hi.
我可否跟你女儿谈谈？ Do you mind if l talk to your daughter?
随便 l think that'd be nice.
-你好，我叫兰迪 -我是莉莎，你有结他 - Hi, l'm Randy. - l'm Lisa. Oh, you have a guitar!
想听歌吗？ l thought maybe you'd like to hear a song.
好！ l'd love to.
让我想想 OK. Let's see...
这是我最喜欢的 This is one of my favorites.
你迟到，我们在等你 You're late. We've been waiting.
-谁先？ -你来吧！家伦 - Who's first? - Go ahead, Clarence.
天气怎样？ How's the weather?
前面有厚云层，要上升飞行 We got some heavy stuff ahead of us. We've got to climb on top.
战后我想尽量离开伤心地 Yeah, after the war, l wanted to get as far away as possible,
故我和绮莲加入和平大使计划 so Elaine and l joined the Peace Corps.
我们被派往接触偏远部族 莫林保人 We were assigned to an isolated tribe, the Molombos.
他们从没见过美国人 They'd never seen Americans before.
向他们介绍西方文化 是一个大挑战 lt was really a challenge, introducing them to our Western cuiture,
起初，他们对我们有戒心 At first, they didn't know what to think of us,
但很快我们获得他们信任 But soon, we gained their trust,
这样保存食物更好 lt'll help you better prepare storing foods
可保留至季候风月份 for the up and coming monsoon months.
这些用来存放吃剩的东西最好 Also, Supperware products are ideal for storing leftovers
价廉物美 to help stretch your food dollar.
这个保鲜盒 This two-quart ''Seals-M-Rite'' container
可以令热狗包保持新鲜多天 keeps hot dog buns fresh for days.
这些人一直与文明隔绝 These people had been completely isolated from civilization,
从没有人替他们制订保健计划 No one had outlined a physical fitness program for them,
他们亦没有运动器材 and they had no athletic equipment,
我教他们做柔软体操 和一些基本球技 l started them on simple calisthenics, worked up to rudimentary game skills,
最后令他们有竞赛能力 and finally, advanced competitive theory,
我很有耐性，他们亦很好学 l was patient, and they were eager to learn,
他们似乎玩得很开心 They seemed to enjoy themselves,
大概因为有先进的美国教法 Probably due to advanced American teaching techniques,
他们再不与世隔绝 we bridged the generations of isolation,
我们成功与莫林保人沟通 and communicated successfully with the Molombos,
他们已把握到个中精髓 再来时，我会教他们打棒球 They're getting the hang of it. When we re-enlist, l'll teach them baseball.
泰德，我不想留在这里 Ted, l don't want to stay here.
该回家实行战前定下的计划 lt's time to go home to the plans we made before the war.
很多人在战前都有很多计划 薛佐治就是其中一分子 A lot of people made plans before the war. Like George Zip.
那刻我知道绮莲对我们的 关系有疑问 At that moment, l realised Elaine had doubts about our relationship,
这引起我的饮水问题 And that, as much as anything else, led to my drinking problem,
我们返美，我做过很多工作 We did come back to the States. l tried a number of jobs.
我可以继续说，但你会闷坏 l could go on, but l'd probably bore you.
实在不能怪责绮莲 她想有自己的事业 l really couldn't blame Elaine. She wanted a career.
-我受不了 -什么事？ - l can't stand it. - What is it?
-什么事？ -我的胃很不舒服 - Yes? - lt's my stomach.
自从看过列根那电影后 我从没试过那么不舒服 l haven't felt this awful since we saw that Ronald Reagan film.
且看我能否找到晕机药 l'll see if l can find some Dramamine.
机长，有一名女乘客很不舒服 Captain, a woman passenger is very sick.
-晕机？ -不是，她真的很辛苦 - Airsick?. - l think so, l've never seen it so acute,
悄悄地找找机上有没有医生 Find out if there's a doctor on board, as quietly as you can.
祖儿，你到过土耳其监狱吗？ Joey, have you ever been in a Turkish prison?
我不该喝第二杯咖啡 l shouldn't have had that second cup of coffee.
占在家从不呕吐 Jim never vomits at home,
抱歉弄醒你，但我想找医生 Sorry to wake you. l'm looking for a doctor. There's nothing to worry about.
小姐，我身旁的该是医生 Stewardess, l think the man next to me is a doctor.
先生，抱歉弄醒你 但你是医生吗？ Sir, excuse me. Sorry to wake you, are you a doctor?
-是的 -我们有乘客不舒服 - That's right. - We have sick passengers.
-可否去看看他们？ -好的 - Could you take a look at them? - Yes, of course.
让我看看你的舌头 Let me see your tongue.
我很快回来 l'll be back in a minute.
叫机长降落，要送她往医院 Tell the captain to land. She must go to a hospital.
医院！什么？ A hospital! What is it?
是一座有病人的建筑物，算了 lt's a big building with patients, but that's not important.
-我得跟机长谈谈 -好的 - l must speak to the captain. - Certainly.
伟达，我们遇上浓… Victor, we're running into heavy...
罗渣，快接手！ Roger, take over!
-机长，何时可以降落？ -我不知道 - Captain, how soon can you land? - l can't tell.
-你该知道的，我是医生 -不，我不清楚 - You can tell me. l'm a doctor. - No, l'm not sure.
-可否猜一猜？ -起码两小时之后吧 - Can't you take a guess? - Not for another two hours.
你要在两小时后才去猜一猜？ You can't take a guess for another two hours?
我们无法降落，太大雾了 No, we can't land. Fog has closed down everything.
我们得尽快降落 We've got to get through to Chicago.
带他走 Get him out of there!
-医生，究竟发生什么事？ -我不清楚 - What is it, Doctor? What's going on? - l'm not sure.
自拜恩的演唱会后 从未见过这种事 Haven't seen anything like this since the Anita Bryant concert.
-我们晚餐吃什么？ -可以选牛扒或鱼 - What did we have for dinner? - We had a choice - steak or fish.
我记得，我吃烤宽面条 Yes, l remember. l had lasagna.
-他吃了什么？ -吃了鱼 - What did he have? - He had fish.
医生，又有两人不舒服 乘客都很担心 Doctor, two more are sick. The other passengers are worried.
我会处理 l'll handle the passengers.
找出病人晚餐吃过什么 我是欧机长 Find out what the sick people had for dinner. This is Captain Oveur speaking.
我们遇上气流但很快会没事 lt's bumpy, but we'll be past it in a few minutes,
我们正飞越胡佛水霸 We're now flying over Hoover Dam,
跟着我们会飞越大峡谷 and later we'll pass south of the Grand Canyon,
与此同时，请放松 好好享受今次旅程 Meanwhile, relax and enjoy your flight, OK?
芝加哥，这是209号班机 我们有麻烦 Chicago, this is flight 209er. We're in trouble.
请给我们优先降落权 Have all traffic below us cleared. l want a priority landing in Chicago.
什么事？ Yes?
我的丈夫很不舒服，请帮忙 My husband's very sick. Can you do something?
医生很快会来 The doctor will be with you in just a moment.
-知否他晚餐吃了什么？ -我们都吃了鱼，为什么？ - Do you know what he had for dinner? - Yes, we both had fish. Why?.
没什么，我们很快回来 lt's nothing to be alarmed about. We'll be back to you very quickly.
医生，夏先生吃了鱼 Doctor, Mr Hammen ate fish,
兰迪说又有五人不舒服 他们全都吃过鱼 and Randy said there are five more cases, and they all had fish.
副机师也吃了鱼 导航员吃过什么？ The co-pilot had fish. What did the navigator have?
也是吃过鱼 He had fish.
好，现在知道什么一回事了 All right, now we know what we're up against.
吃过鱼的人都十分不适 Every passenger who had fish for dinner will soon become violently ill.
-有多严重？ -极之严重 - Just how serious is it? - Extremely serious.
首先会些微发烧，喉咙干涸 lt starts with a slight fever, dryness of the throat.
当病毒进一步入侵 病人会觉得晕眩 When the virus penetrates, the victim becomes dizzy,
感到浑身痕痒 and begins to experience an itching rash.
跟着病毒会入侵中央神经系统 From there, the poison works on the central nervous system,
令肌肉严重抽筋 不能自控地流口水 causing severe muscle spasms, followed by the inevitable drooling.
这时消化系统会完全崩溃 At this point, the digestive system collapses,
肠胃气胀 accompanied by uncontrollable flatulence.
之后那病人会浑身乏力 有如一堆果冻 Until the poor bastard is reduced to a quivering, wasted piece of jelly.
（第11行至21行 第13行至51行）
开启…自动机师 Put it on... automatic pilot.
自动机师…在这里了！ Automatic pilot, automatic pilot... There it is!
我去看看乘客如何 l'll go back to the passengers.
209号班机，请回答 Come in, 209er, This is Chicago,
209号班机，请回答 Flight 209er, come in,
我是空中小姐狄绮莲 This is Elaine Dickinson, the stewardess.
欧机长昏倒了 副机师和导航员亦然 Captain Oveurs passed out. We've lost the co-pilot and navigator, too.
-我们有麻烦 -收到 - We're in trouble. - Roger,
我是芝加哥航空署的麦斯堤 l'm Steve McCroskey, Chicago air control,
我很快会跟你再联络 暂停所有航机起飞 l'll be back in a minute. Hold all takeoffs.
508会报时，立即接进来 When 508 reports, bring it straight in.
暂停由洛杉矶起程的 航机的三餐供应 Suspend all meal service on flights out of Los Angeles.
叫所有调度员留在岗位 Tell all dispatchers to remain at their posts.
-喝杯咖啡吗？ -不用了，谢谢 - How about coffee? - No, thanks.
我要所有可能降落地点的 天气报告 l want the weather on every available landing field.
懂吗？ You understand?
有没有可以降落的地方？ Any place available to land that plane!
往控制塔，找来跑道图 Go to the tower and get a runway diagram.
找来紧急事故器材 Check down the field for emergency equipment.
洛杉矶以东所有地方都有雾 Chief, we got fog every place east of the Rockies.
他们得来芝加哥降落 They'll have to come through to Chicago.
似乎我不该在这星期戒烟 Looks like l picked the wrong week to quit smoking.
找泰山崩于前而不动声色的人 Get the best available man who won't crack under pressure.
罗先生如何？ How about Mr Rogers?
找祈力斯来 Get me Rex Kramer.
在节流杆旁的便是速度计 Next to the throttle is the airspeed gauge,
现在是什么速度？ What speed does it indicate?
每小时520哩 520 miles per hour.
好，很好，现在查看高度 Good. Very good. Now, check your altitude.
即是速度计右下方的针盘 That's the dial below and right of the airspeed indicator.
三万五千英尺 35,000 feet.
不，慢着，三万四千英尺 No, wait. 34,000 feet.
不，不断下降，下降得很快 No. lt's dropping! lt's dropping fast!
为何这样？ Why is it doing that?
天啊！自动机师正在泄气 Oh, my God! The automatic pilot, it's deflating!
绮莲，别恐慌 Elaine, don't panic.
它的腰带有一支管 On his belt line there's a hollow tube.
是吹气孔，拔它出来吹气吧！ That's the manual inflation nozzle, Pull it out and blow on it,
究竟发生什么事？ What the hell's going on up there?
-绮莲 -是，医生 - Elaine. - Yes, Doctor.
你是这航机的一员 You're a member of this crew.
-能否接受可怕事实？ -不能 - Can you face some unpleasant facts? - No.
除非赶快送这些人往医院 Unless we hospitalise those people quickly,
否则我不知道能否救他们 l can't be sure of saving their lives.
机上有没有人可以令飞机降落 ls there anyone on board who can land this plane?
据我所知就没有 No one l know of.
该明白航机上 所有人的生死存亡 You ought to know our chances. Our lives depend on just one thing -
取决于可以找到一个懂驾飞机 又没有吃过鱼的人 finding someone to fly this plane who didn't have fish for dinner.
各位，我是空中小姐 Ladies and gentlemen, this is your stewardess speaking.
刚才机舱震动，对不起 We regret any inconvenience the sudden cabin movement caused.
这是因为遇上气流 This is due to periodic air pockets,
请别担心，好好享受旅程 There's no reason to become alarmed, We hope you enjoy your flight,
此外，有没有人懂驾驶飞机？ By the way, is there anyone on board who can fly a plane?
我是航空公司的贾保罗 是来接祈上尉的 Hello. l'm Paul Carey from the airline. l'm here to pick up Captain Kramer.
请进，力斯很快会出来 Yes. Come in, Paul. Rex will be right out.
羊羊，坐下！ Shep, sit. Sit!
我知道这是急事 l understand there's an emergency.
诸如此类，我也不大清楚 Something like that. There wasn't time to tell me very much...
羊羊，不要！ Shep, no!
你们经常遇上刺激的事吧 l'll bet exciting things happen all the time down there.
航空事业确有其精彩时刻 The airline business does have its moments.
稍后你自会适应 After a while, you get used to it.
羊羊，来！ Shep! Come!
有新访客来到，它就很兴奋 He gets so excited when new people are here.
-你是机师吗？ -不是，我… - Are you a pilot? - No, l'm in...
正接受训练 a training program.
难以置信 lt's unbelievable. lt's just unbelievable.
已警告过你多少遍要检查食物 How many times have l warned about food inspection?
还以为有人会听你说 You'd think someone would listen to you.
机场管理层、飞管局 和航空公司… Well, airport management, the FAA, and the airlines...
他们都是骗子 they're all cheats and liars.
好，走吧 All right. Let's get out of here.
抱歉，我想找懂驾驶飞机的人 l'm sorry, l was just looking for someone with flying experience.
他们筑路时，没考虑去水问题 When they built those roads, they didn't think about drainage,
故我们要乘特制吉普车往大路 so we had to take a special jeep up to the main road.
很幸运我们找来吉普车 We were lucky to get a jeep, since, just the day before,
之前一天 我们那辆吉普车坏了 the only one we had broke down. lt had a bad axle...
先生，驾驶舱有些问题 Excuse me, sir. There's a problem in the cockpit.
驾驶舱？什么？ The cockpit? What is it?
即机师坐的小房子，算了 The little room where the pilot sits. That's not important.
副机师病倒了 机长想找人帮忙 The first officer is ill. The captain needs someone to help him with the radio.
你对飞机有认识吗？ Do you know anything about planes?
多年前我在战时驾驶战机 l flew in the war years ago.
-我不懂得驾驶飞机 -可否跟我来？拜托 - l wouldn't know anything about it. - Would you go up, please?
那空姐说… The stewardess said...
-两名机师？ -你能否令这飞机降落？ - Both pilots? - Can you fly this plane and land it?
-你说笑吧？ -我是认真的，请别推辞 - Surely, you can't be serious. - l am serious, and don't call me Shirley.
医生，我问过所有人 只有史先生合适 Doctor, l've checked everyone. Mr Strikers the only one.
-你有什么飞行经验？ -我驾驶过单引擎战机 - What's your flying experience? - l flew single-engine fighters.
这飞机有四个引擎 是截然不同的飞行经验 This plane has four engines. lt's an entirely different kind of flying.
是截然不同的飞行经验 lt's an entirely different kind of flying.
我已有六年没接触任何飞机 l haven't touched any kind of plane in six years.
史先生，我并不懂得驾驶飞机 Mr Striker, l know nothing about flying.
但我知道你是飞机上 唯一可能驾驶它的人 But l do know that you're the only one on this plane who can possibly fly it.
你是我们唯一的希望 You're the only chance we've got.
对，我也这样说 That's right. That's what l said. You heard me.
叫奥马哈准备 Tell Omaha to acknowledge and stand by.
找来一切应急工具 Every piece of emergency equipment you can reach.
通知由这里至洛矶山的 所有拯救单位 Alert every rescue unit from here to the Rockies.
首领！ Chief!
-我们要检查自动降落航机 -是你的太太 - We'll need a free-landing flight check. - lt's your wife.
我要孩子九时上床、喂好狗儿 替院子洒水、锁上大闸 l want the kids in bed by nine, the dog fed, the yard watered, the gate locked.
给送牛奶人便条，不再要芝士 Get a note to the milkman - ''No more cheese.''
祈力斯呢？ Where the hell is Kramer?
不，他做不来，起火机会太大 No, he can't do that. The risk of a flame-out's too great.
要他保持在二万四千英尺高 Keep him at 24,000... No, feet.
一名乘客打算令航机降落 A passenger is going to land that plane.
-有可能吗？ -机会微乎其微 - ls that possible? - lt's a hundred to one shot.
-我认识这人 -真的？他是何方神圣？ - l know this guy. - You do? Who is it?
史泰德，我在战时曾与他合作 但他越帮越忙 Ted Striker. l flew with him during the war. lt won't make my job easier.
史泰德是个不济飞行小组队长 Ted Striker was a crack flight leader, up to a point.
他是那种…太感性的人 He was one of those men who... felt too much inside.
或许你也认识那种人 Maybe you know that kind.
有一次任务，他一败涂地 He went all to pieces on a particular mission.
希望今晚不会这样 Let's just hope that doesn't happen tonight.
让我看看…高度，二万四千英尺 Let's see... Altitude, 24,000 feet.
保持这高度，速度520哩 Level flight. Speed, 520 knots.
航道090 Course Zero Niner Zero.
切条、搅均 洗净、冲水、摇干 Trim, mixture. Wash, soap, rinse, spin.
泰德，你在此做什么？ 你不能驾驶这飞机！ Ted! What are you doing here? You can't fly this plane!
我正努力告诉他们这一点 That's what l'm trying to tell them.
绮莲，我没时间转弯抹角 得直接对你说 Elaine. l don't have time to be gentle, so l'll be very direct.
大家的情况都很危险 Everyone is in a desperate situation.
史先生是我们唯一的希望 Mr Striker is the only hope we got.
那些是襟翼，这是推力 Those are the flaps. This is the thrust.
这会亮起降落灯 This must turn on the landing lights.
（返回座位）
-救命！… -五月？怎么了？ - Mayday! Mayday! - Mayday?. What the hell is that?
五月是俄罗斯的新年 我们有大巡游 May Day's the Russian new year. We'll have a big parade and serve...
我不能再忍受了 l can't stand it any more.
我要出去！ l've got to get out of here!
-冷静！控制自己 -让我来吧 - Calm down! Get ahold of yourself! - Please let me handle this.
冷静，返回座位，我会处理 Calm down. Get back to your seat. l'll take care of this.
冷静，控制自己 Calm down. Get ahold of yourself.
医生，有人找你 Doctor, you're wanted on the phone.
-一切会没事的 -修女，让我来 - Everything will be all right. - Sister, l can handle this.
走开！ Got to get out of here!
我们想你收下这朵花 We'd like you to have this flower.
先生，你可否… Excuse me, sir, would you...
向蒙牧师捐献？ Donations for Reverend Moon?
犹太耶稣？ Jews for Jesus?
耶和华证人？ Read about Jehovah's Witnesses?
佛教又如何？ How about Buddhism?
救救谢利的孩子？ Help Jerry's kids?
-科学教派？ -为核能？ - Scientology?. - For nuclear power?
（自助行李提取）
各位注意，乘客正在抵达 Your attention, please, No-frills passengers now arriving,
请在离开机场前 Please have your baggage claim checks ready to show
提取及检查行李 upon leaving the terminal,
他没有驾驶航机经验 This guy has no airline experience.
他在空中对一切构成危险 包括雀鸟在内 He's a menace to everything in the air. Yes, birds, too.
他是一大危机 但我们别无他选 OK, he's a terrible risk, but what other choice have we got?
我们所知的就这么多 That's the whole story, Rex. Everything we know.
告诉你，我曾在战时与史合作 Let's face a few facts. l flew with Striker during the war.
当事情不顺利，他就方英寸大乱 He can't afford to worry about those times when... things weren't so good.
-现在事情亦不顺利 -让我告诉你 - Right now things aren't so good. - Let me tell you something.
史泰德很久之前 是空军部队队长 Striker was a top-notch squadron leader long ago.
去说服他吧！ Get on the horn and talk that guy down.
让他有信心驾驶飞机 Let him get the feel of that airplane,
然后令他安全着陆吧！ then you'll have to talk him right down to the ground.
-好，联络史泰德吧！ -用我的无线电 - Very well. Put Striker on the speaker. - Use my radio.
我不该选这星期戒酒 l picked the wrong week to quit drinking.
上尉，你由此直接跟他们说吧 You can work them direct from here, Captain.
史泰德，我是祈力斯上尉 Striker? Striker, this is Captain Rex Kramer speaking.
我听到，祈上尉 Yes, Captain Kramer. Read you loud and clear.
很好，你仍记得我 All right. lt's obvious you remember me.
不如我们忘记一切，放眼现在 What do you say we forget about everything, except what we must do?
少来这套了 Let's not kid each other, Kramer.
你也知我从没驾驶过这种飞机 一切唯有靠运气 You know l've never flown a bucket like this. l'll need all the luck there is.
准备好，史泰德 Stand by, Striker.
我们要令他有自信 觉得自己可以胜任 Our one hope is to build this man up. l've got to give him confidence.
-驾驶过多引擎飞机吗？ -从来没有 - You ever flown a multi-engine plane? - No, never,
岂有此理！这简直浪费时间 Shit! lt's a goddamn waste of time.
-他没可能令飞机降落 -你得说服他！ - There's no way he can land it! - You got to talk him down!
叫他飞往密芝根 这样不会连累无辜 Route him into Lake Michigan, At least avoid killing innocent people,
你是他们唯一的希望 You're the only chance they've got.
好吧 All right.
史，你好好听着 Striker, you listen, and you listen close.
驾驶飞机就像骑单车一样 Flying a plane is like riding a bicycle.
只不过是较复杂一些 你得掌握个中窍门 lt'sjust harder to put baseball cards in the spokes, Get the feel of the plane,
稍后我们会教你着陆程序 Later, we'll run down the landing procedure.
好，先拆去自动机师 All right. Disengage the automatic pilot.
就像你驾驶战机时般 别令飞机强烈摆动 Make no violent control movements like you did in the fighter planes.
好，我会放走自动机师 All right. l'll unlock the automatic pilot.
操纵杆会比战机的重 The controls will feel very heavy compared to a fighter,
别担心，这是正常的 Don't worry about that, lt's perfectly normal,
有一件事 Now, one more thing,
可否找人来负责无线电通讯？ Can somebody work the radio and leave you free for flying?
-空姐就在我旁 -她可以坐到副机师位置 - The stewardess is here with me. - Have her sit in the co-pilot seat,
绮莲，他想你坐到副机师座位 Elaine, he wants you to sit in the co-pilot seat.
发生什么事？我们有权知道 What's going on? We have a right to know the truth.
好，我会向你们坦白 All right, l'll level with you all.
最重要是保持冷静 The most important thing is that you remain calm.
绝对不用惊慌 There's no reason to panic.
我们确有一名机员病倒 lt's true one of the crew members is ill.
有些少不舒服 Slightly ill.
但另外两名机师没事 The other two pilots are fine.
他们正在驾驶飞机，全力以赴 They're flying the plane, free to pursue a life of religious fulfilment.
你来负责无线电通讯 留意第三号引擎表板 The radio is all yours. Keep an eye on number three engine gauge.
有点热 lt's running a little hot.
（有点热）
史，首先我要说… Striker, first l'd like to say something,
我知道现在你那处一定一团糟 l know things must look pretty rough up there.
但若你一切都依我的 lf you do what l tell you when l tell you,
你不该没有自信 there's no reason you should lack confidence
你绝对做得到的 in your chances of coming out alive and in one piece,
天气如何？ What weather are you in?
-有雨 -还有些冰雹 - Rain. - And a little ice.
还有些冰雹 And a little ice.
-情况怎样？ -不大好，湿透了 - How's it handling? - Sluggish. Like a wet sponge.
不大好，湿透了 Sluggish. Like a wet sponge.
史泰德，你做得很好 All right, Striker. You're doing just fine.
幸好他不知道我很讨厌他 lt's damn good he doesn't know l hate his guts.
幸好你不知道我很讨厌你 lt's damn good you don't know he hates your guts.
有什么可以帮忙？ Can l get you something?
抱歉，我不明白 l'm sorry. l don't understand.
-小姐，我懂说非洲话 -好极了 - Stewardess. l speak jive. - Good.
他说很痛苦，想你帮助他 He said he's in great pain, and he wants to know if you can help him?
叫他放松，我拿药来 Tell him to relax. l'll be back with some medicine.
放松，她会拿药来 Just hang loose, blood. She'll get some medicine.
我并非省油的灯 My Mama didn't raise no dummies, that's obvious.
别说废话了 Cut me some slack, Jack.
他不想帮忙… Chump don't want no help, chump don't get the help.
那厮是没有脑袋的 That dude's got no brains, anyhow.
通知欧机长的太太吧！ Let Captain Oveurs wife know what's going on.
刚收到最新的天气报告 This weather bulletin just came off the wire.
-你认为怎样？ -这个？ - What can you make out of this? - This?
我可以用来做帽子 胸针或无尾飞机… l can make a hat or a brooch or pterodactyl...
-你好 -欧太太？ - Hello? - Mrs Oveur?
对，我是 Yes, this is Mrs Oveur.
我是机场的马艾迪 你丈夫的航机遇上麻烦 This is Ed Macias at the airport, There's trouble on your husband's flight,
我们并不知道情况有多严重 We don't know how serious it is,
但麦斯堤认为你最好来这里 but Steve McCroskey thought you'd want to come over,
好，我立即来 Yes. l'll be right down.
我得往机场，你由后门走吧 l've got to go to the airport. You can let yourself out the back door.
冰箱里有果汁 There's juice in the refrigerator.
医生说病人情况转坏 我们时间无多了 Doctor says the sick people are getting worse. We're running out of time.
我得集中精神 l've got to concentrate,
有人吗？ Hello?
回音！ Echo!
拳打柏度 Pinch hitting for Pedro Bourbone,
脚踢文尼 Manny Mota,
-老婆，怎么了？ -我很热，像被火烧 - How you doing, honey?. - Jack, l'm so hot, l'm burning up.
我开窗吧 l'll turn on some air.
-发生什么事？ -关窗！ - What's going on? - Close the window!
乘客开始恐慌 何时可以降落？ Chicago, the passengers are panicking. When do we start down?
还未可以 你该快进入雷达范围了 Not yet. You'll be in radar range any second now.
他们该在十分钟前已进入范围 They should have been in range 10 minutes ago.
古达臣，再查看雷达 有何发现？ Gunderson, check the radar range. Anything yet?
尚要两分钟 About two more minutes, chief.
-他们可能偏离了航道 -没可能！是自动导航！ - They could be miles off course. - lmpossible! They're on instruments.
今次一定很惊险 This is going to be a real sweat.
古达臣，有最新消息就通知我 Gunderson, let me know when you get anything.
-尼斯，有香烟吗？ -我再也受不了 - Got a cigarette, Nels? - l can't take much more of this.
似乎我选错这星期戒安非他命 Looks like l picked the wrong week to quit amphetamines.
-喝点咖啡吗？ -不用，谢谢 - How about some more coffee? - No, thanks.
这些记者想你发表声明 These reporters want a statement.
-他们能支持多久？ -三十到四十五分钟 - How much longer can they hold out? - 30, 45 minutes.
-由谁来驾驶飞机？ -一名乘客 - Who's flying the plane? - A passenger.
他是一名富经验的空军机师 不用担心，你来吧 He's an experienced air-force pilot. No cause for alarm. Take over.
-是怎样的飞机？ -又大又漂亮的白色飞机 - What kind of plane? - lt's a big, pretty white plane
有红色条子、窗帘、轮子 就像一架大模型 with red stripes, curtains and wheels. lt looks like a big Tylenol.
好，拿些照片吧！ OK, boys. Let's get some pictures.
（航机乘客大难临头）
（芝加哥机长作出最坏打算）
（男孩被困在冰箱 吃掉自己的脚）
（危机）
最新消息，那航机飞往芝加哥 This bulletinjust handed to me, Stricken airliner approaching Chicago,
他们自作自受 Shana, they bought their tickets.
他们早知道有危险 They knew what they were getting into.
让航机坠毁吧 l say, let them crash!
-要威士忌吗？ -不要 - Would you like some whisky, ma'am? - Certainly not!
乘客怎么样？ How are the passengers?
我不会骗你，我们时间无多了 l won't deceive you, Mr Striker. We're running out of time.
-你一定可以做什么的 -我已尽一切办法… - Surely, there's something you can do. - l'm doing everything l can...
也不要再说我有办法 and stop calling me Shirley.
兰迪，你没事吧？ Randy, are you all right?
雷医生 Oh, Dr Rumack.
我很害怕，从没这般害怕 l'm scared. l've never been so scared...
而且我26岁了，还未结婚 And besides, l'm 26 and l'm not married.
我们定会成功的，你定要相信 We're going to make it. You've got to believe that.
雷医生，知否我们何时着陆？ Dr Rumack, do you have any idea when we'll be landing?
快了，你觉得怎样？ Pretty soon. How are you bearing up?
坦白说，我从来没那么惊慌过 To be honest, l've never been so scared,
但幸好我有丈夫 but at least l have a husband.
保持队形，目标就在前面 Stay in formation, Target'sjust ahead,
若飞得够低，该能看清楚目标 Target should be clear if you go in low enough,
你得决定… You'll have to decide, You'll have to decide,
你得决定 You'll have to decide,
保持队形，目标就在前面 Stay in formation, Target'sjust ahead,
若飞得够低，该看清楚目标 Target should be clear if you go in low enough,
你得决定… You'll have to decide, You'll have to decide,
你得决定 You'll have to decide,
糟糕！四号引擎没有了 Oh, rats! Lost number four.
发生什么事？有何不妥？ What happened? What went wrong?
我忘了检查油压 l forgot to check the oil pressure.
若给祈力斯知道，定给他臭骂 When Kramer hears about this, the shit's going to hit the fan.
早叫他检查油压，他怎么了？ l told him to watch that oil temperature. What's he doing?
史泰德，飞机无法自行降落 Stiker, that plane can't land itself.
这不是他的错 任何机师都可能会这样 Ease off. lt's not his fault. lt could happen to any pilot.
施丹域亦出现这情形 lt happened to Barbara Stanwyck.
别逼得他太紧，他可能会崩溃 Can't push him too hard. Might break. Remember who you're dealing with.
尼克、彼得、谢利，紧急状态 Nick, Pete, Jerry, there's a fire in the barn.
他说得对，我应付不了压力 He's right. l can't take the pressure.
我以为可以令飞机降落 实在妄想 l was crazy to think l could land this plane.
-泰德，只有你… -我不管，我没有这个能力 - But, Ted, you're the only... - l don't care. l don't have what it takes.
找过从没驾驶过飞机的人来 结果可能更好 They'd be better off with someone who's never flown before.
坏消息，雾越来越浓 Bad news. Fog's getting thicker.
李安亦越来越大 And Leon's getting larger.
我知道你想说什么，省口气吧 l know what you're going to say, so save your breath.
我并没想要说什么 Well, l don't have a thing to say.
你已尽了力 You've done the best you could.
真的，你已尽了力 You really have. The best you could.
凡事岂能尽如人意 We can't expect to win them all.
告诉你我保守了多年的秘密 l want to tell you something l've kept to myself through these years.
我在战时是军医 l was in the war. Medical corps.
有一晚他们送来一名重伤机师 One night, they brought in a badly wounded pilot from a raid.
他几乎不能说话 He could barely talk.
但他望着我说 He looked up at me, he said,
“我们形势不利 但还是勇往直前” '"The odds were against us up there, but we went in anyway.
“我很高兴 上尉作出正确决定” ''l'm glad. Captain made the right decision.''
那机师的名字叫做薛佐治 The pilot's name was George Zip.
薛佐治说的？ George Zip said that?
他最后对我说： “医生…” The last thing he said to me, ''Doc,'' he said, ''Sometime...
“队员都全力以赴” ''..the crew is up against it.
“我们虽然受到挫折” '"The breaks are beating the boys.
“但告诉他们要倾尽全力” '"Tell them to give it all they've got
“为部队胜出一仗” ''and win just one for the Zipper.
“到时我不知道 自己会身在何处” ''l don't know where l'll be then,'' he said...
“但肯定已全身发臭” ''but l won't smell too good, that's for sure.''
医生，失陪 Excuse me, Doc.
我要令飞机着陆 l've got a plane to land.
留在上空，待大雾消散才降落 You'd better stay up there a bit, When the fog lifts, we'll bring you in,
绮莲，让我来 l'll take it, Elaine.
听着，雷医生说病人情况危殆 Listen, Dr Rumack says the sick people are in critical condition.
每分每秒都很重要 要现在降落了 Every minute counts. We've got to land now.
别傻了 你也知道这样降落结果会如何 Don't be a fool, Striker. You know what a landing like this means.
我命令你继续在上空 l'm ordering you to stay up there!
不行 No dice, Chicago.
现在由我话事，我们要降落了 l'm giving the orders, and we're coming in.
现在他反客为主了 l guess the foot's on the other hand now.
这样大雾，他是不会成功的 He'll never make it in this soup.
但现在由他话事了 But it's his ship now. He's in charge.
他是老板、上头、首领… He's the boss, head man, top dog,
-领袖、老大… -上尉，看！ - big cheese, head honcho... - Captain, look at this!
“乘客必死无疑” ''Passengers certain to die.''
“航空当局疏忽” ''Airline negligent.''
百货公司大减价！ There's a sale at Penny's!
我要三人往控制塔 黎保家、马卡斯 l'll need three men up in the tower. You, Neubauer, you, Macias.
还有我， “大树”约翰 Me John. Big tree.
史，我们准备往控制塔 祝你好运 Striker, we're going to the tower. Good luck.
-我们准备往控制塔 -控制塔 - We're going to the tower. - The tower! The tower!
林宝素… Rapunzel! Rapunzel!
小姐，尚有多久才降落？ Stewardess, how soon till we land?
快了，别担心 lt won't be long now. Try not to worry.
我们准备好了 麦机长，这是罗机长 We're all ready, sir. Captain McCroskey, this is Captain Roberts.
祈上尉、高机长 韩机长、简机长 Captain Kramer, Captain Colosimo. Captain Hinshaw, Captain Gantz.
祈上尉、简机长 韩机长、罗机长 Captain Kramer, Captain Gantz. Captain Hinshaw, Captain Roberts.
高，你负责联络 Colosimo, you work the relay.
罗，看看航空交通 Roberts, check air traffic.
拿出手指来，很脏的 Get that finger out of your ear. You don't know where it's been.
-史堤 -尼斯，有香烟吗？ - Steve! - Got a cigarette, Nels?
莲黛，你的丈夫 和其他人仍活着，但昏迷了 Linda, your husband and the others are alive but unconscious.
就像福特 Just like Gerald Ford.
若史及时降落 我们便有机会救他们 There's a chance we can save them if Striker lands that plane in time.
-但机会不大吧？ -不知道 - That isn't much of a chance, is it? - l don't know.
我们已尽了力，失陪 We're doing everything we can. Now excuse me.
你从哪儿买来这裙子？很难看 Where did you get that dress? lt's awful!
还有这对鞋和大衣，天啊！ And those shoes and that coat! Geez!
八哩，转右往044 8 miles. Turn right to heading 044.
我们现在于二千英尺上空 开始降落 We're now at 2,000 feet beginning our descent,
-把跑道所有灯亮起 -已经这样做了 - Pour every light onto that field. - lt's being done.
控制塔呼叫所有救急汽车 前往九号跑道 Tower to all emergency vehicles, runway is niner.
机场汽车，一、二号准备 Airport vehicles, take positions one and two,
平民器材，三号 Civilian equipment, number three.
空军，四、五号 Air force, positions four and five,
所有救护车往三号站 All ambulances go to number three,
以色列航机，请驶离跑道 Air lsrael, please clear the runway,
我们将要你们摆出撞击姿势 ln a moment, we'll ask you to assume crash positions.
椅子下面有救生衣 Life jackets are under your seat.
套上去，我一声令下 就拉右面的绳子 Place it over your head. When l give the word, pull the cord on the right side flap.
你们的椅垫都有浮水设计 Your seat cushions are also equipped with a flotation device.
芝加哥的WAZA电台 永远为你播放 WZAZ in Chicago, where disco lives forever,
你的飞行高度忽高忽低 Your altitude's too erratic.
不能降落 你尚有两小时的燃料 You can't come straight in. You've got enough fuel for two hours.
绮莲，让我来…祈，你听着 l'll take it, Elaine. Listen to me, Kramer.
机上有人在不足一小时后 就会死去 We have people up here who will die in less than an hour.
我或会令飞机损毁 但我可以成功降落的 l may bend your airplane, but l'll get it down.
我要放下降落架了 l'm putting the landing gear down.
-乘客都准备好了 -劳驾 - The passengers are ready. - Thanks, Randy.
你还是出去吧！ 在这儿你可能会受伤 You better leave, sweetheart. You might get hurt up here.
-泰德 -什么事？ - Ted... - Yes?
我想你知道…现在… l wanted you to know... now...
我以你为傲 l'm very proud.
告诉他们降落架已放下 我们准备降落 Tell them the gear is down and we're ready to land.
降落架已放下，我们准备降落 The gear is down, and we're ready to land.
好，已进入最后阶段 只亮起九号跑道的灯 All right. He's on final now. Put out all runway lights except niner.
上尉，我们或许该亮起搜索灯 Captain, maybe we ought to turn on the searchlights now.
不 No.
他们就是以为我们会这样做 That's just what they'll be expecting us to do.
祝你们好运，我们全看你们了 l want to tell you both good luck. We're all counting on you.
小心听着，在三百英尺高度 你便会见到跑道 Now listen carefully. You'll see the runway at 300 feet.
在跑道三分一位置时着陆 有微风，准备好 Aim to touch down a third of the way. A slight cross wind, so be ready.
若着陆得太快，用紧急煞掣 即右前方的红色手掣 lf you land too fast, use your emergency brakes. Red handle's right in front.
若这样还不停下 lf that doesn't stop you...
就熄掉四个引擎 lf that doesn't stop you, cut the four ignition switches.
看到我们没有？ 你该看到机场了 Can you see us now?. You should be able to see the field.
-外面很平静 -对，太平静了 - Sure is quiet out there. - Yeah, too quiet.
似乎我选错了这星期戒闻胶水 Looks like l picked the wrong week to quit sniffing glue.
它来了！ There it is.
他来了！ There he is!
-速度太快了 -我知道… - You're coming in too fast. - l know, l know!
他知道… He knows, he knows!
现在低于七百英尺，仍在下降 Below 700 now. Still going down.
675英尺、650英尺、625英尺 稳住了，不，正下降 675, 650, 625, he's holding. No, he's down, he's down.
发出警号吧 Sound your alarm now.
大家请准备撞机 Now, everybody, get in crash positions.
风门翼要三十度 Put down 30 degrees of flap.
听着，煞掣，按钮，准备 Listen to me. Remember your brakes and switches. Get ready to flare it out!
他一时在九百英尺 一时在一千三百英尺，真是笨蛋 He's all over the place. 900 up to 1 ,300 feet. What an asshole.
靠左，风门翼更加偏侧 More left rudder, Put down more flap,
开玩笑而已 Just kidding!
史，升起机头，伸直机翼 Striker, lift your nose, Straighten your wings,
太快了，留意速度 Coming in too fast. Watch your speed.
他向我们冲来！ He's coming right at us!
太快了，减慢速度 Coming in too hot. Ease up on the throttle.
留意风向，左翼倾侧 Watch out for that cross wind, Level it out, Dip your left wing,
你偏离了航道，望着跑道末端 You're drifting, Keep your eyes on the far end of the runway,
太低了，糟糕！ You're too low, damn it!
留意速度 Watch your stall speed,
慢慢降落！ Flare it out!
慢慢让它着陆，着陆吧！ Ease her down. Down!
煞掣！拉那红色手掣！ The brake! Pull the red handle!
祝你俩好运，我们全看你们了 l want to tell you both good luck. We're all counting on you.
209号班机正抵达八号闸 Flight 209 now arriving at gate eight,
九号闸 Gate nine,
十号闸 Gate ten,
拉！按钮！ Pull out of it! Push that button!
十三号闸，十四号闸 Gate 13,,, Gate 1 4,
十五号闸 Gate 15,,,
天啊！它在旋转！ Auntie Em! Toto! lt's a twister!
23号闸，24号闸，25号闸… Gate 23, 24, 25,,,
祝你俩好运，我们全看你们了 l want to tell you both good luck. We're all counting on you.
史泰德？ Striker?
-史泰德，你没事吧？ -我们没事 - Striker, are you all right? - Yeah. We're OK.
这大概是本机场最拙劣的降落 That was probably the lousiest landing in the history of this airport.
但我们有好些人，特别是我 But some of us, particularly me,
想请你喝东西和与你握手 would like to buy you a drink and shake your hand,
泰德，当遇上困难… And, Ted, when the going got rough,,,
祝你愉快 Have a nice day. OK.
祝你愉快，多谢乘搭本班航机 Have a nice day and thank you for flying TransAmerican.
寂寞是底线，儿时我从不快乐 Loneliness, that's the bottom line, l was never happy as a child,
圣诞对你有何意义？ 对我来说则是活受罪 Christmas, what does that mean to you? Mine was a living hell,
你知否掉在泥泞上 被铁靴踢头… Do you know what it's like to fall in the mud and get kicked in the head
那滋味是怎样的？ by an iron boot?
当然不知道，因从没发生 抱歉，这条问题真笨 Of course not. lt never happens. Sorry. That's a dumb question. Skip that.
祝你愉快 There you go. Have a nice day.
泰德，你实在很出色 Municipal bonds, Ted. l'm talking double ''A'' rating.
是美国最佳的投资 Best investment in America.
完
我只会再给他二十分钟 Well, l'll give him another 20 minutes, but that's it.
Cantonese ENGLlSH