You're always
Sick!
You were sick
when you were my age?
Evening, sir.
Evening, Victor.
I didn't realize that you're still here.
I'm just keeping James company, sir.
If that's all right...
Very kind of you.
- Are you better, son?
- Still cold, father.
It's just a mild fever.
You'll be all right in the morning.
- You always say that.
- And you always pull through, don't you?
Now... take your medicine.
Elizabeth!
Your father's drunk again.
You should help him home, Victor.
It's not my name he's calling, sir.
- Father!
- Stay where you are, James!
Father!
I told you never to come back here!
James...
There are things you
don't understand.
- Don't...
- I need him them to know!
Please no!
- No...more...lies!
James...
James!
He...he wasn't your father...
...son.
What are you?
- I didn't mean it! I didn't--
- Yes, you did!
He deserved it!
And you gave it to him.
We're brothers, Jimmy.
You realize that?
Brothers protect each other.
You have to be hard now.
Hard enough they can't ever touch us.
I want to go home.
We can't. We stick together
no matter what
and take care of anyone
who gets in our way.
Can you do that, little brother?
They're coming.
Can you run? Okay.
Keep on running.
Don't look back.
Back-to-back!
Enough! Enough!
Stand down, soldier!
Stand down!
Victor, no!
Ready!
Aim!
Wake me when it's over.
Fire!
My name is Major William Stryker.
You were sentenced to death
for decapitating a senior officer.
Is that correct?
Apparently we have some
issues with authority.
Just keep a lid on it.
Sir.
The warden tells me that your sentence
was carried out
by a firing squad at 1000 hours
- How'd that go?
- It tickled.
You boys tired of running?
Tired of denying your...true nature?
- What do you care?
- Oh, I care...
I care cause I know
how special you are,
how valuable.
Look.
You can stay here, locked up
like freaks of nature,
or you can join me.
I'm putting together a special team
with special privileges.
Now tell me. How would you like
to really serve your country?
I love this weapon more than anything
in the whole wide world.
- You wanna know why?
- No.
It's memorable.
Sure, it's a little bulky,
to have to get 'em on a plane.
You whip out a couple of swords
at your ex-girlfriend's wedding,
they will never, ever forget it.
That's funny, Wade.
I didn't think you liked girls.
Right, it is...it's probably not
as intimidating as having a gun or
bone claws or the fingernails
of a bag lady...
- Manicure?
- Victor...easy.
Speaking of sharp,
Fred got a new tattoo.
- I'm concerned.
- Oh geez, Fred, you just met her last night.
- I love her.
- You love her after one night?
She's a gymnast.
Bradley, take her down.
Are you gonna puke?
If we were meant to fly,
we'd have grown wings.
Oh, don't worry man. See, more people
die driving than flying.
How about from impaling?
Hey, be nice.
Or your approximation of nice.
Would you like a bucket?
Gentlemen, wheels down
in Lagos in five.
- Why are we here?
- All in good time. Zero...
- Victor, high ground lookout.
- Having fun yet?
- Fred...
- Tank?
- Tank.
- Yeah, I got that.
Great!
Stuck in an elevator with five guys
on a high protein diet.
- Oh Wade!
- Dreams really do come true.
Would you just shut it!
You're up next.
Thank you, sir.
You look very nice today.
It's the green.
Brings out the seriousness in your eyes.
- Oh my God, do you ever shut up, pal?
- No. Not when I'm awake.
Bradley? Top floor, please.
Cover the elevator!
The elevator!
Time to go to work.
Okay!
People are dead!
If you haven't that mouth on you, Wade,
you'd be the perfect soldier.
Take the diamonds, they're yours.
I don't want your diamonds.
I want this.
That? That is nothing. A souvenir.
Where did you find it?
I want the source.
A small village, far inland,
three days from here.
Tell him that this rock is more valuable
to me than his life.
Ask him where he found it.
He says it came from the sky.
He's telling the truth.
- You don't know their language, Logan.
- It's a meteor fragment.
I know what it is.
I'm asking him where he found it.
Sir, base wants to know our location.
Shut him down.
Tell him everyone here will die unless
he tells me where he found the rock.
- He said that is sacred.
- Okay, fine.
Victor...
Victor!
Don't even think about it!
We didn't sign up for this.
Put him down.
What are you doing?
We finally got a good thing going here.
Don't you screw this up.
- Enough, it's enough. We've done enough.
- Who do you think you are?
This is what we do.
Maybe you'd rather be rotting
in a hole somewhere
till they figure out a way
to do it to us, is that it?
Uh?
I'm done.
You coming?
Jimmy!
We can't just let you walk away!
Why are you up so early?
Come here.
See you baby.
Oh, that's nice! Yeah!
No. Come on.
Hey, what do you do?
You turn off the light, you win a prize.
- Two tries for a buck.
- Come on, I wanna do it!
Um, that's obvious.
That's two.
- That's a stupid trick.
- It's not a trick, man.
C'mon.
Bye!
Show's over!
I said, show's over!
The show is never over for us, Bradley.
- Victor.
- Aren't you gonna invite me in?
Yeah, come on in.
You know, I've never said anything
to anyone...about what happened.
I'm living a totally different life now,
but uh...
No need to bring up the past.
You know,
I always thought it would be Wade
coming knocking at my door.
Well, Wade's gone.
I'm not afraid of you, Victor.
I'm not afraid to die.
How do you know?
You've never tried it before.
Was it the wars?
- Which one?
- All of 'em.
Tell me.
It's just a scratch.
Looks like we're gonna need
new sheets again, baby.
Yeah...
Who the hell is this?
It smells like government.
My God!
Haven't aged a day!
Clean living.
You remember Agent Zero.
Still shooting first and
asking questions later?
You still chewing those cheap cigars?
Boys, please.
I have a job for you.
- I already have a job.
- Lumberjack.
- Eighteen grand a year?
- Eighteen five.
Plus I haven't had
to kill anyone in a while.
- Start to miss it?
- Yeah, right now I am.
Zero, back to the car.
Attaboy.
You know, I'm not proud about the way
things ended between us.
Conversation's over.
Play the little house on the prairie
with a...a school teacher.
That's just isn't you, Logan.
And you would know, huh?
I would.
What do you want, Stryker?
Bradley was killed three days ago.
Wade, before that.
I believe that someone is
hunting down our whole team.
Anyone else?
As far as I know,
Victor is safe.
- Whoever it is, he's had names, addresses...
- I can take care of myself.
This is not about you, Logan.
Country needs you.
I am Canadian.
I know you, Logan!
I know who you are!
What's wrong?
Stryker came by today.
Don't worry, I said no.
Why is he bothering you
after all these years?
Because I'm the best
there is at what I do.
And what I do best
isn't very nice.
You're not an animal, Logan.
What you have is a gift.
A gift? You can return a gift.
Come on, fellas!
- Stay in the car.
- I'm just gonna ask nicely.
Mind lettin' us go by?
You're in some kind of
a hurry there, pal?
Are ya?
- Just move your truck so we can go by...
- Trying to have a conversation there, right!
If you start something,
you'd better be ready to finish it.
Hey guys, take it easy!
- Your boyfriend's got a big mouth.
- I know.
Big temper too,
so please, let us pass.
Thank you!
How did you do that?
You know, power of persuasion is a gift.
I see...
Do you, uh, have those powers over me?
Well, you didn't stay in the car, did you?
Why is the moon so lonely?
Why?
Because she used to have a lover.
- You tell this to the kids?
- No.
His name was Kuekuatsheu and they lived
in the spirit world together.
Ah, it's a true story.
Right.
And every night,
they would wander the skies together.
But...one of the other spirits
was jealous.
Trickster, one of the moons from South,
so he told Kuekuatsheu
that the moon had asked for flowers.
He told him to come to our world
and pick up some wild roses,
But Kuekuatsheu didn't know
that once you leave the spirit world,
you can never go back.
And every night, he looks up in the sky
and sees the moon and howls her name.
But...
...he can never touch her again.
Koo-koo-Kachooka got screwed.
Kuekuatsheu.
Means the Wolverine.
What you're doing, Logan?
Kayla!
You're not from around here, are you?
What gave me away?
- You got an insurance in this place?
- Insurance?
No.
Too bad.
Well, well, well...
Look what the cat dragged in.
Guys, whatever this is,
take it outside.
- Why?
You don't call,
you don't write.
How else am I supposed to get your attention?
I hate to say it, James,
but, frankly, I'm a little disappointed.
Stay down.
Tell me some, Jimmy, was she worth it?
When are you gonna figure it out?
we are not like them.
- I...am nothing like you.
- Sure you are. You just don't know it yet.
- What do we got?
- Bar fight. Multiple knife wounds.
What? Is this a joke?
The guy's fine.
Where is he?
I said where is he!
I don't know who he is.
I can help you.
Six years I've been here. No one
knew me and then you show up!
- And the next day, she's dead!
- I tried to warn you.
- Why don't you tell me it was Victor?
- I didn't know!
I swear on my son's life! I didn't...
Victor's appetites were
becoming too public.
I had to lock him up.
He thought I'd betrayed him.
Went AWOL.
He said he was coming after all of us.
You didn't come to warn me.
You came to save your own ass.
So what's your plan, captain?
You can't beat him, Logan,
you know you can't.
I'm gonna find him and kill him.
I can give you the tools to defeat him.
- So we can still save the others.
- You mean save yourself, right?
I promise you two things:
You'll suffer more pain than
any other man can endure,
but you'll have your revenge.
If I come with you, I'm coming for blood.
No law, no code of conduct.
You point me in the right direction
and you get the hell out of my way.
When it starts,
whatever the reason is
that you're doing this,
focus on that. Maybe it will help.
Trust me, I've been through worse.
No you haven't.
We are ready.
We're gonna make you indestructible,
but first, we're gonna have to destroy you.
Remember what we were
looking for in Africa?
I remember.
Well, I found it.
It helped us create a...
metal compound so strong
that you will be able to
withstand virtually anything.
It's called Adamantium.
I can't put Victor down myself, Logan.
To kill him, you're gonna have to
embrace the other side,
become the animal.
Let's do this.
I almost forgot.
I want new ones.
What do you want them to say?
Wolverine.
Generals! Welcome.
General Munson.
Today, we're gonna witness
medical history.
- Today, we're gonna create Weapon X.
- X?
Roman numeral, Ten.
We are about to begin bonding
Adamantium to Weapon X's skeleton
Let's begin.
- We're brothers, Jimmy.
- Logan!
Body temperature is 1-0-8
and rising.
Why is he thrashinglike that?
Why isn't he sedated?
He feels pain, just like the rest of us.
Anesthesia won't work on him.
That's why he had to volunteer.
195.
- Will he survive this?
- I don't know.
200.
...son.
Heartbeat is close to maximum.
- Blood pressure?
- 260 on 180.
He can make it, he can make it.
Victor!
I love you.
You're not an animal, Logan.
It means the Volverine.
I guess he can die.
Come on, old friend.
Come back.
Heart rate rising.
Adamantium reservoir is depleted.
No rejection.
Procedure completed.
We did it!
We take him to the island?
The island? No.
The bonding works.
We use his DNA for the XI.
Erase his memory.
Fry his brain!
I think he heard you.
Lockdown!
Hunt him down.
Take his head off.
Travis!
I think there is some
naked man in the barn.
Yep.
Son...
What in hell are you doing?
- It's cold.
- Cold?
- You got no clothes on.
- Yeah.
- You're not onto drugs, are you?
- No.
- Hmm. You just had a rough night.
- Yeah, you could say that.
Come on up the house.
Some of my son's old clothes
will probably fit you.
Here, cover it up with that.
I don't want to give an old lady
a heart attack.
You're right in there?
Yeah, everything's fine.
- Supper's on the table.
- I uh...Yeah, I'll be there in a minute.
I swear I'm gonna pay for it.
Set it down over there.
Come and sit down, son.
I can't thank you both enough
...for everything
It wouldn't have been decent
to leave you out there to freeze.
- Decent...
- What?
Um... Nothing, I'm just not
really used to that word.
- That's a nice chopper you've got out there.
- You know motorcycle?
Oh Lord, here we go!
My favorite is a '48 Panhead.
I bought one new off the line.
I think you're a little young
for that, son.
You must be exhausted.
You get a good night's sleep.
In the barn.
Nothing you can break out there.
I love you.
- Why is the moon so lonely?
- Why?
Because she used to have a lover.
He can never touch her again.
You sleep ok?
Uh...yeah.
You look like a man fixing
to do a bad thing.
You know what happens
to many looking for blood?
- What?
- They find it.
- We all got a choice, son.
- Yeah, mine got taken.
Bullshit.
This was my son's jacket.
Try it on.
- Thank you.
- Yep...
You wanna take my bike for a spin,
test the suspension.
'64, huh?
- Man, you're heavy.
- Yeah, I put on a little weight recently.
Good morning.
Oh, it fits you beautifully!
I brought you some...
Weapon X is in the barn.
He just murdered two civilians.
Blow him to bits.
Let's see if he can survive that.
Fire at will.
Come and get me!
Blow his head up.
Damn!
Alpha One, do not lose him!
Alfa 2, target's coming to you!
Pull up! Pull up!
Zero, is Logan dead?
Don't know, I'm down.
Zero, come in!
You tried to kill me.
Logan?
Where is Victor?
Come back to base.
I'll explain everything,
we'll take Victor down together.
Wrong answer.
After I've killed Victor,
I'm coming for you.
Logan, listen to me.
If you go down this road, you're
not gonna like what you find.
You wanted the animal, Colonel?
You got it.
Those were good people back there.
Innocent people.
It's funny how good innocent people
tend to die around you.
Zero never stood a chance.
The only thing that'll take him down
is an Adamantium bullet
This facility is compromised.
Prep transport.
Colonel, this is turning into a disaster.
- Don't worry, we'll stop him.
- Really?
You've just spent half a billion
dollars making him indestructible.
- Sir?
- Yes.
The young mutant you've been looking for?
We found him.
General, Logan isn't the only
piece in this puzzle.
I need to evacuate this facility.
Please, go back to Washington.
We've got work to do.
Yo hablo: I talk,
tu hablas: you talk, el habla?
Somebody translate?
Summers?
Sit up and take off those glasses.
I have a headache.
Then you can wear them
in detention after school
whil you add up
this conjugation 100 times.
Somebody else?
He talks.
Thank you, he talks.
El habla.
- You sure it was Victor?
- Yeah.
Damn!
I'm sorry, mate.
What the hell happened
to him after I left?
He got worse.
He felt like you abandoned him.
Hell, we all do.
But Victor, he had to prove you
he was better than you.
Hunting and killing
everything's he was pointin' at.
Quit a few months later myself,
couldn't take rounding them up.
- Rounding who up?
- Leave it alone.
Rounding who up, John?
Hey! God damn it, John!
We hunted our own kind, Logan.
There's a special place in hell
for the things we did.
Mutants?
Why?
Stryker'd say we would
make a difference.
Protecting people from the bad ones.
How are you gonna take
Victor down, Logan?
- Remember that stuff in Africa?
- Yeah, I remember Africa, what about it?
Damn!
What'd they do to you?
Don't ask.
Listen, Zero said something about an island.
Does that mean anything to you?
Nope.
But maybe Dukes knows.
- Him and Zero were real tight.
- Fred Dukes?
- Where is he?
- He's here.
- Well, let's go talk to him.
- Hold on.
He don't get in until around four.
But I gotta warn you,
he developed a bit of eating desorder.
We all got our coping mechanisms.
I'm trying to whoop him back into shape.
Come on, Fred, if you want to get
into shape, you gotta move, man.
I told him he got to move.
Fred Dukes? **** this creature?
That ain't Fred.
If you want his help,
don't mention it to him.
Hey, Fat, Fred, um.
I don't remember that girl
puttin' up eighty five pounds, huh.
Oh that's funny.
You're still so funny, Logan.
You know where Victor is?
No idea.
What's the island, slim?
Don't let the door hit you
on the way out, Logan.
Listen, I ain't gonna leave
until you tell me where Victor is.
Come on, Bob. For old times' sake, huh?
Did you just call me...Blob?
No, but...
I told you not to mention his weight.
Why did you call him Blob?
I didn't call him Blob, I said Bob!
Goddamn it!
I got an idea.
- This is your idea of an idea?
- Trying to help you out, Logan.
Dukes don't like you that much,
and you know it.
The feeling is mutual.
Use those gloves, man,
dance with him a little bit.
Allow him to let his anger out on you.
I figure if you do that
he might tell you all you wanna know.
Come on, man, look at him.
Big old ass comin' out of
the front of his shirt.
Jesus, he's gonna have a coronary
for Christ's sake.
Is there even a stretcher big enough
to take this guy out of here?
It ain't him I'm worried about
getting out on a stretcher.
You're an asshole.
Whoop his ass!
- Let me have it.
- If you want.
Be careful with this.
You wanna dance with me?
Oh. Oh, that feels good.
Hey, guess what?
See, he's gonna talk, man.
You got him right where you want him.
Whose side are you on, anyway?
Now, where is Victor?
A little dark for sunglasses,
don't you think?
Please don't! Please! Don't, please!
Victor!
Where's Victor?
Victor's... with Stryker on...
on the island, they run it together.
What...what?
Victor's being with Stryker?
Yeah.
You didn't know that?
All that's left now is Logan, I...
...trust you can handle that.
I did before, didn't I?
Oh yes, you did that.
Our deal...it still applies, right?
Of course.
Now pack him
and tag him, Captain.
What's the island?
It's where... Striker takes them
after Victor's caught 'em.
Wait, wait...um, what?
Takes who?
Mutants.
The rumor is that Stryker's doing
experiments on them there.
Well, you never wondered
what happened to them?
I tried no to.
They killed her so I'd let them
put Adamantium in me.
They killed her for a
goddamn experiment.
Where is it?
Logan, Stryker kept it real secret.
But...
- A prisoner escaped there once.
- Who?
His name is Remy LeBeau.
He was a street hustler from New Orleans.
The guards at the prison
called him Gambit
'cause he kept taking all their
money at poker, that's all I know.
What's Stryker up to,
what's the end game?
He's taking their powers,
trying to combine them somehow.
It's all I know, Logan.
It's all I know.
If I had to come back here,
I'm gonna take your head off.
I'm coming with you, Logan.
- There's no redemption where I'm going.
- I ain't asking.
There's our dude.
That's cool.
But I'm gonna gonna go and cover
the back if he runs.
I'm not havin' a fight with him.
- Yeah right.
- What?
I am havin' fights with everybody?
Don't dogs kill cats?
Just go cover the back, will ya?
Are you Remy LeBeau?
Do I owe you money?
No.
Then Remy LeBeau I am.
Large blind is 100,
and the small blind's 50.
May I deal you in?
Now what can I get for 17 bucks?
17 dollars?
A cab ride home, perhaps.
You're my brother's new babysitter, John?
I ain't Bradley, Victor.
And your creepy black
coat don't scare me.
Really?
It worked on Dukes.
What a shame, 'cause now I'm gonna kill you
so Logan never gets the chance.
So what brings you to our fair city, sir?
Victor Creed.
And who's that?
The man I'm gonna kill.
He works for a man named Stryker
on, uh, on an island.
- I just need to know where it is.
- Why would you think I know that?
Well, 'cause I know who you are, Gambit.
You are the guy who escaped and you are
the guy who's gonna take me back there.
You know, John...
There's something I always
wanted to tell you.
You're predictable.
I can feel your spine, Johnny Boy.
That's funny.
I never knew you had one.
Those are mighty nice tags
you have on there, sir.
The men who took me
wore tags just like 'em.
Hey, now Bob, you listen to me...
Two years I was rottin' in that hell,
and I'm never going back.
Oh, shiny.
Tell me something, Jimmy.
Do you even know how to kill me?
I'm gonna cut your goddamn head off.
See if that works.
You're gettin' slow, old man.
Son of a bitch.
You're gonna die for
what you did to her.
Victor!
That's a nice stick.
Shithead. Here's the deal.
See, you're gonna take me to this
island, where I can kill Creed,
Stryker, pretty much everyone
you hate in this world.
Do you understand?
You really want to kill 'em.
As long as you stay
out of my way, yeah.
Colonel.
General?
Is this Weapon XI?
All their strenghts
but none of their weaknesses.
You really hate them, don't you?
No, I don't hate them.
After 20 years of working with them,
I just know what they can do.
If we win this war before it starts,
and save countless lives in the process.
Preemptive action is
the only action here, General.
The days of our country sitting
on the sidelines are over.
We need to take the fight to the enemy
before they take the fight to us.
- I admire your passion, I do.
- Thank you.
But this is as far as it goes.
Weapon X was a... a hickup.
We know about your son, Bill.
We know he's a mutant.
And we know he killed your wife.
You shouldn't have kept that from us.
That...
- That has nothing to do with my work.
- Bullshit!
You're too close to this.
I'm sure you know it.
You're right.
I...I won't lie to you.
My son did bring the problem home for me.
But I took an oath...
to protect the American people
from every threat,
both foreign
...and domestic.
- You don't like flying, huh?
- I'm fine.
Just concentrate on
what you're doing.
You sure? You got a bit of sweat on your brow there.
- Very funny. Just keep your eyes on the...
- On the what? Clouds?
We're jumpin' up and down loke a yoyo here.
Where did you get this thing anyway?
Oh, this is my baby, I won her in a game.
- Jacks over fives.
- Great.
Relax. We're almost there.
There it is.
The island.
Three Mile Island.
Hiding in plain sight.
Noone's gonna sneak around
a nuclear reactor.
They think it's gonna turn them into freaks.
Like you?
Right.
All right, you ready?
Cause it's now or never.
Let's go.
About time.
Hey, if it's make you feel any better,
this is really gonna hurt.
Oh yeah. It kind of does actually.
Good luck.
Likewise.
Oh shit.
How are you doing?
Is everything alright?
- Is he ready yet?
- A few hours.
Will he respond to my commands?
Yes, Colonel.
Logan.
Welcome back to the war.
Before you gut you,
I wanna know why.
I needed your powers
for the pool.
For the what?
A mutant killer.
The dead pool.
Years of searching him, to find him,
finding the right powers
that can coexist in one body
without ripping it apart.
My son was the first piece of the puzzle.
Logan, you are the last.
You made Weapon XI possible.
I...
I asked you to help but...
you said you wanted the quiet life.
Well...
I've learned that nothing motivates
the men in your family like revenge.
Who are you?
Oh she's a real old friend.
Do you really think we'd
just let you walk away?
You are a dangerous man.
I like to keep an eye on dangerous men.
Tell him about the
day you died.
They gave me a shot of
hydrochloride thiazide.
It reduces the heart rate so low,
it appears you flatline.
Don't be angry with her.
Real credit to your species.
Did you know that her sister
has diamond-hard skin?
Kayla's mutation
is tacto-hypnosis.
She can influence people as
long as she touches them.
Quite a useful tool in the seduction.
It was never real, my friend.
It was real for me.
I told you if you came down this road,
you wouldn't like what you'd find.
That story you told me...
about man who gets flowers for the moon...
I had it backwards.
I thought you were the moon
and I was your Wolverine.
But you were the Trickster, aren't you?
I am just the fool that got played.
The worst part of this is
I should have known.
But I ignored my instincts.
I ignored what I really am.
Well, that will never happen again.
- Colonel.
- Not now, Kayla.
I have done everything you've asked.
My sister...
You said that if I help you,
you'd let her go.
Kayla, it's not as simple as that.
Her mutation is unique.
Quite beautiful.
We just need a little more time
to analyze it, that's all.
You let him go?
- Victor, please.
- You can't let him go.
- You can't beat him, Victor.
- Give me the Adamantium.
- Tests came out...
- We had a deal!
You would never survive the operation.
- I can take anything he can.
- No, you can't.
You are my favorite soldier, Victor.
Be patient, time will come.
He's using us!
How about this time, you die for real?
Let me go.
Your mindgame don't work on me.
Victor!
Feels good, doesn't it?
All that rage...
Do it.
Logan!
You're not an animal.
Oh yes, you are.
Do it.
Finish it.
Logan?
My sister.
They have my sister.
Please, I didn't trick you deliberately.
It was real for me too.
Please, I'm so sorry.
They have my sister.
Where is she?
- Activate Weapon XI.
- The binding process is incomplete.
Just do it!
Now!
You are okay? Come on.
Ok...
Perfect.
- Kayla, get these kids out of here.
- Logan...
Find another way out.
Come on, let's go!
Wade, is that you?
I guess Stryker finally figured
out how to shut you up.
Wade...
You don't have to do this.
Or maybe you do.
Shoot on sight!
I can help! Point me at 'em!
Go!
Go! Now!
D'you think I got them?
Yeah.
- Let's go.
- I can't go.
Kayla, come on!
I have to stay here.
You take them.
Go!
Left.
- What?
- We go left.
- You can't see.
- Trust me.
C'mon Bob! Let's see
your dance up here.
de
decapi
decapita
decapitate
Nobody kills you but me.
Back-to-back!
- I got him!
- Oh no, you don't.
Stop!
- This can't be the way.
- This is the way!
- How do you know?
- I just know.
Come on.
Adamantium bullets.
Let's see him heal with a few
of these through his thick skull.
You can't stop him.
Even with that.
He'll heal.
His brain may heal.
But his memories won't grow back.
That doesn't change anything
between us, Victor.
We're done.
We can never be done, Jimmy.
We're brothers.
Brothers look out for each other.
- You miss me?
- Jesus...
When you said you'd gonna kill everyone,
I thought you may just've been exaggerating.
Yeah...
Do I look like a man who exaggerates?
You're welcome.
These kids trying
to get off the island.
- Split up. Go!
- I'm on it.
I love you.
No...
I'm so cold.
Listen to me, I'm gonna
get you outta here.
You understand?
Let's go easy, nice and easy.
That's it.
that's it.
I'm gonna get you out.
I should make you
pull the trigger.
But that would make us
not better than you.
Throw the gun away.
Walk until your feet bleed.
And then keep walking.
It'll be all right, Scott.
My name is Charles Xavier.
I'm a mutant, like you.
- I can hear your thoughts.
- Yes. And I can hear yours.
You're safe now.
Come. We have to go.
The kids are safe.
What the hell happened?
- Who are you?
- What do you mean, who am I?
I'm the guy who brought you here.
Now we gotta go.
Where the hell am I?
Listen to me, I am a friend.
A friend.
What's my name?
Your name is Logan.
You need to trust me.
We have to go.
Follow me.
Now!
Do you know her?
No.
These guys are not gonna like
what you've done in this place.
We really need to go.
I'll find my own way.
Good luck.
Colonel Stryker?
- Colonel William Stryker?
- Yes.
You're wanted for questioning in
connection of the death of General Munson.Sir!
Subs by: Junrey Lafuente......
re-sync by alf reinhart