[Music]
[Applause]
for the Chinese the habit of having
breakfast developed during the Han
Dynasty some 2,000 years ago since then
most Chinese have eaten three meals a
day while breakfast has become an almost
universal custom around the world in
China it has sparked a variety of
lifestyles and philosophies
[Applause]
[Music]
for city dwellers breakfast has to be
quick and easy
yunjin people know this best of all they
have a thin wrap of mung bean batter
with eggs to make it more nutritious
[Music]
deep-fries until it's golden-brown dough
fritters in mung bean wrap crisp on the
outside and tender on the inside they're
quick and easy
[Music]
in a Chinese breakfast flavor is
important Jinyan knows the secret to a
tasty breakfast number 32 40:47 chong
qing people are mad about small noodles
it's the only way to start the day can I
have less red chili more flour pepper
and an egg in Chongqing the locals
really only wake up after a bowl of
tasty small noodles and soup
alkaline salts are the key in making the
dough they caused the gluten in the
flour to form a dense network of blocks
in starch particles that way the soup
stays clear and the noodles develop a
firm texture alkaline noodles are found
in all the main cities of the Yangtze
River basin in Sujal noodles are served
with a clear tasty soup Suja noodles are
thin they go well with the soup braised
pork noodles feature noodles in a smooth
soup with a slice of delicious braised
pork
[Music]
in Wuhan
breakfast is simply called early he
tends to be salty savory donuts and tofu
ramps are popular but the number one
favorite is alkaline dry noodles they
are boiled mixed with sesame oil and
dried the sesame paste must be properly
blended so it appears evenly to the
noodles doing this requires a strong
wrist and considerable patience
[Music]
Jinyan owns illusion he has trained over
200 apprentices it's not spicy enough it
needs more salt you need to put your
heart into it
sprinkling some spices on it or doing
some token job isn't going to cut it you
need to know the countenance inside out
what makes small noodles unique is there
12 condiment chillies Sichuan pepper oil
soy sauce they are all mixed by hand the
chef must balance all 12 did stir like
many others in Chongqing Jin's noodle
restaurant is only open for breakfast
and lunch nice and easy
[Music]
the three critical elements in this
cuisine are aroma chili heat and
pleasing colors
[Music]
after small noodles Jin's signature dish
is beef noodles but he limits his output
of beef noodles to only 10 kilos worth
of beef a day this shrewd marketing
strategy guarantees him a long queue of
hungry customers
[Music]
how is it it's spot-on in every level
yes it's actually very good keep it up
and do this every time then you're ready
to graduate
maybe call you'd be dead off who's next
I am the small in small noodles reflects
their low price and their unassuming
place in the gamut of Chinese cuisine
but in Chongqing Jin's breakfast
restaurant is famous not all breakfast
aimed to be quick and easy in Guangzhou
it's the experience that people save us
7 a.m. customers are queuing up in front
of a restaurant in the old part of town
dim sum chefs have already been busy for
three hours the chefs make each dim sum
item exquisitely and bring it to life
morning tea in Guangzhou is rich and
lavish the tea is just an excuse for
other more interesting items such as dim
sum and congee
when the doors open regulars rush for
their favorite seats
the popularity of morning tea in
Guangzhou is linked to its booming trade
one of the regulars is Chung Yasha 56
retiree
a 29 year old son young jingzhong is a
lawyer his breakfast is much more hard I
don't normally have time for breakfast I
just grab something on the way to work
work comes first
work is how you survive that work
there's no like one long dim sum maybe
wet or dry the dry kinda more delicately
made crystal prawn dumplings a perfect
melding of sweet prawn filling and a
clear elastic dough the average one Joe
morning tea lasts over an hour
guangzhou maybe a business metal ground
for the young but for the elderly it's a
paradise in 2013 15 percent of the
guangzhou population or 1.25 million
people were aged 60 or more the city is
a microcosm of china it juggles
development and tradition
[Music]
the city's fast-paced lifestyle gives
young people more opportunities but in
this time for breakfast
[Music]
after morning tea Chung Yasha cooks the
family dinner soy sauce sugar rice wine
vinegar and water the five ingredients
for five flavored duck a fresh Weaver
fish is perfect for steaming watercress
pork soup helps to remove any oily
aftertaste a dinner made with love
awaits her son after his heart day at
work
[Music]
[Applause]
but some young people's meals are much
less interesting yeah top quality 7:30
a.m. a hundred and sixty thousand young
people come and go with a three square
kilometer factory complex the same scene
is played out five days a week school
leavers in their 20s make up most of the
workers in the complex for them doing
repetitive work all day every day is a
real challenge
21 year old young un young was complete
the same task 5000 times a day or every
five seconds for seven hours
the factory central kitchen runs on
similar industrial lines as it turns out
standardized meals it's prime concern is
ensuring the food is safe to eat
followed by balanced nutrition 2 tons of
fish 3 tons of 4 15 tons of vegetables
and 15 tons of rice are needed every day
to feed some 80,000 para 20 miss Hawkins
scattered throughout the conflict with
the largest of them seating 2,000 people
[Music]
the workers take a ten-minute break
every two hours the lunch break is one
of them like the workers in other
Chinese factories Union has to work hard
to keep up the pace
[Music]
shulay from Hunan has worked in the
complex for 11 years he supervises 200
workers making a well known brand of
mobile phone the core workshops a
top-secret adding a sense of mystery to
this large cold complex
[Music]
Shu and his wife wouldn't fail live in
one of the apartment blocks just outside
the complex for them cured fish carries
the delightful taste of home excess
salts and impurities are removed by
soaking the fish in water and then
boiling it
after that it's sauteed until golden
chilies garlic ginger and black beans
are added for a time the steamed fish
transports them back to their hometown
[Music]
in shoes faraway hometown his
mother-in-law
Jojo Zhang is preparing an ancient dish
starting with soil collected in the
mountains the recipe was set down in a
farmers book some 1,400 years ago
Chao and her granddaughter of mine
Duquette a complex cooking
transformation is about to begin
[Music]
one kilo of duck eggs and 200 grams of
salt the duck eggs are fully immersed in
a muddy brine solution the sodium and
chlorine molecules in the salt filter
through the eggshells
[Music]
in the seal jars the eggs lie dormant
waiting to be woken up check out this
new video clip see she loves playing we
can't neglect her studies we both have
to work so we left her with my mother we
miss her so much we ring her every day
a month later salt has filtered into the
bugs and water has filtered out the eggs
are transformed in shape and taste to
keep these homemade delicacies fresh and
protect them from breaking gel coats
them in hey ash she will send them to
her daughter in Guangzhou the best part
of a salted duck egg is the yolk the fat
that separated in the curing process
turns into yolk oil
[Music]
the salty yolk has a uniquely fine and
sandy texture it's so big
[Music]
the flavors of home like a spell that
transcends time and space to bring the
whole family together my goal is to
allow my family to live happily and to
have no worries
which one is daddy one say daddy give
mommy a kiss I started work at 16 or 17
I'm 28 so it's been 11 years I spent my
youth at Foxconn in this industrial
empire millions of young people toil
anonymously to provide the world with an
unceasing supply of globalized products
each day is filled with energy stamina
and free meals
[Music]
in the darling mountains far from
manufacturing there's someone who lives
a challenging life of his own
electricity grid workers have to do lots
of haiku Tao has inspected the grid for
20 years
and district' through the mountains for
much of that time his team of workers
walks over 25,000 kilometers a year
three-quarters the length of the Equator
living near the power lines of the Yi
ethnic minority it's July and time to
harvest potatoes
[Music]
the locals call them Western yams with
large tubers and a high concentration of
amylopectin and dry matter these
potatoes are tender and fluffy
but--will congee is 2,600 meters above
sea level in the highlands of southern
Sichuan it's the home of the so-called
dark potatoes
they're low yielding and hard to grow
but also thin-skinned soft textured and
rich in starch stir fried potatoes is a
simple excellent dish traditionally the
e baked potatoes the taste and fragrance
are delightful it's August the month of
the EES annual torch festival tender
aromatic pork chunks are made from the
native black piglets of a young son the
grilled pork is cut into large pieces
and cooked over a very hot flame then
various condiments are added but goo has
nothing to do with any of this let's
take a cigarette break it's your first
time here don't work on an empty stomach
here you are there's more here boo have
some more you'll need energy
for many people the pace of China's
development means having to forego
traditional home-cooked meals
deep in the Darby our mountains a large
number of young people are facing an
ordeal goshi Nia's mother Lee she cooks
for her daughter every day the national
higher education entrance examination is
a watershed in life for millions of
school leavers
with its 20,000 students Martin Chang
high school churns out more candidates
than any other school in Hungary
province it's known as an exam Factory
its students are under immense pressure
and get little time for rest some of the
parents become full-time carers it's
spring and Leigh she is on the lookout
for a certain while in vegetable sweet
wormwood also known as sweet Annie by
tradition the locals have sweet Annie
cakes on day three of the third lunar
month the sweet wormwood may not be very
abundant but Lee still observes the
tradition once soaked dried and chopped
the herb gives off a pleasant fragrance
[Music]
to improve the taste and the nutrition
level Lee adds salt pork to the ground
rice
[Music]
she loves it
the wild vegetable cakes will delight
her daughter every mom has a culinary
secret weapon there are 90 exam rooms
each holding a hundred candidates the
atmosphere is tense
the students have a 30-minute break for
lunch
[Music]
Shinya has sweet any cakes for lunch her
exam is less than two months away
[Music]
delicious yes Shinya and her mother live
near the school
many students aren't so fortunate
there's no student dining hall the
parents have yet another task feeding
their children at lunchtime every day
thousands of students flock to the gate
to take delivery of their lunch
take your time it's not quite enough is
it the parents dedicate time and energy
to their children but as the subjects
become more advanced all that many
parents can do is ensure their children
are well fed the quality of their
nourishment can affect their exam
results or even bear directly on their
future Mountain Chun is a Riverside town
of 10,000 that number triples at exam
time yet alongside the high pressure
life of the school there's a sleepy
atmosphere that preserves an almost lost
craft tofu mills in the old part of town
still employ ancient methods to make the
famous dry tofu the two centimeter thick
soy product is soft smooth and elastic
[Music]
dang she doesn't see well because her
study schedule doesn't give her much
time for rest what I have to do is make
sure she gets nutritious meals
[Music]
Shinya is leaving tomorrow to sit the
exam in another tongue her mother is
meticulous in preparing the last meal
before her departure
[Music]
it is the delicious braised pork with
dry tofu made with soft tofu pork belly
and a mix of sources are you nervous a
bit really what you nervous to in my day
studying was a luxury now that's a real
trial it's not so bad
caring for her in the last 10 months
while she's been studying has been the
best and happiest time of my life the
slippers of success are finally finished
the time mother and daughter have spent
shoulder to shoulder is coming to an end
you've come here from all over the
province to pursue your drinks why have
you walked along the winding roads and
come all the way to this high school to
study to seek enlightenment it's time to
march off
[Music]
[Applause]
sometimes leading a simple life can be a
lifestyle choice in Shanghai vegetarians
look to vegetables for good health and
the meaning of life over 50 million
people in China are vegetarians by
choice to free oneself of fleshly
desires was a motto of the sages of old
people are starting to regard a simple
vegetarian diet as good for their health
it's even become a selling point may I
have a receipt healthy food is a gentle
weapon that conquers everyone one Iowa
is scouring the streets in an effort to
compile a comprehensive list of gourmet
foods she is organizing a community
vegetarian banquet for the mid-autumn
festival and she's still looking for
some key ingredients her secret
ingredient is a filling made of red bean
paste dried orange peel and sugar
[Music]
in the 1960s some 70% of Hong Kong's
vegetables were supplied locally that
number is now less than 2%
[Music]
but there is still farmland at fan Ling
it's farmers use traditional methods
growing only seasonal vegetables with
organic fertilizers Iowa has confidence
in this type of produce despite its low
years snow skin mooncake s-- are a
highlight of Iowa's banquet moon cakes
are found throughout China the Amitha
docks snow skin mooncake was born in
Hong Kong in the 1980s
[Music]
mung bean paste is wrapped in snow skin
which is made of wheat flour and
ordinary and glutinous rice flour no
baking is needed
they're best served chilled do you know
why it's called happy kitchen in modern
society food is a mere commodity happy
kitchen however invites people to ponder
on the nexus between nature food and
food producers
[Music]
in this ever-changing world
the longer one lives in the city the
more one longs for the life of the land
[Music]
the rapid pace of change affects
everyone in Hong Kong prosperous though
it may be garden patches of replaced
mansions as the most fashionable luxury
on the mainland there are other examples
of people living in harmony with nature
and tradition 72 year old Long Cheng wee
goes fishing in the Gulen River every
day
it's his morning exercise GU lien County
is in sich one southeast the chishui
river runs through it Chinese cities are
classified into three tiers Gulen is
smaller even than the lowest tier tier 3
[Music]
golden handmade noodles with their chewy
it's smooth texture and super absorbency
they're a great choice for breakfast
[Music]
noodles place sure stewed mushy peas
made from ripened Peas the peas give the
noodles a hint of sweetness it's a small
city 20 of fresh produce from nearby
farms it's very accessible farmers can
bring on fresh produce of a sale on the
banks of their motor bicycle in this
Riverside city life is self-sufficient
and sustainable just as it was before
industrialization most food is grown
local long has chosen a three year old
rooster he punctures its skin to ensure
the meat doesn't burst out the marinade
prepared with over thirty spices can be
used over and over for cooking chicken
[Music]
the rich soup is mixed with chili oil to
give good in spicy chicken
it's remarkable taste
Gulen spicy chicken is long made cheese
favorite the great-grandfather wants to
give her a surprise looking everywhere
for you and a bad girl stop crying
[Music]
did you get some lollies yes
well you shouldn't be crying then myself
can you stop being upset with Grandpa
[Music]
are you okay now yes
it's really lovely for four generations
to live under the same yellow head
catfish also known as Korean bull head
is found in China long caught some
yellow head catfish this morning
[Music]
throughout China there are many ways of
cooking this fish duelin people usually
cook it with pickles and capsicums to
remove the fishy smell and bring out the
aroma
[Music]
it's done now hot and spicy chicken is
stewed for an hour
[Music]
immersed in chili oil the meat is hot
tender and aromatic for decades the long
family have gathered almost every
weekend for a family banquet
[Music]
let's drink to your good health to good
health I like living in a small city I
can't get used to big cities here the
air is good and the environment is clean
[Music]
a pleasant environment the low cost of
living and a simple lifestyle
[Music]
these are what makes small cities like
dueling so special
once the normal way of life in China
it's now become rare and sought-after
[Music]
there are some who choose to escape a
stressful being city life to discover
the joys of simplicity let's go Dali a
place familiar to shi xuxia and one
chong of beijing their previous visits
were only brief Oh Highgate in dali is
3,000 kilometers from beijing here you
experience true harmony with nature
[Music]
their acquaintance with their neighbor
mrs. lead is the kind of relationship
that's rare these days it's rapeseed oil
ohyes crucian carp are nice and fresh
medium to medium well-done mrs. Lee's an
excellent cook xuxa is eager to learn
from her search wine Tilly white papaya
known locally as sour papaya is the
signature flavor of this dish but not
diseased the sourness and fruity
fragrance of the white papaya and the
chilies bring out the full flavor of the
fish the fish is tender and the soup is
spicy hot
omits our lake erhai the seventh largest
freshwater lake in China it has a rich
variety of aquatic life and the bio
people have fished its waters for
generations the average height of the
Kong Mountains is 3500 meters above sea
level the blue stain a mushroom harvest
coincides with the July monsoon there
picked in the morning and sold in the
market right away
the locals call them the morning batch
bluh stainer
is the common name for boletus nerdiness
the cap turns blue when cut a sign of
toxicity blue stain errs can easily
poison the unwary but heat detoxifies
them the mushrooms are cooked in oil
before being stir-fried over a high heat
to ensure they are thoroughly cooked
[Music]
I haven't tasted yet despite their mild
toxicity people continue to be
fascinated by the crunchy texture and
incredible taste of fresh blue steamers
[Music]
so delicious yes it is and refreshing
it's free Klee yes a quiet life in the
country with fresh air good neighbors
and natural foods
after spending some time in Dali xuxa
and her husband made a life-changing
decision they quit their jobs and moved
to dolly a simple life isn't necessarily
a hard life to me what others regard as
unambitious is in fact priceless living
so xuxa confides to her diary it's the
5th of June a hundred and forty bus
loads of exam candidates over 10,000 of
them are leaving Mountain Shanghai
school
Forli she caring for her daughter while
she studied for the exam brought them
closer the older the child grows the
further away she will be for young
jingxian leaving for work every morning
is like going on a long lunch
he doesn't rest till he comes home in
the evening to a bowl of soup warmed
with love from the family after a day's
hard work you onion is going out to have
a good time
despite the challenges of her job she
still enjoys her youth the doll young
mountains thoughts festival is reaching
its climax go Tao takes a break from
inspecting the grins to enjoy a meal
[Music]
[Applause]
it's human nature to want to enjoy good
food but everyone has different and
sometimes opposing ideas about good food
we all make our own choices about what
we eat today the Chinese are seeing an
amazing abundance of food as well as
extreme shortages of resources
[Music]
if they turn to their ancestral wisdom
for answers they may find this advice
big a mansion may be but a band is all
one needs to sleep at night rich a man
may be but three meals a day are all one
needs to live
[Music]
in their search for gourmet foods the
production crews for a bite of China
found themselves facing all sorts of
challenges under extreme conditions the
next episode takes you behind the scenes
[Music]
you