تېز بولۇڭ رانجىت، بۇ سىزنىڭ نۆۋىتىڭىز
Come on Ranjeet, it's your turn.
مەن نېمە قىلىش كېرەكلىكىنى ئويلىنىۋاتىمەن
I'm thinking what I'm going to be doing.
سىز ئويلىنىۋاتقىلى بەش مىنۇت بولدى
You have been thinking for five minutes.
سەۋرچان بولۇڭ
Patience
بىز سۆز قوراشتۇرۇش ئويۇنى ئويناۋاتىمىز، سەۋرچان بولۇش ئەمەس
We are playing scrabblo not patience.
قايسى نومۇرنى خالايسىز سۇ لى؟     - ئون سەككىز -
- What do you want Su Lee? - Eighteen
بولىدۇ، مانا ئاتتىم
okay, here we go.
ئون سەككىز، ئون توققۇز، يىگىرمە
Eighteen, nineteen, twenty.
پۈتۈن ئايلانمىدا ئۇتتۇق
Full cycle to win.
ناھايىتى ياخشى، تەبرىكلەيمەن
Very good. Bravo.
ماقۇل، ئەمدى سىزنىڭ نۆۋىتىڭىز زولتان
Right. It's your turn now Zoltan.
ھېي، دىققەت قىلىڭلار. زولتاننىڭ نۆۋىتى
Hey. Atención. Zoltan's turn.
ھېچقىسى يوق، ئاتسىڭىز بولىدۇ
It's all right. You throw
مەن ئۇنچە ناچار ئەمەس، قايسى نومۇرنى خالايسىز؟
I'm no bad. What you want?
بەش
Five.
خېلى ئۇستا بولۇپ قاپسىز     - شۇنداقمۇ؟ -
- You are getting better. - Yes?
تاختايغا تەككۈزەلەيدىغان بوپسىز     - ياخشى -
- You are starting to hit the board. - Good.
نېمە ئىش بولدى؟
What happened?
ئالدى تەرەپكە قارىتىپ ئېتىشىڭىز كېرەك ئىدى، ئارقا تەرەپكە ئەمەس
You are supposed to throw it forward not to the backwards.
ئۇ قېنى؟
Where is it?
ھېچقىسى يوق، مەن ئۇنى كۆردۈم
It's alright. I see it.
ئوھ، ۋاي خۇدايىم
Oh, dear me.
....سىزنىڭ سەللە ئورىۋالغىنىڭىزمۇ ياخشى بوپتىكەن
It's a good thing you were wearing a...
...رانجىت، ئۇنداق بولمىغان بولسا ئۇدۇل
turban Ranjeet otherwise it would...
كېلىپ بېشىڭىزغا سانجىلىپ قالاركەن
have gone straight through your head.
توۋا خۇدايىم! سەن ئۇنى ئازراقمۇ سەزمىدىڭ
Oh, blimey! You wouldn't have felt it.
مۇشتۇمۇمنى يېگەن چاغدا ئوبدانلا سېزىسەن
You will feel my fist in a moment.
تېز بولۇڭ رانجىت
Come on Ranjeet.
مەن تېخىچە ئويلىنىۋاتىمەن
I'm still thinking.
شۇنداق، شىكلارنىڭ ئىنكاسى بەك ئاستا
Yeah, sikhs are slow thinkers.
ئاغزىڭنى يۇم
Shut up.
بىزنىڭ چوقۇم «ۋاقىتو» چەكلىمىمىز بولۇشى كېرەك، تېز بولۇڭ
We must have time limito. Come on.
ئوھ، تازا ياخشىسىدىن بىرنى تاپتىم. شېكەر
Oh, I'm getting a good one. Sugar.
«ياخشو ئەمەس»
No goodo.
دەپ ھەجىلەنمەيدۇ «S-H-U-G-A-R» تازىمۇ ھاماقەتكەنسىز! شېكەر دېگەن سۆز
Quel idiot! Sugar is not spelled S-H-U-G-A-R.
مېنىڭچە سىز خاتالىشىپ قالدىڭىز
I think you are mistaken.
بارلىقىنى بىلىدۇ «G»ۋۇ قاپاق باش. ھەممە ئادەم شېكەر دېگەن سۆزدە ئىككى
You damn fool. Everybody know sugar is spelled with two Gs.
بىز يەڭدۇق! سىزمۇ ئويناشنى خالامسىز جۇئان؟
We win! You want game juan?
!ئەمدى ۋاقتىمىز قالمدى. براۋن ئەپەندى ھازىرلا يىتىپ كېلىدۇ
We no have time. Mr. Brown he will be here pretty soon!
ئۇتتۇرۇپ قويۇشتىن قورقىۋاتامسىز؟
You frighten you lose?
مەن سىزنى كۆزۈمنى تېڭىپ قويۇپمۇ يېڭىۋالىمەن
I beat you blind folded.
ئەمىسە سىزنىڭ كۆزىڭىزنى يۇمۇپ تۇرۇپ ئۈستىدىكى ئىككىگە تەگكۈزگىنىڭىزنى كۆرۈپ باقايلى
Let's see you get double the top with your eyes closed.
ئاسان، بەك ئاسان
Easy. Easy.
كۆزىڭىزنى يۇمۇڭ
Close.
بىر، ئىككى
One, two,
جەمىلە
Jamila.
بۇنى كىم ئاتتى؟
Who threw this?
مەن ئاتقان، ئاۋۇ ئۈستىدىكى تاختايغا تەگكۈزمەكچىتىم
Me. I was trying to get that in top.
قارىغاندا كاسىغا تەگكۈزگەندەك قىلىسىز
Looks like you get it in the bottom.
يارىلانمىغانسىز سىد؟
Are you hurt Sid?
ھە؟
Huh?
ئاغرىدىمۇ؟
Dit it hurt?
سەنمۇ كاساڭغا سانجىپ باقساڭ بىلىسەن
You bend down and you'll find out.
بۇ يەردە نېمە ئىش بولدى؟     - ھېچ ئىش -
- What is going on in here? - Not a thing.
نەيزە ئېتىش ئويۇنى     - نېمە دېدىڭىز؟ -
- A dart game. - I beg your pardon.
سىد بىزگە ئۆزىنىڭ نەيزە ئېتىش ئويۇنىنى بۇرۇن قانداق ئوينايدىغانلىقىنى دەپ بېرىۋاتاتتى
Sid was us telling how he used to dart playing.
...بۇنىڭدىن كېيىن سىدنىي، ئوقۇغۇچىلارنىڭ قىلىدىغان تېخىمۇ مۇھىم ئىشلىرىنىڭ
Well in future Sidney, kindly remember that the students have more important...
بارلىقىنى ئېسىڭىزدە تۇتۇڭ، گېپىمنى چۈشەندىڭىزمۇ؟
things to do, did you get my point?
چۈشەندىم، ئۇنىڭكىنىمۇ چۈشەندىم
Yeah, and his point as well.
ۋاي خۇدايىم!     - نېمە ئىش بولدى؟ -
- Good heavens! - What's the matter?
بۇ ئىشىكتە بىرمۇنچە تۆشۈك تۇرىدىغۇ
This door is full of holes.
بەلكىم ئۇ «ياغاچ قۇرت» نىڭ ئىشىدۇ
Maybe it's a wooden worm.
ياغاچ قۇرتى
Wood worm.
شۇنداق، ھېچقىسى يوق
Yeah, it's alright.
مەن ھېلىلا براۋن ئەپەندى بىلەن تېلىفۇندا پاراڭلاشتىم
Yes. I just had a telephone call from Mr. Brown.
ئۇ ئازراق كېچىكىپ كېلىدىغانلىقىنى ئېيتتى
He says he Would be along later.
ئېنىقكى, ئۇ ئۆيىنىڭ ئىشى بىلەن ئالدىراش
Apparently, he is tied up at his flat.
توۋا خۇدايىم! ئۇنى باغلاقتىن بوشىتىپ قويغىلى بېرىشىمىز كېرەكمۇ قانداق؟
Oh, blimey! Should we be going to untie him?
مەن كۆچمە مەنىدە گەپ قىلىۋاتىمەن
I was speaking metaphorically.
ئىنگلىزچە گەپ قىلسىڭىز ياخشىراق بولاتتى
It is better you speako English.
...تىنچلىنىڭلار! بەلكىم براۋن ئەپەندى سىلەرنىڭ
Silence! Now Mr. Brown may put up with...
...ئەخمىقانە گەپلىرىڭلارغا يول قويىدىغاندۇ، بىراق كېسىپ ئېيتىمەنكى مېنىڭ
your stupid remarks but I assure you...
ئۇنىڭغا زادىلا ئوخشىمايدىغانلىقىمنى ھېس قىلىپ قالىسىلەر
will find me a very different kettle of fish.
كەچۈرۈڭ، «بىر چەينەك بېلىق» دېگەن گەپنىڭ مەنىسى نېمە؟
Excuse me please, what is mean kettle of fish?
...،تېزلا بىلىپ قالىسىز. ئەمدى، براۋن ئەپەندى  يىتىپ كەلگىچە
You'll find out. Now, until Mr. Brown
...سىلەرنىڭ قانداقراق ئىلگىرلەۋاتقانلىقىڭلارنى بىلىپ باقاي
arrives, I intend to find out what sort of progress you are making.
سىز، ئۆگىنىشىڭىز قانداق كېتىپ بارىدۇ؟
You, how are you doing?
نېمە دېدىڭىز؟
Bocsánat?
ئۆگىنىشىڭىز قانداق كېتىپ بارىدۇ؟
How are you doing?
ناھايىتى ياخشى، رەھمەت. ئۆزىڭىزمۇ ياخشى تۇرغانسىز؟
Very pleased, thank you. How are you doing?
مەن ئىنگلىزچىڭىز ھەققىدە گەپ سورىغان
I'm inquiring about your English.
نېمە دېدىڭىز؟
Bocsánat?
ئىنگلىزچىڭىز
Your English
ياق، ياق، ۋېنگرىيىلىك
No, no, Hungarian.
سىزدە ئۈمىد يوقكەن
You're hopeless.
ياق، ياق، قاراڭ، ۋېنگرىيىلىك
No, no, look Hungarian.
ئولتۇرۇڭ
Sit down.
رەھمەت
Thank you.
سىز، «يۆتكىمەك» دېگەن پېئىلنىڭ ھازىرقى پۈتكەن زامان شەكلىنى دەپ بېرىڭ
You. Give me the present perfect of the verb to move.
بىلمەمسىز ئۇنى سىز»؟»
You know it not?
مەن ئەلۋەتتە بىلىمەن
Well, of course I know it.
«ياخشى، ئۇنداقتا دەپ بېرىڭ ماڭا سىز»
Oh good, then you can me tell?
مەن سىزگە جاۋاب بېرىپ يۈرىدىغان ئىش يوق
It is not my place to tell you anything.
«بولىدۇ، ئۇنداقتا «دەپ بەرمەڭ ماڭا ھېچ نەرسە
Okay, then you can tell me not.
سىز!     - ھە، خانىم -
- You! - Si, senora.
پەش» دېگەن نېمە؟»
What is a comma?
نېمە دېدىڭىز؟
Por favor.
پەش» دېگەن نېمە؟»
What is a comma?
پەش» دېگەن سىز سېزىمىڭىزنى يوقاتقان ۋاقىت»
Comma is when you are unconscious.
ئۇ دېگەن ھوشىدىن كېتىش. پەش دېگەن بىر تىنىش بەلگىسى
That's a coma. A comma is a Punctuation mark.
ئوھ، ھېچقىسى يوق
Oh, it's alright.
مەن براۋن ئەپەندىنى سىلەرگە ھېچ نەرسە ئۆگەتمىدى دەپ قارىمايمەن
I don't think Mr. Brown is teaching you anything.
ئۇستاز بىزگە ئىنگلىز تىلىنى شۇنداق كۆپ ئۆگەتتى
Master is teaching us very much English.
مەن يېڭى كەلگەن چاغدا، بىرمۇ ئادەم گېپىمنى چۈشەنمەيتتى
When I am arrived, not one body is understand me.
ھازىر، ھەممە ئادەم مەن دېگەن ھەممە گەپنى چۈشىنىدۇ
Now everybody is understand every thing I am speak.
...چۈشەندىم. بۇنداق ئەھۋالدا، ئەگەر بىر ئادەم
I see. Well, then in that case, if someone...
...سىزنى كوچىدا توختىتىپ سائەت نەچچە بولدى دەپ سورىسا
will stop you in the street and ask you the time...
نېمە دەپ جاۋاب بېرىسىز؟
what would you say?
بۇنىڭ ئۇلارغا قىلچە ياردىمى بولمايدۇ
That's wouldn't help them!
ئەلۋەتتە بولىدۇ، مەن تۇرىدىغان كوچىدىكىلەرنىڭ ھەممىسى ھىندىستانلىق
Oh yes, in my street, it's all Indian peoples.
!تىنچلىنىڭلار. سىز
Silence. You!
ھە
Yes please.
بىر توپ چۈمۈلىلەرنىڭ كوللېكتىپ ئاتالغۇسىنى دەپ بېرىڭ
Give ma a collective noun for a collection of ants.
«ھاممىلار»
Aunties.
ھاممىلار ئەمەس، چۈمۈلىلەر، ھاشارەتنىڭ گېپى. بىر مۇنچە چۈمۈلىلەرنى نېمە دەيمىز؟
Not aunts. Ants. Insects. What is a lot of ants?
ئۆلگۈر ئاۋارىچىلىق دەيمىز
A damn nuisance.
چۈمۈلە توپى دېگەن گەپنى ئەزەلدىن ئاڭلاپ باقمىغانمىتىڭىز؟
Have you never heard of swarm?
ئاڭلىغان، ئەنگلىيە پاكىستاننى «چۈمۈلە توپى» دەپ ئاتايدۇ
Yes please. England call Pakistan a swarm.
!تىنچلىنىڭلار
Silence!
ئوھ، كەچۈرۈڭ، كېچىكىپ قالدىم كورتنىي خېنىم
Oh sorry I'm late Miss Courtney.
مەنمۇ شۇ! ئوقۇغۇچىلىرىڭىزنىڭ قانداقراق كېتىپ بارغانلىقىنى كۆرۈپ بېقىۋاتاتتىم
So am I! I have just been seeing how your students are getting on.
مېنىڭچە ئۇلار خېلى ئوبدان ئىلگىرىلەۋاتىدۇ     - شۇنداق، بىراق قايسى يۆنىلىشكە قاراپ ئىلگىرىلەۋاتىدۇ؟ -
- Well, I think they're progressing. - Yes, but in which direction?
كورتنىي خېنىمنى خاپا قىلىدىغان قانداق گەپلەرنى قىلدىڭلار؟
What have you been saying to upset Miss Courtney.
...توۋا خۇدايىم، ھېچ نەرسە دېمىدۇق. ئۇ بىزدىن بىرقانچە سوئاللارنى سورىدى، بىز
Oh blimey, we are saying nothing. she is asking some questions and we are telling...
سوئالغا جاۋاب بەردۇق
her some answers.
ئۇنداق بولسا چۈشىنىشلىك
Well, that explains it.
بىرەر يەرگە بارامسىز؟
Are you going away?
پەقەت بىر كېچىلا، ئۆيۈمنى سىرلىتىۋاتقان ئىدىم، ئۆيدە ياتسام بولمايدىغانلىقىنىڭ سەۋەبى شۇ
Only for one night. I'm having my flat painted that's why I can't sleep there.
كارىۋىتىڭىزنىمۇ سىرلىتىۋاتقان ئوخشىمامسىز؟
You're having your bed painted also?
ياق، مەن يېڭى سىرنىڭ پۇرىقىغا پەقەت چىداپ بولالمايمەن
No, just I can't stand the smell of fresh glass paint.
بۈگۈن كېچە قەيەردە ئۇخلىماقچى بولىۋاتىسىز؟
Where would you be sleeping tonight?
I'll probably stay at the YMCA.
Hey, much better that the YWCA.
I suppose any of you have a spare room, do you?
It would give me much pleasure for you
to Share my humble house, but unfortunately,
my cousin and his family and also his
cousin and his family are staying with me.
You've got two families both living in one house?
Two families both living in one room.
You are very welcome to come and Stay with me.
Have you got a spare room?
No. But I have a very big bed.
Well, thank you for the offer but I thing it'd better be in the YMCA.
- You can with me stay. - Don't tell me you've got a very big bed also?
No. I have a small bed, better much.
Okay, you stay with us.
Who's Huss? Us?
Me and Giovanni.
Sure we've got a room.
I didn't know you share a flat.
Yeah, I had to leave my other place.
I had a big fight with the neighbor because of the noise.
What noise?
Every night after mid night guitar practice For one hour.
- Surely you can ask them to stop. - No.
- Why not? - It's me who practice the guitar.
And you still practice the guitar, do you?
- No, finish guitar. - Thanks goodness for that.
Now I practice the drums.
What?
That's ajoke. I don't practice anything. What do you say?
- Will you stay with us? - Well, I am
Okay, you stay. Hey, why don't we have a party.
That's a good idea. Everybody comes.
I'll bring a bottle.
Yeah, make it sure it's not empty.
I'll bottle bring.
We'll get us a pizza.
Chicken curry.
Fried rice.
Chapati and popadoms.
Ensalata.
Guiash.
German sausage.
Paella a la valenciana.
Duck.
Quiche Lorraine.
I make you suki-yaki.
We'll give you a night you'll never forget.
That's what I'm afraid of.
Well, come in professor.
Oh, thank you.
This is the hall, this is the kitchen, this is
my bedroom, Max's bedroom, this is the Living room, and this
And that's my bedroom.
No, that's the bathroom.
Oh, where am I sleeping?
You sleep here on the sofa.
Sure, it's very comfortable.
What was that?
What was what?
That awful noise.
It's only a train.
Only a train! This is worse then the Waiting room of waterloo station.
Don't worry, you'll get used to it.
They only run every ten minutes After rush hour finish.
I'll never get to sleep through all that noise.
We'll give you cotton ball to put in your ears.
Well, I would need it.
Hey, we better go get the drinks. You wanna come with us professor?
Well actually I'd like a bath if that's alright with you?
Okay, we'll be back in 10 minutes.
I left them here on the table.
Where is professor?
- Well he said he was going to have a bath. - - Okay, come on. Alright.
Just a moment.
Hello! Max! Giovanni! Anybody there?
The sergeant! Yes madame! A burgaler. Don't panic.
Stay where you are and I'll send a police car around right way.
- He's trying to pick next door's lock. - Don't worry, I'll sort him out.
Oh, I do hope this sort of thing doesn't happen often.
I only moved in here yesterday.
Stand back, I'm going out there. George, you stay with Mrs. Partridge.
Alright, come quietly.
- Oh, look you're making a mistake. - Could be.
No but I'm staying here with a friend.
What's the address?
I don't know. I've never been here before, you see?
I see.
Look there's a perfectly simple explanation
Well, why don't we come down to the station
And tell it to the perfectly simple sergeant.
Hey, the professor is not out here.
He is not in the bathroom.
Well, he's not out the either.
Maybe he decided to sleep at YMCA after all.
No, his bag is still there.
He said he was gonna have a bath.
Oh blimey, maybe he has gone down the plug hole.
A Japanese philosopher has said: When the person
is not here, he must be somewhere else.
We know he's somewhere else, but somewhere where?
Buenas noches.
Hey, what's the matter?
It's Mr. Brown.
- What about Mr. Brown? - He's gone.
Gona?
Ten minutes he was here, now he's gone?
Santa madre querida, espíritu...
He is not dead, he is vanished.
¡Gracias a Dios!
- Alright, what's your name? - Jeremy Brown.
- Brown? - Yes.
I suppose that'll make a change from a smith or
Jones. Now, according to P.C. Barnes,
- you were caught breaking and entering. - I was not breaking and entering.
- Were you picking the lock? - Yes, but
- Do you live there? - No, but
Charge: Breaking and entering.
Look, you're making a terrible mistake.
That's what criminals said.
I demand to see my lawyer.
Sid, they've not nabbed you tonight as well.
Is he one of you accomplicies?
No, I know him. He can vote for me.
He is in a state he ever can't vote for his own mother.
- What has he done Barnes? - Drunk and disorderly.
- Pardon? - Drunk and disorderly.
So am I.
Sergeant, he is the care taker at the school where I teach.
He will tell you who am I.
You, do you know this man?
He's a cop.
Sid, it's me, look! Tell the sergeant who I am.
Charlie Frenzbaf.
What?
Never tell him your own name son.
Oh, take him away. Bring him back when he's sober.
I'll be your sweet heart.
Now, Mr. Brown or Frenzbaf or whatever you call yourself
- Brown - Professor
Max! Giovanni! Thank goodness you're here. Look, tell
this, tell this sergeant who am I.
He's Mr. Jeremy Brown.
He teach us to speak the English.
Do you live in 6 Windsor road?
Sure we do. What happened? Where have you been?
Well, I've got locked out on your balcony and your
and your Public spirited neighbor thought I was
a burgular and called the police.
So you were telling the truth, hum?
And I have a good mind to see you for false arrest.
If you do so, there'll be a charge of asault and battery.
I haven't asaulted anyone.
No, but I should go now before I do.
Hey, everybody. We found Mr. Brown.
Now we all have a party.
Hey where is all the food?
We saved you a piece of quiche.
Oh good.
Blimey, I was hungry so I'm eating it.
Actually I can do with a drink.
No drink.
Nor a drop?
Si! One drop!
Don't worry professor. I'll fix everything for us.
Max, go.
Okay, I'll go get some beer.
Then we'll all have a party.
No, not all of us. I've made a date with Danielle.
We are going to have a dance.
¡Olé!
Señorita.
Enjoy your selves.
We must also be go.
Yes
Master, Ali will let me watch his television.
Yes, we don't want to Starkers and Cruch.
Starsky and Hutch.
Jolly good. See you at school time.
Bye everybody.
A thousand apologies.
Why? What have you done?
Nothing. It's what I'm going to be doing?
What are you going to be doing?
Take Ingrid for a show.
We're going to see Sweedish film.
It's being all about Sweedish Nopal.
I think you mean Noble.
That is correct. You'll be excusing us please!
Yeah, certainly. Have a good night.
Don't tell me you two are going to the pictures too!
No, not so. See Lee and me go to bedo
Not together, I'm going home to read a little red book.
I go sleep home.
Too much sake.
Hope you had a pleasant night.
Ciao.
That's going to be a sleeping party.
Not to worry. Now we got plenty of beer for five.
You have even more for three.
Oh not you too Anna.
Yeah, us too. I help Zoltan mid home walk.
Good morning.
Good night.
I hope.
Alright then, we are three.
Okay everybody hey, where is everybody?
- They all went out. - We've got such nice friends.
Hey, why don't we go down to the disco?
Yes, it's a good idea. And we will pick up a couple of birds.
I don't want to pick up a couple of birds.
Professor is right. We don't want to
pick up a couple of birds,
we'd pick up three birds. One each.
Now you two go on.
Why don't you want to come with us?
Well, I feel tired and wounded. I think I'll just turn in for the night.
You sure now?
Yeah, but don't let that stop you from going.
Okay.
I'll just get ready for bed.
And you'll find some blankets in the cupboard
Any cotton balls?
In the bathroom.
Thank you, see you tomorrow.
Why is he shouting?
I don't know.
You want a beer before we go?
Sure!
It's stuffy in here! That's better.
Nice party!
Fantastic. You know Max? I really fancy that Ingrid.
Yeah, you fancy anyone.
That's not true, is it? I don't fancy you.
Hey, our lights just gone out.
Mr. Brown must wanting to sleep.
We better go to the disco.
Okay.
It's locked.
Hey, professor.
The house was very quiet, nothing could be
heard. Yet the old lady could almost feel a
sense of heaving. She listened, the silence was
opressive. Suddenly there was a knock at the
window.
Yes, sergeant. Oh, it's not you again madam.
Are you sure it's not the same fellow? There are
two fellows? Look, I suggest you just sit there and
wait, go around and see a neighbor and wait till
the constable arrives, okay?
Coming!
Oh please excuse me, the front door was open. I did knock.
Oh sorry, I was a sleep.
There are burglars on my balcony.
Are you sure?
Yes, I saw their evil looks. They might be opening my
doors now.
The front window wasn't locked.
Oh I see alright leave it with me. I'll go see what they're up to.
Do be careful!
Yes!
What are we going to do?
Break the window.
Max! Giovanni! What are you doing here?
You locked us out.
Yeah, we knocked on the window next door
and the woman screamed and ran away.
She thought you were burglars.
Come on, get inside.
Just a moment. I'll go get the beer.
No, no, no. I'll go get it. You stay here.
Alright. Turn around.
Now are you sure you don't mind me staying
Here for the night?
Not at all sir. I think it will be safer for both
Right. At least I'll get some sleep.
Good night sir!
Good night.
Who's that?
It's you Mr. Brown. Let's sing a song!