Zigis!
Why do you jump in if you can't swim?
- I can.
Fond of sunbathing, eh?
Did you swallow water?
That's out of fear.
It's alright.
Fear can sometimes be useful. Hold on.
Here!
Can't you look after
your brother, you two?
What about your communist discipline?
Seems you’re all just talk.
Come and pick up Zigis!
Come on!
Dad, what about the booze?
We'll unload it later tonight.
You'd better think a little.
You think it's funny?
Mum! Mum!
What happened?
Zigis, you're so...
Come here.
- You're wet!
You smell of booze!
The booze is not for you.
Hey!
Way to go.
Get down!
Come on! Let's get lost.
There are things that Dad doesn't tell us.
Secrets must be kept.
Zigis! Go to bed!
Aina. We'll have to hide you.
Stay with us.
You can stay.
Dad, I'll escape with them.
You have to be strong.
Where are you going? The city's on fire!
Aina is nowhere to be found.
- I know.
We have to go and look for her.
- Stop it!
She is gone!
You can't make a hideout for your
daughter! Just for your moonshine!
Perhaps she has retreated
with the Russians.
It's be better for her.
How can you say that?!
I'll pay. - Get lost!
Some potatoes...
- Get lost! Just get lost!
I need no Jews hanging around here.
- I have money.
Please... - I don't need any Jews here.
Get lost!
Go back to the forest
where you came from!
Get lost!
- What are you doing?
I need no Jews here.
- Why aren't you selling him food?
Madam, mind your own business!
Is he any different?
- I need no Jews here!
Look at him? Is he any different?
- I need no Jews here.
Zigis!
- Who deported Latvians?
Here you are.
Ah, madam! You should read the
newspapers! - Right!
Mina, let's run!
Is your Dad home?
- I'll call him.
Arke, we're friends.
Tell me, what's wrong?
I'm begging you.
Take my daughter, please!
You know I can't.
I brought everything of value that I had.
You must keep her safe until...
things calm down.
Arke, stop it.
Why are you wearing that star?
No one needs to know
that you're a Jew.
Take my daughter.
Žanis, please!
Arke!
Mina!
I have a family.
Žanis...
Just go!
- Žanis...
Go!
I know.
Nothing can be done.
Cinema "Renaissance"
The city of Riga is in German hands!
The city was liberated from the Soviets
in a few hours…
Fire fighters worked hard...
What...?!
- Wait, wait, wait!
I let him in, he was hiding
from the Germans.  - What?!
I will pay!
- Shut up!
If you throw him out now,
he'll be shot.
Do you want them to shoot you?
I won't say a word.
- Shut up!
He'll spill the beans
if they catch him.
If you throw him out now,
he'll spill the beans for sure!
A couple of days, no more.
If you blab I will kill you.
Go there.
And don't show.
You are an idiot.
A short rest after heavy fighting...
There's no limit to the anger and
indignation for the Jewish murderers.
The felons were caught
by the relatives of the victims
and brought to justice, as they were delivered up to criminal court.
The Synagogue of Riga...
Damn!
...spared by the commissars before, was swallowed by flames
some hours later.
I have to work for the Germans now.
Do you understand?
Sit here.
Luftwaffe workshop
Please, help me.
Help my brother and sister.
Help me.
- Don't touch me!
Why...?
- Halt, you shit!
My brother and sister...
Halt!
Why aren’t you at work?
Open up!
What's going on here?
- Shut up!
Where's that lousy Jew?
- He is my employee.
An employee?
- You can't come in.
Why not? - This territory belongs
to the German Army.
Do you have a Gestapo permit?
- What fucking permit?
You don't?
- He has it coming.
And behind these tragic documents
we can see the repulsive mug
of the international Jewry!
Move.
Quick.
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
If you say that I did wrong to Arke...
You know it already.
I know that you care.
Think about them.
It's horrible.
We have to go.
Everybody goes.
- Now I have a place to hide you.
No.
There's enough space.
Too late.
- Arke...
Everything will be alright.
Arke...
Too late...
Go!
Name, surname?
I hear you've been associating
with your Jewish friend.
I know nothing about that.
Are these Jewish belongings?
No. These are the family treasures.
From our German relatives.
Take him out!
Your daughter is a communist.
Where is she?
Please! We don't know where Aina is!
I don't know.
What kind of a father are you?
Just nod.
Stay down!
Yes, I understand.
Why are you so rude to him? Leave!
Who are you?
I don't understand.
Then let's get acquainted.
My name is Lehmann.
Lipke.
Jānis Lipke.
But my name will mean nothing to you.
Don't be so sure!
You used to collaborate with the Soviets.
You were involved in illegal trading.
What is your current occupation?
I'm a mechanic...
...at Luftwaffe warehouses.
- No, seriously!
What is your current occupation?
I don't understand.
Well, let's take your daughter...
She is with the communists now,
fighting against us.
My daughter...
I haven't seen her for ages.
I don't know her anymore.
It's not very original.
What about your family?
What would happen to them?
Herr Lipke.
There's no use in keeping silent.
I've told you.
There's nothing I can tell you.
It will weigh on your conscience.
If not now then later.
Perhaps you are helping the Jews?
The Jews?
I don't know any Jews.
And I don't want to know any.
Fine.
However, in the long run
it's no use keeping silent.
You will be all alone.
It's really not worth it.
It all ends with death.
There will be no communists
and no Jews any more.
Rest assured.
We are going to keep
an eye on you, Lipke.
Gauleiter Lauterbacher is talking
about the importance of your mission.
Men from all walks of life -
workers, peasants, civil servants...
Here.
...all are taking part...
Put it down here.
Here.
Fricis!
Are you taking in
some more people tomorrow?
I don't know yet. Damn!
Nine...
Eleven...
Thirteen...
Seventeen...
Halt!
Go on! Eighteen...
Twenty and twenty-one.
The whole group has
returned to the Ghetto.
Arke! Now we can get
more people out of the Ghetto.
This changing of clothes
is no good any more.
We can get caught at any moment.
If the number of people doesn't match,
we're all dead.
You too have to come out.
Žanis, you said yourself…
- That was then.
Now it's different.
You won't manage without me
on this side.
We have to get out
at least your wife and Mina.
They won't leave without me.
We have to stay.
Just don't stay too long.
Alright...
Here's the list of people. - Okay
Anyone trying to climb over the fence
or contact the residents of the Ghetto
will be shot without warning
What are you doing
so late in the Ghetto?
We brought a Jewish work crew.
And it took too long.
- So you say.
I mean, it took too long.
- Yes. So you say.
Everything is in order.
- Thank you.
Good night.
- Good night.
Madness! He betrayed us like that!
You have no idea... That shit...
You have no idea...
Why didn't they take me away?
I don't understand!
Stop it!
- That asshole betrayed us!
A couple of days...
Asshole!
When the Germans came,
I allowed him to stay at the cinema...
Stop raging...
- How could I not rage?
How could I not?
It's absolute madness!
Wait!
So you like blood, do you?
I told you. If you spill the beans...
We'll hide people in our house.
Are you out of your mind?
No, we can't do it!
You may not care what happens to you,
but think about the boys.
We have to take the risk.
There's no choice.
I am not picking up
dead bodies any more.
Žanis. Please!
We must.
We won't hide them inside the house.
In the pit.
You have to trust me.
Halt!
Halt, you Jewish shit!
Stay where you are!
I'll shoot!
Aren't you afraid of dying?
What?
No.
Thats not wise
One must fear death.
so as not to succumb to it too easily
All right, Zigis. Look.
If you see a stranger
walking behind the fence...
press the switch.
Let's go.
Well, Zigis. Come down to us.
Come on.
You have never visited us.
Be careful.
Keep silent.
Careful, careful.
Go on, go on.
Feet first.
That's it.
Clear off! Clear off!
They're coming! The guards!
One more! Quick!
One more!
That’s it. Go!
I'll go.
No, you won't.
That's the right decision.
If Fredis does not join the German Army,
they'll be here in no time.
We'll hide him. They won't find him.
Really?
Maybe they won't find Fredis.
But how about the bunker?
Fine.
Who are we going to send away next?
No need to dramatize.
Mum, really! Don't!
Zigis!
Zigis?
Come with me.
Go back in, quick!
Go in! Quick!
- We came out for a moment...
Go in, quick!
Mummy!
Your brother...
He's gone.
From now on you should stay
in the bunker.
You must not come out.
Žanis. What are we going to do?
I'll think of something.
All right?
He does not have a plan
what to do with us.
It's pointless sitting here.
We have to do something.
All the able-bodied males
in the territory of the Ghetto
must report for transfer.
Any refusal to comply with the order
will be punished.
Attention! Attention!
All the able-bodied males
in the territory of the Ghetto
must report for transfer.
Any refusal to comply with the order
will be punished.
Attention! Attention...
Daddy! Daddy!
Don't go anywhere!
Out! Out!
There are some people there.
Out, out! Quick!
Out!
What happened down there?
Were you entertaining yourselves?
This one ate up everything.
That one got mad.
You understand.
- No, I don't.
We have enough food.
No, we don't.
We have to ration.
People will freeze to death.
You’ll have to somehow
weather the night.
You and you. Come with me.
Your mother is a very good person.
We can go.
Get down.
Careful.
There is no more space here.
- Stop it! Be quiet.
Then think of something!
- Hush!
We would be lost without him.
...Then he went to the pub
and saw that girl, Lola.
Her hips and her boobs...
And the professor forgot
about his students.
All he could think about was that beauty.
The film was set in a
small German town...
I can't...
I can't stand it anymore.
What are you blabbing about?
I can't stand it anymore!
What are you blabbing about?!
Let me out! Let me out!
Let me out!
Calm down!
- Let me out!
Let me...
You must not go there!
You have nothing to do there!
Soon they will be gone.
And then you’ll miss them.
Go and play with the dog.
It's pointless.
All right. Who wants to come with me?
All right. The ones who'll go...
Nathan...
Avi...
Your papers.
Civilians are forbidden
to leave the city for now.
What are you carrying?
- Nothing special.
Old rubbish that may come in handy.
And underneath?
Just a couple of Russians.
Go back.
I can't let you pass.
Here's your papers. - Yeah, thanks.
Shit...
Get lost! Quick!
Get lost!
Hey, do you have a smoke?
Hey...
Arke, are you there?
Send out the next ones.
Žanis, there won't be any.
They won't come.
They're afraid.
I can't persuade anyone.
It's no joke!
Something's not all right.
Don't just stand here. Go away!
You and your family must leave.
Yes. Soon.
Damn!
Fucking Russians!
Just don't talk about guilt.
You have changed.
You're like a child.
We have become strangers.
It's not true.
It is.
Quick!
All the able-bodied males
in the territory of the Ghetto...
They were taken away.
No more...
This very morning...
my little girl...
We have to go. We have to go.
Almost all were taken away.
They didn’t let me go with them.
Arke, you can do nothing about it.
I have nowhere to go.
I can't, Žanis...
Žanis must leave the Ghetto
immediately. The guards are coming!
Arke...
Just go!
Faster!
Faster
Move!
Faster!
I can't stand it!
What are you doing? Are you mad?
Go on! Go on!
Move on!
Not so slow!
Go on, go on.
I said, move!
Soon there won't be anyone left there.
We have to...
We have to get out more people
as soon as possible.
There was...
There was a crowd.
You cannot save everyone.
But there should be more….
More should be saved.
More...
You're risking your neck.
They'll come.
Sooner or later.
Sharya here used to know
someone at the port.
He said he could take some people out.
I'll take them to the port.
Then we'll see.
Thank you.
Quiet now!
Lipke?
Yes?
Are these your papers?
- Yes.
They were in the pocket of my coat.
The coat was stolen from me
a couple of days ago.
I was really freezing.
- Cut the crap!
What about these Jews here?
Do you know them?
Did they rob you?
No.
I don't know. And these robbers...
I don't know them either.
They say all kinds of people
are showing up here.
You meter is running really fast.
Turn off the heater, quick!
If it turns out that you've sheltered them,
you'll be guilty not only of...
My house is...
no shelter for any Jews.
Tell me, boy, do you know these men?
- No.
You can tell me,
nothing will happen to your father.
You know these men, don't you?
- No.
Hands off!
Go there.
That's it. Stop the search.
He won't be a nuisance any more.
There's nothing.
We are lucky.
Damn!