Go to sleep.
I'm not tired.
Ok.
Let's make up a story together.
- You want me to start? - Yes.
Once there was this village, that all of it's inhabitants had left.
Even the rats had left it.
And so stood this village, silent, abandoned for many years to come.
Rain beat on the streets,
washing away the traces of people.
When the rain stopped,
Birds flew over the village.
There were so many that it was difficult to see the sky.
The whole day was night.
While in a small house ...
A little boy opened the door.
He was the only one left in the village.
"Story of love and darkness"
38 years old my mother was when she died.
In my present age, I could be her father.
Many things have happened in Jerusalem.
The city was destroyed, rebuilt, destroyed and rebuilt.
The conquerors, one after another came to Jerusalem, ruled it for some time,
left behind several walls and towers, a few notches on the rock, a handful of shards -
and disappeared,
like the morning mist from the slopes of these mountains.
Jerusalem - an old nympho, shake off the lovers, after having squeezed them.
- We are late. - The child, Arie.
My mother grew up in the city of Rovno,
who was then in Poland, today in Ukraine.
Her childhood there consisted of words such as chandeliers,
servants, mystery,
romantic melancholy.
At a time when anti-Semitism had spread across Europe,
she dreamed about Israel,
the land flowing with milk and honey, that pioneers turned the desert into a blooming garden.
She imagined a pioneering poet, worker, a revolutionary,
a man born to bear arms, to cultivate the land,
and, at the same time, to love the culture, possess a rich soul and developed intellect.
After mom and his family fled to Palestine,
Pines in the forest,
in the forest, where my mother and her sisters
He loved to pick mushrooms and berries,
spend the night in sleeping bags in the creek under a starry sky,
Germans, Lithuanians and Ukrainians murdered in
within two days more than 23 thousand Jews ...
Almost everyone who knew my mother.
A million little children ...
A million little children they killed! Children like you!
Slaughtered!
Jerusalem, 1945. The British Mandate.
Good afternoon, dear lady. I would like Tel Aviv 648.
Please wait, sir, a little while.
Right now Mr. Nashashibi is speaking.
I'm waiting my lady, of course, I'm waiting,
- But people are also waiting at the other end. - It's too early, Arie.
- But still we connect ... - But what will happen if we connect,
but they're still not there?
Hello? Zvi?
- It's me. - It Arie. From Jerusalem.
Yes, Arie, hello. It's me, Zvi. How are you?
We are fine. We call you
- From the pharmacy. - Ask my sister, how is.
What do you tell? What's in Tel Aviv?
Everything is fine. Nothing special. We live.
If not news - it's too bad. And we have no news.
We will write a letter and agree, when we will speak over the telephone the next time.
- Take care of yourselves. Good luck. - And you.
They were not sure at all that they would really talk another time.
A million little children ...
Suddenly there could be riots, pogroms, massacres, the British could turn against us ...
The curfew will be starting soon.
Hello everybody.
- Good evening. - Good evening.
Close the window! Close the door, please.
They went away. Everyone.
It's as if Rovno was only a dream.
It arrived.
New book directly from the printer.
"Novella in Hebrew Literature"
My first book.
"IA Klausner. Novella in Hebrew Literature"
This is almost like having another child.
I'll invite your parents.
My first teacher of literary history - my only brother David, who I lost in the darkness of exile. Where are you?
Who said that only your uncle would be the one with higher education in the family?
- It is - only my first publication. - Yes.
Not the last.
Borscht cute. Not bad.
Almost tasty.
But even peasant cooks in Jewish homes,
knew that the soup must be sour and only slightly sweet,
and in any case not the other way around - sweet and a little sour, as it is accepted by the Poles,
that pour sugar in everything in the world beyond measure.
Even they herring, they dip in jam.
Let's raise our glasses in honor of the book, which was published.
- Good luck! - Let's drink! - Good luck!
If forced to choose between lying and the ability to cause offense to a person,
Choose to be generous.
I'm allowed to lie?
Sometimes yes.
It is better if you're sensitive than direct.
Good. Come on.
Come, hold a peg.
We will create a small kibbutz.
- Own hands will get the bread out of the earth! - Kadima (forward).
You know, "Kadima" - means "to move" or "forward".
But...
the word, in fact, derives from "kedem" (Antiquity)
implying ancient times.
Therefore, speaking in Hebrew is, in essence, looking back in time.
- Interesting? - Yes.
- Good. - Are you okay?
Arie?
You recognize me even underneath all of this sweat? Pay attention to this.
- That's it. - That's it?
That's it.
My father told me once.
Amos, pay attention to the connection between the words:
"Adama" (earth, soil), "Adam" (man)
"Dam" (blood)
"Adom" (red)
"Dumiyah" (silence).
You sit for 6 months by yourself writing a new novel,
and immediately all the beautiful girls snatches them from the shelves,
and takes them straight to read in their beds.
At least, my books deliver a bit of fun.
If your goal is to get girls,
then maybe you should write romantic stories.
All I am saying is, don't hurry.
Ask your sisters, your life belongs only to you
for a very short period of time
after leaving the parental home before the first pregnancy.
And when your child is grown up, you will not become, as before, by yourself,
because you go from being a mom to being a grandma.
But everyone says that children is the best thing that can happen to you.
Who is everyone?
Remember what happened to the neighbor?
- Ira? - Yes.
Wife to Stilyetski.
- Yes Yes. - Yes, she had an alcoholic husband,
who ran our fathers mill.
He was betting her in a card game and lost her ...
everytime until one night.
Until at last she left him and fled with the son of the coachman.
Anton!
So, from his house,
she could see her children playing from a distance.
One day she decided to visit her daughter.
When she approached, her daughter called her a whore,
and did not want to talk to her.
That night, Ira gathered remnant forces,
entered into the small hut with kerosene ...
and lit a match.
Our children do not understand how much they can hurt us.
I just do not understand why ...
Why nobody warned you?
What do you want, a warning written in small letters,
that says, in the end, you are - just food?
That you are what the chick eats in order to grow and get stronger?
Polina, no one warns us,
because every mother thinks she is the only one who feels like this,
and every mother is crying alone in her pillow at night.
Exept for our mother who cursed us.
"Tarzan the invincible"
- Don't do any tricks. Be a good boy. Ok? - Ok.
My parents friends, Statzek and Mala Rudnitzki,
were childless,
so sometimes my parents left me with them.
Dad, as usual,
explained that the word "Chasuch" in the expression "Chasuche yeladim" (Childless)
Indeed, was connected to the word "Chashecha" (darkness),
and is similar in sound and spelling to the word "Schichecha" (oblivion). And perhaps, the ancient sense of the word -
lack of memory,
the absence of children,
absence of light.
My mother would sometimes leave by herself.
Where?
I could only imagine.
When we visit the Arab house,
it is important to remember courtesy.
No children or even young people, should not,
in any case, interfere with the adult conversation.
Only if we turn to you directly,
answer briefly, energetically, but politely.
If refreshments are served,
Do not dare to take something that will crumble or spill.
And if they still insist that you take something, then refuse,
but delicately, like a gentleman,
even if you can not resist the sight of sweets.
After all, we were invited only through Uncle Stashek,
who helped al-Hilwani's son get out of jail.
If we hold negative attitudes
we behave like animals,
and that is not only first-class insolence,
that can do terrible damage to the future of the two nations.
Coat? Coat?
My friend, you are welcome!
Pleased to meet you, madam. Pleased to...
I would like you to meet with my friend the great Mr. Sarf.
Mr. Sarphil helped to clear my son, Edward from that unfortunate incident
at the beginning of summer. Thank you for coming.
Please come. Maybe the young sir
Maybe the young sir would like to go play in the garden?
Please, please, madam.
Come on, dear, let's go home.
Good morning, my lady.
My name is Amos. And you?
My name is Aisha.
This - my brother, Awad.
Your father, your dear father,
He invited me to go out to play with you.
He is not my father. He is the uncle of my mother.
I do not live here, I live in Talbieh.
How do you know Hebrew?
I have been learning to play the piano in Rehavia (In Jerusalem) for 3 years now.
Hebrew is a beautiful language, and the Rehavia quarter is also very beautiful.
Clean and quiet.
The Talbieh quarter is also clean and quiet.
Is it possible to talk a little bit?
Aren't we already talking?
The land of Israel has enough space for two people.
You just need to learn to live together in peace and respect.
I have another older brother in London. He is studying to become a lawyer.
What do you want to study, when you grow up?
What do you want to be?
You will eventually lawyer. Judging by your talk.
Why do you think so?
I'm going to write a book.
Indeed? Which kind of book?
Poems.
- Poems? - Yes, in French and in English.
I also write in Arabic, but do not show it to anyone.
- Are there beautiful poems in Hebrew? - Of course.
Levin Kipnis, Rachel, Zeev Jabotinsky, Tchernichovsky ...
"A generation of the land,
full of life,
withdraws from the chains of slavery."
You know how to climb trees?
I do not have any minute.
Give me a minute.
Give me a minute ...
This is the father of Amos.
May I please speak with Mr. al-Hilwani?
Well, could you please tell him how very truly sorry we are about what happened?
We are anxious for the health of the dear child.
We will pay any of the childs medical expenses of course in full.
We sincerely wish to set a meeting at an early date to clarify
we tried to right a wrong ...
Once upon a time there were two monks who had taken upon themselves all sorts of strict vows.
In particular, they vowed to walk on foot through all of India
from end to end.
And they also vowed complete silence
not utter a single word, even in a dream, during all the years of travel.
But one day, when they went to the river bank,
they both heard a cry for help. A screaming woman drowning in the turbulent flow.
Without words and conversations the youngest of them jumped into the water,
and on his back brought the drowning woman to shore, silently laid it on the sand,
and both the monks continued on in silence.
And now, after six months or even a year,
suddenly the young monk asked his companion:
"Tell me,
do you think I have sinned, carrying the woman on my back?"
But comrade replied with a question:
"What, you still continue to carry her on your back?"
You know, Amos,
when I was a student,
I loved to sit here among the flowers, and read.
And one day, after school, she met your future father.
Do you remember? I told you about the word "Perach" (Flower).
The word "Perach" (Flower) is composed of "Par" and "Reach" (Fragrance).
"Par" is the root of "Pirion" (Fertility)
and "Reach" is the fragrance that tempts the insect to fertilize the plants.
He exploits your mothers weakness for words.
Well, what could I do?
All the students courted her. I had to stand out.
Exactly.
Remembering -
it's like trying to build an ancient building
of the stones of its ruins.
And the stones remember.
Could I please get some A.P.C?
Yes, immediately.
I have a headache that does not leave me.
I do not believe them. No, I do not believe.
- It's a huge affair. - You think so?
What are you saying that all this - only intrigue?
All of this - a huge affair, as in the theater.
After all, Ben-Gurion had already quietly agreed to sell all of Jerusalem to King Abdullah.
And for that the British and the Arabs leave the kibbutzim alone.
And what will happen to us -
- to slaughter us, or burn us? It makes no difference to them. - What is with you? What are you saying?
A million little children ...
If there is a war, when there will be a war, we will win it.
Our state is literally standing at the gate.
- A million little children. - It is not standing. There is no gate.
There is an abyss. - Not in front of the boy.
Ugh.
- Nothing has grown. - Come here.
You know, if you open a human skull and take out the brain,
You will see that our brain is merely a cauliflower?
Merely a cauliflower like this.
But what a miracle:
Such a small cauliflower
holds the heavens and the earth,
and the sun and all the stars,
and Plato's ideas
and the music of Beethoven,
and Chekhov's play's ...
And maybe all of the dinosaurs and whales ...
And the hope of humanity, and passion, and lust, and errors, and fantasy ...
And that's it.
You do not know how to throw.
Amos!
Come play with us.
I can not. Grandma comes today.
Children! What are you doing there?
You abandoned me. I have no life here.
You spat in my face, in the face of your mother,
the only person who ever cared about you!
Look at yourself.
How do you stand it?
This place is disgusting.
Oh, I'm not good enough to recieve an answer from you?
I should have left you in Rovno!
It would have been better for me!
Fanichka!
Fania.
Amos, where is your mother?
You will not believe.
My books are sold, all five!
He said he will order more. And he have already ordered five more by phone.
He said that this is only the beginning.
Let's go to the movies and see "Edison", the new film.
You will go to Zarkhi at this time, okay?
For us.
Both hell and paradise
can be found in every room.
A little bit of wickedness -
and a person is in hell.
A little compassion, a little generosity -
and a person is in paradise ...
Hello, congratulations.
I still do not believe it.
Regards from Garbo.
Amos, behave yourself.
Book?
Tchernichovsky.
I think your patience helped our plants.
Why do not you go and take a look for yourself?
When my family moved to the house on Dubinskaya street,
They continued to live tenants there "inherited" from the previous owners.
In the anterior room lived a Polish officer with the name of Jan.
Every Friday, my mother sent one of us
with a tray of poppy biscuits, fragrant, fresh from the oven,
I wish him "Shabbat shalom" on behalf of the entire family.
Shabbat shalom.
Cutie.
And he stroked the girl's head,
He called her "gypsy"
and he promised her that he was waiting only for her,
and he promised to marry her as soon as she gets older.
But one day,
Sunday, before dawn,
even before the first glimmer of light,
The officer decided to check how his gun.
First, he released two bullets to the closed window facing the garden.
By chance he hit a dove.
The next day, this pigeon was found in the courtyard, wounded, but alive.
Then officer drove one bullet
in a wine bottle standing on the table,
He shot twice at the chandelier in the ceiling ...
and ...
Once I found a note in the closet hidden in a slot,
written by a female hand.
"My little Zevon, know that you are very dear to me!
Throughout my life I have never met a man better and nobler than you.
I am not worthy to kiss the soles of your shoes. "
In the word "sole" I found two grammatical errors.
The note was signed with the letter G.
and in the end it was painted with puffy lips, the substitute for a kiss.
No one knows anything about the other.
Even about your husband or wife. And no one knows anything about himself.
We know nothing.
And if at times it seems for a moment that we know, then it's even worse,
because it is better not to know anything,
than to live deceived.
November 29, 1947
Tonight, in Lake Success, near New York,
The United Nations General Assembly
will meet to vote for that?
For the adoption of UNSCOP Committee recommendations.
And what is the recommendation?
Create the territory of the British Mandate of two independent states:
One Jewish and one Arab.
Who objects?
Islamic countries, along with the UK Government.
And why?
Their goal is the transformation of the whole of the land of Israel into an Arab state under British protectorate,
like Egypt, Transjordan and Iraq.
Well done.
You know, Lake Success, means in English the "Lake of Success".
That is the exact opposite of "Sea of ​​Tears"
The term Bialik used to symbolize the fate of our people.
- It's interesting. - Wow, that's interesting.
Mali: yes.
Pakistan: no.
Panama: yes.
Paraguay ...
Yes.
- Peru ... - Excuse me, can you help me? - Yes.
Take him to his mother.
- Netherlands: yes. - Yes!
- Saudi Arabia: no. - Come, my dear.
Siam: no.
Sweden: yes.
Syria: no.
Turkey: no.
Ukraine: yes.
Union of South Africa: yes.
- Yes ... - The Soviet Union: Yes.
United Kingdom: abstained.
USA: Yes.
- Uruguay: yes. - It was a "yes"!
Venezuela: yes.
Yemen: no.
Yugoslavia: abstained.
The resolution of the special commission on the question of Palestine
was adopted by the Organization of the United Nations.
The people of Israel are alive! The people of Israel are alive!
The people of Israel, the people of Israel, the nation of Israel lives!
Everything changes, everything must change.
I told you so.
"We brought peace to you ...
We brought peace to you ... "
Finally.
You can not imagine at all how the boys mocked me
In the Polish school in Vilnius.
And when the next day, my father, your grandfather,
came to the school, demanding justice, and hooligans attacked him.
Knocking him to the ground ...
and pulled off his pants in the middle of the courtyard.
All the kids were laughing,
and teachers watched in silence.
Some of them, also, laughed.
Of course, one day bullies will annoy you, on the street or at school.
Perhaps they will do it just because you're a little bit like me.
But now, from the moment that we have a state,
bullies will never bother you, because you are Jewish. Never.
After about three hours,
seven in the morning, while we were sleeping,
Jerusalem Arabs began armed attacks on Jewish vehicles
which spread throughout the country.
My nickname is Garibaldi.
I will instruct you,
how to help our patriots.
You will help ...
You will search through all the yards, all the sheds and warehouses,
will collect and empty bags to fill them with sand,
and empty bottles. Some will be able to fill them with a cocktail,
very tasty for the enemy.
On vacant lots and abandoned backyards you will collect "Chubeza" (a wild plant)
to somehow counter the threat of famine in Jerusalem.
We also set the duty observers
to prevent any movement of the British. Go.
How nice. Wash, and I'll make some right now.
Of course, you are hungry after your search.
Fill this with water.
Fanichka.
I mobilized in self-defense units, Fanichka.
You have nothing to say to this?
What do you want me to say?
Well done, you are very brave.
The war invaded our house.
Life turned into rations, sandbags, work.
In the life of individuals,
as well as in the lives of the people as a whole,
the most terrible conflicts erupt between two sides that are persecuted.
Only in fantasy, do both sides that are persecuted united in solidarity
to fight with the cruel oppressor together.
But in fact,
two sons of the same father,
do not necessarily become allies.
It often happens that they don't see a brother as a fellow,
but as a reflection of the face of their common oppressor.
Europe, mocked the Arabs,
humiliated and robbed them by colonialism,
and it was the same Europe, that persecuted and destroyed the Jews.
But the Arabs, looking at us, they see in front of them not a nervous handful of refugees,
but an extension of the arrogant European colonizers.
And we, on our part, look at the Arabs
and we see before us not victims, like us, but bloodthirsty anti-Semites,
Nazis in disguises.
At midnight on May 15, 1948
The 30-year-old power of the British Mandate ended ...
... Proclaimed by Ben Gurion in Tel Aviv
a few hours before midnight.
For many weeks our basement apartment served as a kind of refuge
for the residents of the upper floors.
I have a connection ...
- You're pulling, it hurts. - Sorry, sorry.
100 Jews were burned alive yesterday, not far from the quarter Sheikh Jerash.
They were in a convoy that was on it's way to the Hadassah hospital and to the university.
100 people.
Doctors and nurses, workers and students.
Why did they stop?
The British gave no exit.
How can you enjoy the taste of a quarter of this chicken,
when there is such misery going on right before your eyes?
The children have not gotten any meat for months...
Please, madam.
- I do not know why we stayed here. - Who is next?
When they killed her friend,
when a tragedy occurs outside pages of my mother's novels,
suffering did not seem romantic to her at all.
We reached an armistice agreement with Egypt.
After Egypt there will be an agreement with Transjordan,
and then in the end there will be an agreement with Syria and Lebanon.
Thank God!
When the British left,
the green line was established around Israel.
The neighbors returned to their homes enthusiastic and optimistic,
and left us alone.
With the founding of an independent Jewish state,
It disappeared as if it was not,
thousands of years of longing of the Jewish people
for their homeland.
Maybe my mother felt the loss of desire, dreams,
because suddenly she ceased to tell their stories.
"And there, what do my eyes see?
A boy of about three years stands in the middle of the street,
in constrast to a flying war machine.
I braced myself and I shouted:
"Boy, boy!"
- "And as I shouted, I rushed up to him ..." - What's he saying?
and he quickly moved aside.
Who knows? Maybe his mom left him?
Maybe his family is very poor, and was not able to feed him,
and could not see the child hungry?
And perhaps the boy is an orphan without parents?
Yes, there are such in our world. "
- I told you, wait for me! - Who do you think is the best football player?
- It seems to me like Dado is. - I think I am.
- No, I think I'm a little better. - I am. - No, I am.
- David, Moshe, you and me. - What if? Look at it this way:
Me, and then David, then Moses, and then you.
You are very funny, you know.
Give me your sandwich.
I'll be back in fifteen minutes.
Can I go with you?
I need to spend some time alone.
Stay here.
I'll be back soon.
Maybe, you can tell me, finally,
what it is about you, that I love so much?
More than anything..
More than anything I love your naiveté.
Never in all my life I have never met such naiveté.
Even after you will lived a long life,
and have had many experiences,
This naivete will not leave you. Never.
I think that when you grow up, you will be that kind of man that is ...
open and enthusiastic like your father.
But at the same time you will be quiet and closed man,
deep and full, like a well in a village abandoned by its inhabitants ...
It's possible to be simultaneously thus and thus.
I was suddenly filled with horror.
It seemed, from a distance, on the horizon,
coming and gradually becoming ever more clearly, some unknown disaster.
My mother started having headaches.
Together with migraine
came insomnia.
The doctor prescribed all sorts of sleeping pills and anti-anxiety medications,
but it did not help.
Please do not be mad at me, Amos.
It's a little rough for me right now,
but you can see that I am trying to make everything ok.
Thank you, Amos.
I know I can count on you completely.
- Good night. - Good night.
- Dad? - Sleep, sleep.
I'm a lucky girl, I'm a lucky girl.
Thank you.
Your Mom punishes herself,
just to punish me.
Go.
Go, play a little bit on the street.
Just be very careful. Women are different.
They're not all as good and honest as you.
Come back when you want.
You need something?
Amos is here.
Dad and I had to tell the neighbors,
that she had the flu or a special sensitivity to daylight,
or that she was very tired.
We did not tell anyone what was only known to both of us.
The only one who knew was her closest friend.
Amos, you are a ray of light, you know that?
Your mom says you're her sunshine.
You are such a intelligent and sensitive boy.
You know, I have a feeling,
that when you grow up, you'll be a writer.
I will not be a writer. Feelings disgust me.
I will be a farmer, or one of those who poison dogs with a syringe.
- Have a good day. - And you.
You know what happened when Tarzan met the cowboys and the Indians?
What happened?
Tarzan watched from the tree,
while the cowboys and Indians fought under him.
One cowboy grabbed the throat of the snake that was crawling under his feet,
and forced it's poison into the mouth of the Indian.
Then Indian grabbed a prickly cactus and stabbed ...
the cowboy between his blue eyes.
Tarzan watched them from above
while thinking what to do.
And then what?
I'll tell you tomorrow.
Wow, that was a great story. Where did you hear it?
Tell me isn't that your dad?
Where?
Amos, you're a very good boy.
Your mother is suffering from a terrible headache.
Just talk quietly
without running or going on a rampage, ok?
Open, quickly.
- Do you need anything? - No thanks.
So why don't you lie down?
I'm good like this. Thank you.
- Did you see a doctor? - I don't need a doctor.
Mom, leave her alone.
Don't interfere, Arie.
Comedian ... as if coming to the moon.
Well what, the melancholic mood?
This is a sign that the heart is still young.
You may think that it has only been hard for her here,
that apart from her, we're all munching on honey here.
Did you finish your homework?
Fania?
How did you sleep?
Good. Finally I slept well.
Well, the new pills are really working.
So many dreams I dreamt yesterday.
A dream of a man that I have not thought of for a long time.
In Rovno there was a wealthy trader in furs,
he even recieved couriers from Paris sent,
since he had a rare sort of fur, which was called the "silver fox":
it shone and sparkled like frost on a moonlit winter night.
And then one day the merchant became a staunch vegetarian.
He left his house, built himself a small hut in the forest,
because he could not forgive himself for the thousands of foxes,
that hunters had killed for him.
And so, this man disappeared completely.
When me and my sisters wanted to scare each other,
The three of us would lay on the carpet in the dark,
and each described in turn,
how the man who once was a wealthy fur merchant,
Now was wandering naked through the woods.
Perhaps he is mad now
and howling in the thicket like a fox. And maybe this howling has made his hair stand on end.
And surel, everyone who has a chance encounter in the woods with the fox-man at night
the horror
- All the hair on your head become white. - I'm sorry, it's supposed to mean?
Allegory? Superstition?
Sorry.
Don't be late to school and work, guys.
What happened to you? What's that supposed to mean?
I'm sorry. This is all because of me.
Today, I decided to invite the two men in my life
for lunch at my expense at a restaurant.
- Dad knows? - We'll surprise him.
Let's go to his work,
and pull him out, like you pull out book moths from books.
Let's go.
Today you will be my cavalier.
- What is a "cavalier"? - A cavalier is a knight.
"Sheval" - is horse in French. A "chevalier" - a horseman, a knight.
- You are welcome. - Thank you.
Arie.
Excuse me.
What happened? Are my parents all right? And yours? Everything is fine?
Yes, everything is all right. We wanted to surprise you.
We're taking you to eat lunch.
Well, why not, in fact?
Today, I'm the hostess, and I'll be glad if you order
the most expensive dishes from the menu.
You are ready?
Yes.
Vegetable soup and chicken cutlet with mashed potatoes, please.
I'm the same, please.
Fania?
Only white rice, please
and black coffee.
Thank you.
Fania? Fania?
Fanitshka.
Mom, are you okay?
She needs absolute rest.
I will take care of it.
Thank you Doctor.
These are new tablets.
They will help you sleep.
Drink some more water.
I do not know how to help you.
You're not responsible for me.
Fan, I do not know how to help you.
Maybe I'll take you a while to Tel Aviv?
To be with your sisters, ventilate.
Yes, a little bit of air.
We can not allow to leave the killers
the property that they stole from us.
And we need the money in order to take in those who survived the massacre.
What are you talking about?
We do not sell the forgiveness in exchange for money stained with blood.
A few days in Tel Aviv, and you will be as good as new.
Not surprising, that you're unhappy, while living in Jerusalem.
We will pamper you.
You do not have to do anything except how to relax.
Fania, maybe eat a slice of cake?
I'm not hungry.
Do you eat at all?
You sound like mother.
Good, if that's what will be good for her ... She is a Jerusalemite.
Yes, it has no sea, she does not know what it is.
Just don't come to us in the summer.
Does not matter.
That winter
Ayalon river, also called "Wadi musrara"
overflowed and flooded the neighborhoods of Tel Aviv.
My mother grew up in a kind of vague fascination - in the world of spirituality and beauty.
When the wings of this fascination, in the end, hit
the Jerusalem stone floor - naked,
hot and dusty.
20 years later, after graduating from high school in Rovno,
when this romantic schoolgirl
suddenly appeared on the bumpy road of everyday life -
among heat waves, poverty, violence,
diapers, migraines, queues, family life disappointments -
her childhood promises have been violated, trampled,
and even turned into a mockery of life itself.
Maybe when life is not filled with any of the promises of her youth,
Mom painted death to herself
in the image of an exciting lover
and at the same time ready to hide under the shadow of its peacefulness.
If I was writing the story,
it would have another ending.
But so it's decided.
Dad is at home?
There was a telephone call from Tel Aviv, please, this is urgent.
Two years after my mother's death,
I left the house,
left Jerusalem,
Changed my name
and went to Kibbutz Hulda.
Mom Dreams:
milk and honey,
to make the desert bloom,
to be a pioneer.
- Hi. - Amos?
Hi.
You're taller than me.
Can I get the suitcase please?
Thank you.
No matter how much I learned to drive a tractor,
move irrigation lines on the fields,
shoot with an old Czech rifle,
I could not escape out of my own skin.
No matter how much I sunbathed, I couldn't fool anyone.
Everyone, and I myself, too, knew very well,
that even though my skinned had been tanned, inside I stayed pale,
I stayed inside the pale.
This is my school now.
The only way to keep the dream alive,
full of hope and not disappointing
is to never try to implement it.
A dream brought to life, is disappointing.
This disappointment -
is the nature of dreams.
"Мom"