[MUSIC]
Hi there and welcome
to week two of
Nanotechnology:
The Basics.
My name is Dan Mittleman.
And I'm going to be delivering a series of
lectures this week on nanoelectronics,
which is the intersection
of Nanotechnology with the electronics
industry.
By electronics, what I'm referring to are,
the electronic
components that are inside many of your
consumer devices today.
They make your TV run, they make
your cellphone run, they make your
computer run.
All of those components that have
obviously gotten better and
more powerful and smaller as the years
have gone by.
Which is why our computers become obsolete
every three
years and we have to buy a new one.
What we will talk about in this lecture is
the trend of how that's happened and why
that's happened and a little bit about
what we
might expect will come next, so let's get
started.
To put things in context, we can take a
look
at the, these images here, which show a
cellphone and a
computer from about 30 years ago and they
were obviously
much less functional and also much larger
than they are today.
Nowadays, we understand that electronic
components have begotten a lot smaller and
a lot faster and a lot more powerful.
In your cell phone, if you have a
smartphone, then the phone in
your pocket has more computing power than
the entire world had in 1950.
That's a fairly extraordinary advance in
really, just about one lifetime.
So, to understand what's going on here,
let's first
look inside a cell phone and see what we
see.
What we find is that there are a number of
electronics circuits
components, these little black boxes that
I'm circling
here are electronic circuits and you can't
see them.
They're packaged inside of thermal
packaging
and inside there you have Semiconductors.
The semiconductor in this case is silicon,
silicon is
the material that makes all of these
devices work.
Silicon can be formed into transistors and
diodes and other components and these
need to be all connected by wires and we
can make little logic circuits.
And the smaller you can make the
transistors
and the wires, the more of them you can
pack into a certain space and therefore,
the more
computing power you can get in a certain
space.
Those these electronic devices are inside
everything you use these days,
practically.
Their shrinking size has been,what has
revolutionized has
brought us what we call now the
communications industry.
The context that we can use to understand
this is a
paradigm known as Moore's law, which is
not really a law,
there's no law of science or nature that
says this has to happen.
But Gordan Moore, which was one of the
founders
of the company Intel noticed in the mid
70's,
that the number of transistors that one
can put
on a single chip, was doubling
approximately every two years.
And he observed that if this trend were to
continue, we would very rapidly
reach a regime, where we had so many
computers on a chip that the computing
power on a single chip, would be
extraordinary, by the standards of the
day.
Well, he was absolutely right, as this
graph shows you, here's the first,
this is the 286 computer, here is the 486,
here is the first pentium
right there and so on it goes, all the way
up to, this
graph ends in 2008, but it has continued
since then, even up until today.
So, the number of transistors on a chip
doubles every 2 years and
therefore, the computing power scales
exponentially with time.
And this trend is why computers are so
powerful, so
much more so than they were even just five
years ago.
There have been many occasions on which
prognosticators, including Gordon
Moore himself, have predicted the end of
this law have
said, no, it can't go on forever, it's
going to
stop in a certain year and yet it hasn't,
it continues.
I think it's safe to say that it will end
eventually,
but there's a lot of discussion about when
that will happen and
that's an interesting question, which
really will be answered by
Nano-technologists.
Because, as we will see, the devices that
are being built, at in the modern times,
ever since about here, are all devices
that are
based, that have nano- technology in them
the materials are nano sized.
So here's another version of Moore's law
and it
turns out there are many versions of
Moore's law.
This one
doesn't show the number of transistors on
a chip, versus here.
This one shows the size of those
transistors, the feature size, as
a function of year and this is also is
honoured exponentially favorable trend.
In other words they gets smaller and
smaller as time goes
on the doubling, the having time may not
be two years.
In this case it's actually a little faster
but
you can see that there is a an exponential
scaling.
And about the year 2001 we passed the
point at which transistor
sizes be, where, now below 100
nano-meters, this data point here, this
data point here is 35 nano-meters, that
was in about 2009 or 2010.
Right now, in 2013, we're down here where
the size is about 22 nano-meters and it's
a
very interesting question to ask, what
happens when we
try to extrapolate this line and predict
the future?
Another version of Moore's law is the cost
of a transistor, transistors get cheaper
as you make them smaller.
And so here, we see another exponential
scaling and nowadays, the cost of
a transistor is point oh, oh, oh, lots of
zeros one dollar per transistor.
There are lots of zeros in there
and that's why we can afford personal
computers.
So, really, almost anything associated
with
computation or the semi-conductor industry
is on
some sort of exponential trend and has
been for several decades and that's really
what has driven that industry forward.
That industry has taken to using Moore's
law as a method for predicting, for making
market forecasts and so the fact that
things
continue to fall along the Moore's law
line.
Is not really surprising, it's, it's been
predicted and it's what they're
aiming for, so it's not surprising that
they get what they're aiming for.
There are also some unfavourable versions
of Moore's
Law, for example, here's a plot of the
power
density on an integrated circuit, as a
function of year
and this is actually a predicting that was
made in
2001, by a vice president at Intel and he
predicted
that if power scaling continued around the
Moore's Law trend.
That very quickly we would get to a point,
where the
power density inside the chips was as hot
as the surface
of the sun and of course this would be
bad, because
then the chip would melt Prediction has
not come true, because of
multi core processors, the transition from
single core processors, to multi core
processors.
And also because of the development of
clever
ways, to do power management inside these
chips.
But it is true that the power scaling is
going up and
so eventually that becomes an issue that
one has to deal with.
Here's another unfavourable version of
Moore's
law this shows the cost of building
a factory where you can manufacture
integrated circuits as a function of time.
And that also goes up exponentially these
days, if Intel or one of those companies,
wants to build a factory to, to
fabricate chips, that costs them several
billion dollars.
And if you extrapolate this forward, you
can see that what you get
in 2025, you get a ridiculous number, so
that's clearly not going to happen.
They're not going to be spending $1
trillion to
build a factory, so clearly, something has
to change.
These forward extrapolations are actually
in some sense very important drivers
for Nanotechnology research.
Here's the plot I showed you earlier, the
same one which shows
the feature size and if we try to
extrapolate that forward well,
very interesting things happen, we very
quickly get to a regime where
we can say; that conventional computing
architectures simply aren't going to work
any-more.
So here's 100 nano meters where we were in
the early parts of the 2000's, 2002 or so.
And at that point, the distance across
a transistor was about 100 nano meters,
which corresponds to about
350 atoms and the silicone still behaves
like silicone at that point.
in a few years we will be at the point
where the distance to
cross the transistor is only ten
nano-meters
and that's only 35 atoms and then
you become to wonder: does, if a chunk of
silicone that's only 35 across
still behaves the same as a chunk of
silicone that has lots of atoms.
And you get down to one nano-meter, now
you can be pretty sure that
the silicone is not going to behave the
way bulk silicon behaves.
And so at the very least, we know we're
going to
have to completely change the system
architectures in order to adapt
to the fact that the material is no longer
behaving the
way it used to, when we had a large chunk
of it.
That's putting aside the questions of, can
we
even fabricate things that are one
nanometer in size?
Which is a whole different challenge, that
is really an open
question at this point one nano meter
probably is too small.
What
I've told you today, really kind of
immediately illustrates
some of the grand challenges facing the
semi conductor industry.
Number one, they have to figure out how to
make these things, these features;
transistors and other components.
And they have to make them small and
smaller and smaller
and smaller as time goes on and eventually
that becomes really hard.
Well, it's already really hard, eventually
it becomes impossible
and you have to be able to do it
economically.
number two, we haven't talked yet about
the wires,
you can't just have a bunch of transistors
on
a chip, you have to connect them together
with wires.
And in the past and today, that's just
done with copper wire but
eventually, when your wires get small, do
they continue to behave like wires?
That's an important question to ask and
actually they don't.
So then you have to worry about that and I
mentioned
a little bit this issue of the heat
generated inside these materials.
Thermal management is a huge issue facing
this
industry and they, that may be the game
changer
in the end, the thing that just stops them
from using silicon and forces them to use
something different.
So, is Nanotechnology the answer to these
grand
challenges well, I think Nanotechnology
clearly plays a role.
The question of whether it's going to be
the answer and what the answer
in detail is going to look like, that's
still very much an open question.
So to wrap up here and remind you of what
we just
said, the key ideas are number one,
electronics get smaller and faster and
better, as time goes on.
Smaller is what enables better and faster
and that's a prediction of
Moore's Law, which is not really a law,
but it has been true
for a very long time and it will continue
to be true
for at least another decade or so, people
argue about exactly how long.
But at some point it is going to stop
being true at some point, it will no
longer be possible to stay on that
forecast
and so then the question is, what comes
next?
If you'd like
to find out, then stick around for the
rest
of the lectures this week and we'll talk
about it.