to me teaming
the Ching Ming festival is a day of
reverence for Chinese people hold
ceremonies for ancestors and sweep their
tombs on April 5th every year according
to tradition during the Tomb Sweeping
people put food in front of the tombs at
new soil on the to decorate the tombs
with some fresh branches and not hands
a traditional Chinese painting named
Riverside seen on the Ching Ming
festival drawn nine hundred years ago
shows the prosperous atmosphere and
activities on that day
people returned from tubes whipping with
horses and packages in the picture
now it is a public holiday in China
although ceremonies have changed a
little with time Chinese still express
their grief for the disease
to mean to mean