The is chu-tu, in his late 40s
night club owner,
trader and realtor
All his business
are losing money
How are things up there?
This in Mad Wing, his body-guard
these are all
his hit-men
take care, see you at the Dye Factory
Wait for me up there
OK
This Danny Chu, his nephew
Always has an army hanging around him
this is John Ko, Chu tu's brain
this is Salina Fong
Only been hanging
around Chu recently
Does she know everything about Chu yet?
Well, it's difficult to tell
Our objective
is to take them all in
Our code is Operation Roar Hung
Understand?
Yes
Read what's inside your envelope
Each one has his own instructions
Remember by heart and
destroy the written orders
Each man does his own job
Hurry, come on
Attention,
this is t.O.C. headquarters
Operation begins at once
I'll get you a tea
two teas please
OK
I'll come for them later
A guy looks suspicious here
two teas please
Signal them below, I'm going down
Kim
One for me?
We've been discovered
What?
Follow the one in red shirt and white pants
What's up?
I'm Salina,
Kueng said there're a suspicious guy
What's up with you?
I'm a cop
Cop, help
Cop?
Freeze, I'm a cop
I heard shooting
they opened fire
now what?
Let's scatter the bystanders first
We're cops. Go
Special Corps over, what happened?
I'm a cop, don't stay here
Go
Here
Attention, watch out for
the civilians, explosives
Careful of kids
Hurry, run, kid
Hurry, run
this way
You all go give a hand
We have orders to stay
You must improvise for the situation
Go
Let me go
It'll get tighter when you move
I've got this covered. You can leave
Quick, cover the boss
Go on
there's a girl suspect
up there, take her back
It's me
How come?
Don't ask
Calm down
Help me...
tak, tak
Cover me
Be cool
It hurts
Help me
take care of him there
they've got a lot of guns
Watch out for the villagers,
that's our order
Have they told the crooks too?
Who told you to be a cop?
Come here
Watch out Ka Kui, they're fearless
Over here
Get in
Get away
Get back, get back
no
What?
It is blocked up there, move back
Move back
Can't, go back up
It is blocked below, go up
We're stuck, boss, now what?
We fight our way down
Let's go
Boss, Hurry
Hurry
Let's go this way
Freeze
Watch out for the pedestrians
Where have you been?
This is your station
I went up to help
Who gave you orders, they're gone now
What do you mean by that?
Hurry, go
Excuse me
tell them to get down, out of the way
Get down
Don't let them see my face
tell the driver to step on it
Step on it
Get down
turn here, turn
Make a run for it!
Make a run
Easy, boss, we'll make it
Look
Go, take care of him
tell the driver to step on it
Hurry down
turn quickly down the hill
Are you nuts? Right in
the middle of the road
Move over, I'm a cop
He is right in front
Run him over
Yes
Step on it, run him over
Don't be scared
Don't move
You're under arrest
Let me go, and this is yours
Once in a life time,
no one will know
Smart guy
Don't move
Good show, isn't it?
Be modest when he praises you later
Don't let it get to you
You better tell Ka Kui
I didn't do it by myself
I acted according to orders
that's fine
Don't forget this line later
when Raymond comes
He must be happy to hear that
Operation Boar Hunt
is a carefully planned jolt
Didn't you
cover every side?
The prime suspect almost got away
Didn't Chou give you
clear orders?
Yes, he said...
we were under good leadership
What?
The job was carefully planned
But our execution had a few flows
Why were there flaws?
Must be before
we got to the store
Ka Kui couldn't handle the secretary
And she created a mess
How could Chu tu get away?
This was your spot
What do you mean by that?
It's no time to point your finger
What is it?
The PR madam is here
Ask her in
the press is here, inspector Lee
What press? tell them no comment
Look, I asked them here
tell them to wait
Ka Kui, you'll be our speaker
Me? no, no
the speech has been written,
just read it
Go learn it with Madam
You can go now, Man
YES SIR
the superiors are pleased
with Ka Kui
they see a lot in him
take him to do
a recruiting poster later
Arrange to have him on our tV program etc
An example of the force
the superiors see him as a model cop
He can handle that easily
What are the charges on Chu's secretary
Drug trafficking, resisting arrest
Drop all charges
Drop all charges?
You played a big part, Sergeant Chan
Our superiors' leadership
accounts for the success
Good job
Will you be promoted?
We don't fight crime
for promotion
Our superiors take care
of promotion matters
Chu tu tried to bribe you
with millions, right?
With that money,
he could buy the whole force
Just kidding, don't put it down
Please sit closer
What's up?
Just saying hi
Don't sit so close
We two
Let's do it this way
- Understand? - Yes
Start
Straighten up
Open you eyes
Open your mouth
Wider
Wider still
Forget it, just be yourself
Be natural
Ready
the handcuffs in the middle
Smoother action
Your way wouldn't work
Why not?
She's Chu's secretary,
won't cooperate
If Chu knows
she'll be our witness
What would he do?
He would stop her
appearance in court
Our man who covers her would be in danger
Don't be a cop
if you want to live to 100
You want this line
on the recruiting poster?
We don't have enough
to prosecute Chu
We must push him
into a corner
Let him make a mistake
I suggest a man
to protect our lady witness
I have someone in mind already
Are we thinking of the same man?
Good luck to him
Why only you free on bail?
Lucky you
they are to see Inspector Lee
Please wait
You can go after seeing the inspector
You can go in now
thanks
Please sit down
You can go now, Miss Fong
Wait, before you go
Keep this subpoena
to appear in court
What is the charge?
There are no charges
You'll be our witness
Sorry, my client isn't prepared to do so
We are not asking her permission
She is required by law to do it
Officer Chan
YES SIR
You're attached to Miss Fong from now on,
24 hours a day
Until she appears in court
Me
You don't like it
Yes I do
I don't need his protection
You can't refuse
Officer Chan
YES SIR
You must know as an escort of the witness
that the witness
is constantly in danger
Of threat, assault, and disturbance
Or irritated by the intentions of such
It is your duty to see to that
Her safety and personal rights
are intact
Yes
But can someone else go
You'll get a bonus
for the duty
$32.80 per day
It's an old tradition,
unchanged for years
Bring your own money, that's all
Can we talk to you alone?
I refuse to have my client
interrogated alone
this is not an interrogation
Just a few hints
for her benefit
You can refuse them
Let's hear what they've to say
Mr. Counselor, please excuse us
Remember,
any questions concerning this case
Or anything else, you can keep quiet
What are you standing here for?
I have to go out too?
You've got high rank?
You said you had things to say to me
nothing else now, you can go
See you in court
they're...
Ka Kui
tape it down if possible
OK
What did they say to you?
They didn't say anything
I'm your lawyer, you can trust me
they didn't say anything, really
Why just her...
Here they are
How about the boss?
Can't bail him & the others out
What about Salina?
She's their witness now
What? Witness for prosecution
they asked me
You'll do it just cause they asked?
Please leave the witness alone
Who're you?
I'm a cop
I'm her escort
I can charge you for disturbance of peace
Salina
You can say so long or good-bye
One more word and you'll be under arrest
I'll take you home
It's my responsibility
I won't say anything
What now, counselor?
I'll see your boss later
OK. Let's go
It's dangerous to roam around,
go home
none of your business
It's for your safety
I don't need you, parasite!
You know what happened
to four of our witnesses
who said the same thing
What?
They were shot
Don't scare me, tell me what happened?
Your guess is right
they're actually all OK
You have the right to say so
that's a threat!
All evidence is against the defendants
Only you will fare better
I'm depending on you
I'll do my best,
but be prepared
the chance is slim
If I'm discharged,
you'll be rewarded
One problem
Salina is going to be their witness
Witness for the prosecution
She's been bailed,
now escorted by a cop
the one who nailed you
Salina doesn't know much, she's new
that doesn't concern me
She might
surprise us
no
Call up Danny
tell him to take care of her
Alright
that's it
Keep the change
For the tea
It's dangerous alone
I like to see how dangerous
John? I'm home
Someone's listening
Let's meet and talk later
I'm scared
You think you can frighten me
Help
As good as dead
that'll get you
I'm gonna shut you up
You're finished
I'll get you
I'm going to kill you
You're finished
I'll get you
Stop running
No escape now
Stop
Here...
Here
Well?
No way out
Finished
I'm here to rescue you
She's terrified, can I quit now?
Yes, you can go anytime
Hold on to him, I'll call the police
I knocked him out, I knocked him out
not yet,
he's still fighting back
Don't come near
Go, you can't be here
Don't faint
Go
I'll go
He passed out
no, not totally out
Go, don't faint
Go, go, can't stay
Go
Stop acting, go, hurry
Let me
He fainted
Yes, for real
One more for safety
Don't smash his face,
it's for identification
no, shouldn't be like this
I don't know him
Of course, they'd hire stranger to kill you
Mr. Chu wants me dead?
Sure, he's capable of anything
inspector Chou, this is Ka Kui
Such a tough case,
please send a replacement
no
I won't risk my life,
it's just a job
I might as well be a mercenary
Well, let her take care of herself
I'll quit then,
never mind
Where are you going?
Home
What? Home? You're here to protect me
But you're so uncooperative
How can I work it out?
What do you have in mind?
No need, I'm quitting
Where's your
sense of duty?
But there's nothing I can do
We'll just die together
I'll cooperate
Don't let me talk you into it
Of my own will
it'll be safer
at my place
OK. Let's go
Like this?
I'll go change
Chu's men will return anytime
I won't change then
Well?
What's up?
I'll take a good look
Get back in
Come out
What are you up to?
I'm taking your clothes
I told you to wear them
Yes
Closer
Use my car
All these cars are yours
No, just this one
Why aren't you nervous?
I'm used to this
See, told you to keep quiet
What?
My kid
Your kid?
Close the door
It's me, it's me
My gun...
My gun is in the pocket
Let go
Stop running
Freeze
take it easy, give me the gun
take it easy
Don't come near
Go
Give me the gun
It's me
Are you alright?
Where are they?
Don't get trigger happy
Get away quick, this is for real
For real, what was that before?
That was real too
But this is more real
that's why you are more nervous
Get in
You are capable of crying too
I didn't expect Mr. Chu to do this to me
Don't be naive
He is capable of anything
He will make sure you won't be in court
What now then
Speak out in court tomorrow
Put him in jail and you'll be safe
What am I to tell?
What business he's in, who's his contact
Number of drug deals
Why are you taping all this?
Taking notes
When did you start working for him?
Four years ago
He's a family friend
Mum said he always lent us milk money
Now you help him sell drugs
I know very little
Just tell what you know
Anything else you want to add,
tell me later upstairs
What I've said is enough
to put him in jail?
I'm not the prosecutor
But what you're said
will be useful
Come in
I'll turn on the light
HAPPY BIRTHDAY tO YOU
May
I've almost forgotten it's my birthday
Are you alright?
Let me introduce, May
this is Miss Fong
Let's go
How are you doing?
I'm fine
May
Gone? What's the hurry?
It's my fault, it was a surprise, right?
And you brought home a girl
dressed like this
Who wouldn't be angry?
I can be angry too
Didn't even let me explain
Leaving me the whole cake
this time I won't forgive her
No matter what
I don't think she will
I knew she'd be back
Happy Birthday
Why so happy?
Why did May go in rage?
She saw me bringing a girl home
that's love,
I'll explain it to her
no need,
ask her to reflect on her faults
Have to explain to my boss,
the suspects
I'm sick and tired of explaining
Care for a piece of cake
Anything to drink
Orange juice, thanks
Help yourself
You live by yourself?
A big place!
Don't I worry about the ICAC?
I share it with a friend, he's on vacation
Sorry
Your girlfriend must be mad at me
never mind
that's part of the job
Come, let's go back
I'll go now
Just like that
I might be a movie star
Kissing my leading ladies all day
She would have to hang
herself 3 times a day
She's jealous because she loves you
I'll explain it to her if possible
What for? Such a narrow minded kid
It'll only spoil her
Aren't you going to say
something nice to her
No chance
If I care to sweet talk,
I could have hundred of girls
She'll have to wait for her turn
Don't you like her
Frankly, yes
But that's no reason
for me to apologize
I know she's going
to call back to say sorry
What a waste
See
Can't wait to get home
Hello
Is it your girlfriend?
Yes, she's speechless with tears
Stop crying
You should have behaved yourself
What, misunderstanding
You might think I'm gay
if I escort a man
Go reflect on your faults
What
Can I explain it to her?
No need
Unless you promise
to control your temper
Show me respect in front of my friends
Stop crying, bye!
I must teach her a lesson
When did she come in?
When you said she would hang herself
So you've heard everything
the call...
that's a dirty trick
May, May
Listen to me, May
She's our witness under my protection
I'm mad at
what you just said
You should know I was kidding
Didn't I call first every time
we had a fight
But you treat me badly
in front of another girl
You make me lose face
Go away, go away
Listen to me
May, listen...
Are you alright?
It hurts, go away, happy now?
Happy? It hurts me too
I'll get the shoes for you
Put on them first
Go away
May, listen to me
No, no
Control yourself
Listen to me first, OK?
Let go
Be careful
I hate you
Where's your girlfriend
I accepted her apology,
she went home happily
What are you doing?
Nothing
It hurts
It's breaking, easy
It's breaking
What's this ugly thing?
Get rid of it
What, this is my precious
You got me wet
I'll wipe it for you
Oh, no
not there, here
Here?
Easy, you're so rough
So uncomfortable on the
sofa, let's go to bed?
OK. Let's go
Where do I sleep?
In my bed
How about you
next to you
I like your style
I'm going to sleep now
Don't disturb me
Women are strange
Hi
Ka Kui? Wait a second
Uncle Bill, it's him
Hurry Ka Kui, they're waiting at the court
He's out already, may be there's a jam
Stop fooling, bring the witness, hurry
What was your duty that day?
I was observing the squatter huts
behind the site
there were about a dozen
suspects getting away
I arrested the 6th & 7th defendants
thank you
Your honor, allow me
to question the witness
Mr. Kim
You said you saw a dozen suspects escaping
Did all 13 suspects
pass in front of you one by one
Or you have a new
electronic device
to enable you to see
all the action at once
I object
the question played with
the witness's wording
to undermine his credibility
Objection overruled
thank you, no more questions
Bring on the next witness
of the prosecution
You took my parking space
I'm in a hurry
Hurry up or I'll kill you
Nice parking
What? Gone?
What kind of an escort are you?
Now what?
Can't think of anything
Hopeless
tell me when you saw
the suspect running
What made you think
he was my client?
By his clothes and his build
that means you didn't see
his face clearly
You can say that
Are you near-sighted?
No
Good. No more questions
Next witness for the prosecution
...and nothing but the truth
I was at the squatter huts on duty
the 1 st, 2nd, 3rd
& 4th defendants opened fire
they got on a bus
and I cook a short cut
A civilian...
used his car to block the bus
3 defendants fell off the bus
I arrested the 1 st defendant on the bus
He tried to
bribe me
Very clear, thank you
You said you were at the squatter huts
What time was it?
It was about six
About six?
5:55
So let's stay 6:00
Do you know in December
the sun rises after 6:23
no
Ls that right?
How would I know?
Do you know that saying
"Darkness before dawn"?
No
The meaning is
there is darkness before the sun rises
I might have heard of that
Great,
under such circumstances
Should we believe
you actually saw my client as a suspect?
Believe it or not, that's your business
You said you took the short cut
to stop the bus
Was the bus always in your sight?
Yes
Why did you hesitate?
I want to be sure
that means you are a bit doubtful
I object
Objection sustained
Witness should be sure of his answer
How much time did you
take to go down the hill?
And you kept the bus in sight all the time
I was rushing down,
my sight was blocked momentarily
May be during this short while
Another bus overtook the original one
there was only one bus on the road
You are lying
I object
Sustained
Defense should rephrase his question
Are you lying?
No
Do you know...
there are four lines of
bus routes passing there
two of the lines have a bus
running every 5 minutes
the other two every 6 minutes
that means 88 buses
passing through per hour
More than 1 per minute
I didn't know
From the time you went down to stop the bus
How much time did you use?
About 2 minutes
More precisely
2-1/2 minutes
that means at least 2 or 3
buses would have gone by
Or even up to 7 or 8
But you said only one, that's lying
Haven't you ever waited
for a bus for 1/2 an hour
So, let's say
there was only one bus
And you insisted you saw the bus
all the time
Which part of the bus was in your sight?
The body
How much of the body?
The whole bus
You are lying
What's that, again?
You saw only one side of the body
No more than 50%, that's half
You couldn't see
the other half, right?
Yes
On the other side...
which you couldn't see
anything could have...
happened there
Yes
Anyone who jumped off the bus
would be unseen
Yes
Louder please
I would jump, but not him
Just answer the question, no comment please
You think anyone can jump off a bus
You try it
Calm down please, Constable Chan
Why did he want to bribe me then?
How did he bribe you?
He said I could have the case of money
if I let him go
If someone stopped the bus and...
Pointed a gun at you,
what would you do
I object
Objection overruled
You must answer
I'd give my money to him
that's what my client did
under the circumstances
Right, Constable?
No
I had shown my ID
there were cases
where robbers pretended to be cops
I object
Objection sustained
Please ask relevant questions only
My apology
It happened like this
A business man
was on the way to a deal
A heroic policeman pointed a gun at him
by mistake
the business man thought he was a robber
So he told the robber
he could have the money
Is that right?
I object
You don't have to answer
But we all know the answer
No need for Constable Chan to say it
I have finished
Great
now what?
I know what to do
It is unfair to let him free
Of course
We apply for postponement,
our prime witness is absent
I object
A postponement
is unfair to my client
the prosecution has little evidence
to charge my client
I ask your honor to dismiss the case
We have a taped evidence
from our witness
But tape is not legal evidence
But the absent witness plays a key role
I object
Since this is an important case
A postponement
is unfair to the defendant
Let's hear
what the witness has to say
this is the only way
Louder please
thank you
Your Honour, it is an old tape
Please keep on listening
Coming up
What are you doing?
Nothing
It hurts
It's breaking, easy
It's breaking
What's this ugly thing
Get rid of it
What, this is my precious
It's a cactus
How come?
You got me wet
I'll wipe it for you
Oh, no
I spilled the orange juice
It wasn't what you think
Easy, you're so rough
So uncomfortable on the
sofa, let's go to bed
OK. Let's go
Where do I sleep?
In my bed
How about you
next to you
I like your style
It's coming
thank you for your cooperation
not too close please
Get lost
Ka Kui
Give me a report of the whole case
YES SIR
Boss
Coming out now
No photos
Get lost
Reserve a room at the country club, John
A toast to justice
OK
I must go, Mr Chu
thank you
Goodbye
Hire him as a prosecutor next time
It's time for the Police Stories again
We have here...
a brave officer for our guest
Sitting next to me
is Constable Chan Ka Kui
Greetings, Constable Chan
Hello
Hello everybody
Inspector Chan
After cracking down the greatest drug case
You've become a familiar name
to every citizen
Would you please describe
the operation to us
the success is due to
the team work of the unit
I'm only one of them
We did a lot of homework
What makes Special Corps
so different?
To be in the Special Corps
One must be strong,
swift and fast
And have great will power
Boss
What's the matter?
He is on the cover of
at least 3 weeklies
He's been nominated for some award too
Oh, thailand is out of stock
Why
they've all changed jobs?
No,
but all the goods have gone to no. Seven
they want cash
Boss, Mr Cheung is here
Please come in
Mr Chu
I've received your check, thank you
thank you
How is it?
I've studied with my colleagues
things remain confiscated
during prosecution
that means I can't get my stuff back yet
Including your passport
and you bank accounts
to them it is just an intermission
If you are found guilty
All your properties
will be confiscated
I won't have money to escape even
Boss, a call
Sorry
Hi, Salina
So boring here, I want to go out
You can't for the time being
I want to see you
Later, you can't show up yet
the police are looking for you
I'm planning your Europe trip
Once there, you'll be OK
Listen
Wait till everything's quieted down
Hello
Where were we?
We were lucky...
this time
If they have more solid evidence...
or Salina
It would be a different story
they won't find her
that's good them
I have to go, bye
Bye
Boss, Cheung is right
Salina is a problem
You can't hide her away forever
Yes, uncle
that cop is after Snakie to find Salina
Can't we send her away?
She must never return
Let's make use of the cop
to kill her
there're lots of other beautiful girls
We've all those beauty pageants
inspector Man wants to see you
Send him in
Hasn't he been paid?
$100,000
but he's contemplating retirement
So what?
He wants more
Inspector Man, please
Inspector Man
Mr Chu
Sit down please
Please
I'm here for...
You'd like to retire to small business
I support your idea
thank you
You are a man of substance
I'd like you to do one more thing for me
What is it?
We want that cop to disappear
You want glory, I'll give you glory
take down your number
1985, come to patrol with me
YES SIR
- Sergeant Chan - YES SIR
If anything happens,
call...
Call you with the radio
Call me at home
But you'll be on patrol
We go by my home
Excuse me, I need to go to the toilet
Don't break the John
Sha tau Kok Station
You want me, Chan?
Of course, any information?
Salina? Give me more time
It's a tough job
though? tough to get paid too
I know my job
I'll do my best
What? Wait
Wait?
Sha tau Kok Station, wait
I'll give you 3 days
3 days?
That's not enough
What, later?
4 days then
You'll be in trouble if I get transferred
that's it for now
Who do you want?
Ka Kui, why keep me waiting?
Chan? Just a second
Your call, Chan
thanks
Who do you want?
This is May
May
Who was that?
Yes that rude guy
Lau, you should be...
more polite to civilians
Sorry
OK. I've scolded him
What is it. May?
What are you doing?
Me?
I'm speaking to you
Have you eaten yet?
No
I'm cooking some noodles,
have you eaten yet?
No
Wait a second
Sha tau Kok Station, hold on
May
My mom invites you to dinner
Is that so? Anytime
Wait a second
Sha tau Kok Station
My husband beat me up
What? What about your husband?
He beat me up
You beat him up or he beat you up
My husband beat me up
Don't cry
I'll give you the right line
May, I'm free Sunday
Don't hang up
I'm still connecting for you
Sha tau Kok Station, speak up
I've lost a cow
Oh! I'll connect you to Missing Persons
It's busy
Sha tau Kok Station
I've been raped
What? Rape?
Wait, let me write it down
When were you raped?
Rape, no, my husband beat me up
Oh! It's you
I'm still connecting your call
It takes so long
It's a big station, be patient
Who's been raped?
Me
The cow has to wait
When were you raped?
Last year
Last year, why report it now?
I want to know if there're
any afterward pills
Pills?
I'll find out for you
Hello, Missing Persons Department
I've lost a cow
Bring in a photo
of the cow
Hello
May, I'm very busy
I name a place for dinner
Let me think
Hello
Where shall we go?
Go to Family Planning Association
tell her to take double portions
It's free
May
tell my mom to take the pills?
What's up? May
Hello
tell my mom to take the pills?
She isn't pregnant
Sha tau Kok Station
this is telephone Co. testing
testing?
Is there a traffic jam?
No, there's no traffic jam
Why then?
If there's a jam, I wouldn't be here yet
My mom hates people
who are late
Let me explain, May
I've been waiting for Snakie to call
Because of this case,
you've been transferred
Why don't you leave this alone?
I want satisfaction
I'll return call first
Hold on to the car, the handbrake is broken
Hold on to it
Hello, Snakie, it's me
the girl witness you are looking for
Is hiding in a villa
in Rosary village
Where?
Hurry up!
Or Mr Chu will kill her first
No kidding
I won't kid you, hurry
May
Don't tell me you're not coming to dinner
Chu's going to kill the witness,
I must go
No way
If she's dead, Chu is going to be free
You know what Chu has done to me
And it's a matter of life and death
What are you doing?
The car...
What about the car?
Taxi
Call a tow-truck
And apologize to your mom, bye
Be careful
Keep the change
thank you
How come?
I don't know why they tied me up
Any body else here?
They are all gone
Now you know what kind of person is Chu
If only you had...
cooperated with us
Lucky I'm well informed
Or you'd be dead by now
Hurry up
Let's go
Don't move
Step aside
How did you know I'd be here?
Of course I know
It couldn't be...
Surprised?
There are a lot of surprises
According to plan?
Yes, according to plan
But the Boss...
wants to shoot him with his own gun
Once and for all
Shoot who?
Hurry up
Go
Don't, I can't
Don't
Jump
Move
Don't move
Get Salina
You are a worthy opponent
Enough
take care of him, I'll clean up
I guarantee
he didn't do that
We need proof
How come...
he's gone with his gun
And the bullet
is from his gun
How do you explain?
A cop has a lot of enemies
Someone might want to frame him
If this happened to a civilian
not happened to Ka Kui
What would we have done?
Sir, one shouldn't always go by the book
One must also show trust in his men
I have nothing against Ka Kui
I just want people to know
that we don't cover up...
our own faults
But I think...
you are overdoing it
OK. Bill
What would you do if you're in my shoes?
Hello, May
Yes
I understand
OK. I'll wait for you
What now?
Mom worries about you
Ka Kui, be careful
Ka Kui's back
- Ka Kui - Ka Kui
Ka Kui
I didn't do it
We believe you
Where have you been?
I don't know
Don't say you don't know
Drunk? With a girl?
I was fighting Danny Chu & his gang
Man came in and pointed his gun at me
they took my gun and shot Man
And I can't remember the rest
So?
Everyone knows you & Man
weren't good friends
And you bullet...
is found in his body
I didn't kill him
I wouldn't do it over
such small conflicts...
But who's going to believe you
We need proof
But at least you are back
Hand in your gun first
Call homicide
that the prime suspect has given himself up
Call two men in
Don't worry,
we'll help you
take him to the cell
YES SIR
Charge him with murder
Sir...
Freeze
What are you doing, Ka Kui?
I didn't kill anybody
Why charge me with murder?
I didn't say you killed him
But I must charge...
according to evidence
I've been framed
Can't you tell?
I'll look into it
Don't give me that!
Ka Kui, let him go
no
Ka Kui, this is dangerous
Dangerous for him
When we were risking our lives
He was sitting here
thinking of his girlfriends
We put the crooks under arrest,
he argued about procedure
And that stupid idea
of protecting the witness
One move from his lips,
we've to risk our lives
- Ka Kui - Shut up
You got promoted at our expense
Have you ever thought of us?
A man killed...
only means 3 bows and a full report
We are human too
If we hadn't fought for you
Would you have such a luxurious office
- Ka Kui - Get away
Don't come near
Or I'll shoot him
Ka Kui
Don't
Open up
- Listen to me - Don't move
Don't come near
- Don't - never mind me
I know what I'm doing
What a mess!
Ka Kui has Lee for a hostage
What's the matter?
Everyone stays where he is
Don't move
Don't come near
Calm down
Ka Kui, take it easy
Don't come near
think carefully, Ka Kui
Let's talk about it
Yeah?! Let's talk about it
Hands on the table so I can see
On the table
this is very stupid
Calm down
before it's too late
We'll clear you up,
trust us
I trust you,
but I can't depend on you
But you'll be in deeper trouble
Don't push me
Freeze
Ka Kui
Don't push him
Alert all units, send in sharpshooters
Easy everybody
Ka Kui
Get in the car
Drive off
Ka Kui
Don't follow
the superintendent's life is at stake
Where are you going?
Stop
Get off
I couldn't shoot even
if you didn't cooperate
this isn't bad
I don't know
how else to help you
As soon as I get back, I'll come after you
I won't let you get me
before I get Chu
From now on, be very careful
thank you, sir
But it's tough to find where Salina is
Let's just get a couple of girls
He forced me...
to do it
I have nothing to do with it
Eat
Can I eat? I'm hungry
Boss
that cop is on the loose
Didn't the police take him in?
He kidnapped the superintendent
Great guy
We should have
killed him too
Once and for all
Where is Salina?
Wing and Snakie are on her heels
But no news yet
Would Saline be with the cop?
What is it, Boss?
Someone stole my computer data
Who?
Must be Salina
Only she knows the code
Go get he
Alert all men
Call counselor Cheung
Yes
How much longer?
Impatient?
No
I'm scared
You two stand guard over there
Here
What?
Call up Bill, hurry
Must get the data, or we're in trouble
Hurry
this way, go
Ka Kui
Why didn't you go to the police?
Thee might be Sergeant Man's men there
You are my witness,
I'm counting on you
I've got Chu's data
Right here
take her back to the office, hurry
not here
none of your business
Go
Get him
Go away
Go
I don't
Kill him
Catch
Here, get it back
May
Are you OK Ka Kui?
Get the brief case
Yes
Go to hell
Chu tu
Hurry
Go
Ka Kui
Don't
Easy, Ka Kui
Put down the weapon
We'll take over
Ka Kui
this is between us
the law will take care it
the law? there is no justice
the law is on his side
Don't do anything foolish
I could kill him now
with no regrets
Danny Chu killed Man
All evidence is in the brief case
Are you alright?
May is hurt, take care of her first
Block all exits, take them all in
You cops are going too far
threatening innocent citizens
with a weapon
You are not above the law
On behalf of my client
I'm going to sue you
for assault, kidnap
And threat
this is miscarriage of justice
Disturbance of peace
You can all see
Let go Ka Kui
Don't fall into his trap
Get ready for jail
threatening the counselor too
thanks for coming
You...
You must help me with the report
What!
Let's write it together
I didn't see anything
Ka Kui, enough