# Let's play
# Let's have an adventure, hooray
# Who could we be today?
# What could we do?
# I'd like to drive a racing car or fly to the moon
# I could be a fire fighter, a farmer or a vet
# A knight in shining armour
# Or I could be a chef
# Let's play
# Let's have an adventure today. #
Right, that should do it. I'm taking a picture.
I have to make sure I'm ready before the...
CAMERA CLICKS
Oh, no! It's taken the picture already. Let's try it again.
There.
Hey, Sid, what are you doing?
HE MUMBLES
- Sorry?
- I'm taking a...
- CAMERA CLICKS
- Oh, no, it's done it again!
Why are you taking a picture of yourself?
I've got a brilliant frame and want a good picture to go in it.
- A good picture?
- Yeah.
- Why didn't you say? You can take my picture.
I have lots of pictures of you with your thumbs up.
Rebecca at the seaside. Rebecca at Christmas.
Rebecca running the egg-and-spoon race and winning.
Aww, I quite like that pose.
I'll tell you what, I'll use the other thumb.
I like the thumbs-up thing,
but I'm looking for something a little bit more exciting.
- Hold on, Sid. That picture will have to wait. It's time.
- Great!
- It's time to play.
- Whose turn is it today?
- Let it be me.
- Me!
# Let it be me, me, me
# Let it be me
# Let it be me, let it be me
# I really, really, really, really hope that it's me
# Let, let, let, let, let, let, let it be me!
# Let it be me, let it be me
# I really, really, really, really hope that it's me. #
- Could it be me?
It's me!
# Yes, it's me, yes, it's me
# I'm really, really, really, really happy it's me! #
Look, there's the dressing up room.
# Let's play. #
So what are we going to play?
Let's find out.
So, a hula outfit, a sea captain's hat
and animal feet?
Well, that's silly. Let's try again.
So, we've got on a wet suit and flippers -
so what do you think we're playing today?
Of course, we're playing at being divers who jump into the sea
and swim around and look at fish.
So what do we need to know?
Bouncy ball, Rebecca.
Divers swim under water using air tanks to breathe.
They also wear heavy weight belts
to help them sink down as far as they want to go.
Divers talk to each other by using special hand signals.
This means "OK".
This means "octopus".
And you'll need to do this one if you see a shark.
Not all sea creatures swim.
Some, like anemones, cling to rocks and have stinging tentacles
which they pull in when things touch them.
So that's what we need to know, and do we need anything else?
Oh, what's this?
Well, it looks like a metal pointy thing.
Well, I'm sure it will come in handy.
OK, so we've got everything we need. Let's go!
Ssh!
- Oh, Rebecca!
- Sorry, I couldn't resist.
Can you guess what we're playing today?
- Oh, yes, you're going to be a doctor in the surgery.
- Eh? No!
- We're playing at being divers.
- I know you are. I'm only joking.
- You're going to see lots of cool fish.
- Oh, I hope so.
While you're gone,
I'm going to practise making the best picture ever for my frame.
- Perhaps I'll give a nice, big, dramatic pose.
- Wow, that looks good.
- Well, wish me luck.
- Luck.
- Bye!
# Let's play. #
Come on, then, let's play at being divers.
Woo-hoo!
# Let's play. #
Whoa!
Oh, wow, I'm in a boat
and I'm in the middle of the sea.
I wonder if there's anybody else out here. Oh, a telescope.
Right, let's take a look.
There's somebody and he's in a boat too.
Right, let's row over and say hello.
# La la la la la. #
- Excuse me.
- Oh, I heard something!
- Hello!
- Hello, Mr Fish. How can I help you?
Do you want to come out of the water, Mr Fish?
No, it's me, Rebecca, over here in this boat.
Ah, it is you talking.
It is not him down there.
Right.
Can I come into your boat, please?
Yes, yes, yes, come, come, come, oui, oui, oui.
There you are. Be careful. Bravo.
- Hello, I'm Rebecca.
- Hello, Rebecca. I am Jacques.
- Nice to meet you, Jacques. What are you doing?
- I am looking for treasure!
- Treasure?
- Yes, gold and silver coins.
The lost treasure of the Good Ship Neptune.
Where?
Down there somewhere.
- Ooh!
- You will come with me. Yes, we will dive deep in the sea.
- Right.
You will need a few things. Take this.
Ooh, a watch, so I know how long I've been under for.
- Here, take this.
- Oh, a special underwater camera.
- And here, take this.
- A brown teddy bear?
Oh, no! This is Brian.
Brian stays on the boat. Brian, you stay there.
Come, come, we shall dive deep into the sea and find the lost treasure
of the Good Ship Neptune!
- Oh, hooray! I'm ready.
- And maybe...
- Maybe what?
- ..we will find the talking fish.
- Eh?
Come, come, let us go now.
Here we go.
Oh, wow, fish!
And jellyfish!
Starfish and seaweed.
I'm under water. This is fantastic.
Hold on, what's going on?
I'm floating back up.
How am I going to find the treasure?
Hold on, I remember. Do you?
Divers wear heavy weight belts
to help them sink down as far as they want to go.
I need a heavy weight belt.
I wonder if Jacques has got one. But where's he gone?
If I float back up, maybe he'll come and find me.
Phew! That didn't last long.
I want to go back. It was amazing down there.
Rebecca, what is going on? Why did you come back up?
- Do you not like it in the sea?
- No, I mean, yes, it was lovely, amazing.
- Great, come then, let's go.
- No, hold on, wait.
- What?
I need a weight belt. You forgot to give me one.
Oh, yes, of course, you need a weight belt to stay under the water.
- Yes, I know.
- Here we have one.
Now, be very careful.
And, yes, it is very heavy. Let me help you. Here we are.
I will lift it up. That's it.
Now you turn around slowly and put this inside the buckle like so
and pull it nice and tight.
- Ready? Voila!
- Thank you.
- Now come, let us go and find us some treasure.
- Right.
- Let us go this way.
- OK.
Wow, this is really amazing!
I must take some pictures.
Thank you.
Wow!
Hold on, Jacques, I'm taking pictures.
Oh, no, an octopus!
Hold on, I want to take your picture.
Oh, it's very fast. Hey, hold on. Slow down, Mr Octopus!
Oh, he's gone. Maybe that's where he lives.
I'll go and take a look. I'd better just tell Jacques.
Over here, Jacques.
I'm going this way.
Eh? Why is he tapping his head like that? Any idea?
I can't understand him at all.
Why is he waving his hand over his head?
Oh, I remember. Do you?
Divers talk to each other by using special hand signals.
This means "OK".
This means "octopus".
And this means "shark". SHARK?! SHARK?!
Oh, no, I've dropped the camera. Quick, let's swim into that boat.
Phew, that was close.
It's good to get out of the water.
There's plenty of air to breathe in this air pocket but where are we?
- Shark.
- Looks like the inside of some kind of an old ship.
Oh, and look, there's a picture on the wall.
"The Good Ship Neptune."
Hey, this is the treasure ship we've been looking for.
The Good Ship Neptune!
Jacques, get up. We've found the Good Ship Neptune!
What?
- The Good Ship Neptune? This is it?
- Yes.
If this is the Good Ship Neptune, you know what that means?
- It means there must be treasure on it.
- Come, we must find it.
Ah, look.
It must be around here somewhere.
Usually they keep it in wooden boxes.
- Heavy wooden boxes with handles on the side.
- Like this, you mean?
No, I was looking for...
Yes, that is it! The treasure! We found the treasure.
Oh, happy days.
# We found the treasure We found the treasure. #
Er, Jacques...
- there's just old boots in here.
- What?
What?
- Rebecca.
- Yes.
- This isn't treasure.
- No.
- Just old boots.
- Yes.
It doesn't look like we'll find any treasure today.
Well, at least the shark has gone and we can go back to our boat.
- Bye-bye, Good Ship Neptune.
- Bye-bye.
HE SOBS
Oh, well, no treasure,
but at least I got to see the lovely underwater things. Bye-bye, fish.
Bye-bye, seaweed.
Hello, Mr Octopus, it's you again.
Oh, I think he wants me to follow him.
Ah, this is a different part of the ship. Now, where did that octopus go?
There he is and he's pointing over there. Maybe he's found something.
The treasure! It's the treasure in another trunk!
But I won't be able to get that out. There's too much stuff in the way.
I must go and tell Jacques.
Nothing but old boots. No treasure. Brian, Jacques is very sad.
- Jacques, I found it, the treasure.
- What? Where is it?
- You have not got it?
- No, it's still on the ship. I couldn't reach it.
- It's stuck behind loads of old wood.
- Oh, no.
But tell people we found it and they can come back and get it out.
They will never believe me.
Ah, unless...
- Unless what?
- A picture. You can take a picture.
Then I will show it to the people
and they will help me take the treasure out.
- Oh, yes! Oh, actually, no.
- No? Why?
- The camera - I dropped it when I saw the shark.
- Oh, no!
Oh, but I could go back and get it.
- Yes! Yes, go, go, go.
- OK.
Treasure, Brian, treasure!
Right, where's that camera?
It must be down here somewhere.
Oh, look, there it is.
Now I just need to reach it.
Hold on, those are anemones, so what do we need to know?
Oh, I remember. Do you?
Anemones have stinging tentacles that they pull in
when things touch them so I'd better be careful.
But how do I get them away from my camera?
Oh, hold on, I can use my pointy metal stick thing.
This should do the trick.
Ooh!
SHE LAUGHS
Great. Got it.
Now to get that picture.
SHE LAUGHS
Smile, Mr Octopus.
Now we have proof that the treasure exists. Fantastic!
Woo-hoo!
- Here you go, Jacques. Look at the picture.
- Ah, a treasure picture!
I will show this to everyone
and they will help me get the treasure out of the sea.
Thank you, Rebecca. Thank you.
We did it but we would never have managed it without remembering
everything that we needed to know.
Divers wear heavy weight belts
to help them sink down as far as they want to go.
They talk to each other by using special hand signals.
And sea anemones have stinging tentacles that they pull in
when things touch them.
- I think it's time we went home. Bye, Jacques.
- Goodbye, Rebecca.
- Say goodbye now, Brian.
- Let's go.
- So this octopus swam away and I followed it and guess what.
- What?
- It led me to the treasure.
- Wow! Now, that is what I call an adventure.
- Beats what I was doing here.
- So your picture-taking didn't work out?
I still haven't found the right pose. Nothing exciting.
Oh, well, not to worry, because...
you know that shark I told you about?
Yes, the one that came up behind you and gave you a surprise?
Yes, because when I dropped the camera I had my finger on the button
- because, as I let it go, it took a picture.
- Yes.
- I hope you like it.
I put it in a frame for you.
Oh, Rebecca, that is great and the picture is perfect for the frame.
I'm glad you like it. Playing at being divers was great fun.
What do you like to play?
I like to play builders and build huge towers.
Rugby playing is great fun.
When I play rugby players I warm up like this.
I like to play nurses and look after people.
I use bandages like this.
It's fun to play. Start playing today.
Go to...
..and click on Let's Play. See you soon.