This programme contains some strong
language and some scenes of a sexual nature.
My name's George...
and I'm a werewolf.
Everything that Owen and
I ever had can go to ash.
Bitch!
Aaargh!
We've got to eat.
I can't do this. Make your mind up time.
I choose them.
This land is ours and we have
all the time in the world.
I am the weapon.
Do it!
It's over. Are we safe now?
Professor Jaggat...
We've found them.
So I followed her into the
kitchen and I said to her,
"Nina, please tell me what's wrong. "
And she said, "It's a lot to adjust to. "
Is she frightened of anything?
What, like the attacks? I don't know.
No, not the attacks. You know, I
was actually looking forward to this,
living with Nina, but
I'm not sure we're even...
I mean, yeah, there's moisturiser
and there's Tampax in the bathroom,
but it's not like we're having sex.
We watch TV and she's just
sitting on the other...
I mean, if she could see the screen
from the patio, she'd sit there.
She saw you kill someone.
And that's aside from
all the stuff about us.
So leave! Leave.
What?
What are you looking at, Mitchell?
Nothing. Why are you so bothered
about Nina all of a sudden?
It's called compassion, George.
Ah-huh.
So are we staying here
or going somewhere else?
Because I hate this place.
I'll meet you outside.
I need to take a piss.
Hello?
There was three of them. And
they came from the darkness.
Their eyes were black and
their teeth tore at me.
Hey, are you OK now?
Can I just state for
the record? Huge fan!
Gotta say, in the flesh?
Very disappointing.
Come on, walkies. Come on.
Come on, Fido. Show me
what you've got, come on.
Woof! Woof! Down now!
Down, Fido! Down!
It's Mitchell!
Evening. Ivan?
You OK? Yeah, come on! George!
George's... Thing...
The thing that happens to him.
Does he ever talk about it?
I mean, do you know how he caught it?
Yeah, he was on holiday
and he went out walking
and he was attacked.
He actually met the guy...
The wolf. Small world.
Certainly seems to be for us.
So the wolf scratched George
and that's how he caught it.
Well, you've seen his...? Yeah.
Well, let's just say, his
vest-wearing days are over.
I need to show you something.
When he pushed me back, I got these.
But he hadn't changed, though, had he?
Well, his nails needed clipping.
But he hadn't changed. Not completely.
No, he was still George,
but... So, so you're fine.
But the change had started, Annie.
Nina, one thing I've learned about
this world is it doesn't follow logic.
We're talking about magic and curses.
We're off the map here.
In there. What?
Oh, my... That smells
disgus... They've split up.
The guy.
The girl, I can smell her perfume.
You go after him, I'll go after her.
George. Why are we doing this?
Three times. Three times
I've been attacked now.
We should let them go.
Be careful.
I think I can handle her.
I know her. Be careful.
That whole thing
outside with my husband,
that was rude.
I'll talk to him.
Once you get to know us, you'll
see we're not really like that.
A lot of vampires, it's all about
the blood and the world domination.
But me and Ivan...
.. we're just about the tourism.
Oh, mate.
You look awful.
You just smacked me in the face!
I think you know what I mean.
So it's true, then, you're clean?
Yeah, you should try it.
Oh, yes, and maybe one day
I could look like shit, too.
How long have you been back in
the country? Couple of weeks.
Daisy's visiting family.
Why did you attack George?
It was my duty. Your duty?
You didn't even like Herrick.
There are rules, Mitchell.
He was one of us.
Bet I'm not the first. I
won't be the last either, no.
Insurgents, Herrick loyalists,
just anybody wanting to
make a name for themselves.
His dance card's going
to be pretty full.
I couldn't wait to meet you.
The killer of kings.
I wanted you for my scrapbook.
What was it like?
I don't remember. A liar.
Sometimes, I actually hear the life
leave them in a sigh.
His blood was cold.
Like water from a stream.
Hello.
Is that for me or for the story?
I've been having nightmares.
I'm at work, on a ward and my
skin shreds and my bones crack
and I attack people.
It's got so bad that I'm
frightened to go to sleep.
It is all I can think
about. I want to scream.
I want to pull my hair out in clumps.
What are you going to do?
Well, the first time he
said he went to some woods.
So he wouldn't hurt anyone. Or
there's that room where it happened.
George said he wouldn't use
it again, I could go there.
I mean about telling him.
Oh, I don't know. I guess.
Will you come with me?
Well, it's the full moon tomorrow.
I don't want to go on my own.
Of course, yeah. Course I will.
Thanks.
You're going to be fine.
So you come all this way just
to have a pop at George, huh?
Not just that, no.
There's a power vacuum here.
And you intend to fill it? No, no, no.
I just want to sit back
and watch the flames.
Brush up on your history.
Taking out someone like Herrick is
never clean, it's never clinical.
It leaves a wound. And
wounds get infected.
I was in Baghdad.
I saw Phnom Penh.
I want to see what happens here.
Let me make this clear.
An attack on him is an attack on me.
You meet anyone,
you tell them that.
And tell them to hide.
We go back to the
shadows, where we were.
The revolution has been cancelled.
Daisy!
We're leaving.
Sorry. That's my ride.
We're staying at a Travelodge. Find me.
You come back!
Daisy!
Yee-hehe!
Hey, pumpkin. Did you have fun?
Heaps!
You're sliding into chaos here.
Should be an interesting show.
Hey, Bouncer!
We're not done yet.
We're a long way from being done.
I'll be seeing you.
Toodle-pip.
I'm hungry, baby.
We should grab someone on the way home.
What happened?
She attacked me.
But I managed to fight her off. Yeah?
You've got lipstick on your mouth.
You are very pretty.
So are you.
You've only just showered.
So, I'll have another one. After.
Look, sit down.
Look, I know lately
things have been a bit...
It's a lot to take in. You know,
werewolves, ghosts, vampires.
I didn't even believe in
homeopathy before this.
So why are you still
here? Just tell me that.
If it's so difficult,
why are you still here?
I need you to see me through
this. See you through what?
George.
You...
You? What, yeah, sorry? Hello?
You've forgotten what it's
like, discovering this world.
It's not exciting, it's frightening.
You're the only constant I have
left, even if you are part of it.
I need you to see me through this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Have you?
Hiya, Annie, I've been meaning to ask.
Have you started dunking
biscuits into your tea now?
It was the next logical step.
Dunking biscuits you can't eat
into tea you can't drink
is the next logical step?
This should be good. It's
like occupational therapy.
What do you do with
them afterwards? What?
Wrap them in kitchen towel, George.
I'll, um, see you later.
Hmm? Yeah, yeah.
Black coffee. Cheers.
And weird camp herbal fusion thing.
Yep, that's me.
OK, shut up! I'm going to tell
you! I've applied for a job!
As what? Well, it's something
that I've always fancied.
Well, marrying Colin Firth
isn't, strictly speaking, a job.
They're advertising for bar
staff at the New Found Out.
The pub?
That's a job you've always
fancied? Jesus, aim for the stars.
Well, it's one of the jobs
that I've always fancied.
Well, your first week's wages
are going on Hobnobs. Hold on,
are you serious?
I'm as serious as cancer when I say,
# Rhythm is a dancer. #
You can't get a job, Annie.
But who would know?! I'm
visible now, I'm solid.
You're not, you're squishy!
What about when people touch you?
What kind of pub do you think it
is? Have you worked in a pub before?
No, but I've watched The Apprentice.
And in the current job market,
there's less emphasis on experience,
because at the end of the day
it is just about giving it 110%.
Did that just happen?!
Well, I think it's a good
thing she's moving on.
No. No, you're right.
The disembodied spirit
of a dead woman is getting a
job in the service industry.
What could possibly go wrong?
Mmm. I know what this is about.
Oh, you do, do you?
That's, that's great.
It's your own lack of purpose.
My what?
Well, you're not in a relationship,
you don't have a family or a career.
Even the blood lust, a struggle
that's defined the last...
How many years? Even
that's under control.
After a life that's been
consistently violent and chaotic,
you've nothing left to fight
and nothing left to safeguard.
What about the vampire attacks then?
But you're not the target,
it's not about you any more
so there's nothing left for you to
do. You're like a piece of, um...
deadly furniture.
Did you just call me deadly furniture?
Annie, meanwhile, has a
purpose. She wants to get a job.
And I guess that must be
disconcerting to see that purpose
in other people when you
don't have one yourself.
That's completely... You're an idiot
at the moment, do you know that?
Wooahh! Just saying.
Hi.
What's this? It's a business plan.
For what? Here.
Far as I can see, your main
competition is the Duke of Avon.
They've got the whole
ironic retro thing going on.
Table football and board games.
I come in here and
I'm on a school trip to HMS Belfast.
And who's that?
That's Jack.
What's his story? Well, I don't
think he really has a story.
If it's busy he collects glasses
and we give him a pint but...
OK, well he can stay for now, we'll
review that situation in a month.
OK. What about you?
No, I... I should stay really.
No. I mean, what's your journey?
I'm guessing this wasn't
your first career choice?
So what brought you here, Darren?
Hvgh. Wh4t3v3r.
Um. Well, it was my father's
pub. Well, it is my father's pub.
But he's ill, so I'm just
here to run things, you know,
till he gets back up on his feet.
Listen, I think it's great that,
you know, you've come so well
prepared, but I just think that
my dad might be a bit resistant
to some of the things that...
Like just for one thing,
I don't think there's really
room for a climbing wall.
Oh.
There is another option here.
We could just ignore all that and
you could just give me the job?
Would that be all right?
Uh, what, what are you doing?
Cleaning. This is the Ladies.
It's a unisex toilet. A what?
There's a sign on the
door. A unisex toilet?
Are we in a fucking kibbutz?
Yeah, I'll, uh, I'll come back.
Look, are you OK?
I was a house officer at
the Whittington in London.
I had a boyfriend, a
goldfish, a flat with a garden.
When it was someone's birthday
at work, we'd have wine in mugs
and eat Twix fingers and
you know what? It was lovely.
But because I am an idiot and because
it was a promotion, I gave it all up.
Me and my goldfish moved here,
where the doctors have an acronym
for unattractive female patients,
I- W-E-J-F.
"I Wouldn't Even Jizz In Her Face".
And last night I got home
and my goldfish was gone.
No body, no note, nothing.
So, no, I'm really not OK.
D'you have a cat? Cos, well, chances
are that's what ate the goldfish.
I don't. But if I did I think I
would have made that connection.
A cat must have got in somehow.
Yeah, actually, could you
sort of piss off for a bit?
As my best friend kindly
pointed out this morning,
I don't have a girlfriend,
all my family are dead
and I mop up puke and pee and
shit for five quid an hour.
So, as much as I sympathise,
if we're comparing isolation
and disappointment I think I win.
I'm Lucy.
Mitchell.
I keep screwing up, Mitchell.
Well, you're in good company.
One bottle of fresh aqua minerale,
and one poulet and a string.
Annie?
Mr Galvin? Can you hear me?
Yes. Hi.
OK, we're live.
Professor Jaggat has explained
what we're about to do.
This is a decompression chamber.
Like for deep sea divers.
In a sense. The changes you go
through, we believe they're tidal.
Just as the gravitational
force of the moon pushes the sea
onto the land, it triggers
a transformation in you.
This chamber will be pressurised
in such a way it will negate
the natural tidal force of the moon.
So I won't change?
So you won't change.
Where is Professor Jaggat?
Moon up in two minutes.
You hear that, Mr Galvin? In
two minutes, nothing will change,
and everything will change.
Are you excited? I guess.
'Thank you for all this. '
I don't know how I can
ever thank you enough.
One day, you, the professor and
I will sit and take tea together
and gaze up at a full and harmless
moon, and that will be our thanks.
That's odd.
What? The bits of Herrick.
They've gone.
Could I hurt you?
No. No, no, no.
I am completely dead.
Anyway, it's going to be fine.
Hey, there's a werewolf
called Nina in Buffy!
I've never seen it.
No, well, I stopped watching it
once, you know, I started living it!
What does George do? To prepare.
You saw him transform
once. What did he do?
# If you go down to the woods... #
'Do you think he gets frightened?
Yes. I'm sure he does. Every time. '
# If you go down to the
woods today you'll never... #
Nina, what if you're fine?
I'm sorry, I can't.
This, this life is too much for me.
Sure.
Shall I take my top off?
Oh, yeah. Just in case.
Be a shame to ruin that.
Rocha. John Rocha.
So, um, what do we do?
We just wait.
'20 seconds. '
'Can I have a cup of water?'
'We'd prefer you not to eat
or drink till afterwards. '
I feel sick. That happens.
We've already increased
the pressure to 20 psi.
What do you mean, "that happens"?
You said you'd never done this before.
Well, did it work? Did you cure them?!
'You said you'd never done this before. '
Did you cure them? Mr Galvin,
we'll need you to talk us through
any changes, any discomfort,
any overwhelming emotions.
What happened to the other
werewolves? Are they human now?
Full moon. We're at 23 psi.
Mr Galvin, we are at full moon.
It's coming!
Come on!
'Mr Galvin. What is happening to you?'
Nothing.
Nothing's happening.
Stop it!
'Let me change! Let me change!'
Oh, oh God!
Stop it!
'Let me change! Let me change!'
Increase the pressure.
Get me out! Get me out!
That was the last Type Three.
We, um, should go. George...
George'll be home soon.
He'll be wondering where I am.
Tut-tut.
You're very close to the city.
Was that intentional? There's like
four houses just over that ridge.
Did you follow me? No need.
You guys are very easy to predict.
Oh, I found this maybe a mile away.
Aw, that's sweet.
You might tear someone's throat out
but God forbid anyone
should see your winky.
When are you going to
tell him? I'm not. What?!
It shouldn't be too hard.
I mean, he kept it secret from
the rest of the world for years.
I just have to keep it
secret from one person.
Then I'll tell him. If you do,
I'll give you fucking rabies!
I can't know and not...
He's my friend.
He won't care what you are.
You think this is about my vanity?
It will destroy him.
Your "friend". It will destroy him.
I get to choose this.
You don't get a say.
Nobody gets a say.
Oh, don't get dressed yet.
I'm liking the whole caveman thing.
Why are you so keen to
drag me over to your side?
I have a "side"? Yes, there
are two types of supernatural.
There are those that hate
it and those that love it.
And your side are always
desperate to make us enjoy this.
To drag us across.
It's like you're trying
to infect us twice.
What makes you so convinced
you're not already there?
I don't like this.
It happens TO me.
Every day, my life before
gets more and more distant,
like it happened to somebody else.
And I hate that.
I'm being robbed.
Yeah, that's all very nice and
martyr-y, but there's one problem.
I don't believe you.
You killed Herrick and
it's like opening a door
and now you're wondering
whether to step through.
When I met Ivan,
he said to me,
"Come, see the world and fuck. "
Sorry, but can you think of a
better way to spend your life?
You knew.
Not for sure.
Not till now.
Um, OK!
Well, I'm going to...
When I changed, I lost myself.
I did things...
And George and Annie, they...
They hid.
This is a different life for
you now, Nina, but it's a life.
It'd be so easy for you
to surrender right now.
You know what I think?
I think this is about your conscience.
You encouraged me and George.
You told him to live a life.
You loaded a gun and you
fired it into a crowd.
Bang.
You OK? What's up? Nothing.
It's all wine and roses, George.
Mitchell?
Like she said, it's nothing.
I'm late.
What's going on, Nina?
You hungry?
No, I ate a... I think it was a stag.
Bit too much information, George.
OK.
We can add that to the list
of things we don't talk about.
Have a shower.
You're covered in
blood. It's disgusting.
What was that? What happened there?
You, you think you scare me?
Look.
I'm doing my best. But this...
This is not the person I need right now.
You... FUCK YOU!
You think the last few
weeks have been easy for me?
The last few years?
No, but you've lived in this
world a lot longer than me.
I'm saying it's a lot to
deal with... Oh, here we go.
The same bloody
conversation, over and over!
So why are you still here?
You can walk away from
this any time you want.
I can't go. Oh, come on!
It's not like I wouldn't understand!
It's not like nobody's
walked out on me before.
I can't go, George.
Why? I can see it in your eyes.
The disgust. I touch you and
you flinch. You literally flinch.
My God, do you know how that feels?
I'm not saying you should find
this easy, but do me a favour, Nina,
and take your disdain somewhere
else. Because to get that every day,
to see that from someone I
love, is just another punishment.
I didn't just find out there's no Santa.
You've wrecked everything.
You didn't mean to, I know, but
you've torn everything apart.
You're doing it again!
This is not about YOU!
What are you doing?
Is that perfume?
Don't be ridiculous. My God, it stinks.
You're imagining it, Nina.
Hold on. I've smelt that before.
Last night, when you and
Mitchell went for a drink.
Mitchell. Oh, is this about Mitchell?
What? Is there a...
My God, with him?
I'm not even going to
dignify that with a response.
Well, it makes sense, doesn't it?
I mean, you can't touch
me, you won't go near me...
Jesus Christ.
Jesus Christ!
Now you give me this as well?
Isn't that what you just accused me
of? I didn't accuse you of anything.
You both seem very cosy all of a sudden.
Plus I've had Mitchell telling
me off for being unsympathetic,
and that explains the reason
why you're so reluctant to leave.
Mmm. Yeah. Well, this
should put your mind at rest.
That's great, yeah(!) Oh, my God.
All those things you said about how
you'd had enough of men like him,
how with me you were finally
making the right decision.
Don't you get it? I need
you. You can't push me away.
I can't face this on my own.
Everything outside is torture.
You gave it to me, George!
What?
In that room.
You pushed me away and you
scratched me. You gave me the curse.
But last night...
Was very busy.
I'm a werewolf!
I'm a fucking werewolf!
There's a goldfish on my table.
He's not your original goldfish.
I haven't been holding him hostage.
Um, are you even allowed to
put goldfish in jars any more?
Who says you can't? I
don't know. The people.
I'm sure there's a thing now that
you can't put goldfish in jars.
You made that up. It's very possible.
So what's his name?
Trevor.
Trevor? Hmm-mm.
Hello, Trevor!
And do we have joint custody?
No, he's, um, all yours.
But I might want to visit
him from time to time.
OK, that's, that's fine.
I'd like that. I think that will happen.
I've just got out of a,
a, a thing with a guy.
I've just got here. It's...
You're right. I'm sorry, that was...
It's cool. These things take time.
And that's one thing I've got.
So soft drinks at the bottom
and then lagers at the top.
Lagers at the top.
OK? And aside from that, just
make sure that we're stocked up.
OK. OK?
Right, well I think the best thing to do
is just let you loose on a
customer, see what happens.
Bring him/her on!
Yes!
OK.
Right.
Gosh, and he's handsome.
Maybe I should do this one. Oh, no,
no, no. I am going to serve his ass.
Yeah. OK. All right.
Hello, sweetheart. The usual?
Er, I've never been here before.
No, you don't look like
our usual clientele.
Well, it's like Driving
Miss Daisy in here.
Annie.
Hold on there, squire. All right?
Hi. Um, it's great that
you're being so friendly, yeah,
but just keep it simple for now. Right?
Just find out what he wants
and make him feel welcome.
OK. Got you. OK? Yeah. All right, yeah.
You're fine. OK.
What would you like?
Vodka, soda, no ice.
I'm afraid we don't do cocktails.
I'm... I'm just kidding!
I'm just kidding, no! We are
just so thrilled that you're here.
Ooh, whoops!
It got me! Man down!
Anyway, that's nine pounds.
What? Two pounds. Two pounds,
two pounds. Eighty. Eighty.
Er... here. Two sixty. Shit, sorry.
It's fine. Yeah? Really. Yeah,
it's fine. Don't worry about that.
It's my first day.
Really? Well, you'd never know.
# It's a simple town
# With a lonely sound
# There's demons in the trees
# Come and rescue me
# It's a simple town
# Where the face becomes a veil... #
Concentrate.
Hush little
baby, don't say a word.
Mama's going to buy you a mockingbird.
And if that mockingbird won't sing...
.. Mama's going to buy
you a diamond ring.
Now who's following who?
I work here.
You're kidding. Small world.
What are you doing, Daisy?
Just visiting family.
Doesn't she look pretty?
Sure.
Is she your mum?
She's my daughter.
I met Ivan just after I had her.
She was fine. She had aunts and cousins.
Besides, look at her.
Good innings.
Wedding ring.
I could be a grandmother!
Oh, that makes me feel old.
She's the last thread.
I thought I'd cut it.
Daisy.
Give me the scissors.
It scratches you inside.
Even from the other end of the world.
And you have to stop it.
I called in
to see her at her house.
I thought I'd done the job,
but she's a fighter, like me.
Don't hurt her any more. Let her sleep.
Look at you. Still so moral,
so desperate to be human.
Like mooning after a lover
that left you years ago.
She had everything.
Become cruel.
It's fun.
She's the last person who needed you.
What?
She wanted...
you.
Ivan just wanted a portable fuck.
I guess that must hurt.
You... you don't know
what you're talking about.
It's not her fault.
Where are you going? I
could tear her throat out!
Go for it. But don't imagine
it'll make her go away.
I'll do it. I'm not like you.
I can't be like you!
Not you.
Don't let me have done this to you.
Not to you, not to you.
You didn't know, baby.
You didn't know.
Are you having another drink
or not? Well, here's the thing.
I'm looking at a property on Oxford
Road and... Saul's a property developer.
Yeah, high-end stuff. Corporate lets.
The properties round here are
low-hanging fruit, Saul says.
Well, I love it round here. Yeah? Yeah.
Anyway, Duncan who I work
with, he drops me off,
and I leave my jacket in his car.
No phone, no wallet, no cash.
Ah. I just need to make a
call, get him to pick me up.
Well, there's a payphone
on Windsor Terrace. Yeah?
Yeah. Then that's where I'll go. Cheers.
Oh, no, no, no! Why don't you just
use the one at my house? Oh, well...
I don't think that's such a good idea.
Yeah, he's right. I might murder you.
Oh, God.
Plenty have tried!
No honestly, it's fine.
Customer care is very important
to us here at the New Found Out.
Isn't that right, Hugh?
Well, yeah, but... Great.
Shall we? After you. OK.
Well.
We all saw that coming.
He must have got held up. Oh,
would you like a cup of tea?
You are an angel, I swear to God.
Thank you.
Hey, I'm a friend of Annie's.
I thought you two were working?
Finished early. Went drinking.
Ah, are you both drunk? Er, no! A bit.
Why's there a really handsome
man in the living room?
That's Saul, a customer from the pub.
You think he's handsome?
Hey. All right? I'm with Annie.
Who's the guy? Saul. A
customer from the pub.
You're already bringing work
home? Nina thinks he's handsome.
Annie will back me up on this.
God, yeah.
Nah, he's not handsome.
Ah, thank you. Why does this always happen
when you tell a man another man is handsome?
It is possible for
two men to be handsome.
Three men.
Although he is really handsome.
Look, can we talk about
something else? I'm a werewolf.
I guess he's fairly handsome.
Yes, well, let's hope
he's deaf as well. Nina.
I don't know what happens now.
I don't know how I feel about this,
or any of you or what you expect of me
or how you think I should react.
Well, no-one helped us.
Annie was here for a
year before we moved in.
George was alone for six
months before I met him.
And until then I had
no-one in the world.
It's going to be different for you.
Whatever happens next,
there's four of us now.
Hiya.
Hey. Avon and Somerset Energy.
We've had reports of a gas leak, so
we're checking all the households.
Right, erm... do you need to come in?
Actually, we need to move
everyone out, till it's safe.
You're kidding? What's
going on? Gas leak.
Everyone's got to leave their houses.
Where have they all gone?
Just around the corner.
Should only take about ten minutes,
but we need to keep the street clear.
You know, I bet those people
are going to be really thirsty.
What's going on?
# Time and space stretch out before you
# And the universe implores you... #
I've made teas and coffee, so I
don't know if you're interested...
Do you want to get tea or coffee?
But there's no biscuits or anything,
so don't freak out. Hi. Tea? Coffee?
There's sugar if you want some.
Thank you. That's all right.
There's tea, coffee over
there. Hi. Tea? Coffee?
Thanks very much. It's all right. And
there's sugar there if you'd like some.
I'm sorry about all that
trouble a few weeks ago.
All the people shouting at you
because they thought you
were touching that kiddie.
Oh, come on. That's
water under the bridge.
Yeah, and there's sugar
there if you'd like some.
Thank you. Lovely.
Tea in a crisis, that's what I
say. Is it Earl Grey? PG tips.
My God.
Finally.
# You are part of everything
# You are part of everything. #
Come on.
Who did you talk to?
Sir? Which of the three?
Yeah, all of them.
Yeah, they seemed nice.
Nice?
We're clear upstairs.
Bring in our guest. Come on. Come on.
I have to be back by four.
You said this could help me? Because
I'm up for parole at the end of the year.
God's work is its own reward.
Oh, yeah, no, it totally is,
but Professor Jaggat said,
because I'm helping you, then...
We can talk about that later.
Is there anybody in this
house that we can't see?
No. There are no presences, spirits
or unquiet souls in this house?
There was something.
There's been a lot of
activity, a lot of...
And it's left a kind of...
What do you call it? Residue. Yeah.
But it's not here now.
It's funny, you see these things on TV.
I didn't think they actually worked.
They don't.
But you didn't know that.
"Then the king commanded,
and they brought forth Daniel,
"and they cast him
into the den of lions. "
"Now the king spoke
"and said unto Daniel... "
".. 'Thy God whom thou
serveth continually... '"
"'.. he will deliver thee. '"
You've gone native.
The three of you.
Beasts should be put in cages.
Long live the king! Long live the king!
GEORGE!
Uploaded by:
Lauta