Hey, Sing
Hey, sorry
What are you doing? You want to be beaten?
Guests are waiting, go and serve
Ok...sorry...
Go quick
I'll deduce your wage if you go on reading comics
Shit, look how lousy you are
You can't even walk properly. Hurry up
Watch up
Don't kill him, I want him alive
Let's chase
- Are you alright? - I'm fine
Bill. Thank you for protecting me
Come on. Are you alright?
Alright, it's trivial
This is my name card
Just ring me up if you have trouble
Thanks
Say it. So stubborn?
Say...don't shut your mouth
Won't you tell us?
Kid, this is your last chance
Say what you know or we'll burn you up
Shit, you aren't saying? Burn him!
If you remain silent, but even if we let you off
your boss won't believe you haven't betrayed him
He will never let you off
In fact, I know who sent you
You'll be my man if you'll tell us
I'll then protect you
And give you some money
Think it over
Let him go
It's your luck
Hung Yi
Hasn't Hung Yi arrived?
Just this?
Old Wai, you're old now
You're getting more and more stupid as time goes
You take so many men with you just for a talk
Are you mad?
I've been in this field for decades
I've always taken them with me
and we've always been so straight
Just say whatever you must
You've taken this position for long. It's time gave it up
Don't you even know what I want?
I want your collaboration in Thailand. Got it, nuts?
Kid, don't try if you can't take it up
All greedy cats die of choking with bones
You must die like that too
Are you blind?
I'm a tiger, don't compare me with a cat
I swallow bones easily
You escaped last time but I must kill you now
Hung Yi, how many people you can kill?
Dad, help
Look at yourself. You are grown up but stupid
Go on shooting, won't you?
Old Wai, you have such lousy men. That you'll surely die soon
How's that?
Look at yourself. You get scared so easily
You should be as brave as your father
Master Hung, no...don't
Stop him. Don't let him go!
Shit
Master, why?
Please make it clear, say...
Master Hung asked me to do this
as you bullshit
Master, you took me for someone else. I don't know Hung Yi
You...
What? Again?
It's too good I arrive late, shit
Hey, Sing
What's the matter?
Turn around
I am busy
I ask you to turn around
I hurt myself while drinking
What are you laughing at? Don't laugh
I don't
You were laughing at me in your mind
How did you know?
Why must you get involved with Hung Yi?
It's bad to have you here. Go away
What are you talking about? Who is Hung Yi?
Leave...quick...leave this minute
Why must I stay? You are too proud
Who the hell is Hung Yi?
I must teach him a lesson if I see him
How are you, Mr. Wai? I come to...
Are you Sing?
Yeah, I come to...
Ok, I know what you want
Find Bill at the lounge. He'll arrange you a job
Thank you, Mr. Wai, anything else?
You may leave now
I may?
You are too good at boxing, Mr. Wai
I've leaving, Mr. Wai
Shit, damn you
Shit
How many are you, Sir?
I come for Bill
This way please
Be careful
Come in
Please come in
Master Bill
What do you think?
You are pretentious
Not the least, Mr. Wai asked me to come
-Are you hungry? -A little bit
Give him money to buy us food
Buy food?
Master Bill, I've seen all things these years
I'm well-prepared. I'm not rubbish
Not rubbish?
Show us something then
Master Bill...you have bad breath, is there decay?
Bastard, you want to beat me?
No, I dare not
Please listen to me
I didn't mean that but he really has bad breath
Dare you say that again?
Master Bill, don't be rash, don't use the gun
Let me go...
What does he mean? Mr. Wai sent me here
Who does he take me as? Buy food for him?
Mr. Wai asked me to look for him
He's insulting Mr. Wai when he did that to me
Master Bill is not such a person indeed
You'll know if you get along with him
I dare not
I can't put up with such a person
You are so narrow-minded?
You're wrong, I won't remember that
What's going on?
You are that guy
I recognize you, you have two things, don't you?
What two things?
Guns
Don't you put them here?
What are you trying to do?
Nothing...| just want to see
You are not that narrow-minded?
They are handy, how much are they?
Catch her
-What do you want? -Go
Nothing to see, kid, haven't you seen this before
Bitch, don't pretend, take her there
Take off all her clothes
I must see how special she is
-What do you want? -You asked for this
What is it...Are you ok?
Miss? You might just tell me
You're just kidding, men?
Yeah, just kidding
You know him, miss?
Yeah, this is only a joke
Then it's nothing if this is a joke. It's a joke
You fool us with that toy gun. You want to die, kid?
What is this?
Beat him up
Go to hell
-Get up -You bastard
Don't fool here, get lost
Run quick
Don't be afraid, miss. Shall we see you home?
-Are you ok? -Are you alright?
I'm fine, thanks
How's been business recently?
Just so and so
-Be careful -I will
Shit, why are you so scared?
- I've had enough - Wait outside then
It's not yet up
Hey, what are you doing? Where are you going?
Am I stink? Sit down
Hey, pour some water on
Add some water on
Good, well done, both of you, really good
-Thanks -You're flattering me
Sing, I am right to hire you
Learn from Chun, ok? You'll have brilliant future
My future depend on you, Mr. Wai
Ok, you must be tired, go and have a rest
Thanks, we must leave now
Don't forget to back me up, thanks
Shall we play mahjong after work?
Sure
Don't move, a bit weak on the middlefinger
Hey, you understand music?
I'm just too good at it
Too good? Are you boasting?
I was to have been a singing contest champion
That Jacky Cheung would not be so famous
Why don't you sing for me?
Ok, I'll sing a whole song for you
-Sorry to bother you -Not at all
You must make me show up
What song are you going to sing?
Any song will do
What key?
As you like
Good
Sorry
What song is this?
Jacky's top song, don't you know?
Yeah...
Go ahead then
I'd better...sing without music
OK
Come on
Your dad is pregnant.“congratulations
How then?
Why do you laugh at my technics? I've practised for long
What so funny?
I'm just happy
Are you laughing at me...? Come on, come and sing together
No, I can't sing
You must even if you can't
Thanks, this is yours
Mine?
Thanks
Do you like it?
Since Hung Yi's death
All the drug traffickers come to us
So...the stuff is badly demanded
Chun, you go to Thailand with Bill
and talk to Uncle Chuen
We want 5 more kilos a month
Bill, you are most experienced
There should be no problem
If anything should happen
make your own decision
Got it, Mr. Wai, I will
Chun, send me my regards to Uncle Chuen
I Will
Tell him I'll go see him if I have time
Got it, Uncle
Sorry, Mr. Wai
Sing, you might as well go too
You can be of help to them
And you can learn something too
Got it, thanks Mr. Wai
Sing, did you have anything to tell me?
Yeah, in fact I was...
I was going to say...in fact...
What in fact, in fact?
We're going for business, not for sightseeing. Be smart
Don't scare him, Bill. It's nothing, imaging you're travelling for fun
I will, Master Chun. It's hot there. I'd better take insect repellent
Mr. Brown, please contact our information desk
This is Final Call for flight 202
For security reason, please do not leave your bags behind you
Sir, happy to meet you. Mr. Kim sent me to meet you
Please follow me
Get in the car
Kid, who asks you to sit in the middle?
Shut the door
How long does it take to Mr. Kim's villa?
Not far. It's very short time only
Yeah...short time...
Yes...short time...
I've told you many times not to read comics
We're working, not fooling
Listen to me, will you? You must do whatever I ask you to
Hey, Master Bill, don't fool him anymore
This is for the sake of him, right?
These female mosquitoes keep biting me, lousy
Great, how can you tell they're female?
Of course I can
How to?
They have breasts
Chun, is that true?
No, not the breasts
Only female mosquitoes bite, it's easy
Those who have low IQ don't know
- IQ'? I had little education - I know
-But I have high IQ -Do you?
Just test me
It's not necessary
I ask you to test me
Ok...I'll do as you say
It's said that Ming's dad has got 3 sons
The eldest son is called Big Hair
What's the youngest son called?
-Little Hair -Wrong
-No Hair -Wrong
-Armpit Hair -Wrong
What Hair is he called then?
I told you it's Ming's dad. So he's called Ming
I shouldn't have tested you. Too easy for you
Bastard, dare you fool me?
Master Bill, don't caress me, Master Bill
I don't like this, Master Bill...don't...
Where are my shoes? What happens? Where are they?
Hi, do you speak Chinese?
Why, get aside...| told you to get aside
-I saw her first -What do you mean?
Heynlook
You are junior only
How are you?
I saw her first
Get lost...quick
You are pretty
$3000 for a short fun
- It's yours - Hey“.
Where are you going?
Don't go, honey
I'm aged, I can't walk easily
You thought I was like before
It's not time when I fought with your uncle
Especially after your uncle fought with Hung Yi
I must be very careful when I do business. You too
Right, how is your uncle?
Uncle is really well...
Uncle Chuen, I was sent here by Mr. Wai
He wants to increase 5 kilos more a month
No problem, since Master Kit asks for this
I'll then do as he wants
Right, Bill, you are so helpful to Master Kit
You're flattering me
Master Kit and I are both aged now
I'll say this will soon be your world
Kid, did you hear? I didn't boast
In fact...
Crouch
Catch them alive
-Chun -Don't move...
- Don't move - Please don't!
Go away...
Get down
Come down
Don't be so timid
Shit, that must be him
General, I've contacted with the boss. He killed Hung Yi
Don't move
Master Chun
Master Bill
Master (Shun...
Stop!
We must make it clear
It is because I killed Hung Yi. Then your business cut down
Shit, what the hell is Hung Yi?
We will sell it to you even now he's dead
Trust me then or you must kill me
I know Hung Yi used to buy 40 kilos from you monthly
We can buy 50 kilos from you monthly too. We can surely do this
No one from HK will buy from you, except us
But I have terms
My men are badly injured. You must send them back to HK at once
I'll stay behind to talk with you
What...what do you think?
Too rash, very brave?
Just think about this
You should not make yourselves as hostages. Do you read me?
Hungry? Eat something
You detest this? Just eat when there's food
Go ahead, eat it
Do you have news of Sing?
Don't say so much
Just take a rest
There's news of Sing, don't worry about him
He's like a King in Thailand
He was better than you, and you worry about him?
Ann, I've told you he'd be fine
ExceHent
People here are awful. I don't see this in HK
We play this, don't you understand?
It's called Snooker in English
Come to HK and I'll treat you to all this
Water melons here are great
But papayas in HK are great too
Do you want to go back to HK badly?
I'm lying if I say not
Don't worry, I'll do what I've promised you
I'm sure my colleagues will come back for me
Just like you trust me
ExceHent
Shit, I've been waiting so long
Shit, what kind of colleagues are they?
How could they have done this?
I don't even have enough money for a taxi home
Damn all of you, you're so evil
Who do you think I am?
I fought so hard in Thailand
I nearly got killed
Sorry, boss, I am to blame. I'm so bored that I come out
I'll go back at once if you like
I was beaten up last time
Can you save this, please?
Hero is hero, so stylist at kneeling
You lost temper? It's only a joke
You get proud just as you saved us?
You're really mad with us?
Let's go away then
Don't act so bravely alone next time
Or I'll cut our relationship
How is that?
Kid
|...| thought you were really deserting me
Bullshit, you lived like King in Thailand
Bastard
Why must we stand here?
-What do you want? -Must I say?
Help...are they touched?
I'm 0k...
They aren't touched...
Are they touched?
Don't fool, we must go to dine at Bill's place
Hey, go change your clothes
My wife is waiting for you for dinner
She wants to thank you, let's go
Ok, let's go...
Hey, how can you go like this?
I'll change my trousers
Not funny
Come in...
-Daddy is coming back -Honey
Daddy...
So many? There's still one?
Let me introduce, Sing, Ann, Chun
Lousy
Sorry to bother you
Please make yourselves at home. We will soon eat
Bill, serve your friends now
Come and make a queue...
Tell uncles your name, quick
Chu Hung
Chu Kan
Chu Rou
Chu Ti
Chu Fei
Chu Er
Chu Wei
Chu Ya
All eight of them are my daughters
Greet uncles, quick
Uncle, brother, sister
Good, come here
Go and play
Eight now and a pregnant one, aren't you tired?
But my wife gives birth to them, not me
Yeah, I forget that
Hey...Remember, in front of my wife
don't mention about anything of Thailand
Ok, I won't
Hey, and you're so smart in Thailand
I am in HK now. I can answer any of your questions
Why?
Because this is my place, I have clevermind here
-Do you? -Sure
What about Ming?
Can you say something other than Ming?
What about Keung?
Ok, Keung
Keung saw five female tortoises. Crawling into a hole
Then five male tortoises crawled in hurriedly to hole
After a while, the five male crawled out
but the five female didn't, why?
It's too simple
The female ones got lost as it was dark in there
Wrong
-They fell asleep? -Wrong
-Because". -Wrong
Hey, because is wrong?
As 'because' is not an answer
-Right? -You're right
Bill, come and help
My wife ask me, I'll answer in a while
Just think over
A bird is falling into the river...
-The female were laying eggs? -Wrong
Wrong again? No reason
Sing, they left by another exit?
Wrong
But, it's not reasonable. Am I so stupid?
Be careful, wife
I've guessed, they all got pregnant
-Wrong -What did you say?
Nothing...let me do it
Stop playing for the moment, time to eat
Come here...come on...
Thanks very much. Let's eat, and play later
What is the answer?
I'll tell you later
Can't you tell me now?
Answer is the female tortoises were turned over by the male ones
Why did they do that?
What do you think then?
-Make love? -Right
But your mind is so dirty
Bastard! Nothing...go on eating
Eat this
Master Bill, what dog is it, French one?
Wrong
-Pet dog? -Wrong
Chun, have you had enough?
I'm stuffed
Master Bill, I envy you to have a sweet home
and eight daughters too
Me too
You have someone too
What someone?
Something wrong with her?
Forget it
Thanks to Sing's cleverness in Thailand
Don't mention such things again
I was forced to do that. I am really regretful now
I hope it never again
This is the cleverness I've always told you
Thanks
Bill, come in for a while
My wife wants me, take your time
ls this a dull dog?
Yeah, like you
You fooled me
Sing. You're fighting hard now, but for what?
For what...
I must think for what. What can I say?
For what...for...
This is for you
Take it
Are you crazy? Fifty kilos a month? You must be kidding
And you don't know a bit about the case
You thought it's a market affair?
You mustn't blame him. He saved our lives
Mr. Wai, as Sing was so clever then
otherwise we would all have died
We don't necessarily have to buy it
Are you nuts? Baichai is not a human
We are not up to irritating him. We just can't make him away
And we can't buy from Chuen anymore
So we must buy from Baichai
Let me handle it as I caused all this
How are you going to handle?
Uncle, I must bear responsibility too. I'll handle it with him
Mr. Wai, don't worry
We three will handle it all
Ok, have it fixed within 2 weeks
Now, Shark Tak has supply
He said Vietnam people of Holland are now in HK
They want to deal with big business
Shark Tak has fixed a time for us
Let's go on with that
Master, this is superb stuff
If you like it, take sell it to Holland
How much stock is there?
35 kilos
Can you take it all?
We can guarantee the quality and quantity
The most important is money matter
The price we used to buy from HK...
Price is not your business. Who are you to speak?
Remember why you come to HK?
You wasted time finding your wife
You bastards, you're just juniors
How can you supply us with 35 kilos a month? Shit
We people strive to coming to HK
But you force them to die back
Look, you HK people. You'll be refugees sooner or later
Damn you bastard
Don't argue like that, masters
We all want to make money, don't argue
Don't lose your temper, we'll leave
It's ok, boss, it's ok. I'm sorry
The sea is calm and the weather is fine
And there's the sun
Chun, give way
Master Tak, walk two steps ahead
Just two steps, thanks
Thanks, right, a bit more ahead...
A bit to the left, thanks, to the left
Lower your bottoms, a bit lower
Ok, fine, dare you fool us?
Forgive me, don't spank we anymore
Dare you fool us? Who do you think we are?
You made us come for a cruise?
Get away, I must kill you
- Let go - Ok...let me do it
Master Sing, help
Beg me? I must go on beating
How can you beat like this? Don't you know?
I didn't lie to you
Damn it, dare you fool me?
Don't beat me anymore or you'll kill me
A Vietnamese there. He just wants to find his wife
No...
Bill...
Don't beat him anymore. It's not his fault
Forget it
I'll castrate you next time
Still alive?
Yes...
Let's go
Get up now
How can he get up? ls he injured?
Drink this, it's all right
You said that Vietnam guy wants to find his wife
What exactly is it?
This is a long story
You keep on beating him. But why so softly?
My suit
It's shit you must lie down again
I must train you of beating
Come on, drink this
You are so happy today
And so is everybody. I must introduce you
Judy, she plays flute
Don't say such things again
You are evil. You say bad remarks, I won't care you
But I am serious
But I am only joking. Come on, cheers
Cheers
All women out
Don't be so polite, come on, cheers
Cheers
Thanks
Heung“.
\'i
Heung, why are you here?
You friends brought me here
Thanks very much
You come to HK right
Sit down first
Thanks everybody
Just tell me if you need any help
Right, Master Yi, I haven't finished the discussion last time
Sorry, I can't be of help in this case
You saw it last time. I just can't make decision
I do want to help but I can't
Maybe after seeing this present
you can make decisions
Don't move, why are you moving?
Hands on your head, crouch, guns down
You want to remember my face?
Move quickly
Sing, why don't you shoot? You want to die?
How do I know he has guns?
I do want to choose one person among you
to be the successor
Mr. Wai, why bother?
Master Ming is the perfect person
But Master Ming is so timid
No way, we all fought up for our business
How can I leave it to my own son?
Uncle, don't worry, we'll all assist him
Yeah, Mr. Wai, with our help he'll do well
I can't leave my position to him
Then Uncle Chun will be the next best person
He will do well
I'm old, it's now a world for the young
They should take the lead now
Then it should be Chun. Chun has been with Uncle Chun for so long
He should be the leader
If Chun refuses, it should be Sing. Sing is very clever, right?
Or else Master Bill, he is competent too
No, how can I? Should be Ming, as he's able
We shall help him, right, Mr. Wai?
I know what to do, Mr. Wai
Cheers...
Freeze
I'm really too happy today
A cigar for each of you, pass them
Master Bill, you are smart
lam, if I don't have a son
How can I face my ancestors?
You must drink more...
Cheers...
Cheers, will you?
Sing, don't you find I'm more clever now?
Are you?
Because I have a son now. So I become cleverer
You mean it...
I can absolutely answer any question you ask
Ok, let's say Beethoven
Not Ming?
It's the same. Ming is his nickname
You know Beethoven, don't you?
Yeah, he was a great musician
Right, you know what instrument he was excellent
- Flute? - Terrific, you are right
When he was playing the flute
He never used this finger, why?
Why? He picked his nose with this?
Right, perfectly right
I envy you
Chun, this way
Sorry, everybody
Chun
Sorry to have come late
Come on...Sit down
Don't say a thing, take one
Drink more
I'm really too happy, Chun. I've ask you a question
Sure
Beethoven's nickname is Ming, you know
He was a great musician, you know
He was excellent a playing flute, you know
Why did he never play flute with this finger?
Why? Do you know why?
I do, as this is not his finger. But yours
You bastard, you fool me again
Forget it, let's cheers
It's so small
I'm too happy
Let's shoot at each other
Come on...
Sing, I want to ask you a favour
Please
What is it?
I had little education
You did
I have eight daughters
And how do you find their names?
Not bad
-Really? -Really
Now that I have a son
Sol must make up a name
I want a real good name
Real good name?
I've thought for a long time and got the name Lung
But with Chu it means bad
Yeah, so I want you to help
Help me find another name between Chu and Lung
No problem. Don't worry, let me think
Sit here for a while
Let me think...Ok?
Thanks
Chu Lung? Chu Yuen Lung
Which Yuen?
Like Chow Yuen Fat and Jacky Chan
Chow Yuen Fat, Jacky Chan
Chow Yuen Fat...Jacky Chan...
How is it written?
It's like nourishing, really good
But I don't know that either
Write for me quick
Why don't you learn writing?
I am learning from you now
- Are you ok? - I'm alright...
Let me see you home
No, thanks
How many fingers?
I must go home and see my son
Ok, I'll leave now
Go ahead...thanks...bye
Be smart
Chum...come here...you're smart
Take one
Do you know? I have a son now
Do you know his name?
He's called Chu Yuen Lung. ls this a nice name?
Can you write the word?
It's written like this
What is it?
It's not my business
I can't insert this
It must be this one then
No...don't, you are nuts?
Shit, don't run
I must chop you up if I catch you
Don't run, shit
About Bill's death and Sing's vanishing
Do you have any opinion?
This is Sing's pen. Why was it found on Bill's body?
The car was smashed and he disappeared. I feel suspect
Shit, rubbish, you made it a mess
Get out and don't hinder me
Hey, how's it?
Shit, I didn't kill anyone. There's no point in explaining to you
I tell you once more, I haven't killed Master Bill
But nobody believes you now
Why don't you shoot at me then?
You say I'm a fool at guns. You do it
Freeze, bastard
Don't...
Let me go...
Sing
Master (Shun...
Shit, let go
Master Chun. Forget me, let go
Master (Shun...
Let go
There's a bomb
Run for your life, quick
Forget about me
Sing, why don't you shoot?
Master (Shun...
Come here quick, run
My legs' broken
I'll carry you
Alright, yours is a minor injury, it'll alright
I'll carry you, come on, quick
Sing, just one shot is enough. No need for the second
I know...come on
-Sing -Be quick
Sing, don't ever tell Ann
Ok, I'll never let Ann know
I will never...Master Chun...
It hurts, give me liquour...
ls it here?
Drink it quick, I'll carry you on
We're going to escape
Did you hear, Master Chun?
You must live on, you mustn't die
We've now ridded all the hindering
I've laid a smooth way for you now
This will forever be our business now
Do you understand me, Ming?
Got it, dad
Have you heard about a person, Lau Pan?
He made use of men to fight for him
One day, he felt threatened
He then killed all
Then another men Lau Pi
In order to safeguard the throng for his son, he thought of all ways
To make his men to fight for him
Because...they were all heroes...
But the most hindering for me is you
I can't get in your position one day you don't die
I have put up with that for years do you know?
Sing
Why haven't you seen me for so long?
But I'm seeing you now
Where's Master Chun?
Master Chun and Master Bill have gone to the Pole
I'm going to join them there
Chun asked me to give you these two things before he left
We may stay there for a long time
He said you needn't wait for him
Sing
Don't worry, take care of yourself. Goodbye