Previously on "Gravity"...
Diego didn't know the right where to
talk the people who he owed money to.
As a result, they didn't
leave him much of a face.
Trying to kill yourself
to be with your dead wife.
I'll take good care of him.
And you won't be forgotten.
I thought you should know.
I can't have kids.
- Adam Rosenblum. I'm
Shawna's boyfriend. - Boyfriend?
I got a bigger dick
because I thought
That it would help me
to find true love.
Filthiest colon I've ever seen.
What is that, a cheeto?
This... is... your... man.
There's no detective
Miller on the NYPD.
Well, who comes up
with that badge number?
No one.
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:nophone
Gravity
Season01 Episode01 Season Finale
You're kind of
scaring me a little bit.
Call me "hombre."
Why?
Just do it.
Hombre?
I like that.
When you said you didn't
want to have kids,
Was that because
you couldn't
Or 'cause...
You wouldn't want to
anyway?
I really want kids.
Do you?
Yes.
Let's start trying
right now.
Hey, I thought you couldn't.
Well, I can't,
But right after
we make love,
We could go online
And pick out a cute little
brown or yellow one.
Yeah, sure, why not?
Mom, what?
Hello, Adam.
Where are you?
I told you. Mom, I told you.
I'm at a friend's house.
It sounds like
you're whispering.
Why are you whispering?
No, I'm whispering because
he has an inner ear infection.
Inner ear infe...
well, is that contagious?
No, it's not contagious.
Now, hold on
while I google it.
Now, you know I prefer
to use webmd.
What? Now I can't hear you.
May... maybe it is contagious.
Well, perhaps you can't hear me
because you're having symptoms of...
Bye.
I'm surprised
it wasn't your mom
That was discovered
in your dad's trunk.
Wait,
maybe that's not funny.
You want some of this, papi?
Come and get it.
It hurts so good.
You like that?
This is part of this body, baby.
You like my tight little ass?
Well, you gotta earn it, baby.
That nipple's for you.
Go ahead.
No.
Nipple's not for you.
Damn, I'm pretty, man.
I threw my purse at your head
when we first me.
Why'd you do that?
Because from the moment you told
your story, I wanted in.
What's your name?
Evil.
And yours?
"fuckin' happy."
all right. And you?
No? Okay. It's okay.
You guys ever been to
"the rocky horror picture show"?
As if. Posers.
Dress-up freaks.
Really?
I kind of got into it one
summer back when I was your age.
I thought
it was kind of cool.
I think it's still playing
at midnight on the weekends.
You're good kids.
But I'd really
appreciate it
If you didn't hang out
around here anymore.
Because you represent a part
of my life that really did...
Die.
Okay?
Okay.
Thanks.
Well, if we did go
to "Rocky horror,"
Would you come with us...
just once?
Sure.
Just once.
Okay.
I love you!
Oh, my God!
Mr. Champagne,
thank you for seeing me.
I appreciate it.
I'm detective Miller, NYPD.
How do you do?
What is this about?
Not some D.U.I., I hope.
I did the community service.
I reported it correctly.
No, this is a completely
different matter.
May I have a seat?
Yeah. Be my guest.
Thank you.
Gotta say, you're
scaring me a little bit.
Did you establish a trust for a
boy named Cary MacDougal in 1982?
He would have been 10
at the time.
I don't know.
Did something happen
to this boy or...?
Did you establish a trust
for him?
Well, you know, you and I
have to establish a little trust
Before I'm gonna talk
about a thing like that.
I have no idea
what's going on.
We're investigating
the death of his mother.
Do you know her?
No.
No, I can't say that I do.
I'm sorry.
Did you establish a trust
for her son?
Well, you know,
to be perfectly honest,
You know,
I would have to check.
As you must know,
I do establish trusts
For kids that are in
foster care, state-raised.
Give them a chance at something,
maybe go to college.
I'm just curious.
Why do you do that?
Because, if you must know,
that's the way I was raised.
That's very generous
of you.
We do what we can.
So you don't know offhand,
really,
If you established a trust for this
particular boy... Cary MacDougal.
No, detective,
but like I said, I can check.
I will check for you.
I'd be happy to check.
I appreciate that.
But you feel certain
that you don't know his mother?
No, I do not know
his mother, no.
How do you think
your fingerprints
Ended up in her apartment,
then?
That's impossible.
You must be mistaken.
I've been working this case
for a long time.
We always had fingerprints,
and we never a match.
Last year, you had a d.U.I.,
and then we had a match.
When did this woman die?
1982, the year
you did or didn't
Establish a trust fund
for her son.
Well,
that's a long time ago.
There are still some people
who haven't forgotten her
And who care very much
about who killed her.
Yeah,
I'm not comfortable
Having this conversation
anymore, detective.
I still
feel like talking.
Well, then I'm gonna have to
speak to an attorney.
Yeah, hi.
It's B.C.
You're not gonna need
your lawyer today.
But keep him nearby.
I'll have some more questions.
I'll be in touch.
Thank you for your time.
Sorry to keep you waiting,
detective Miller,
But one of my nurses
is retiring,
And she wanted
a pizza party.
I offered to throw her
something more extravagant,
But she insisted on pizza,
so...Would you like a slice?
No, thanks.
So what's up?
Drink?
No, thank you.
Well...
We...
Would you mind
holding that?
Thanks.
We... did a liver biopsy
on you, right?
A colonoscopy. That's right. I'm sorry.
Sorry, it's Friday afternoon.
Okay, okay.
It's Friday afternoon.
I had a couple of those.
And my mind's already
on college football.
You a college-football fan? Yeah.
You in a pool?
No.
Wanna join mine?
No!
All right.
What are my test results?
I know. I know.
Believe me.
No one cares about it
more than me.
Okay.
Oh. All right.
What do we have here?
Thank you for coming.
How are you?
Around your neck, please.
Dogg, how are you?
Very good.
Here you go.
What's the significance
of the pictures?
Well, everyone's story is
on the bottom of their picture,
And I'm gonna pin it
to the clothes.
So they aren't just
nameless old garments,
But they're
living reminders
Of the people
who aren't here anymore.
I like it.
Oh, here! Try this.
They're really good.
I hear they're amazing.
Mmm. Mmm!
Oh, that's good.
Hate it.
Why? It reminds me of my aunt mildred.
It's a very fine line
that we walk here, you know.
What does that mean?
I've seen a lot of life,
you know?
And, over time,
you will come to understand
That there are just gonna be
days when our pace is off.
But don't worry, darling.
I will be patient with you.
Okay.
Toast?
To what?
Second chance.
I'm gonna go see
how Lily's doing.
Robert?
Don't fuck her over.
Be sure.
You know I'm not for these
inter-group relationships.
I'm against that 24/7.
And if you tell her
we had this conversation,
I'm gonna have to
kill you,
And I'm against that 24/7
even more.
* every single time I see you *
* my heart's on fire,
'cause you inspire *
Seems like
a huge success.
It's so surreal to me.
Are you missing someone?
No.
There's something
that I want to say
That...
I haven't said.
Oh, God, I feel like
I'm the bachelorette.
Do you think they throw
up and just cut it out?
You watch
"the bachelorette"?
Yeah, everybody does.
Lesbians, punks, chicks
in prison... everybody does.
If they say they don't,
they're lying.
As you were saying?
He's here.
Lily.
Dad.
How do you do?
I'm Robert.
I'm sorry.
Dad, this is...
Robert.
...Robert collingsworth,
my...
...My boyfriend.
Well...
You are a very unique man,
Mr. Robert collingsworth.
Tell me something about
my daughter that I don't know.
I'm curious because,
Well, my daughter's
never had a boyfriend before.
So something.
Anything.
Well...
She has your work ethic,
I imagine.
I love that I never know
what she's gonna say next.
And she's soft.
She's softer
than even she knows.
Very sensitive.
And despite all that,
She's got the greatest capacity
for forgiveness
Of anyone
that I've ever met.
I'm sorry, I didn't really
answer your question,
Did I, Mr. Champagne?
You knew all that
already, right?
Yes.
She's just like
her mother.
I am?
Mr. Champagne...
Maybe you can tell me something
that only you know
About your daughter.
I'm gonna take "conversations
more appropriately had
When Lily's not standing
right here" for 500, please.
Can I have everybody's
attention, please?
I would like
to make a toast
To Lily's story.
If it wasn't for Lily,
there would be no story.
Right? So...Lily?
Thank God.
Excuse me.
Hey. Congratulations.
This is great.
Hey.
I'm so glad you came.
I can't... I can't stay long.
I'm not really a party guy.
What are you talking about?
No.
Get some... get some champagne
and food, and we'll hang out.
Okay?
Congratulations.
- Are you wearing mascara?
- No, no.
No.
So...
Everyone that matters to me
is in this room.
I almost didn't get
to have this story.
But thanks to all of you...
My friends and my...
I'm sorry.
I can't breathe.
What?
I can't breathe! Oh, my God.
Oh, it must have been nuts.
She's allergic to nuts!
Call 911!
She's going into
anaphylactic shock.
Do you have an epipen?
My bag. It's...
it's in her bag!
Are you okay?
What's the matter?
Honey, what color is it?!
It's okay.
I can't find it!
Okay, I don't...
I don't have time for this.
I'm taking her to st. Luke's.
It's five minutes away.
Get my... get my b...
the back door! Back door!
Carla...
Tell Samantha
I love her, okay?
Tell her I love her.
Wait, Lily,
I didn't mean it like that.
I didn't mean it
like that!
I think she needs to be
by herself now, Robert.
Oh, really?
Do you, Miller?
Look, not now, okay?
Look,
she's gonna understand.
You didn't mean
what you said.
Right?
Well, that's a conversation for
me to have with my girlfriend.
That remains to be seen,
But I think you agree
that now is certainly
Not the time to have
that conversation, right?
Don't you have a down doggy
to do somewhere?
She's strong, Ralph.
I mean, look at what
she's been through.
If there's anyone
who can get through this...
It's good news.
She's gonna be fine.
Oh, God!
Oh, thank you.
Thank God.
She just needs to rest.
As long as I live,
I never want to
fucking see you again.
Wait.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Thank God.
So, I make these
really, really good
Vegan
chocolate-chocolate chip,
Peanut butter,
banana cookies.
"Super stupid."
Mother?
Hello!
Mother, not really
the best time.
I'm your mother.
It's never the best time.
I didn't think I could ever
let go of Samantha.
But now I think I can.
I adore Lily.
I wanted you to know.
Try not
to let this one die.
The Miller lives
in swanky town.
Who knew?
Yeah. Wasn't that swanky
when I bought it 20 years ago.
So, I melt down
baker's chocolate
And maple syrup
when I'm making
Chocolate-chocolate-chip
version,
And when I'm just making
regular chocolate-chip,
I do the same thing, but I
don't add the melted chocolate.
Would you like to save any
to bake or...?
Maybe, maybe not.
So, do you believe in God?
I believe...
Half the time,
I believe in something.
I don't know
exactly what it is.
I wasn't raised any religion
or anything.
But some kind
of spiritual thing,
'cause I just feel, magic,
You know,
too much of the time
Not to believe
in something.
But then other times,
I feel with complete certainty
That there's nothing
and that we just live and die,
And once we die,
it's just over.
And...
That scares the shit
out of me.
Yeah, me too.
I have cancer.
Why would you joke
about something like that now?
I'm not.
I'm sorry.
I realize it probably seems
selfish to bring it up
In light of what's happened
tonight,
But...
I just don't have
anyone to tell.
Where is it?
It's in my stomach.
I've been so lonely
my whole life.
And now it's eating up...
My insides.
I went into my bedroom,
When I was a little boy,
To get
my baseball glove,
And I found my mother
Hanging by her neck
in the closet.
Who would do that?
Who would
do that to her?
You're gonna be fine.
Do you still feel like...
You found your big love
when you died?
In heaven?
I thought I did,
but I don't know.
Where's your bathroom?
It's upstairs,
down the hall, on the left.
Don't get any ideas.
I'm married.
I'm sure your husband
would forgive
A heat-of-the-moment
mistake.
In this world?
This is what
forgiveness looks like
When you make a mistake.
Who made you sad?
I did.
We're all okay.
We're here.
Ice cream?
Whatcha doin'?
Nothing.
I got... I got lost.
You got lost?
I don't think
you got lost.
I think
you're a snooper.
I think you're
a snooper-snoopy-snoopalicious.
You know, I don't really...
I really don't feel
like cookies anymore.
I'm just gonna go.
You sure?
No!
Back the fuck up!
Nice hat, Lily.
I do like an irish plaid.
Step away from Miller
before you get blood on it.
Diego?
Put the gun down now!
Fuck you.
You bet. You lost.
I want my money.
Wait, you're alive?
How are you alive?
Magic of Miller. What's
going on? Am I dead?
Are we all just dead?!
Broken record,
this girl, right?
You're dead, I'm dead,
everybody's dead.
No, but I saw you
in the morgue.
Wasn't me, babe.
Ask your cop boyfriend.
Oh, you can't do that.
He's not a real cop.
Kidder!
Miller?
Be quiet!
Miller!
Shut the fuck up!
Fuck this! I'm leaving!
Don't fucking move! What
are you gonna do, shoot me?
Yes, I will fucking
shoot you!
Why would you do that?!
Because your fucking father
murdered my mother!
Lily?
Lily!
You're wearing his
hat already, huh?
That was fast.
Robert, you should go.
I wanted Carla
to tell my wife...
...My wife, who's dead...
That I still love her.
But I wanted it
to be a goodbye.
I love you.
I don't want to die anymore
to be with her.
I want to live
to be with you.
We would've never been right
for each other
Under
ordinary circumstances.
The only reason we even met
was because of this glitch...
This fucked-up thing
that we have in common.
But that's not a reason
to be together.
We should be smart enough
to know
Not to waste
any more time on this.
It's dead.
I don't love you.
Goodbye, Lily Champagne.
Wow. Rough crowd,
guttin' a man like that.
Remind me
not to get on your bad side.
I want to know
what the hell is going on.
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-
proudly presents
You know what, Lily?
I take it back.
Dumping him was
the right thing to do.
Suicide dummy,
you're a fucking idiot.
Don't call me "suicide
dummy" anymore!
No!
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-
sync:nophone
* when I walk, I touch the sky *
* I feel 10 feet tall,
and I know why *
* it's everywhere,
it's in your eyes *
* the secret that we can defy *
* gravity *
* la da da da da da *
* you helped me grow,
now you gotta let me go *
* 'cause I have learned
to fly on my own *
* and it's gonna be
pulling on my heart *