Et, where are you going?
To buy some drinks!
Buy some for us.
Okay!
Come back quick!
Steve!
Thanks!
Did your uncle suspect you?
It's all fixed. It should be no problem!
What? It's because of my food.
His uncle is so smart that I worry about it.
Worry? Just worry about yourself.
Shut the fuck up!
- What? - So what?
You wanna to be hit?
No!
Then Polish the car.
What?
Polish the car right now!
Oh, shit! The police is coming.
Cover the car, quick.
It's too late.
Hurry!
Take it as nothing has happened.
And we must tell the same story.
Bob, don't fuck up.
Shit! Calm down everbody!
- Sir! - Sir!
Racing tyres. Intercooler engine.
Double exhaust pipe.
You can't drive this car on the street. Whose is it?
- The engine and James' and mine. - Right!
The wheels belong to Bob and me.
Yeah! They're all good stuff.
I'm asking whose is it?
Sir! That's mine.
You bastard!
It's yours?
No. It's my friend's.
He'll drive it the competition in Macau.
So we fix it up for him.
So you have been Macau for a few days?
- Yes! - Have fun!
Yeah! We played firecracker.
I nearly burnt my hand.
The food are nice. We slept in oriental hotel.
- Steve! - Yes!
Come here!
How much did you pay for the hotel?
500 a night.
5007? I still lying?
Ben has just told me you went to pattaya.
I work in the traffic department.
Your lie is no use for me. Don't treat me as a fool.
You're really friends.
Each shares a part.
And force him to race.
We're good friends.
Yeah! Good friends.
Shame!
You guys fucked up in the race.
Everybody is talking about this.
I warn you. Don't drive this car.
Or I'll take it for inspection.
I got it.
I know, uncle!
Steve, come here!
What's the matter?
Next time to pattaya, I go with you.
I can help you in the race.
I know
don't sneak away for the race.
This is Hong Kong, not Thailand.
Bye!
Uncle said next time he'll help us in the race.
- What are you saying? - Is it true?
Let's go to uncle chu's shop.
Thanks! Bye!
Dad, our friends come to see you.
How are you, uncle?
Sit down, please!
So what's about trip to Thailand?
Great!
Order anything you like. I treat.
You are so nice. You pay evertime.
Don't bother. Because I'm your uncle ch...
Make yourself at home.
15.6 dollars.
Keep your eyes on the cash machine.
- Okay. Take care your friends. - Okay!
How can you talk to your dad like this?
None of your business.
- Fred! - Come on!
Boss pays for them.
Thanks!
The chicken soup is very nourishing.
- Take some more. - Thanks, uncle.
You always take care of him.
It should be me to thank you.
Don't bother.
My dad says the same line to everyone.
Stop speaking against me
when I talk to the others.
Dad, I'm not against you.
I'm helping you.
Helping me?
Please behave yourself.
Don't be so narrow-minded.
Don't be so serious. I'm just kidding.
I'm kidding too,
my little fool.
You really scare me. I won't do it next time.
Okay, forget it.
Let's have lunch together tomorrow.
Okay!
Let's go!
You come at the right time.
What's the matter?
I want to change all these pictures.
How is it?
Sit down and I'll tell you.
Here comes the business! Great!
Sit!
Miss... thanks!
Miss, may I use the telephone?
- Over there. - There?
What do you want ot drink?
- Coke! - Beer!
- What? - Go to dance.
Two beers, one coke.
- Thanks! - No!
Quick!
Be quick, you fatty.
The song so wild.
16, including these three.
- Finish them quick for me. - Okay, Richard!
Thank you!
Good! One more!
Good, Shirley!
Good!
- Thanks! - Hello!
You are...
Delia college.
You draws pictures outside the gate.
- Sorry! - Never mind!
I'm cherry!
I'm Steve!
I got to get changed. Bye!
Bye!
Steve, wanna sleep. Go to bed.
You drive better and better.
Good parking
really?
Kk, say hello to your mom for me.
Okay!
Me too.
Brother, look at this creep.
That's fashion.
Fatty, you got a problem?
None of your business.
So tough. Who's your boss?
I belong to lun's family.
Lun? I never heard of it.
Never?
I don't give a damn. Get out.
Get out!
- Painter! - What are you doing?
You're too thin. I won't talk to you.
What's about me?
You want to hit me. Come on.
You fucking, fatty. If you got guts, don't go!
I'll come back with my guys.
So what! I wait here.
What should we do now?
We wait here.
Mom, I'm back.
You're back.
- Brother! - Aunt!
- How're you, Steve? - I'm fine.
Aunt, this is for you.
Thank you!
Why so upset?
Let's have some tea.
When are you back?
How are you?
Mom, is brother sick?
Yes, almost a week.
Steve!
Thanks, aunt!
Please sit, mom!
Did he see the doctor?
Yes, we have spent a lot of money.
Take the money for the doctor.
I give you more soon.
The doctor said he got meningitis. Very dangerous.
He must go to hospital for observation.
Don't worry. I'll take care of money.
Aunt, here's some money. Maybe it can help you.
No, I can't use your money.
I'll talk to kk.
Take it.
- Steve... - Don't be silly.
You guys bring weapons. You'll be surely dead today.
- Let's move, guys. - Joe!
What a coincidence!
Does all your guys gonna kill my friend?
Are they your friends?
We're old friend.
Can you give me some face?
Okay. You fatty, get lost quick.
- What are you saying? - So what?
You wanna hit?
How's your brother?
He said he hasn't seen for a long while.
I'll visit him soon.
That's fine.
Bastard! Don't let me see you again.
You know their brother?
I was brought up here. Surely I know him.
But I didn't go with them.
Don't worry. I won't join the triad?
You better not.
I'm no fool.
Get in!
Not bad! Next time I want some scenery pictures.
Scenery?
Richard doesn't suit here.
Bob, afraid of getting drunk?
- Oh, full it. - If afraid, I will not play it.
Don't worry, rich. I design for you.
Just count on me.
I give you rest of the money.
Listening to music.
Thanks!
- Change those over there. - Okay!
Please come in.
Look. Bastard over there.
There's nothing in his eyes now
except the girl on stage.
What are you talking?
None of your business.
Give me back.
- Kk... - I give you.
Mick!
James!
- Yes. - Settle it for me.
Cherry, why don't you tell me you work here?
Come and join us.
Sorry, I don't have time.
Hi!
You got to dine with my boss.
- Let me go! - Go!
No.
James!
Give me some faces. Don't mess around here.
I pay for your bill.
We're old friends. I won't mess around.
Thanks, Richard!
Take a rest! I have someone for next session.
Boss, what the girl thinks she is?
Bill!
It's you. You scare me!
I'm sorry!
I think your outlook is very good.
Really?
So I've drawn a picture of you without asking you.
- Really? - It's for you.
Thanks!
You're welcome.
Bye!
Miss, is it a taxi?
Yes!
Steve, you're so smart.
Come on, chase after her.
Juist take courage & go for it. It'll be no problem.
Right? Am I right?
You say, yes or not?
Shut up!
Are you angry?
So pretty
just like a pekinese.
Chance is here. Why not take it?
We wait for your great romance.
Good idea!
Come on, do you think I'm bogrart or something?
I'm much smarter than they.
Just give me a break.
Sir, do you want to stop here?
Get out of here.
Get in.
- Move! - Let me go!
- Get in the car. - Let me go!
Move!
Get in the car.
Who the hell do you think you are?
What are you doing?
I like this kind of woman very much. Get in.
Get in'move!
Get in!
What are you doing?
Please stop.
Bastard! Go to hell!
Bastard!
Please stop...
Shit...
Steve, are you alright?
Go to hell!
Please stop...
Get lost!
Go!
Kill you bastard!
Come!
Don't let the bastards go!
Run?!
Stop!
Don't let them go!
Get in!
Don't runaway!
Hurry up!
Shit!
Get in. Quick!
Stop!
Kill you!
Get in. Don't fight again, kk!
- Bastards, don't runaway! - Quickly...
Stop it!
Stop it, I'll pluck the bastards out tomorrow.
- Okay, boss! - Okay, boss!
My underpants are all wet.
Go!
You want me to see you in, thanks!
- Good-nite! - Bye!
Can you be quicker?
Do you have time tomorrow?
Yes, I have.
Shrank back quick.
- Uncle! - You're back?!
Yes!
Let's try the dumpling.
All wet. No umbrella.
I never think that it'll rain.
Get changed quick.
Steve, let's try.
I'm coming.
Come on!
So you just have a fight?
No, I have a little accident
when I drive the way home.
Who are they?
I don't know.
Did you take their number down?
No.
It must be because of girls.
Give me a break.
It doesn't matter to have girlfriend.
But those nasty girls
will only get you in deep shit.
I know, uncle!
If you know, I don't have to worry.
Come on!
So that's why you bring this home.
This is the first time you buy something for me.
Uncle, by the way.
Why don't you get married?
Marry? Most of the girls we policemen meet
are those working in clubs or
those with background.
Can they be a good wife?
It has been years.
It's because of you. After your parents died,
I take care of you till now.
Girls only take you as my son.
Will they marry?
Day shift tomorrow.
You wash the dishes and go to bed.
I got it. Good-nite!
For testing.
Mom, I'm so scared.
Have I cheated you before?
The producer is auynt chow's son.
I've talked to him. Don't panic.
You better remember you lyrices well.
Cherry!
Do I scare you?
I think you won't come.
No way. I just went the wrong flat.
Are you alright? Just too nervous?
Be confident.
Okay, I trat you a meal
to celebrate the testing.
This is our first date. Won't you refeuse me?
Cherry ho, mui ng.
Mandy siu, come with me.
I go in with you.
Settle you stuff.
Without us, will Steve date the girl?
It's alright...
None of your business.
Mind you own business. Tidy up your stuff.
Bitch!
Et, Bob. Stop it.
I tell you to stop.
- What are you doing? - Finish them off.
- Please calm down. - Don't move!
Don't move!
Next time, mind your own business.
Or you'll be in deep shit, jerk!
Bastard!
Mom, I'm very scared.
Take it easy.
I know the producer. He will treat you well. Okay!
Don't go, mom. I'm so scared.
Are you ready? We gonna start.
Okay!
Mom!
If the passion becomes cool,
let me stay with you.
Thank you, miss. Wait for our letter. Next!
Sorry!
Ready.
Higher.
Sorry!
Paging company.
password.
Myself.
Kk is in trouble. Back quick.
Thanks!
Why do you come out so quick?
I just make a call.
Do I sing well?
Very good!
Cherry, I got to go. I can't dine with you.
Sorry!
Shit! They broke all the cars here.
How can we pack our client's back?
Fucking bastard!
Kk, where have you been?
We've been meaning here for hours.
What do we wait for?
Uncle'll be back. Just wait.
You wait. I won't listen to him.
Come on! What's done is done.
Let's find a way out.
They're fooling us around.
It's no way out.
Stop it. It's all my fault.
The guy has background.
We only have five people. How can we fight against them?
Okay, you want to quit?
You feel scared, right?
I won't need your help.
Kk, please calm down.
No way. I'm reckless. So what?
I run this garage hard. Now it all fucks up.
The garage isn't yours.
Surely you'll calm down.
What do you mean?
Forget it. I won't need your help.
I'm looking for the guy in triad.
He will settle it down.
Are you crazy?
If you count on them, you'll be in deep shit.
So what can I do? How can I pay my clients?
Kk, kk...
Fuck, they treat me as nothing!
I must pluck them out
and see who the fuck they are?
Don't worry. I'll take care of everything.
Don't worry.
Kk, you can count on me.
Thanks, nut!
You can do whatever to the bastards after I got them.
I just want them to compensate
okay. I'll take care of it.
Okay. I tell you our rules now.
You must pay us to help you.
Shut the fuck up, you motherfucker.
We are brothers. Never mention about money.
Remember, we are good brothers,
you can count on me.
Do I have I join the triad?
You fucking fatty,
my boss is taking care of you.
You're so lucky.
We'll be brothers and families.
Nobody will do anthing aginst you.
We must make ourselves clear.
Haven't I made myself clear.
Nut, I must make clear
my friends won't get involved.
If there's any trouble, I'll bear it.
Okay, we're brothers,
and your friends and you are brothers
we'll be brothers
and families soon.
Okay, lets pay my boss now.
Never mention about money
but after we've done our job!
It's okay. Keep in touch.
Paper tiger!
- What's the matter, boss? - Take the stuff away.
Be careful, boss!
Nut, they are up there.
Keep alert. Don't say a word. I'l fix it.
Paper tiger, give them the stuff.
Do it yourself.
Get it.
Get lost.
Don't move!
Move or get hit.
What's the matter?
Where's your boss?
See what happened?
You can talk to me.
Nut, it's him.
I'm nut. He's my brothers.
What do you count on against him?
Buddy, let's sit down and talk.
Okay. Wait a minute.
This is my boss, Mr. kam.
So you can make decision.
What should we do now?
Shut up!
No bullshit. You messed up his garage.
You should pay him back 300,000.
300,000? Are you kidding me?
Listen. I won't give a penny.
Bastard!
Don't move!
Wanna fight? Come on!
Bastard, where are you from?
Nam tin. Let's talk it over.
Nam tin? Do you know George kam?
Yes, he's my dad. Just give him some faces.
Go against kam's son. You wanna die.
You're young kam?
Do you want me pay you now?
No. No. I'm just pushed by them.
Only a misunderstanding.
We are friends,
so I must be on your side. Right?
If you don't want my dad knows that,
get lost now,
okay. I'm sorry. I'll get lost.
I'm sorry, young kam!
Nut, what's up?
You bastard. I've told you to join me earlier.
What can I count on to help you?
Let's go!
- Nut! - Jerks!
Nut!
You pay me or not?
Wanna die. Close the gate.
Run!
Go to hell!
Bastard!
Stop!
Stand still!
Fatty, run away!
Chase him!
Run!
Hurry up!
Stand still!
Run away?!
Go to hell!
Hurry up!
You wanna to go?
Stay there!
You go first!
Upstair!
Don't move!
Down!
Sir! My son is a good kid.
You can ask my neighour.
Quiet. One by one.
You two over there.
You get the wrong guy.
My son won't do this.
Kind of bad thing.
I'll check it out.
Be patient, okay?
What's your relationship?
I'm his father. I'm his mother.
Identity card, please!
Thanks!
Sorry, sir!
Did you arrest a guy called Steve cheung?
Who are you?
I'm his friend.
He's making his statement.
You wait there.
What the hell has happended?
Would you wait there?
Which group takes case of cheung's case?
Action 2
thanks!
Tell me what's wrong with him?
Don't you see I'm busy now?
I tell you to wait.
Tell me what has happened.
I've told you so many time.
I haven't seen you
tell me clearly. I'll help you.
Write it down correctly.
My lawyer is here. He can sue you anytime.
What's up?
The kids blackmailed his office with weapons.
Thanks!
These gangsters came to my office
and blackmailed me 300,000. I refused.
I'm a good citizen.
They messed my office up
and intended to kill me.
Then why it's them who get hurt but not you.
Of course. I wouldn't just stand there to be hit.
So I'm hit them back.
Stop it.
I must confess.
My client acted on self-defence.
Stop talking, sir. Just put them behind bars.
Fuck you. I haven't hit you.
Don't wrong me.
Shut up!
Are you here to argue?
Uncle, don't listen to their bullshit.
We're trapped by them.
Trap? Why didn't you call the police?
No use to say anthing now.
Tell the sir what'd happened.
The cop is his uncle.
That's why they have guts.
He can count on the triad and police.
Lawyer wong!
Mr. kam!
If they cover their guys,
how should I sue them?
I know, Mr. kam. I'll take care of it.
Shut up, you fucking bastard.
Let your lawyer talk to me. It'll do good to you.
What the hell do you think you are?
Mind your business. Get back to your work.
Don't have to be that fierce.
You don't have to talk that loud.
I haven't made you pay for messing my garage.
You are mad.
I'm destroyed your cars. What's the proof?
Come on!
What the hell is going on?
What's your name? Which area are you working?
Tom cheung. Hong Kong island.
What are you doing here in kowloon.
Not any work in your area?
Sorry, sir!
What's case?
The boy Steve cheung is my nephew.
He and his friends are clean, sir!
They are good citizens, not triad members.
Hem and haw? What do you want to say?
They're only acting on impulse.
Do you know they've got weapons?
Sir, I hope you check it out.
If I won't, then what?
No sir, sorry sir!
Sir, would you do them a favour?
What? A favor?
You've been a policeman for year.
Haven't you forgotten our rules?
To cover a suspected relative is against the law.
I can sue you.
Yes sir! Sorry sir!
I know that's my fault.
It's okay if you know.
Thank you, sir!
Okay, I won't sue you.
Yes sir!
Get back to your own area.
Dismiss!
Thank you, sir!
They gonna sue you
for blackmailing and criminal damage.
If they succeed, you can't have any help.
Uncle, you've seen everything.
They stirred up the trouble, not us.
Why didn't you call the police?
Is it any use to call the police?
If the police arrests them,
how can I make them to play?
So you ask help from the triad?
I just want them to pay.
Pay? Nut asked for 300,000.
You're used by him, jerk!
It's my fault.
Is there anything you can help me?
How can I help you?
The evidences are there. How can I explain to others?
All messed up. I can't tell my father.
It's not because of the girl, nothing will happen.
I've told you don't go with that kind of girls.
You take my words as nothing.
Uncle, there's nothing to do with cherry.
Nothing!
Then how come the triad get involved?
What can I say?
You won't believe whatever I say.
Speak against me?
You don't want to help me. Forget it.
What?
My captain scolded me of leaving my post.
I'm nearly accused of against the law.
If I hadn't taken care of you, you would be shit now.
Think about it.
Shit! I must end up in jall.
Come in!
Morning sir!
It's you, master.
- How are you? - Long time no see, sit please!
You must come here for something.
I want you do me a favor.
Come on. You've helped me before.
If anything I can do, just tell me.
My nephew have trouble with the triad.
His garage is ruined
- and he's now accused. - Really?
He's now out on bail.
Don't worry. I'll try my best.
Just tell me what you want me to help you.
One shouldn't knee down to facts
then one can live meaningfully.
What wrong have I done?
Steve, please stop it.
What can I do? My uncle is nearly fired.
Kk's garage is ruined. We are out on bail.
What are these for?
It's because of me. I'm sorry!
I'm sorry. It's not your fault.
I just lost my temper.
Steve, promise me never go against those people again.
Unless they leave me alone.
How will you listen to me?
I beg you. That's for me. Okay?
Believe me, don't worry.
This song...
I want to tell you
I've signed with the record company.
Really? Congratulate, cherry.
Not yet. The company just signed with me.
You'll be great. You sing so well.
Have enough?
May 1?
Sorry! Go!
To bar the way!
Excuse me. We're police. Inspection.
Stand over there.
Identity card, please. Stand over there.
You two, there.
Do you know bill lau?
No.
Drift along?
Where do you live?
Kwoloon city!
All?
Do you know bill lau?
No.
Don't fool me.
I really don't know them.
You drift along here. You must know him.
I relly don't know him.
Identity card.
Prosecution? What for? No identity card. Just get me.
What a guy! Stand there!
What the fuck! I'll sue you.
Stand properly. Don't push me.
Identity card, please!
Why are you so fierce?
- Just hit me, you fucking cop! - Don't be so wild!
Let me.
I'm captain wang of anti-crime bureau.
Do you know bill lau?
No.
- What about young kam? - No.
What's about James?
No.
Identity card.
Next time when I ask you, must be cooperate.
Stay there.
Captain wang, should we chase him?
No. Just let him tell his guys. Inspection finishes.
Yes, sir!
Crazy! Are you doing stunt?
Bill, the cop is looking for us. But I runaway.
What the hell are you talking?
Don't let others I'm your friend.
Get away from the police.
Don't you know I fear that?
Fear? What can the police do without evidences?
Okay. Wait for me.
What a shame!
- Surround the area. - Yes, sir!
Bill, many cops outside!
Leave them alone. We spread.
Hurry, let's go!
Police. Stand there for inspection.
Stand aside.
Tell them stand there.
Take care.
Captain wang, everybody there.
Hurry up!
Listen! I don't want to waste your time.
Does anyone know young kam, James or bill lau?
My name isn't kam.
Why are you so nervous? What's your name?
I'm John la...
Don't you believe?
I show you my identity card.
Okay!
Listen everybody.
We're looking for these people. Please help the police.
If anyone sees them,
please tell the police.
- Captain! - Yes, sir!
Let's go!
Yes, sir!
Thank you!
Everybody can carry on. Go!
What a police!
- You go back to headquarter first. - Yes, sir!
Thanks!
- You're welcome. - Bye!
Boss, telephone.
Hello?
- Mr. kam! - Yes, I'm!
The cop is looking for your son.
Do you know what's up?
No. But it isn't simple.
Okay, I got it.
This way, please!
Captain wang!
Order a bowl of shark's fin for captain, quick!
Please sit, captain wang!
This is the captain wang I always mention.
This is boxer.
Mr. kam, I'm not to meet your friend.
I'm cooperating with you.
Okay, I would like to listen to your advice.
This is my captain.
I take this chance to show my respect.
Captain wang, please try it.
No, thanks. I'm on duty.
Then let's try the dishes.
We've just had our meal
in a fast-food shop.
Captain wang, you're so busy.
Not even a proper meal. Too hard for you.
Captain wang...
I got something to you, sit!
Mr. kam, I can hear clearly wherever you sit.
Captain, we should take down whatever Mr. kam says.
Yes, sir!
Captain wang, we want to
know what's wrong with our young kam?
We suspect him of blackmail & serious assualt.
My kid won't do this kind of things.
Surely he won't do it. We suspect that he delivered the order.
No way.
He always can't make decisions.
Whatever you say.
If we've evidences, we'll catch him.
My kid is nasty, but not as nasty as that.
Nasty or not. He's your son.
I'm just doing my job.
Excuse me, everybody.
Captain wang!
What do you want?
Bastard!
Young kam, I even say didn't go back nearly.
Kam, come here.
What's up, dad?
Aren't you out?
You bastard.
I tell you suckers to take care of him.
You let him stir up the trouble.
- No, Mr. kam... - Shut up. Get loss.
Yes.
Tell me, haven't you stirred up the trouble?
Yeah. I got nothing to do.
Bastard, don't you know
the cop is looking for you?
I know. They've guys, so do we.
Bastard, do you know you're in deep shit.
Dad, just hit me hard.
When you finish. I'll go finishing them.
You bastard. I beat you to death.
You got lost.
How dare you speak against me?
Go to the states to see you mom.
Get out of my sight.
Ded, when I get there, I find you some powerful guns
and send them to you.
Stop it. Do you have enough?
Okay, forget it.
Be a good man when you arrive there.
Or I'll kill you.
Don't worry, dad.
Bill, please check is there any good university.
I want to study a degree or ph.D.
Is it okay, dad? You must like it.
Ph.d? What ph. D?
Take care, dad.
Remember, study hard.
I got it.
Don't go against your mom.
Go!
Don't you welcome me?
No, come in!
Take yourself!
Wait!
The place is a mess.
Come to see me?
No way. Come to see your uncle.
He hasn't come back from work.
You have something?
You try this.
Great! Try together.
Beautiful.
Stop praising yourself.
You're too much.
Sorry. I open the door.
Call the police.
Don't go bastard!
Call the police?
Help!
Don't shout!
What do you want?
Cherry!
Don't come over!
Shout!
Cherry!
Boss, cops!
Shit. You've luck.
Cherry!
Help!
Help! Cherry!
The bastards are going Wilder and Wilder.
I don't know what will come next.
I've told you don't go for others.
You didn't listen.
You tell me what should we do now?
It doesn't matter against me.
Don't go against my dad.
Why can those bastard remain at large?
Isn't there any justice in this world?
There'll be a way out.
Hope they'll stop after this.
Stop being naive. They will stop?
I've sworn
if they come against us again,
I'll kill them.
Steve!
How do you feel?
I'm alright. You?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
No. My fault. I can't take care of you.
How many?
Look for friends.
Please!
Coke!
- Sir! - Thanks!
You say where to go, I never mind.
Boss, the cop!
Sir, nothing to do with me.
Nothing? Haven't I asked you?
- Sir! - Stop doing this.
Just calm down.
What's wrong?
I want to talk to you. Come on!
- Okay. Talk to me here. - Go in!
Do you know?
No. My fault. I can't take care of you.
Get lost!
Sorry, would you come out?
Hong Kong is ruled by law.
Your must act on evidences.
Wanna hit me?
It's for the justice.
Stop being wild.
I can make you out of job.
Good!
I must teach you a lession today.
What's up?
Out!
You sucker, you know what you've done.
Do you really have to do this?
If there's any wrong with the kids,
it's all your responsibility.
Isn't there any justice?
Fuck. You talk to me about justice?
That's not you should talk.
If I can't get those who burnt my house,
you'll be in shit.
Boss, prosecute him.
Prosecute? Too easy to him.
See who'll be in shit!
What are you doing?
Uncle!
Is that all?
Take it or leave it.
Just a small failure and give up?
What's about cherry?
She's alright.
Give this to kk to open a new garage.
Give me back when you have. Okay?
And I don't think the thing is settled.
Young kam won't let is go.
Tell me if you've any trouble.
I got it.
Clean up the stuff.
Uncle!
What?
Do I only cause troubles?
Why do you say this?
You can't get married because of me.
So silly.
Last time I was only joking.
I would have dumped you
if you're a trouble maker.
Marriage?
Isn't it nice wihtout a woman troubling me?
I really mean that. But do treat cherry good.
She's a good girl.
I'll uncle.
You're a man now.
To your left a bit.
Is it right?
- To you right. - Is it right?
Hold it, don't move.
Come on, higher.
- That's right? - Yes.
Do you know which side is left and right?
Don't say like a shit.
Is it right?
I'm so tried.
Okay!
Tired? I've told you to stop.
- It doesn't matter. - Is it okay?
Steve? I'm so tired. I gonna faint.
Come hug me, Steve!
Quickly.
Then you will be check it.
Uncle!
So you're here?
Where are you up to?
Almost ready to open.
Not bad.
Much better than the last one.
Uncle, thanks for your money.
Come on. Remember to pay me back when you make profit.
Sure.
Remember, work hard.
If those bastard go against you again,
call the police at once.
Don't fight with them.
I got it. We're not stupid.
Work hard. I got to go.
Uncle, we've a meal tonight. Come join us.
Night shift tonight. I can't come.
Have a good time, bye!
- Bye! - Uncle, bye!
Have fun.
Follow him.
Steve!
Steve, what are you going?
What's wrong?
It's time to dine? What's wrong?
Uncle!
Uncle... what's happened?
Please don't die.
Uncle...
Help...
- Excuse me! - Uncle!
Steve!
Steve...
Steve, what are you going?
Tell me what are you going?
Steve!
Steve, what are you going?
- Do you like it? - I like.
Go away!
Boss...
- Bye! - Run!
Drive!
I want him dead.
Come here.
Crash him.
Come on, crash him.
Quick!
Bastard!
Get down, quick!
Go to hell!
Don't let the bastard go.
Bastard!
Young kam!
Come on!
Bob, are you alright?
Bob, don't scare me!
Steve!
Steve, no!
Put it down.
No...
Steve!
You bastard.
Let me handle it. Go there!
- Come here, over there. - Yes, sir!
Get up!
Stevel...
No.
Enough!
Stop it.
Steve!
Be careful.
- Bob! - Help him up.
Quickly.
- Help him get in the car. - Yes, sir!
Get in the ambulance.