Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Bohus ! Are you there ?
Get up. You lazy-bones !
That goat'll strangle herself one day !
You've knocked it over again !
Let me unwind you. Go over there !
Go over there !
Those are Bohus's pancakes !
Go on. Take one then !
They'll be all muddy !
Chick, chick ! If it weren't for me.
You'd have nothing !
Chick, chick !
Bohus, Bohus !
Why don't you answer me ?
- Stop fussing.
I've got pancakes for you.
The pig's got out again.
He's getting his exercise.
D'you know 2.750 pubs
were opened this month ?
That means more rascals. - Oh, come on !
What's that doing in here ?
Come on. Out you go !
I'm looking for an older woman,
I'm 70. A widower, businessman.
That's something for you.
- I've finished with all that.
But you should marry
and stop all that whoring.
Finished ?
You've never been a whore.
You just laze about.
You don't work on the house.
The roof's got holes in it
and you just lie there.
If you at least did something
to help -
Feed the hens or the rabbits...
You just lie about idle and do nothing.
That pig's a real swine !
- Bohus. Are you at home ?
What d'you want ?
You didn't show up.
- What was it like ?
We waited for you until four
in the morning.
Vlasta didn't come either.
The pub's shut.
So what ?
She'll open up now. eh ?
- Where was she, then ?
And who with ? - Eh. Bohus ? !
- Leave it out !
Stop shouting !
Bohus !
Are you here ?
Stop hiding. I know where you are !
D'you want that gas or not ?
What for ?
- Hergot ! !
We fought for it under communism
and now no-one wants it !
I'll withdraw the application !
I'll do without since you've
done nothing about it.
I'm cancelling the application !
You think you'll get a girl here
without gas !
I'm cancelling the application !
I'm opening up in a minute !
Stop that. You idiot !
We did it yesterday,
and the day before !
I'll be five minutes !
- More like seven.
God knows what they'll think !
- You're sitting on some bacon.
I'll do it - I'll cut myself !
You're too high. - Stand on your toes.
Open up ! What's she doing in there ?
Just can't do without it, can you ?
I'm glad I'm not your wife !
- I'm single.
If I were as young as I'm single,
I'd be a teenager.
We're queuing in the rain like
Russians buying bread !
Christ, I've got washing hanging
outside !
It's not raining, idiot !
It's bit damp, though !
Forget your knickers and get serving !
Put the telly on.
Have a fucking rest !
There were 2 metres here
yesterday - where's the other one ?
Who d'you mean ?
Have you seen another one here ?
Have some brandy.
You'll have to get out
of the habit of doing that.
You mean, you'll have to.
I'd like to see you or Bohus.
...with three kids
coming to see you !
You'd be in the Party too.
They're all trying to be clever now.
I am and always will be a Communist !
I joined the Party
and I had no children.
I'd rather see them peg out
than join the Party.
You can talk, you haven't got any.
As a Communist it bugs me
that you left the Party. - Cut it out !
Just be glad it's behind us now.
Is it fuck !
Good morning. - Gutten Tag !
Good morning.
Two years after the Revolution
and Krauts everywhere !
Lovely fresh air...
...peace and quiet.
Birds twittering sweetly,
What an arsehole.
Christ !
Don't try hide from me !
There's no-one here, only a pisshead !
Just wait till I get home !
You drunken oaf !
The good thing about marriage is
you can have a fuck
even when you don't want to !
Look at our sexy number !
She's really something !
She knows a thing or two !
I could do with a drink.
And I'm starving and I've got
no-one to sleep with !
Lend me thirty, or twenty.
Why should I lend you money ?
Young lads and they haven't got
any money.
Shut up and play.
- The game's not going your way.
Look at clever young Vanek.
He sells those lotteries.
I've won nothing all year.
- I'm not surprised. - Here you are.
Give us three beers. Hello !
Four beers and four vodkas.
You're drunk,
you haven't got any money. Go home.
Give us some. For fuck's sake !
Where'd get money from ?
We've co from work !
Don't be such a cow
and give us four beers.
Give them the beers on me.
- They're not getting anything.
Go home !
Wake up. She'll give you some.
You'll give him some, eh ?
- Keep your insults to yourself !
Who d'you think I am ?
I'm declaring a protest sleep.
Today's youth can't manage anything.
Good afternoon.
I'm looking for Mr. Stejskal.
Is he here ?
They've come for you !
Are you Bohumil Stejskal ?
Good afternoon.
Could you step outside for a moment ?
Me ?
Why ?
Be on the alert, lads.
What has he done ?
Where are they taking him ?
Must be the secret police.
- You should know. - Leave it out.
Rubbish. They've been disbanded.
The police have now issued
information concerning
the crimes committed by a teenage gang.
He's gone off his head,
the poor bugger !
Damages amounted to 375.000 crowns...
Yeah, me ! Me ! Me !
Sergeant, have any further
arrests been made ?
How is the investigation progressing ?
We have discovered more details
about the crime.
It's quite clear...
I'm rich ! Stop the car !
I'm rich !
To your health ! Cheers !
Cheers !
I don't have to answer
to anyone anymore !
What are you going on about ?
I'll pay you back.
I've got money, haven't I ?
Have a drink.
- I can't, they'd lock me up.
What d'you mean, you can't ?
I'll pay for everything.
I've got money.
I'll pay you out of prison.
I'll bring him over.
Come on, come with me.
He won't believe me otherwise.
Give me some money !
I'd love to help you out
but there's no point now.
Am I rich or am I not ?
Of course, but it has
to be sorted out legally.
More formalities !
I'll pay you back.
I'm getting it all back.
Come to Vlasta's tonight.
And they won't take it from me again ?
No. In all probability.
I don't think so.
You don't think so ?
I don't believe it !
I mean, definitely not.
Only if the system changes.
You mean the Commies will be back ?
I'm easy... You're easy, eh ?
We're easy.
How much does it come to ?
How much ! ? How much ! ?
It depends.
D'you mean the market value
or the book value ?
All this is making my arse sweat.
Market fluctuations affect the value.
Just give me some idea.
You're either lucking stupid
or you won't tell me.
It's upward of six figures.
More than six figures ?
Then I'm a millionaire !
I'm a millionaire !
Stop the car, I'm a millionaire !
I've got to get out of the car !
God, I knew you were up there somewhere.
Don't pretend you aren't.
Teacher !
I'm rich !
They gave it all back to me ! Kids.
I'm a millionaire -
I can buy you what you want.
Say hello, children. - Good afternoon.
Hello, kids. Let's go.
Let's go, doc !
We're here.
That's mine, too ?
- Only up to that fence.
We can buy it, can't we ?
It's nice...
And a church.
That's not part of it.
- I know. I'm not stupid.
How many bricks are made here ?
I'll look it up for you.
These haven't been in the kiln yet.
What're you standing around here
for smoking ?
You have to get a move on.
Who d'you think you are,
the President's brother ?
Don't talk to me like that,
you old fart !
Who are you calling a fart ? !
- You shit.
You're fired !
Get me the manager !
Why didn't you ram him one ? !
Manager !
What's going on ?
- I want the manager.
I am the manager.
You've got some real rabble
working here.
I'm Dr. Ulrich. - Good day, comrade...
May I present the new owner
of this brickworks.
Mr. Bohumil Stejskal.
Glad to meet you.
I've been working here 25 years.
And look at the mess everywhere !
Bricks lying around -
25 years and it looks like this !
The chimney's the only thing
smoking around here !
Come on, boys. - Don't pander to them.
Get to work, gentlemen !
- These are our bricks ! - Of course.
I've got a brickworks ! Fantastic !
The value of bricks has gone up.
I'll expand.
See that big house over there ?
That big one ? - Yes, it's yours.
I don't believe it !
And that block over there.
With all those shops ?
That ? ! - Yes !
And that food shop ?
- Of course, let's go.
Good afternoon.
Give me a bottle of plum brandy.
You going to give it to me ?
Get into the queue.
She won't give it to me !
I'll take it myself, then. - Wait !
There we are !
- That'll be 56 crowns.
What do you mean ?
You pay for that brandy !
You can't drink that !
It's not paid for !
Sir, tell him not to drink that !
Why should I ?
I'm sorry about this.
- Don't pay anything in my shop !
Why are you giving her money ?
In my shop ? !
It hasn't been legally settled yet.
So, she doesn't know yet !
Will she be surprised !
Tell her it's mine.
Excuse me.
Mr. Bohumil Stejskal here is
the new owner of the shop.
You're getting pay from me
for the last time.
What d'you do with what you don't sell ?
It goes bad otherwise, eh ? - No.
You throw that salami out ?
No. It gets sold off.
Only buy what you sell.
You're a good-Iooking bird.
You couldn't work here
if you did stupid things.
Wait, wait, stop ! Stop ! - What now ?
It's Kaja, my old mate !
Hello, Kaja !
I know you ! You don't know me ?
I don't remember you, sorry.
Let's go and get smashed.
I'm in a real hurry. I am sorry !
I've got a taxi.
I'm sorry, but... - Take a photo...
Let's go for that drink.
Have a nice time. I have to go.
Come on. Kaja. This is all mine !
Off we go.
I'll find you... in Prague.
Or on television.
- We haven't got time.
We can go by taxi.
He didn't stop to chat.
They're all watching.
Bit of an idiot, eh ?
- Of course, he is.
Could've had a drink. - Get in, please.
- Where's that brandy ?
It's shame. - We don't need him.
Let's go.
He could've come with us.
That's mine, too ? - Of course !
Part of this block and this hotel.
Let's go for an inspection. - What ? !
Let's go for an inspection.
- I'll just get my papers.
Wait, wait !
Good afternoon.
Don't say anything.
Don't say it's mine.
We've been here 5 minutes and no service !
I'm sorry, gentlemen, but...
- What's up ? - We're reserved.
I'm sorry, but you'll have to go
somewhere else.
Got some problems ?
Let's go and sort it out.
What'll it be ?
Two soda waters. - And what else ?
What else ? Nothing else. Two soda waters.
Can you remove your cigarette ?
What d'you mean ?
You might like to remove your cigarette !
I don't believe it !
This table-cloth needs changing.
Waiter... - Quiet !
You're here already ? !
You can sit here, madam.
The gentlemen are just leaving.
Repete !
I'm sorry ? - We want some more !
I think I'll have an ice-cream sundae.
No ! Just two sodas.
Two soda waters.
- Only with a coffee order.
Two coffees, then.
You'll spoil it !
Let the idiot get on with it !
Who are you calling an idiot ?
I'd like two sugars.
Is that yours ?
What would you like ? - A whisky.
Where are you from ?
Prague, and this is my cousin
from Africa.
A Praguer ! That's the capital.
It must be really smokey there
everyone's black !
No offence, boys.
We ordered something and they didn't.
I ordered coffee so I could get a soda
and I get nothing !
They got their drinks
so who's the idiot ?
Who d'you think you are ? !
This is a five-star hotel !
Mr. Five-Star should behave better.
People trying to flag you down,
people want to pay and take no notice.
The table-cloths are dirty...
It's a real mess here !
You waddle from one table to the next.
You let in blacks and not gipsies.
You know how much money gipsies have ?
I'm not racist, don't get me wrong.
You think you're so clever !
You think I'm some kind of idiot ?
Tell him who I am !
Unfortunately,
this is the new owner, the heir.
Unfortunately for him, you mean.
I don't give a damn, you're an oaf !
I won't be ordered about by anyone !
You try rushing around all day !
Let the owner try it !
You think I've never worked ?
I doubt it from the way you behave.
You just don't knowthe terrain.
I can leave anytime.
Off you run, then.
I don't need people like you !
It's the new age !
The guest throws the waiter out !
I'm leaving !
It's new age !
Off he goes.
- You shouldn't have done that.
Why ?
I'm rich, aren't I ?
Look at him pacing out the land.
Have a drink.
Tell him all this...
Strong stuff, eh ?
Tell him all this is mine !
That I'm a millionaire.
If they need any apples
or pears in Africa.
We'll send them over.
Why is he laughing ?
I am Bohumil Stejskal.
What's this... Ahoso vidaho... ?
The son of the Highest.
There's only one...
The king's son !
I just thought...don't worry.
But you've no phone. - No. He hasn't.
We can fax stuff instead.
Your land starts at the stream
and finishes at the woods.
Over there you've got 20m...
- Stop telling me what I own !
I've got quite enough already.
Have a drink. - No thank you.
Have a drink,
or I'll use someone else's services.
To the son of the highest !
Sit down.
Have a drink.
Lie down.
We're living in a democracy !
It's fucking hot !
Hey. Slav !
Do you want some help ?
- No. Off you go.
Are you all right ?
I might be sick over you !
Off you go !
I'll go with you !
Go on ! - Bye !
Get going !
My dear lord !
You're still in your shoes !
Dirty, horrid...
You don't know what happened.
I'm a millionaire.
You stupid millionaire,
your goat's strangled herself ! - What ?
She's hanged herself ! - What ?
I can't be here all the time.
Your goat !
I told you not to tie her to that tree.
How did it happen ?
She fell and got caught on the rope.
Lizinka, what have you done to me ?
I've got all this money.
My little goat.
I had all these plans for you !
A new goat-shed.
What's the point of money now ?
You won't come back to life.
You're sorry now but you can't help her.
You won't come back,
not even for a million !
You shouldn't have done that to me !
I won't pray for ten days.
Don't blaspheme,
you're always in the pub.
So your farm's going into ruin.
I'm inviting you all. - Bohus !
It's a funeral wake.
- What's happened ?
In memory of my goat.
She hanged herself, the swine.
To goats !
Don't eat that !
I'm inviting you.
Don't give them that shit.
Get changed.
In front of the pub in an hour.
I'll pay for these beers.
- No, I'm paying !
Liduna won't let me go.
She'll have to.
Jackets, ties, we're going into town.
Don't drink that pig swill.
Me, too ? - Of course.
Forget the cards, we're off to town.
But I'm winning ! - So what ?
I'm inviting you all.
I've just been to a cremation.
I don't need to change.
OK, stay as you are. Let's go.
Just finish my rum. - Leave that.
What about me ?
Sorry, no girls allowed.
Come right back home. - No, I won't.
You not coming, Josef ?
He's giving you money.
- It'll all be paid for.
Arnost, come with us.
Where to ? - To celebrate !
You thick, or something ?
Great nose, great spirit.
He didn't mean it like that, come on.
The double decker is here !
Isn't that fucking fantastic ?
OK. On you get.
If you get on that bus,
don't come back again !
You promised to chop the wood.
Just be good, here's a thousand.
Bohus !
I said, no girls !
For the journey.
They'll be fighting over me next !
There's old Kostal.
Stop the bus.
Come and have dinner with us.
I stopped having dinner since
the invasion of Kuwait.
Get him in. - What are you doing ?
- Let's go.
I have to feed my rabbits.
You'll make me sterile !
You're making it dirty,
you know how much this costs ?
So what...
These guys have a really hard life.
They need some fun, put the TV on.
Faster, here we go...
Look, boys, go at 120km/h.
...eighty...
...ninety, hundred...
...a hundred and twenty !
Ninety...
I said 120, do what I tell you !
Hello ! - Hello.
I'm Bohus.
We agreed no girls !
Let me introduce you to my wife.
Dr. Ulrich.
Doctor ?
Are you a lawyer as well ?
No, a plastic surgeon.
What ? - A plastic surgeon.
Say, someone wants to make
their nose smaller.
Sorry.
You can't be a man
without a proper nose.
Arnost's got a problem with his nose.
They laugh at his, it's so small.
I don't get any ?
To the memory of my little goat.
To a little goats !
What shit is this ?
It's fucking sweet !
I've drunk all my money away...
Please be quiet.
- That's what we're doing.
You can't shout in a restaurant
like this.
It's alright.
What sort of pub is this
if you can't have a sing-song ?
It's not even in Czech !
I'd recommend the ham roll,
then the turtle soup.
I'm not downing turtle !
Then the Chateaubriand.
I've have that, too.
But medium rare.
I want goulash and dumplings.
I'll have the medium rare, too.
Bring me a beer before I snuff it.
What about your venison ?
We'll have goulash and beer.
Goulash and beer for me.
Beer and rum.
But these are specialities !
Just bring the food and don't ask.
They're dick-heads.
Don't act like peasants !
Could I have caviar ? - Of course.
What an arse-hole - caviar !
Sit down, Arnost !
Look at these portions !
Sparrow food.
I'm going for a slash.
Get a load of that !
She's something else !
Bohus will buy her for you, eh ?
Stop shouting.
What would you like to drink ?
- Beer.
You're always downing beer.
What about the best wine they've got ?
I'd like to try that blue burgundy.
I've never tried blue wine.
Some of that blue stuff.
Come here, come here !
What does that girl like drinking ?
Scotch.
Send a bottle over there.
Certainly.
Have some, it's good stuff.
Christ !
Have some - it'll clean out your system !
Perhaps it'll really clean you out !
Cheers !
To your health, my beauty !
- To your health ! - Cheers !
What a looker !
You have to drink it all
or we're not going home.
Must be an actress.
Or a whore.
Or both.
Don't insult her !
Don't be a clever dick !
- Who's being clever ?
He thinks money can make him president !
Don't fuck with me or you'll be sorry,
you old fart !
Try me, you capitalist !
Who are you calling a capitalist,
you shit !
I could pretend to be clever
if I had money, too.
Leave him alone !
Fuck this town !
Let's go home, come on !
You're not leaving me here !
My leg...
It'll be OK.
You'll pay for the damage.
- We'll settle up, of course.
Are they gone ?
Have they really gone ?
Bastards !
We'll pay up, you pay them,
You're the only normal person
around here.
You know what ?
I'll pay for you to have a nose-job.
Really !
You'll do it for him,
no matter how much it costs.
Do you believe me ? - What ?
I don't care how much.
Doctor, are you a doctor ?
Yes.
D'you believe in God ?
Me ? No.
I don't understand
how anyone can believe.
Why not ?
There's no proof,
no-one's ever seen Him.
I've never seen your cunt
but I believe you've got one.
Try a bit higher.
OK.
Look at them go !
How fast can it go ?
That left one could be our mayor.
Who did you vote for ?
What a woman !
OK !
They're only Czech programs or what ?
You're in the way !
More to the left.
That's too much.
What shall we have ?
Plum brandy, eh ?
To your health.
D'you believe in God ?
I do.
And I don't.
How can you work together ?
It's not possible.
It's a sin not to believe.
Want some rabbit ?
The devils are multiplying.
I can't kill them all
and no-one wants to eat them.
You can forget about meat.
It's money now !
You get hold of my neck
like that rabbit's.
We've an appointment with Dr. Siroky.
Phone for you !
I've got a phone call !
I'll go on up. - Yes, off you go.
Yes, this is me.
Who's calling ?
No, it's not raining.
You're trying what out ?
He's trying it out to see if it works !
I've got a meeting so piss off !
I can't have this !
Whose name shall I say ?
Bohumil Stejskal.
Mr. Stejskal's here...
You can go in.
Do I have to knock ? - No. You don't.
Good afternoon.
May I introduce you...
Mr. Stejskal, Dr. Siroky.
Pleased to meet you.
She doesn't smile much,
but she's pretty.
Take a seat.
Christ, yeah.
What can I offer you ?
Coffee, vodka, whisky.
- I'll have a coffee.
I'll have plum brandy.
That's the only thing I haven't got.
I carry a hip-flask, just in case.
Two coffees and a glass.
Three glasses, you have to try it,
it's last year's.
Three glasses, then.
Just the bottom of the glass !
Bottoms up, you mean !
Isn't it lovely stuff ?
It's good...strong...
We've been negotiating
with a Japanese firm.
Where can I have a slash ?
A piss...pee.
In the corridor, third door on the left.
Christ, what the hell sort of person
is that ? !
Clever to have bogs in the corridor.
Come on, quickly.
Where was I ? - At the Ministry.
The Japanese are interested...
Sit down !
The Japanese are interested
in your brickworks.
What interest ?
- They want to buy it.
And the 7 hectares of land with it.
Eight.
I've got seven down here.
And I've got eight there.
- It doesn't matter.
A minor detail,
a hectare here, a hectare there.
Why would they spend money
on a brick-works ?
I can sell my brick to them.
How did the yellow buggers
find out about it anyway ?
That's not important.
It's not the bricks Japanese want.
Hang on a second.
What about the men there ?
- What men ?
The men working there.
That's not our worry.
Yeah, but it's mine.
It's my brickworks and my people.
I'm just coming !
Think about it,
there are huge sums at stake !
Tell the Japs that I'm not selling
and they'll be lucky
to get any fucking bricks !
Let's go, Doc.
Slanty-eyed fuckers !
Good...
Come on, Mr. Kostal.
I don't think this is for me.
Really, I can't.
You can be my sex bodyguard.
What if I catch something ?
The ladies are waiting.
- Come on, off you go.
You can have a bark inside.
Good evening.
That one's smiling at you.
She could be my granddaughter.
If you'd like to choose
what you'd like.
"Indian Pipe".
That's something for Kostal.
I've hadn't smoked since
the Russians invaded.
It's a special oral erotic experience.
What d'you mean, oral ?
Don't stick your little tongue
out at me.
She a pretty little thing.
How much does she cost ?
- Champagne for the gentlemen.
This is a massage salon,
you can't buy the girls.
You choose what you would like
and the girl
whom you'd like to perform it.
If she's not reserved already.
It stinks like a brothel in here !
I'd recommend Journey round the World.
I can't, I'm driving.
He hasn't got a licence.
How much does it cost ?
And how many times ?
To your health, gentlemen.
It's an hour's massage
with bath and everything.
I don't need a bath.
I had one on Saturday.
You'll be bathed by one of our girls.
The champagne is on the house.
Rubbish, don't you know
how rich I am ?
Look !
Good evening !
D'you remember me ?
I sent that bottle over. - So what ?
Nothing, it's OK.
Wish me luck,
I'm going for Amadeus's Dream !
Come in.
If you'd like to take your clothes off.
I'll just go and get ready.
What's your name ? - Irena.
That's me done. - Already ?
I'll bathe you first.
Don't worry, come on.
- I'm not worried.
Come on, don't worry.
Look at all those bubbles !
Take your clothes off !
And your underpants !
My watch is Water-tight.
This is so nice !
You don't remember
how I fought the boys over you ?
They were arguing
whether you were an actress...
This is lovely !
Are you really a masseuse ?
This is bloody nice !
Don't you remember me ?
This is so nice ! - Up you get.
I don't want to.
You don't remember me ?
- Of course, I do.
I fought over you.
I'm Bohumil - Bohus.
Out you come, careful you don't slip.
I don't want that !
He has to wear his little hat !
I don't want a little hat.
What is this ?
You'll like it.
I don't want it, I'll pay extra.
It'll cost you 500 crowns.
That doesn't matter.
No little hat !
You can't do that !
This isn't Journey round the World.
It's Journey to the Universe !
Vlasta !
That was fantastic !
Did you like that ?
Another 500 crowns, then.
"The Journey" costs 1700 !
You pay that at the cash desk.
I'll take the the 500.
But don't tell anyone.
They'd throw me out.
- What d'you mean ?
A clever girl like you sweating
for a few hundred.
Such a shame !
You can live with me.
You can't keep being thrown out
by people.
I'm completely whacked.
I paid 7800 for you.
I just had Journey round the World.
You're a real stud -
you must have been twice.
Three times ! Three times
plus Pipe of Peace.
I feel like a new man !
Can you drive ? - Just watch me !
You've given me something
I'll never forget !
I've fallen in love.
That Irena's so pretty,
it's a miracle !
I have to have her home.
Why ? You've got enough money.
You could come here whenever you want.
The greatest thing is freedom,
and you can't buy that.
I want her only for myself.
It's stopped coming out !
It's not coming through ?
The water's not coming through !
What d'you mean ?
It's not working !
I don't believe it !
- It won't work, I tell you !
We haven't had any water for a week
- low pressure.
There's no pressure !
I keep telling you.
There's a drought, like last year.
This is the end !
She's coming in an hour !
You're doing it on purpose.
I've got an idea,
for five hundred. - Five hundred ? !
- Will you give it to me or not ?
Come on, guys !
What the hell are you doing ?
It's like water cannons
on Wenceslas Square !
Sorry, they're beginners.
What are you doing ? !
What is this ?
Cakes bobbing about like musk-rats !
Aim it in the water !
It's a bit yellow.
There's no suckling-pig,
just rabbit again !
Looks pretty yellow to me.
Like piss-water.
- I'm not swimming in that.
Who's asking you to ?
This is the limit !
What d'you expect for 500 crowns ?
The tank's been rusty
since the Revolution.
If it catches fire,
you're in the shits.
What d'you mean, you are - we are !
Don't throw it in there.
Quiet !
Take that into the house.
This is Irenka.
It's her birthday
and she'll be living with me.
What in heaven's name
have you brought home ?
If your Mum could see this...
God in heaven !
Don't take any notice of auntie.
She's not my aunt,
just a friend of Mum's.
Go and help Mr. Kostal,
for Christ's sake !
I'll buy you some earrings,
come with me.
You bastard ! - Don't be so stupid !
Let's go, Irena.
What do you do ?
- Stop kidding about.
Irena's an actress.
I did lots of parts as an amateur.
You haven't eaten much.
She's on a diet.
I'm not on a diet, why should I be ?
I eat everything - but no rabbits.
You should've said.
We'd have made you something else.
- There's nothing else.
Be glad it's gone.
Don't do that, idiot !
This is my friend,
he went to college.
This is Irena, sit down.
I had her brought here to live with me.
What did she say ? - Nothing.
She's got to...
Down there.
Past the chickens.
That's it.
What's the difference
between a woman and a man ?
A man has to decide
on a no.1or a no. 2.
A woman sits down and sees what happens.
Here she is, quiet.
I had a birthday present
brought here for her.
Don't let it out yet.
Go round the other side of the stable.
It's here.
Have you finished ?
No, she hasn't yet.
Tell me when you've finished.
When she opens the toilet,
I'll give the sign,
Kostal will signal to the band.
The band starts up
and you let it out.
Have you finished, Irenka ?
This isn't a funeral, we're celebrating !
Get ready...
An ostrich ? !
It's for your birthday !
What do I want with an ostrich ?
You've never seen a bird like this !
What would I do with an ostrich ? !
Don't be afraid of him.
Come and stroke him.
Look at that neck and those legs !
In South Africa they use them
to protect property.
Why do you need a guard ?
I've got a video,
television.
And Irena.
What does it eat ?
- It won't eat you !
Lovely and warm !
Come into the water !
I don't think I will.
You're fired if you don't !
Are you mad ? !
Don't you dare, in that new jacket !
- Don't worry !
This is fantastic !
I'm so happy !
Good, eh ?
Yes, it's nice.
I'll take three of them.
- Pardon ?
Three of these suits.
You can't buy three identical suits !
Why not ? I like them !
Are you sure ?
It's not such a good idea.
Think I haven't got the money for them ?
What about a leather jacket...
...and jeans ?
They'd squash my balls.
I need something loose.
I love wearing my track-suit at home,
don't I ?
He loves wearing his track-suit.
What about a tie ?
No shit colours.
I want lots of colours.
Not in public.
You're a pretty girl.
You could earn a lot more.
How much do they give you ?
Will you take the suit ?
- Three of them.
Come and work for me.
You'll make some money,
I've got a hotel, restaurace.
If you knew about all I had.
You'll be inviting her home next !
Let her come -
I've got a pool, ostrich...
The ostrich's mine !
Who bought it for you ?
I'm not your property.
You're not going to talk to me
like that !
How dare you talk like that !
She's complaining
and she doesn't even cook !
Auntie has to do it all,
poor little thing.
Who made your breakfast ?
- It was inedible !
Where would you be without me ?
Supposed to be a masseuse,
she's a whore.
I live with her - fuck her !
It'll be all right.
- Has she really gone ?
I'm fucking fond of her !
I really love her !
It's all right, let's pay for this...
We've finished.
You think I'm some whore ?
You whistle and I come running ?
I'm not having any.
- Vlasta !
You're the only one.
- You're not getting any !
Don't be silly.
No chance, forget it.
- Forget it ?
Only if we live together.
But we are together.
I'm not being a slave for anyone.
I'll move in and that'll be that.
You stink ! God knows
what you've been doing !
She's the one doing things !
What do you want ?
I want gas.
I withdrew the application !
I want it.
I'll pay for the whole village
to have it.
Vlasta needs it.
- She lives with you ?
Are you living with him ? - Yes.
She's living with you ?
- The gas is what's important.
Pull me in, let's have some brandy.
Careful... I don't want to get wet.
Give me your hand.
Now my bum's wet. Christ !
Stop all that drinking !
You've got a horse as well ?
That's no horse, she's a treasure.
We going to get that gas ?
It'll cost half a million !
It's not a matter of money.
Yes, it is and stop drinking !
I'm glad I've got you !
You were always stupid !
You could've had it for free
but you didn't want it.
She's back, the one who was here.
Irenka's come back to me !
You're not coming here !
Go back home -
what are you doing here ?
Tell her something !
This is Vlasta.
Have we got a servant ?
- How dare you !
They told me what you were.
You're a whore !
How dare you, you village cow !
Who are you calling a cow ? !
- Hands off me !
You keep your hands of Bohus !
Cut it out, girls !
Irena ! Vlasta !
Stop that !
She scratches like the devil !
Scratch her eyes out and drown her !
The rich bugger won't do anything
for the village !
We swim in this filth
and he gets a swimming pool !
I bought you all gas !
What would you like, children ?
I want to stroke your horse.
Better not, he bites.
He's an Arab bugger !
I want a merry-go-round !
- Great idea . I'll get one !
Gutten Tag !
I fucking said "Gutten Tag"  !
- Where's your cowboy hat !
I don't need one, I've got glasses.
How's it going ?
- The work goes on.
We won't get anything for free.
If you knew what a slog it is
having so much money.
You wouldn't envy me.
That spring is pure water.
We could bottle it.
We'd sell fucking gallons !
3 or 4 crowns a bottle.
A machine to do it can't cost
that much.
I'm buying a merry-go-round.
Have some fags instead.
Everyone wants to borrow money.
Dig the well by hand !
I pour water - I sell water.
- So you're not in ?
I'd buy the machine
and you'd work on it.
You'd still be in the shits.
Some bottles might go missing...
They give money to maternity hospitals.
You read about murders, rape...
Where does it start ?
In the maternity ward.
I'm not giving my money
to some perverts.
Where the hell is my horse ?
She's Arabian. - What's her name ?
Hathavitlah.
You've got to be polite to her.
- Come back !
Don't breathe alcohol fumes
all over her !
Hathavitlah ! Wait !
Stop that !
I want to read my paper !
You're always asleep !
- We want to go to the theatre.
You promised.
- The promises he makes !
You've got your satellite, ostrich...
...video, gas.
The gas isn't working.
And you've got the pool.
I'm bored !
Let's go.
The water heater doesn't work.
What shall we do ?
Let's go shopping.
What now ? - We want money.
I haven't got any -
I bought the kids that ride.
Well, 5000 at least !
- I haven't even got 1000 !
I'll get my lawyer to bring some more.
Take off that stupid beret !
I need it against the sun !
Give me my beret !
You think we're your servants ?
Let's go.
What are you then ?
You don't cook...
I'll fucking kick you out !
- He's angry with us !
He's frowning at us !
What are you doing ? Stop it !
Where are you dragging me ?
Just putting you to bed !
- I don't want to !
You do, really !
I don't want to go to bed !
Let me go !
But it's filthy in there !
We'll wash you first !
I don't want to go to bed !
We're all going to Africa
to see their women !
No girls allowed on this trip !
Get me a bottle !
Catch !
Where could I find Mr. Stejskal ?
Where could he find Mr. Stejskal,
girls ? !
They're down by the lake.
He bought them a merry-go-round !
What did he buy them ? ! - A merry-
go-round ! - What are you saying ? !
It's true ! - That cretin !
Take the Doc's car.
- How dare you !
I'll settle up.
No, you won't, you pauper !
You're poor !
I'm finished !
It certainly is !
Where the fuck's my beret ?
You haven't got a brass farthing.
This is terrible !
Why didn't you tell me ?
What ?
- Your father's a step-father !
My Dad wasn't my Dad ?
But I'm my Dad all over !
All that money ! - Then my Mum...
Who was my Dad ? - Who gives a damn ?
What'll I tell my wife ?
Who gives a toss ?
You'd better watch your manners
with me.
You owe me 1.453.000.
Without that fairground ride. Sign here.
I feel sick,
I haven't even got a pencil.
You rascal !
Just you wait !
Why ?
Why... ?
I'm asking why ?
I'm asking you why ?
Can you tell me why ?
Don't do this to me !
Come back home !
Don't be silly !
Get lost !
Don't be stupid !
I love you even if I haven't got
any money !
You smoke ?
Just the odd one.
"Start" brand.
You drink ?
Occasionally I have a glass.
To clean out the system.
Have some, I made it myself.
Do you speak the truth ?
Well, the boys helped me.
We help each other.
Have some.
You've got wings instead.
You can't use a glass.
Can you drink anyway ?
Are you afraid of me ?
I'm just a bit surprised.
I've always believed but
sometimes I've had my doubts.
A person's surprised when he
suddenly sees the truth.
He sees that the truth exists.
Look, I've got wet knees.
Let me pour you some...
I forgot, you can't.
To your health.
I'm surprised,
I think I'll get plastered. Sorry.
I've just lost everything.
- I know, Bohumil.
They took away my horse.
I know, Bohumil.
They all call me Bohus.
No-one's called me Bohumil in years.
Dad called me Bohumil.
He'd say: Bohumil, you're going
to get such a hiding !"
He loved me. - I know.
What's person to believe ?
I always thought my Dad was my Dad.
I know. - What do you know ?
Irenka's gone,
Vlasta won't talk to me.
They all want money,
they're all laughing at me.
No-one believes anyone.
Can't you do something,
for fuck's sake ?
Bohumil !
You shouldn't say "fuck"  !
Your plum brandy smells wonderful !
Pig ! - Listen to her !
Me, too. - I'll have you, gorgeous !
How's it going, Onassis ?
Stupid idiot !
Give me another.
Good day to you !
It's Arnost !
I'd completely forgotten about you !
Where'd you get that nose from ?
Bohus paid for my cosmetic surgery !
Thank you very much.
Come and sit down.
- He looks like a man now !
Here's the hospital bill -
9.600 crowns.
Thank you so much for my nose.
You haven't heard.
We're fucked !
I haven't a bean !
- What do you mean ? !
I'm as poor as I was, a complete beggar !
No pool, no ostrich, satellite gone.
No-one gives a shit.
You're my only friend.
You'll just have to start saving.
From what ? I've got a disabled pension.
Just fuck it, they're not going
to cut it off.
The bastards took
the marry-go-round as well.
I didn't give the doc anything.
I never signed anything.
I'm not stupid.
What can they take away from you ?
Maybe your old banger.
My old banger ? !
How much did it cost ?
- 9.650 crowns.
You just add another fifty
and you've got it.
No, I'll have money left over.
Now you've got 9600.
- So, I'll have 50 left.
You'll make money on it !
Always someone going on about money.
You're not going to believe this...
...but an angel appeared
in front of me.
What angel ?
Onassis needs an angel now.
What are you laughing at ?
He just came out of the water
and talked like I'm talking to you now.
As they say:
I'm an atheist, thank God.
That's him.
I'm looking for Bohumil Stejskal.
I'm Dr. Guardian.
Your father died in Argentina
and left you his fortune.
Roughly 10 million dollars.
Now I can buy you all !
english subtitles: Karolina Vocadlo
edited by: czerny
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player