The worst thing that we could do right
now is to ease up too soon,
allow a second peak of the virus to
hit the NHS and hit
the British people.
Good evening.
"There is light at the end of the
tunnel."
The words of the Foreign Secretary
Dominic Raab,
deputising for the Prime Minister, as
he announced the expected further
three week lockdown, at least.
There was encouraging news from the
press conference that
transmission of the virus has been
reduced to less than one to one,
due to adherence to social distancing
and self-isolating.
But there was no information about
what that light at the end
of the tunnel might look like - no
detail of what an exit
strategy might entail.
The Government says it does not want
the public
to receive "mixed messages."
Raab acknowledged that several other
countries have shared their exit
strategy with the public, but he said
it would be
irresponsible at this stage here in
the UK.
Later we'll look closely at the exit
strategy in Germany,
and the reasons for it.
And we'll hear from the former Foreign
Secretary David Miliband
on how the world may be reshaped
post-Covid.
But first our Policy Editor Lewis
Goodall examines the Government's
strategy over the lockdown, and their
refusal to discuss options
for the way out of it.
Day 24 of lockdown giving way to day
25. We have done 45 days of lockdown
before it is over. It is remarkable
that it no longer seems remarkable.
Britain will remain in confinement
until 7th May. Based on this advice,
which we carefully considered, the
Government has decided the current
measures must remain in place for at
least the next three weeks. Dominic
Raab announced five tests which must
be met until any relaxation. The
Government is looking for:
But there was encouraging news too,
the Government scientists think the
average infection rate is now below
one. R value is important, it is the
number of people an infected person
comes to infect. If R value falls
below one, they're infecting less than
one other. If it is more than
one it goes up. Other places like
Germany and Norway have focussed on
R value. It was when it dipped below 1
that Governments started to talk
about relaxation of lock down. Not
here, because we are not testing
enough. They can use proxy indicators
to try and understand
where we are currently and what the
reproduction number is and looking
at fatality numbers and look at their
sites to understand how it
affects particular communities and how
they're doing. I don't see how
they can say it decisively until they
have the antibodies in the
community. That first mistake of not
getting ahead of testing returns to
haunt us. But the other reason Britain
isn't showing more leg on
exit strategy is political. The Prime
Minister is recovering and for
as much as we may here about
collective responsibility it seems
unlikely that ministers will be able
to pull on the big levers until he
is back. These weeks about allow time
for the virus to recede and
time for the Prime Minister to get
better. The questions of when and
how will continue to grow louder. What
is going on in the economy.
Something over which Tory backbenchers
are mindful. The real
question is we need to ensure that
bounce back happens straight after
coronavirus, because if it is a blip
for three months in the figures,
then that is one thing and that is
something that we obviously can look
at and it will be difficult and add to
the national debt, but that is
something that is manageable. I think
the entire, the real issue
here and which is lie the lockdown is
important and we get it right and
don't end up with that second spike,
so that is why it is important we
get it right now is that if we can get
that, we can probably keep on
with the broader agenda that the
Government is pursuing. The economic
catastrophe is real. Data showed 5. 2
million Americans have applied for
unemployment. One in six of the
American labour force are out of
work. In Britain we have seen 1. 4
million apply for universal credit.
The whole goal of the programme is to
not just keep people in work, but
keep companies solvent. If they are
still solvent and the degree of the
lifting of measures allows companies
to get towards normality, we can
hope that all these people who are
furloughed will more or less keep
their jobs. But that is a huge
question mark and we have seen the
numbers, wre know a lot of companies
that were relying on the scheme are
not going to exist when the lockdown
finishes. 45 days to save the NHS
and save lives, but at the cost of
house arrest for the population and
life support for the economy. It will
be VE Day before this is
lifted, but victory won't come with a
parade, just people quietly almost
certainly in fear trying to resume
their lives.
Any decision about an exit strategy
will ultimately
be all about the data, and add to that
modelling,
but without widespread testing both
are lacking.
Our Health correspondent Deborah Cohen
reports on another
source of information that could
provide some fresh insight.
There are various different data sets
in England that can give us an
indication about what's going on with
the virus.
One of them is from the Royal College
of GPs.
It has over 500 specialist practices
that
monitor what is happening with all
different kinds of respiratory
illnesses all year around.
Public Health England is relying on it
for
information in this pandemic.
When one has signs and symptoms of a
respiratory illness, the health
workers at those centres will swab
them, if there is a test available.
At the moment, there are 26,000 people
attending these practices
being monitored for Covid-19.
However it is worth remembering some
people may not go to see their GP -
either going to NHS 11, or to
hospital.
The green line shows people going to
GPs with Covid-19.
Currently, the data is showing for the
past few weeks, there are 5
people per 10,000 with Covid-19.
In the past two weeks, it seems to
have plateaued.
The red and yellow lines also tell an
interesting story.
They're people going with any
respiratory infections to their GPs
and they show a dramatic drop on 16th
March.
The early hand washing effect and the
encouragement of
social distancing has had a dramatic
effect to drop all acute respiratory
infections, up and lower those like
pneumonia,
which are the most worst that we are
worried about.
And, prior to 24th March, about half
of all the reductions in
infections occurred because of those
measures.
Another data set is the one the
Government releases on
deaths occurring in hospital, which
you can see in this chart.
Now, there are more numbers to come
for
the shaded area, so these could
change.
Professor Heneghan suggests that the
peak happened on 8th April.
The hospital death data is becoming
much clearer now that the peak of
deaths in hospitals in England
occurred on 8th April.
And that date's now moved outside the
uncertainty zone and it's flatlined
since that point, right up to now.
So we can be much clearer that we have
hit the peak of deaths on 8th
April and then you can track that from
that date,
you go back at least two if not three
weeks and
assume that is the point at which the
infection peaked.
Now, we have spoken to Public Health
England
and they say they don't recognise
there being
a peak at that time.
Data are now being released about the
results of tests for the
coronavirus in front line workers.
During the outbreak in Italy, around 1
in 10
health workers accounted for
infections in all those
who were tested.
It looks like to me in the data about
a third of all the
infections are now potentially in
health care workers.
That figure has trended up and up and
I suspect, as we
test more nursing home workers, more
of the people working in settings
like community hospitals potentially,
but particularly in
hospitals, it is worrying that
actually a high proportion of those
are infected and they have the
potential to keep the infection
ongoing, if you like.
One of the European countries which
has embarked
on its exit strategy and has shared
its "workings"
with its population in Germany, and
the way that Angela Merkel has
handled the coronavirus and delivered
the exit strategy has
sent her approval ratings and her
authority, in the doldrums
for months, sky high in the opinion
polls.
Gabriel Gatehouse is here to tell us
why is Germany so different from us.
Why is that happen something By the
figures, Germany just looks so much
better, under 4,000 deaths they have
recorded as opposed to 13,000. That
is in a country with a larger
population and more reported
infections. There were numerous
possible reasons, one might be the
structure of the health care system
and scientists believe the initial
infection was in a relatively young
and fit population. But that
wouldn't account for this huge
difference in the death rate, the
case fatality rate, the percentage of
people who die. 13% in the UK. 3%
in swraermy. -- Germany. N't One
reason is testing. The Germans have
done a huge amount and they have a
picture of the number who contract
the virus, maybe without symptoms, who
go on to die. Scientist there
are urging caution and are saying the
death rate may go up and Angela
Merkel when she announced the partial
lifting of lockdown was
cautious. She said partially
re-opening of school, but still
banned gatherings of more than two
people and pubs and bars closed. She
spoke about that R number that Lewis
talked about and the Government
talked about. They think it is about
at 1 in Germany now, which mean it
is number of infections shouldn't
rise. But look at the level of
detail that Angela Merkel goes into
her. Here she is yesterday.
The key phrase was at the end, we have
an infection figure that we can
monitor and track. It goes back to
testing. Germany has a better
picture of what is going on and they
can be more confident in lifting
some restrictions, knowing if they see
the rate go up again they can
act in good time. The The UK and
Germany set off in the same dreshgs.
Pub -- Direction. Yes they worked
together on one of the first tests
and the UK and Germany were doing what
is called community testing and
contact tracing and then quarantining
them and people that
they have been in touch with. Germany
did more of that than we
did. But we were also doing it. Until
there was a policy change.
12th March when the Prime Minister
announced we were moving from the
containment phase, IE stopping the
spread to the policy of delay,
delaying the peak to try and take the
pressure off the NHS. This is
when the Prime Minister, the headline
figure he was asking people
with a mild fever to stay at home for
seven days. But potentially the
more significant change of policy was
articulated by Chris Whitty who
said on the 12th March that community
testing and contact
tracing would stop.
It is no longer needed for us to
identify every case
and we will move from having testing
mainly done in homes and outpatients
and walk-in centres to a situation
where people who are remaining
at home do not need testing and we
will pivot all of the testing
capacity to identifying people in
hospitals who have got symptoms.
So, the Germans also pivoted from
containment to delay but they never
stopped community testing and contact
tracing. I spoke to one of
the most senior virologist in Germany
this evening and they said
it was never stopped because they knew
it would be one of their main
tools, not just to contain the spread
but also to give a clear
picture of what is going on thereby
allowing you some way to make
decisions about how you get out of the
lockdown. Chris Whitty
specifically said we will pivot our
testing capacity to the hospital.
That was on the 12th of March. We are
still only today at 80,000. It
was presented then as a policy change,
but it almost certainly had
as much to do with capacity as policy.
We have basically gone back
to a policy of community testing, it
is implicit in the 100,000 figure,
but I still think that the actual
reality is lagging behind. Thank you
very much indeed, Gabriel.
Martin McKee is Professor of European
Public Health
at the London School of Hygiene and
Tropical Medicine.
And I'm also joined by Justin Madders,
Labour's Shadow Health Minister and
Steve Brine, who was
Conservative Health Minister between
2017 and 2019.
Good evening all. I would like to
start with Martin McKay. Do you
think that we are getting fixated on
the idea that we are making a false
choice, health versus wealth and what
we are doing is we have stopped
the economy in its tracks and we will
do it until we get the virus
shifted? Absolutely. We have to
remember one simple fact, people who
are dead do not contribute to the
economy, they do not go to the shops
or restaurants and unless we control
this epidemic, frankly, we will do
much more damage to the economy in the
long run. We have good evidence
from the 19 -- 1918 flu epidemic from
the USA when city closed down
and opened up at different stages that
there was a close down earlier
and stayed close for longer recovered
much more rapidly when the
pandemic the past. It is not a false
choice. How long do you think
restrictions can continue before real
damage is done to long-term
health because of things like the lack
of work, depression and so
forth, don't you have two operate an
economic model that looks to the
future, while you're dealing with with
the virus? Absolutely. We have
done a lot of research on the impact
on primarily the global crisis after
2008 but also other periods going back
to the Great Depression and
there are serious health consequences,
particularly when
people face a precarious existence,
Preparatory of employment, income
and housing. You talk about a disease
of despair. Exactly. Those
of the diseases which have been
rising, the debts from those causes
in the United Kingdom and the United
didn't state a greater extent from
other industrialised countries over
the last ten years. We also know
that there is a lot you can do to
mitigate the effects of the economic
problems. Take suicides, they are very
good marker of things going
wrong. We were able to show that
during successive financial crisis
and recession is in Europe, that in a
number of countries, southern
European countries primarily, when job
losses went up, suicides went up
as expected and when the economy
recovered, they came down. But in
the Scandinavian countries, there was
no connection at all. Those
countries could face major economic
problems and mitigate many of the
effects and we know a lot more about
what needs to be done for that to
happen. Active Labour market
programmes, helping people back into
work, fundamentally sending out a
message that the government cares
about you. You have been helping to
inform the government 's exit
strategy, do you think there is plan?
I haven't been helping the
UK,. The World Health Organisation. I
am also on the European
Commission. The European Commission
has published an outline of what
exit plans would look like and that
came out in the last day or two and
that sets out the stages that we need
to go through and it is very
clear that we need to be driven by the
epidemiology. The reproduction
number that you are talking about,
that is absolutely fundamental. We
need to get that below one and keeper
below one. That means that as
we open up and loosen the
restrictions, we need to think of
how we do that in a way that keeps it
below one. That may mean that we
do other things, like maintaining
social distancing. I think we will
see much more attention to wearing
masks in public, as is happening in
the Czech Republic, Austria, and
elsewhere another things that could
be done, you open up a little bit and
then you evaluate, monitor and
check the impact and you move very
quickly. That comes back to the
point you're making earlier, we need
far better data than we have in the
United Kingdom at present. We simply
don't have the information we need.
Thank you. Let me turn to the MPs,
Justin, first of all, you think it
would help people to understand and
help people 's sense of their own
future, the government detailed its
exit strategy, not to activate right
now, but to say what is likely to
happen in the near future? Yes, I do
think that would help, because all
along we have been saying that the
government needs to be very open and
transparent about what they are
doing and why. I think at this stage,
if we are being told, this
will carry on three weeks, three
months, whatever, without any real
sense of where it is going to end up
on what it will look like, people
will begin to lose a little bit of
confidence and they need that open
dialogue with government to really
keep going with the current
restrictions and have faith that it
will actually turn in the end. Let
me put this to you, Steve, perhaps the
reason, because people are
thinking now on what we are talking
about tonight is the fact of the
data, there is not enough data there,
that actually there has not
been enough data for the government
actually to work out a plan? OK, let
us look at some data, 861 people lost
their lives in the reporting
period that you are reporting today on
the BBC. If that was a train
crash or an accident that happened in
one day alone, that would be an
enormous story. You don't get to a
game where it is one apiece and you
settle for the draw, you go for the
win. To relax now would be dangerous
and would be an quick... I'm not
actually talking about relaxing now,
what I am talking about is having a
plan, a plan that you would then
share with people to show confidence
in the public. There is a plan, a
very clear plan that the government
are working to a you heard Dominic
Raab today talk about the five test
and I thought that was incredibly
sensible, they are the yardsticks by
which they will measure where we can
move to the next stage. That was
criteria, not a plan. It was not
sane as angler Merkel has said how she
is going about it. I understand
this obsession the BBC have with
Germany. Germany is not the same as
the United Kingdom, they are at
different countries with different
systems and I suspect there are two
answers to the planned question of
that Keir Starmer who has to try and
stay in the story somehow. I suspect
there is an elegant answer which is
that they will be led by the science
and that three weeks is a long way
away right now and I suspect there
is an inelegant answer which is not
that there is a filiform plan as to
how do you move out of this and
anyway, we have been criticised we
have not being clear enough, there is
not enough clarity of message, I
think the message is absolutely
crystal clear. Stay-at-home and
therefore protect the NHS and
therefore save lives and if you
ask... There is no point in us
standing on the two -- backward step
and banging saucepans and then taking
a fit of the pedal, if you
listen to anyone working in the NHS or
has lost someone or had a fight
for their own life on this, what did
they say? They say please,
stay-at-home and follow the advice. We
have got to take this one step at
a time. I realise it is boring and
difficult. I don't think it is
boring. I think it is interesting. You
have to stick with the plan,
Kirsty. Let us look at what Labour
might be suggesting for example, let
us talk about Sadiq Khan, Justin, in
London, what he is saying to Grant
Shapps, the Transport Minister, is we
would like to see all public
transport have masks for every one
travelling. Do think that is
something that Labour as a policy be
supporting? Well, I think again, to
repeat what people have said in the
past, this is something that needs
to be guided by the science and I
think there is certainly now a
growing body of evidence that masks
may be part of the solution to this.
Certainly London transport, which of
course is notoriously overcrowded,
is somewhere where a lot of people
will probably feel that that is
something I would want to do,
regardless of what the official
advice was. I think it should be
looked at closely. I think the big
thing for strategy in the current
situation is actually the testing
that is going on, as your piece
already said before, we have not
really gone anywhere near the numbers
that we were originally
promised and I think that if we are to
review the lockdown, we need a
proper tracing strategy which means we
will have to have mass testing as
well and I think until we get to that
point, we are going to be
struggling a little bit to move into
another area without the risk of a
rebound. You agree with the government
on that, we are in a
situation where we don't have the
amount of testing that we need and
we are meant to have very quickly, so
you would be with the government
on that strategy, but you can't
actually move ahead until you get
mass testing in place. There is no
doubt that the government criteria,
which as you rightly point out, it is
a criteria to decide the next
phase and identify the shortcomings
today which include the lack of
testing capacity and also the
infallibility of PPE. We need to
understand what has gone wrong with
the testing ratio because as you
pointed out earlier, it was back in
January that the government
announced that they had got this world
leading test and clearly
Germany have managed to get into a
situation where they have been able
to mass-produce that we haven't and we
need to understand what the
problem is with that because that will
be key in getting through to
the next phase. If I could move on,
finally, with you, Steve, really
referring back to what Martin was
saying, do you think there will be a
tipping point at which time the
economic damage from the lockdown,
including two people because my
personal health, well-being and
future is outweighs the damage from
the virus itself? No, I don't agree
that it is a choice between the
economy and public health, I think
this is a whole national effort. To
give you an example, we heard today
about new ventilators which are being
developed, the McLaren Formula
1 team are involved, if we do that,
then business returns to doing
business as usual and we need them to
carry on with the national
effort. There are plenty of companies
that make ten but they are
making alcohol hand gel and that is
really important. I think there is a
way out of this, but it is ultimately
not just going to be
about testing in the community, people
wearing a dirty or clean
wristband, it is ultimately the only
real way out of the pandemic is when
you have a axing and what will have to
happen is have a sensible,
evidence-based, led by the science,
and social distancing is going to be
with us for a long time and I think we
are going to have to get used to
that, until there is a vaccine in
place, and that is the reality of
this. There is no textbook as to how
to get yourself out of a restriction
from a pandemic, it will have to be
based on the evidence, as the virus
develops, and three weeks is a long
way off right now, but I am
absolutely certain the government made
the right decision today. They
made it based on the science and I
think that the messaging is crystal
clear from the government and I
realise that it's frustrating for
people, it is frustrating for me and I
realise it is frustrating for the
media but it is working and it is the
right thing to do. Thank you
very much indeed.
No one can yet know the social,
economic and political consequences
of the coronavirus disease, and talk
of a return to normal
once this is all over seems almost
implausible.
So what will define the world
post-Covid 19?
Earlier, I spoke to David Miliband,
the former
British Foreign Secretary, now the
Chief Executive Officer of
the International Rescue Committee for
his perspectives
on what happens next.
I think there is no doubt that the
scars of this crisis will last a
long time. But the vital thing is
whether or not we learn the lessons
of this crisis. The lesson is about
the holes in the global safety net,
the massive inequalities, three
billion people have no access to
running water and within countries
like the UK, the poorest are being
hit hardest. It is also about
nationalism against
internationalism. And I think there is
a vital question about the role
of government. It is a new economic
and social contract if we learn the
lessons properly. That is the only way
to address the social and
economic ills as well as the health
ones. We were talking about the
social/economic contract, do you think
that will change now? I hope
it will change and the undervaluation
of all sorts of
sectors of society that are recognised
to be central, the key
workers are in the health service and
they're carer, but if you're
stacking shelves, you're part of a
vital role and we know that
especially the last ten years in the
UK, but globally over a longer time,
the growth of inequality has scarred
those countries. When you have
someone like Boris Johnson in that
heart felt video when he left the
hospital, talking about the NHS saving
his life in a sense the
bedrock of society becomes something
like the NHS, do you think that is a
cultural and emotional shift? We could
have a 1945 moment. But the
danger is we have a 1918 moment when a
land fit for heroes was promised
but the lessons were not learned and
the social safety net was not fixed
or built and we led through the 30 it
is mass unemployment and globally
the failure of the league of nation
gss and the collapse world into war,
we know that story. The post 1945
moment was a different moment. I do
believe that this crisis, so global
so, universal, is so big that any
notion of "return" is not just on.
There is a danger
There is a danger that the zen phones
see this as their moment.
This politics of anger and
demonisation has no answers when it
cops to question of health or economy
that you have been debating.
You have Donald Trump railing against
the WHO and their handling
of coronavirus out-Breck. It Trump
right that the WHO didn't move
quickly enough. They made mistakes and
the Chinese practiced denial.
But the World Health Organization
needs to be stronger not weaker,
there will be greater health
insecurity if we undermine them. The
danger of the cuts that are being
discussed by President Trump, they
are a potential death sentence for
people who rely on vaccine and
programmes that is funded by the
American contribution to the World
Health Organization. The danger hear
the the post Covid world falls into
a US versus China stand off is real.
The Chinese will say it is their
system that has proved its worth. It
is important to say yes there are
democratic governments like in the
United States that have not handled
it. But countries like Germany show
open and free societies can deal
with cry cease like this. Ursula von
der Leyen apologised on behalf of
the EU to Italy for his failure to
help when the coronavirus hit. Do
you think it poses a threat to the EU.
The way Italy has been felt to
be on its own has not been a good
advertisement for the way in which
the EU can pull together and it has
made ideas of European solidarity
seem unreal. What you're seeing from
Ursula von der Leyen is a
determination that Europe will play
its part collectively as well as
individually. Europe has to pull
together and that will be important
not just in health and economic terms,
but also in political terms
and it is vital that it doesn't see or
find the Covid crisis as a spear
aimed at its heart. Thank you very
much. Where
As we emerge from this pandemic,
amongst the welter of reports
and inquiries, one thing is already
clear - the bravery of workers
in the NHS and the social care sector
as they help save lives
and care for the infected.
Many of these workers are from
overseas - the latest
Oxford Migration Observatory figures
for non UK citizens in healthcare
jobs is 20%; in care homes it's 18%.
But how many of these will remain
after Brexit?
One argument for us leaving the EU was
that the government wants
to upskill the UK workforce.
As many as 2 million more of us could
be unemployed by the summer -
so will the UK workforce be able to
deliver what we need most?
Take back control.
Three words that define Brexit, but
the coronavirus is no respecter
of borders or nationalities.
The sight of seasonal fruit pickers
from Romania
arriving at Stansted today, headed for
the south-east
of England and Lincolnshire,
underlines that the entry
of so-called unskilled workers to the
UK, on average 90,000
fruit pickers a year, allowed to
remain for three months
under the new rules, may have to the
resort the longer
the virus plagues us.
Under lockdown, UK workers are not
allowed to head for the fields
and our fruit and vegetable crops will
not wait for this
disease to pass.
We need help and there may be many
more planes carrying even
more pickers than usual.
There was no more stark or poignant
reminder of the debt owed to foreign
nationals working here during this
crisis than the video message
the Prime Minister delivered after he
left St Thomas' hospital
to begin his convalescence.
Amongst the many NHS hospital staff
you mention,
he said he was especially grateful to
two nurses.
Jenny from New Zealand, Invercargill
on the South Island,
to be exact and Luis from Portugal,
near Porto.
Jenny and Luis are part of an Army of
NHS and care workers
who are integral to the welfare system
and our welfare.
Many so-called low skilled migrants on
the Covid front line,
refuse collectors, bus drivers and
supermarket staff,
would not pass the new immigration
rules under newly released guidance
by the Home Secretary.
Something's come from overseas and
taken your jobs, but not me.
Or me.
This week, a video was posted on
social media to accompany a poem,
You Clap For Me Now, to make the case
for immigration
and the danger of racism.
Brexit is a fixture, but what is not
fixed is how much
this era of the coronavirus will
impact on who are the most
valued people in our community and in
wider society.
I hope to be joined by the Labour
Party MP
the Labour MP
Rushanara Ali and David Goodhart,
head of immigration and integration at
Policy Exchange and author
of The Road to Somewhere
Looking at the debt that Boris Johnson
paid to two workers and I
wonder if the mood has shifted in this
country about who is valued and
whether they come from here, there or
anywhere, does that matter? I
certainly think it is true that ethnic
minority Brits have been
visibly in the front line of the
crisis, as NHS doctors as nurses and
on what one might call the home front
of the invisible army of low
paid, low status jobs in retail and
cleaning and indeed care. But the
idea that... These people are kind of
second class citizens, who have
only just now been embraced by
mainstream Britain I think flies in
the face of all the evidence,
everything we know from opini polls
and the public domain. Look at the
cabinet. It is 8% of Brit, only 8%
of Brits who say you have to be white
to be valued. I think what is
coming out is that people that are
most valued, you know, are people
that actually do the jobs that are
needed most now and if you look
at... That huge group, particularly in
the poorly-paid care sector, a
lot of people that do that job would
not qualify, because they earn so
little, to be able to come to the UK
in the future and now it used to be
talked in abstract terms about care
home staff from other European
countries and how we will miss them.
Now we know it is important to have
that expertise regarded in many ways
as being low skilled and therefore
not important to this country? Yeah, I
mean I think, I hope we are going
to have some change in the status
hierarchy. It is very noticeable
that most of the key workers, the
people that keep the show on the
road, are not graduates, we have made
cog nittive ability the
greatest esteem. But it is raising the
pay and status of the jobs, so
people here would be more attracted to
do them. We have a recruitment
crisis in social care. It employs 1.4
million and they have 120,000
vacancies. The average churn is 30%.
We need to do something more
radical. Interesting to say that, what
I would say, if you look at the
wages, for example, a carer in a care
home would start at 12 and a
half thousand. You know, a supermarket
worker who now is key to
whether people can get food and drink
to keep them going, might earn
as little as 11,000. Lots of UK
workers don't want those jobs. So...
Those people are not going to be able
to fill jobs, because they're
not going to be earning enough to get
into this country. They have to
be learning, unless they're NHS
workers, something like 24,000 to
be welcome in is in country, but no
British person has stepped up to the
plate for these jobs. Well, we are
going to see that change, employers
will have to start training more. That
is the whole point of
Government's post Brexit immigration
policy. Nothing has changed on
immigration, the story remains the
same, we are a pretty open society.
We have had historic levels of
immigration and there is a national
consensus that that those numbers
should be reduced. Remain an open
society, but reduce the numbers.
Ethnic minority Brits also believe
that. We have a new system that is
pretty open at the hard skill level
it has come down and become more open
you only have to be A-level
type qualifications to be highly
skilled and earn 24, 25 grand. At
the lower end, they need to train
people better so people want do
those jobs. That is a reasonable thing
and it is popular with public
opinion. I'm afraid technology is
defeating us somewhat, thank you for
sticking with it and we are sorry we
are lost our other guest. Here is a
look at the front-pages. The FT: The
Guardian says lockdown may last to
June. A picture of war veteran Tom
Moore raising money for the NHS.
Three more weeks under lockdown say it
is Mirror. The Mail says there
are plans for office asked staff to be
asked to wear masks. That is all
from