Listen to me.
- Hey, man, get your hands off me.
- Listen. Listen!
You want respect in this game,
then you're gonna have to earn it.
I know they taught you that
at Cheyney State.
Why don't you teach your kids something?
Yeah, he made a bonehead move
but you had 30 before that.
And it didn't affect the outcome.
You want respect, you give it.
You earn it.
Come on, Coach.
- All right. All right.
- We got a long drive. Long drive.
Okay.
- Get back, guys. Come on!
- Come on, get your stuff.
Get back, everybody.
Come on, let's go. Get your stuff.
I couldn't swim right?
No, 'cause I was blinded
by the reflection off his white behind.
I'm telling you, man,
bobbing up and down in the water.
I couldn't even... I couldn't even see.
Best stroke out there
was Willie's butterfly.
Yeah, we were all watching that.
Hey, I'm just glad to be out them boonies,
you know what I'm saying?
- Them white boys...
- Man, hey, you know.
Them white boys
ain't never seen nothing like that.
But you almost drowned, though,
you almost drowned. I told Puddin Head.
What you talking about? I was down, man.
I may have swam backwards,
but I ain't...
What's so funny, man?
I want to laugh.
- What's funny? Don't you wanna laugh, El?
- I can go for a chuckle or two.
- Come on, what's funny?
- You know, nothing's funny.
We just clowning.
- You know how it is.
- No, Mr. Taylor, I don't know how it is.
Maybe you should explain to me
'cause I don't know how it is
to get my ass whooped,
and then to get on the bus and ride home
and act like it didn't happen.
- Like it's your birthday.
- Yeah, how does that happen, exactly?
Come on, Coach. It was just swimming.
Swimming? That wasn't swimming.
- You know what I saw?
- What did you see?
I saw a bunch of Negroes
who thought because they were black
that they were better than the other people.
Did you see that?
I thought I was the only one
that felt that way, you know.
- No, but you know also what I saw?
- What did you see?
- Some white kids was there, too.
- Talk to me.
And they thought the same thing.
They thought that because they were white
they were better than you.
And you know what?
They were.
- They proved it today.
- I thought so.
Yeah, but they cheated.
You saw him kick me, Coach!
You know who I think cheated,
Mr. Williamson?
You did.
You all cheated.
Because here you had a golden opportunity
to do something special,
but you pissed the whole thing away
'cause you wouldn't take it seriously.
- Say, man, what's happening?
- Nothing, man.
Right on, man.
But let me show you what's happening.
You see your rec right there?
In a couple of months, it's gonna be gone.
You know why, Mr. Carter?
Because the people it was built for
don't care about it.
This is your house.
And I tell you something,
my life is way too short
for me to spend my time around people
who don't care about nothing.
So you see your little
basketball court there with no hoop?
Go play life with no hoop.
Laugh it up, man. It's a joke.
He just playing.
- It's funny, ain't it, man?
- Yeah.
- Right on, man.
- Right on.
Give me some of that, man.
Sue. Sue.
- Elston, what you doing here?
- Hold on one minute.
Need to talk to you about something.
- Well, can it wait? I'm late for a meeting.
- No.
Sue, we had our first meet yesterday.
- I'm telling you.
- Yeah, I met your coach.
He got his work cut out for him, girl.
You came all the way down here
to tell me that?
No.
Chocolate-covered cherries.
- What do you want, Elston?
- Please take it, please.
Sue, I need you to pull some strings.
We need all the publicity we can get.
Sue, that's the only way
we gonna be able to keep that center open.
- Elston...
- Look, I'm telling you.
And by the way, your little brother, Hakim,
girl, he's turned
into one hell of a swimmer.
Hakim isn't supposed to be swimming.
Hakim is supposed to be in school.
And he's doing that too.
Get on it.
On it!
Okay.
Listen to your biceps.
I wanna see those ears
right against the biceps.
There we go.
See your goal, do an alley oop.
Dive in, right under the ball.
Everything tight, arms as close as you can.
And you slice through that water.
Reach for it with everything you've got,
like it's your last bit of life.
Go.
Get to that wall
like you're right within reach of it.
You can't be scared of him.
You got the whole other side.
Look at that water,
that's your world, you own that.
The race ain't over
till you ain't got nothing left.
It ain't about being tired,
it's about being strong.
When your legs get tired,
let your heart do the rest.
Come on, Mr. Davis, bring it up,
you the anchor.
You see, when you're training,
resistance is your friend.
But when you're trying to race,
it's called drag.
If you cannot see your face in the mirror,
your head is too low.
You can go faster, Mr. Taylor.
All you gotta do is kick your legs.
Hey, Elston,
don't you think they can go faster?
They're too busy admiring themselves
in the mirror, Coach.
You know, I still haven't found an anchor
for my relay yet.
- You think we got one here?
- They all anchors.
And they gonna sink us right to the bottom.
You see, coming together
is just the start of it.
Yo, yo! Hey, Coach! We got a special guest.
Staying together, winning together,
that's success.
Nice of you to join us, Mr. Williamson.
Come on back.
Everybody come back.
For every minute you're late, that's 10 laps.
- Hey, Elston, you got a slide rule on you?
- Mine don't count that high.
Yeah, you know, I majored in Mathematics
and that's 100 laps.
That's 2,500 yards you gotta do.
- I ain't doing no 100 laps.
- I know you're not.
- They gonna swim it for you.
- What?
You gonna sit there in that chair
and let them do your work for you
since you don't know how to show up
when you're supposed to.
We gonna start off with 2,500 yards.
That's four sets of 500.
The last 500
is gonna be broken up into two 50s.
The first 500 is breaststroke.
Second 500 is gonna be freestyle.
Third 500, I wanna see backstroke.
Fourth 500, I wanna see a butterfly.
You either work as a team
or you're nothing at all.
You're your own worst enemy.
You got so much potential.
But you ain't gonna do none of it because
you won't get out of your own way.
Have a seat, son.
Okay, let's go.
I believe in them so much.
There's so much they can do.
Hey, dig, Coach.
Let them stop or I quit.
If that's what you wanna do, then go.
It's your choice,
but your team is doing your work for you.
And remember, if you walk out,
you are walking out on your life.
You don't wanna leave,
and I don't want you to leave.
Hey. Hey, little man.
Little man.
Time to pay up, little man.
I figure that radio I stole from that guy
must have cost a good 50 bucks.
I've no money.
You think I want ice, waterman?
Hop in the car.
Hey, hey, wait up!
Hey, Reg. What's going on?
Your boy's got a job to do for me
to pay off his debt.
Reggie, man, look,
you don't need to do this.
- You don't have to, man.
- The boy's gotta do a delivery for us.
I gotta do this or he won't ever
leave me alone, you know that.
Time is money. Get in the car.
I gotta do this.
I gotta do this. I got it. I got it.
I got it, okay?
I got it.
Frank, let me do this for him.
It's me you want, not him.
That's looks like a real nutritious dinner
right there, Miss Carter.
Well, I've got protein in the eggs,
calcium in the cream frosting,
not to mention fruit
in the fruit topping, yeah.
Mind if I join you?
Please.
Thank you.
Ma'am, can I get a piece of cake, too?
So, how's things in the big City Hall?
You win some, you lose some.
I bet.
So, I understand Hakim is swimming again.
I assumed that
he had your permission earlier.
No, he didn't.
But it's a good thing
'cause he's back in school.
- Mr. Ellis, I just...
- Come on, Sue, we're having cake together.
It's Jim.
Hakim is not much of a student.
Yeah, I just think he's waiting
for something to catch his attention.
That's all. Thank you, ma'am.
Guess I just don't know
how to get through to him. I try.
Don't know how?
You've gotten through to him.
He's back in school, right?
And he hates it.
But he's doing it
because he wants to make you happy.
Yeah.
How's the cake?
Good.
So, Hakim's a good swimmer, huh?
Yeah, like a little tadpole.
- Well, Jim, I will make a deal with you.
- Proceed.
If Hakim stays in school,
he stays in the pool.
So that means we can keep
the rec open, right?
You said deal.
- You...
- I like the deal.
Excuse me.
Mr. Jones, get out of the car.
Come on.
Hey, baby boy,
why you so bent out of shape?
- Now!
- Coach, I can handle this.
I said they're with me, baby boy, chill.
Why you doing this?
Man, get on home.
Don't you ever come around my kids again.
Nigger, who the hell
do you think you talking to?
You don't understand, do you?
These are my kids.
They will always be my kids.
Welcome to Franklin-town, nigger.
I'm gonna tell you one time.
Don't you ever come around my kids again.
- You understand me?
- You stepped on the wrong toes.
We ain't done yet.
Come around my kids again
and watch what happens to your ass.
I'm not gonna tell you again.
That's a dead man walking.
Just get on home.
Come on, let's get inside.
Mr. Jim?
Hey, what's happening?
I think you need to take a look at this.
We got what we wanted, Mr. Jim.
The Philadelphia Department of Recreation
is pleased to inform us
that we have been sanctioned to...
We've been sanctioned
to hold a meet right here,
at Marcus Foster Pool.
Jim, you keep this up, you'll be unpacking
all those boxes out there.
How did you arrange this, man?
Well, Jim, I know a lot of people, too.
Yeah.
But you might want to thank
that councilwoman, that pretty little girl,
when you get a chance.
You know what I mean.
Thank you, Mr. Jim. Thank you so much.
How are you?
Elston.
Bingo night is on Tuesday
and Easter is eight months away.
Reverend, I've been thinking.
You know, it says in John 3:16
that God so loved the world,
he gave his only begotten son.
You know it.
Look at you, all decked out.
First meet in PDR in 10 years, Jim.
Yeah, I'm just hoping that some people
show up there for them kids, you know.
The Lord works in mysterious ways.
Yeah.
There, they're coming.
Keep your head. Keep your head.
Hey, Bink, good to see you, man.
How you doing?
- How's the kids?
- You know, same old stuff.
Yeah, wife?
Yeah, same, how about you?
What's going on?
New wife, smaller than the last one
but a lot more expensive.
- Yeah.
- You're a smart man
staying married all these years...
Excuse me a second. Say, Coach Ellis.
Hi.
I regret to inform you that
some of my young men
have come down with the flu
on the trip down here today.
And we had the best intentions
to support this community effort of yours,
but unfortunately we are not
gonna be able to compete today.
- So you're saying that you're forfeiting.
- No.
We will reschedule at a different time
and, perhaps, a more appropriate location.
What, some type of 24-hour, 14-minute flu?
You know, I bet you
they gonna feel a whole lot better
by the time they get home. Won't they?
Yeah, I bet they will. Thanks for caring.
If he walks out of here, that's a forfeit.
- They're all sick.
- No, they're leaving.
They can't compete.
- What do you want me to do, Mr. Ellis?
- I want you to be fair.
If that happened to my boys...
No, it's a forfeit.
I guess this meet is canceled.
- Good day, Mr. Ellis.
- Come on, don't do this.
Don't do this right now.
Come on, don't walk away from me.
It's a forfeit.
What's going on?
Where did the other team go?
Just some things don't change.
But thank you.
Thank you for everything you did
in trying to help us but...
I've gotta go and explain this to my kids.
Y'all should be proud of yourselves.
You got a huge crowd here today.
You came here to compete and you won.
Coach.
What happened?
Oh, no, they're leaving now.
- What?
- Why?
You know why.
You can't change some people.
You know, some people
are just born messed up,
but I am so proud of you all.
And I want y'all to walk out of here
with your heads held high.
And tomorrow we'll come back
and we'll practice
and we'll act as if
none of this ever happened.
But y'all are PDR.
I can't believe they're doing this again.
This is our house, Coach!
On your mark.
This is our house!
This is our house, Coach.
He's a man, now. He's a big boy now.
We're just so proud of Andre.
He's the first person in our family
to learn how to swim.
This is great for our community.
It inspires all of us and we love having
the Foster Center come back.
It's wonderful.
She could always swim like a fish.
She was the butterfly champ
at summer camp.
PDR. Number one.
I'm very excited 'cause
I never been outside of Philly before.
Just three months ago,
these kids could barely swim.
Next week, the kids of Marcus Foster Pool
are heading
to the National Swimming Championships
at the University of Baltimore.
I would like to thank Coach Jim Ellis
for all he's done for our youth.
Thank you, Councilwoman.
We really appreciate it.
Absolutely.
Coach, why don't we go inside
so we can interview you by the pool?
Sue, you think you might
get a craving for one of them
healthy slices of cake?
Maybe?
Maybe.
Tonight.
Okay.
Thanks.
Wait.
- Get a shot of this! Get a shot of this!
- Told you, we ain't done.
I can't swim!
Come here.
Now, say something.
- Make sure you got it.
- Come on, man!
- Help me!
- Let him give it to him.
Elston, do something!
Let him go!
Let him go, Coach!
- He ain't worth it, man.
- Come on, help him. Come on, come on.
Get him out of there.
He ain't worth it, Coach.
Mired by another night of violence,
intruder Franklin Pierce
is in stable condition
at Philadelphia Memorial Hospital.
Now, according to police, no charges have
been filed against Coach Jim Ellis.
Now, all this comes on the eve
of what should be the biggest night
for the kids of Foster Rec
who tomorrow leave for the National Finals
at the University of Baltimore.
So, I'm a big hypocrite, you know.
Turns out I'm no better than that little thug.
Tell you something, Elston. I need to quit.
Get out of these kids' way, you know.
What?
Man, if you quit now,
you quit on them kids.
You quit on this center.
You quit on this whole community.
And most importantly, Jim,
you quit on yourself.
I'm glad you came.
You must have seen the report.
Who are you?
Are you a con artist?
You tricked our children into trusting you.
You tricked this community
into trusting you.
First of all, I haven't tricked nobody.
You know where I was?
I was at the police station.
And I told them that Jim Ellis
is not the type of man to hurt anybody.
And you know what they told me?
That you have a record of arrest.
Okay.
There you have it.
The world isn't black and white.
When I was young, I hit an officer.
But I had a damn good reason
for doing that.
I know, I know. You're innocent.
Everybody's always innocent, remember?
I was the one
that put those innocent people away.
And funny how they are innocent
every time.
You know, out of all the people I know, I...
I would think you would understand
that the world isn't black and white.
You almost had me.
You almost had me believing
that you could make a difference.
Good night, Mr. Ellis.
Right on.
What?
On the bus.
Hey, Jimmy.
We brothers.
Let's do it. Let's do it, man.
Good luck.
What's happening, Coach?
You know, when I was a young man,
I made a lot of mistakes.
I made another one yesterday.
That's not the example I want for you.
And I'm gonna have to pay for that.
So I've decided
I'm not gonna be coaching you
but I'm putting myself on suspension.
Wait, so who's gonna coach us?
You got each other.
'Cause in the end, that's all you really have.
And you got your captain, Andre.
You know what to do, Mr. Williamson.
You see, we've been chasing dreams
for many, many years.
But tomorrow, you'll all get an opportunity
to fulfill some of those dreams.
You and the letters
that stand for this place.
You stand for PDR.
But what does it mean to us?
Pride, determination and resilience.
That's what's brought
all these people together.
You've given them something to believe in.
Because this is our community.
This is our house.
And it's built on pride,
determination and resilience.
Just pride, determination and resilience.
PDR! PDR! PDR! PDR!
We're gonna win for you.
Go get them, brothers. Go get them.
Man, this pool is big.
It's like an ocean.
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen,
and welcome to the
University of Baltimore Aquatic Center
for the Eastern Regional
Swimming Final.
We have teams from Baltimore,
Harvard, Plymouth and Mercer.
Defending their championship,
from Philadelphia,
the Main Line Barracudas.
And for the first time,
also coming from Philadelphia,
representing the Marcus Foster Rec Center,
Team PDR.
Listen up.
We are the official representatives
of the Marcus Foster Pool.
We're
Philadelphia Department of Recreation.
PDR.
We came a long way.
Let's show them what this family's about.
Swimmers, to the starting block,
please, for our first race,
the 100-meter backstroke.
Take your mark.
Come on, push, Mr. Taylor.
Get back, come on.
Go! Bring them in!
Bring them in! Bring them in!
Yeah.
Bobby Baskins wins for Main Line.
Wilson Peterson coming in second
for Arlington.
Up next, the 200-meter breaststroke.
All day, you dig?
Hey, focus. Don't worry about him.
Okay.
Swimmers, to the starting block,
for the 100-meter breaststroke.
Take your mark.
Go!
Good job! Hey! Yeah!
Reginald P. Jones
finishes in third position for PDR.
Swimmers, take your mark.
Come on, baby. Come on.
Come on, Willie!
Speed up.
And again.
- Go, Willie!
- Come on!
Come on!
Son of a bitch!
PDR's Wilhelmina Thompson comes in first.
Nick Post comes in second for Main Line.
And Carl Walters
finishes third for Arlington.
This gives Mercer the lead.
Main Line in second place.
PDR currently has 58 total points
placing them in fourth place.
PDR! PDR!
Come on! Come on!
PDR's Walter Davis
is struggling with a leg cramp.
Steven Epson wins for Main Line.
Yes!
Yeah.
Stretch it out, stretch it out.
My leg!
This brings us to the last race
of the individual competition.
This will determine
what teams advance to the team relay.
Swimmers, take your mark.
Swim, baby! Swim!
Go, Andre.
You can do it!
Well, boys, apparently
we got ourselves a little rivalry here.
Now, obviously, that's not the same team
that came up to Main Line.
You realize that, right?
Killing, man.
Guys!
Guys, look!
After completing the individual events,
we have three teams
within reach of the championship.
Main Line is in first place with 101 points.
PDR is just five points behind with 96.
And Mercer is in third place with 93 points.
All right, this is what it's all about.
It's the relay.
And we in second place.
We can actually win this thing,
just like Walt said.
We win this relay, we're champions again.
But we lose and they're champions.
Walt, how's that cramp?
I think I can swim, man.
I'm ready.
Sit this one out.
- Then who's gonna swim the first leg?
- I am.
Dre, you're the anchor, man.
You can't swim first.
Yeah, man, he's right.
I mean, you know the anchor
has to have the fastest time, man.
The anchor's got to have the biggest heart.
Reg, you're our anchor.
You sure about that?
So, let's win this. Come on.
- Go Main Line!
- Main Line!
That's right! Come on!
PDR on three.
One, two, three.
PDR!
Teams, prepare for the last event
of today's meet.
The 4x 100-meter relay.
This will determine the championship
for the 1974 season.
Swimmers, take your mark.
Fifty meters.
Barracudas!
Go!
Come on!
They got you swimming anchor?
Come on, Mr. Taylor! Go, Mr. Taylor!
Come on!
Again! Again! Again!
More!
Reg, Reg. What you doing?
Look at me, man.
You can do this.
- Come on.
- Come on, Mr. Jones.
Go! Go!
I'm proud of you, Coach Ellis.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have a photo finish.
A photo finish.
What happened?
I couldn't watch.
I just couldn't.
Win or lose, we still got our pride.
PDR! PDR! PDR! PDR! PDR!
I'm proud of you.
Thank you.