Hello, everyone.
Welcome to the class of College English IV.
Today, our topic is creativity.
What is creativity?
What can it bring to us?
How can we be creative?
Stay with me, and you will find the answer.
First, let's talk about the question.
What is creativity?
How do you understand it?
Maybe, it's difficult for you to give a definition.
But I believe some words will come to your mind.
So would you please tell me the words?
New ideas.  Yes.
Ability.  Good.
Eh, would you please?
Invention.
How about you?
Original.  Good.
Imagination. Quite good.
Yeah. When it comes to creativity,
Some words will flash in our minds.
And actually I've consulted some materials
and found many people have tried
to give a definition of creativity.
But they have explained it in different ways.
Yet generally speaking, creativity can be described as follows:
It is a kind of ability based on imagination and inspiration.
It includes thinking up new ideas, producing new things,
choosing new perspectives and adopting new solutions.
It is the source of creation, invention and innovation.
So look, there are so many words related to creativity.
But I have connected them with words
like based on, includes and source.
So I hope you can do the job as I did,
so that you can have a better understanding of creativity.
Let's do it together.
Creativity is a kind of ability based on
imagination and inspiration. Good.
It includes thinking up new ideas, producing new things,
choosing new perspectives and adopting new solutions. Yes.
It is the source of creation, invention and innovation.
Yeah. You did a good job. Very smart.
And then, what can creativity bring to us?
Maybe, it's a little bit difficult for you to answer this question.
So I'd like to show you some pictures.
Let's look at the first one.
What is it?
It's a chair.
But it can be folded and carried everywhere.
So, we can say creativity can make the life more convenient. Yes
And how about the second picture?
They are playing, right?
Yeah. So creativity can make the life more interesting, colorful. Good.
Or we can say rich, right? Yes, exactly.
How about the third one?
Creativity makes the world more beautiful.
Yes. You like it?
Since creativity is so significant and important for our humanbeings,
so we should be creative, right? Yeah.
And the problem is how to be creative?
What should we do?
Let's have a discussion.
Try to come up with effective ways to be creative
as many as possible.
Ok. Have a discussion with your partner or deskmate.
Ok. Anyone would like to say something?
Volunteers. Yeah, you please.
We should have curiosity
and don't be afraid to make mistakes.
Don't be afraid of making mistakes and be curious.
Good, good idea.
Anyone else? Would you please?
Write down the ideas when some something flash in your mind.
Yeah. Write down something or
write down some ideas when they come to your mind. Right? Yes.
How about others? Yeah, would you please?
I think you should spend more time thinking
and observe the world more carefully.
Yeah. Spend more time thinking
and observe the world carefully.
Good. I will follow your suggestion.
And anyone else?
Yeah, this boy.
I think we can do some crazy things.
If you like sing,
you can sing in the shower.
Yes. You are very creative, I think.
Do some crazy things.
Sing in the shower.
Do you often do that?
Ok, yeah. Since you have told me your ideas or your ways to be creative,
I'd like to share my ideas with you.
In my opinion, to be creative,
we should be curious about the world.
Learn to take risks.
Be enthusiastic about life.
Have positive attitude toward people and things around us.
Think outside the box.
You know. Think outside the box means
think in different ways. Understand? Yeah.
And then, imagine fully.
View from different perspectives.
And last but not least.
Explore what interests us.
In other words, creativity involves the following words.
Let's learn them together.
One two start
Curiosity.
Risks.
Enthusiasm.
Attitude.
Thought.
Imagination.
Vision.
Exploration.
Quite good. You've done a good job.
I'm really appreciated your participation.
By far, we have discussed the meaning and significance of creativity.
And we have found many effective ways to be creative.
Next let's show our creativity by playing a game.
Are you interested?
Yes. Let's do it.
In the following table, there are many words.
So try to find some words
and set their relationship with "creativity" or "creative", respectively.
Look. First, let's try to find these words.
You see, so many letters.
And what words can you find?
Block.
Computer. Good.
Imagination. Yes.
Rest. Good.
Singing. Yes. Here it is.
Writing. Yes.
Drawing. Yes. The last word drawing.
Ok. And then, let's try to set the relationship
between these words and creativity or creative.
Anyone would like to say something?
For example, "block".
So anybody would like to say something about "block" and "creativity"?
Anyone?
Would you please.
Playing block is helpful to developing the creativity.
Yes, exactly, good.
Playing blocks is very helpful to develop creativity.
So that's why blocks are very popular in western countries.
You know? Yeah.
Computer. Anyone would like to say something?
Yeah, would you please.
To be creative, we should stay away from computers.
Yeah. To be creative, we should stay away
stay away.
But the fact is we are addicted to it. Right?
Remember. To be creative, we should stay away from computers.
And then. Imagination. Would you please?
Imagination is the source of creativity.
Yeah. It is the source of creativity.
We can say creativity can not exist without imagination. Right?
Good. Thank you.
And then, let's move on.
Next one, rest.
We need enough rest so that you can get some creative, creative ideas.
Good. Yes. We need enough rest to get creative ideas.
Good. Thank you.
And next word singing.
Just now someone mentioned singing.
Yeah. Let's do the job together.
Singing is helpful or harmful?
helpful to develop creativity.
Good. Very good.
And then, how about this word, writing.
Writing. Anybody? Yes.
Writing is very important to develop creativity.
Yes, writing is important to develop creativity.
Drawing. Drawing.
Can you say something?
What's the relationship between drawing and creativity?
Yeah. This boy please.
Drawing is helpful to develop creativity.
Yeah. Drawing is very helpful to develop creativity.
You know, so when children, we say when children are very young,
they are usually encouraged to draw pictures. Right?
Yeah. Because it's very helpful and effective.
Ok. So much for this game.
We have done a good job.
Some people have believed that
creativity can solve almost any problem.
And we can't not use it up.
The more we use it, the more we have it.
So, let's stay creative
to make the life more convenient, colorful and beautiful.
In other words, let's stay creative and be happy.
Will you?
Yeah, ok, that's good.
So much for today, thank you.