A story spread among the Phoenicians
In 814 BC
the Tyrian king Mutto had a daughter named DidoBefore his death
King Mutto decided that his daughter Dido and
his son Pygmalion would ascend the throne together
However
Pygmalion did not want to share the throne with her sister
So
he murdered Dido s husband who was  the high priest that time
All happened unexpectedly
Princess Dido did not have time to resist
and she and her followers had to hurriedly sail across the sea and landed in Carthage
in what is now modern Tunisia
She wanted some land to make herself and her followers settle down
Dido bartered with the locals and finally agreed to purchase
a piece of land what she could contain within the skin of a bull
The question is
how big can a skin of bull cover
The savvy Princess Dido came up with an idea
She cut the hide into very thin strips
connecting the ends of the strips
In order to save the hide
the land she chose was sea-based
so that the sea formed the other side
In the end Princess Dido laid the hide out in a semi-circle
Is the area circling this way large
Mathematically
we classify it as a maximum problem
when the perimeter of a rectangular is constant
what are the length and the width making the largest area
This problem is similar to that of Princess Dido
In fact how to get a largest area when the perimeter of a rectangular is constant
In mathematics
such problems can be called constrained optimization problems
also called conditional extremum
To concise it to a mathematical problem
that is
When the perimeter of the rectangle is constant what are the length   and the width   maximizing the largest area of the rectangle
According to the extremum theory
we need to find the maximum value S=xy where max represents the maximum value
and the constraint condition is 2x+2y=L
The solution to the above problem is not complex
From the condition
we rewrite y as y=1/2L-x
and substitute the expression for y into the area formula
which can make S be organized into
If the term   equals to zero
the area S becomes largest
Then when x and y are equal to L/4
the area of the rectangle at this time takes the maximum value L^2/2
The above problem is about the rectangular area
now return to the problem of Princess Dido¡¯s land area
There is a key difference between the Princess Dido¡¯s land area and the rectangular area
that is in the Princess Dido¡¯s area problem
we have no idea of the land¡¯s shape
but we know that the shape of the rectangular area problem is rectangular
which is easy to know its area formula and its perimeter
For the Princess Dido¡¯s land area which have no idea of the land¡¯s shape
mathematically
we employ the general curve equations to describe the boundary curve
Let the parameter equations are x=x(t) ,y=y(t)
and t is greater than or equal to t1 and less than or equal to t2. In summary
the Princess Dido¡¯s land area problem is to determining the boundary curve equations x(t) and y(t) and get the maximum area under the condition the perimeter is constant
On the other word
the Princess Dido¡¯s land area problem is to cover the maximum land area when the length of the bull skin strip is constant