两
站
联
合
The video subtitles are made and released by both【HEY_GOT7 China Fansite】and【Baidu Jackson Wang Bar】Translator:Meg,Shelly,Jessi[hey] jenny caitlina,Huan,melon,Yexu[jsb] Video clip making:Meg,Sylvia,Lynn,Emily_X,jacky_tutu,little blood,Ariel[hey] Crown[jsb] Proofreader:CC[hey] jenny caitlina[jsb] Resource:melon[jsb] Poster:GAYO[jsb] The source of the video comes from the Internet.The copyright belongs to the original TV station which broadcast it .Any enterprise or individual must not put it into commercial use,otherwise you will bear responsibility for all the serious consequences arising therefrom.
off-site assists
Can't help to become a real bear
Broken chrysanthemums soy milk
Forthright way
What have i done to you
Empty the glass first to show respect
Little tip:
DO NOT take any drinks from a naughty child
Poison start working
Force drinking like feeding a baby
Mutant taste sense
Then what were you two doing just now
An uncle without any pursuing in food
Special food conception
Strange thought
CHINESE GHOUL
Timid Jackson end this conversation immediately
Western food material again
Waiting for this explanation
Protecting food?
What is he doing?
Professional gastronome: Littile AN
Tip from AN:only shell-looking spoon can matches caviar
I think i might be not quite dead yet
Whatever
eat first
Still missing
Fortunately
Uh..maybe
Curry chicken
Exciting
I thought it's you
My wife don't leave me any strawberries
so I don't wanna see other people has strawberry on
If I had
why would I care about my staff
Like you ever be grown
What? I'm having a great time
NOT a great uncle
technical exchange
I don't believe you
An anti-strawberrylism
App advertising
This young buddy has faith
Your turn
We still have our AD time
It's fate