SIREN BLARES 'Octonauts to your stations.'
Barnacles!
Kwazii!
Peso!
- Explore.
- Rescue.
- Protect.
GRUNTS
Nothing tastes better than a carrot fresh out of the garden, Turnip.
DISTANT SQUEALING
Ye-e-e-e-e-e-ow!
I'll get this one for you, me hearty.
Ha! On guard.
These vines are perfect for swinging. You should try it, Tweak.
No thanks, Kwazii. I'm happy just pulling up carrots.
Oh, that's not very exciting.
There's got to be some action around here somewhere.
Captain, I think I'm going to take the GUP-B out for a spin
because...because I need to, erm...
Let me guess, practise your driving skills?
Ah, that's it! Practise my driving skills.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ye-e-eow! Hoo-hoo-hoo!
- HE GASPS
- Dolphins!
Those dolphins are fast. Even the babies...
DOLPHIN CLICKS
..but I reckon I can catch up with them.
Wow!
Woohoo!
So long, Dolphins!
Ah! It's always nice to take the GUP-B out for a little excitement.
Looks like you brought back a friend.
A friend?
DOLPHIN CLICKS
- KWAZII GASPS
- A baby dolphin.
He must have followed you inside, Kwazii.
Oh, he's just a baby.
Poor little matey. He needs his mother.
And we're going to find her. Tweak, sound the Octo alert.
SIREN BLARES
Octonauts, to the launch bay.
Octonauts, our mission is to get this baby dolphin
- back to his mother.
- DOLPHIN SQUEAKS
I wonder how he lost his mummy.
I was driving the GUP-B near some dolphins. He must have started
following me instead of his mother.
- He must have got caught in your slipstream.
- What's a slipstream?
Dolphin mothers swim so fast that they make a path
in the water behind them called a slipstream.
The slipstream pulls the dolphin baby along
and helps it keep up.
But this baby dolphin must have got
carried away in the GUP-B slipstream.
Aw, I'm sorry, little matey.
It must have happened when I drove between you and your mum.
DOLPHIN SQUEAKS AND WHISTLES
I wonder why he keeps whistling like that?
Every dolphin makes a different sound that other dolphins know.
Dolphin mothers know their babies by their special sounds.
So, we can use this baby dolphin's sounds to help us find his mother.
Tweak, we'll need the microphone and recorder.
Got it, Cap.
First we'll record his sounds and then we'll play it while we search.
And his mummy will recognise the special sound.
Ready, set, whistle.
DOLPHIN SQUEALS
Come here, little matey. Don't be afraid.
DOLPHIN CLICKS
He likes you, Kwazii. Why don't you try.
Um, give us a nice whistle now.
DOLPHIN SQUEAKS AND WHISTLES
Perfect! We've got our recording.
Shellington, Dashi, into the GUP-E.
Peso, into the GUP-A with me.
We'll spread out and search for the dolphin's mother.
- Kwazii, you stay here and babysit.
- Aye, Cap.
I'll... What? Did you say stay here and babysit?
- You're the best one for the job, Kwazii.
- Me? A babysitter?
Yes. The baby dolphin really seems to like you.
Keep a close eye on him.
- But, Captain...
- Kwazii, open the Octo hatch.
KWAZII SIGHS
Let's split up so we can cover more ground.
Aye, aye, Captain.
Don't worry, little matey, they'll find your mother.
All we have to do is wait.
KWAZII HUMS A TUNE
KWAZII SIGHS
Waiting's not very exciting.
DOLPHIN SQUEAKS
Come on, matey, we're going outside to play.
DOLPHIN CLICKS
Aye, this looks like a good place.
Well, go ahead now. Play.
But don't go far, little matey.
Yar! Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Where d'ya go?
DOLPHIN CLICKS
Ha-ha, yeah, you got me again.
A seashell? You want to play fetch, do ya?
DOLPHIN CLICKS
Ah-ya!
Ha-ha! You're a mighty fast little dolphin.
Ha, try again.
Ooh, yeow!
DOLPHIN CLICKS
What is it, little matey?
DOLPHIN CLICKS AND GRUNTS
Careful, matey! Those lobster claws can really pinch.
Yar! Go snap somewhere else.
OK.
Here you go, little dolphin.
Yeah, all right, all right.
Let's race to the other side of the rocks, eh?
Ready, set, go!
Ha, dolphins!
Excuse me, do you recognise this sound?
BABY DOLPHIN WHISTLE PLAYS
Nope, doesn't sound familiar, but earlier
we saw some other dolphins back that way.
- Maybe they'll know the sound.
- Thanks.
I hope we can find them, Captain.
BABY DOLPHIN WHISTLE PLAYS
Never heard that whistle before, I'm afraid.
THEY SIGH
But I did see a dolphin looking for her baby a few minutes ago.
She was on the other side of that reef.
Oh, thanks. Dashi to Captain Barnacles...
'We have a lead on the mother dolphin.'
'She's on the other side of the reef.'
Good work, Octonauts. Let's go.
Yow!
Atta-dolphin!
Now try this...
Hey, where's he go?
Oh, no. Where is he? Little matey, come back to Kwazii.
Where are ya?
Look, over there.
DOLPHIN WHIMPERS
Um, excuse me, is this the sound of your baby?
BABY DOLPHIN WHISTLE PLAYS
Yes, it is! I've been looking everywhere for him.
Do you know where he is?
We'll take you to him. Follow our slipstream.
Oh, thank goodness.
Barnacles to Kwazii, we've found the baby dolphin's mother
'and we're on our way back to the Octopod.'
Er, great. Me and the baby will be right here
waiting for you when you get back.
'Barnacles out.'
Oh, this is terrible.
I can't find him anywhere.
SHARK SNIFFS
Mmm! Lunch is served.
Ye-e-e-e-eow! Dah!
Oh.
SHARK SNIFFS
Oh, no, lunch is cancelled.
KWAZII SIGHS
He's gone and you're safe.
You can't just go off on your own like that.
Stay close to me, matey.
DOLPHIN GURGLES
DOLPHIN CLICKS
Huh?
Ha-ha!
It's your mother.
Oh, my baby! I'm so happy to see you.
Thank you for keeping my baby safe.
Just doing me job as an Octonaut...
and a babysitter.
Come on, it's time for us to go.
BABY COOS
Go on with your mum now.
For me?
Thanks, little matey.
Goodbye. And thank you.
BABY MIMICS "THANK YOU"
Good work, Octonauts and especially you, Kwazii.
Thanks, Captain.
This belongs with me other treasures.
I'll remember you always, little matey.
KWAZII SIGHS
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk