两
站
联
合
The video subtitles are made and released by both【HEY_GOT7 China Fansite】and【Baidu Jackson Wang Bar】Translator:Meg,Shelly,Jessi[hey] jenny caitlina,Huan,melon,Yexu[jsb] Video clip making:Meg,Sylvia,Lynn,Emily_X,jacky_tutu,little blood,Ariel[hey] Crown[jsb] Proofreader:CC[hey] jenny caitlina[jsb] Resource:melon[jsb] Poster:GAYO[jsb] The source of the video comes from the Internet.The copyright belongs to the original TV station which broadcast it .Any enterprise or individual must not put it into commercial use,otherwise you will bear responsibility for all the serious consequences arising therefrom.
Come on ...
Oh my gosh !!!
Its not my bridge but ad's .
Looking my bridge is more than over the hump.
Change quickly
Candid boy
The best team member!
I guess both of you accept money
What are he saying?
Strawberry manor?
sheet like mc
I wanna meat.
You get me.
not chatting to a common girl
aggressively！
I wanna chatting with girl,too
What are these dishes?
village head
there is a pool of light before my bed
WOW
and I will stay with you in the future
GOOD
wait
Bro TianShu
what's up?
What did you say just now?
just skip it, they didn't find it at all
Slip of tongue
It's not correct.
Cook cheers for later.
Deal, go on.
Thank you very much!toast~
Lucky I was not punished.
Success!
tonic in life
make up, just make up.
The evil we bring on ourselves
is the hardest to bear.
dude, wanna date with me?
The first chef in season2
will be lele?
False Alarm