- SIREN WAILS
- 'Octonauts, to your stations!'
Barnacles!
Kwazii!
Peso!
- Explore!
- Rescue!
- Protect!
Octonauts!
Yaw!
Whoo-hoo!
Kwazii, have you collected those seaweed samples?
Aye, Captain. I'm heading back to the Octopod right...
- Shiver me whiskers! I thought
- I
- was a hotshot pilot
but these little fishes put me to shame! Octonauts!
'Can you see this?'
They're sardines, Kwazii.
They always travel together in a school.
But how do they all STAY together?
The scales on their skin help them feel when others are near them.
That's how they stay together when they move.
'A triple curlicue with a half-pike squiggle!'
I've got to try that. Kwazii out!
I'm going to show these fishes some moves of my own!
Ha-ha! Get a load of that!
A super-fast flip turn with a backwards loop! Not bad!
- Hey-hey! Top that!
- You're on!
BOTH: A backward rollover with a one-and-a-half inward split!
Ha-ha! You swim almost as well as a sardine!
- You're not too shabby for a little flipper-flapper!
- The name's Dina.
Kwazii. Maybe we'll have a rematch someday.
You're on! Better get back to my school before they...
Uh-oh.
Did you lose your school? I'll be glad to help you find them.
- No, thanks. I'm sure they didn't go too far. Bye, Kwazii.
- Bye, Dina.
Be careful, matey.
Mm, lunch is served.
Ah!
Not so fast, ye scurvy shark!
Oh, no! Lunch is cancelled.
Oh, thanks, Kwazii! I guess it's not so safe out here without my school!
- They say there's safety in numbers.
- True.
That's why sardines travel in large schools.
Then, when a fish who wants to eat us shows up,
- we swim in different directions. It doesn't know who to follow!
- Clever!
- There's only one of me but I'll take you to your school.
- That's very nice!
Avast! There they are now!
I know a shortcut through this old shipwreck.
Ahh!
What happened?
- I'm caught in this old fish net.
- Are you hurt, Kwazii?
Nah. I just bumped my head.
Don't worry - I'll get myself out of this mess.
Yah! Stuck!
Maybe I could chew through the ropes.
No, Dina. You go on ahead, or you'll lose your school again!
Nope.
You didn't abandon me when I needed help.
I'm staying here with you till I know you're OK.
You're a brave lass, Dina, and a good friend.
I'd better call the Octopod.
What's wrong, Kwazii?
Well, I hit my head, the GUP is trapped,
and a little sardine is in danger cos she lost her school.
- Other than that, everything's fine.
- Hiya!
- Sounds like you need a hand.
- Dashi, sounds the Octoalert!
- Aye-aye.
ALARM WAILS
Octonauts, to the launch bay!
We've got an emergency rescue/ first aid/lost sardine situation.
ALL: Huh?!
Oh, I'll explain on the way. Tweak, into the GUP-D.
Peso, into the GUP-E.
- OK!
- Right-o, Captain!
- Dashi, open the Octohatch!
I'm on it, Captain!
Kwazii, your school is here.
Aye, you could call them that.
How's your head, Kwazii?
Do you feel dizzy? Sleepy?
How many fingers am I holding up?
- That's a trick question - you have none.
- Great.
You don't SEEM hurt. But I'll check you over as soon as I can.
That's where I come in!
Thanks, everybody.
Oh, where are my manners?
Octonauts, meet my new friend, Dina. Dina, Octonauts.
Hi, everybody. Sorry if I caused any trouble.
Nonsense!
The Octonauts are always happy to help.
Kwazii, which way did the school go?
They went that way, but they could be anywhere by now!
Barnacles to Shellington.
We've lost track of the sardines. Is there a way to find them?
Yes. We can find the sardines by listening for their burps.
Sardines burp?
Yes. Sardines - and many other fish - swallow air to help them float.
When they want to sink lower, the burp the air out again.
You can pick up the burping sound on the GUP's underwater microphone.
Now, just listen and be very quiet.
SNORING
- I don't suppose the sardines are asleep.
- That's a seal snoring.
CLICKING
- What's that?
- A crab clicking its claws.
BURPING
Ah - burping!
- Dashi, can you tell us where it's coming from?
- I'm on it.
Straight ahead...near a coral reef.
That's where we're heading. Barnacles, out.
Dina, we may have found your school.
That's good news! Best be on your way, Dina.
But I don't want to leave you here.
I'll be fine - I'm with my school!
And you need to be with yours. Go on now.
Thanks, Kwazii, for all your help.
Any time. Stay safe out there!
Just follow me, Dina.
BURPING
The burping's getting louder. We must be close.
Don't tell me sea horses burp too, Shellington!
Lots of fish do, Captain. We must have picked up sea horse burps.
What if my school is so far away we never find them?
Captain, the burps you hear now are from above you.
This could be your school, Dina. Let's go.
BURPING
- We must be very close now.
- I can feel them with my scales!
There they are!
Whoops!
Almost forgot to say thank you!
- And please thank Kwazii for me.
- Don't mention it, Dina.
Helping sea creatures is what we do.
Bye, Dina!
I'll let Kwazii know you're all right.
There you go, Kwaz. You're free!
'Come in, Kwazii.'
We found Dina's school - she's safe and sound.
That's happy news indeed, Captain.
Everything looks good here. See you back at the Octopod.
Mmm. Breakfast, lunch AND dinner is served.
That shark looks hungry for sardines.
I've got to help them!
Oh, no!
Nah... Ah... Er...
Hmm.
They're swimming in different directions to confuse the shark.
Oh!
Uh-oh. More sharks. Looks like the sardines could use some backup.
Calling all GUPs. Sardines in trouble!
Yaw!
I don't know if I can hold them off by myself for much longer!
You won't need to, Captain!
YAW!
Octonauts, follow the sardines' lead. Swirl and confuse!
- Over here!
- This way!
- Catch me if you can!
- This way?
Ow!
Breakfast, lunch and dinner - cancelled!
THEY CHEER
- Kwazii! I'm so glad you're OK.
- And I'm glad YOU'RE OK.
I guess we both needed our schools to help us!
DINA BURPS
Excuse me!
THEY ALL LAUGH
更多产品请咨询QQ：799562590