And so, clearly one of the big challenges
is that graphs are really big.
Big, massive, really massive.
You can add any kind of these fancy
adjectives.
And more importantly than just having the
graphs getting larger, the queries that
you fire on these graphs are getting more
and more interesting and exciting and
harder to evaluate.
So one is, you can have the standard
pattern like queries, which you can, all
of you, I think some of you already said,
it's similar to SQL with few drawings.
Yeah, SQL has drawings, but really done
well for draw inquiries.
But you can actually go into a little
more complicated things in these graphs.
And say I wanted to cut some troubles
with unbounded recursions.
I just want to keep doing bits of
validities than have no good solution
which is really efficient, right?
This is a load in sparkle ex regions
people are talking about.
And then you have, on these graphs, many
inequality that you can, I mean you are
all already familiar with page wrap,
basically these analytic way we translate
the entire graph twice to rank based on
the random walk potentials, right?
You can also think of our I'll first fire
1 query, get subgraph out, some ad hoc
subset of the entire el woody.
And then from this I will extract then
subgraphs or some kind of K cord of
decomposition of this compute standard
lease right?
If you are familiar with this keyword
search and graph this is basically what
they do.
They fire some inch inside of queiries
which will figure out certain notes And
then try to connect them up using
standard [INAUDIBLE].
Again, these are not so easy to solve
using relational databases.
The solution most of the current
approaches use is, let's take this graph
and put it in memory and deal with it.
Okay?
While it is a valid solution, given that
the memory is getting cheaper
>> It's still no cheap enough to hold
30 billion triplets.
Okay, so we need to come up with better
strategies for dealing with it.
>> Is this a concept of uh, [INAUDIBLE]
sets and rules, in the
[INAUDIBLE].
>> Yes.
So you can always looks at frequent
subgraphs.
>> Like, so in fact, there is another,
as they say, some kind of
>> [INAUDIBLE]
>> So, you can relax, you can relax the
labels on the ages, and say I will, I
don't care about the ages, but Really any
kind of structure, we can say I will
include just the labels but I relax on
the subjects and objects that are there.
So people have worked on these kind of.
>> Sequence the subgraphs and then also
interesting subgraphs.
>> Interesting subgraphs, okay.
>> [INAUDIBLE].
>> Just to reiterate my point, so far
we have never talked about how exactly
they're evaluated.
So far I have never even mentioned how
>> [INAUDIBLE]
>> So created, you can just create any
graph you, in the good old way that you
you take your relational database,
perform all your joints, and store it as
a graph.
Right, I mean that's one cheap way of
answering it.
But in other words, there are so many
efforts coming, both from automated
methods as well as from manually
hand-coding stuff, so if you go back and
look at it, DBLP, for example they
maintain huge records of which paper
appeared in which conference, which
journal, what author, and so on.
And they, again, wrote scripts, from this
structured relational table they had.
To turn it into and ideas.
And then give it out as part of RDF data
set, which is essentially a graph.
Right?
So that's one method of doing it.
Iago, free-base kind of efforts, they're
there focusing on, Iago and DDPDS, sorry,
are focusing more on, let's take some.
Almost structured data like Wikipedia,
and apply whole bunch of machine learning
tools, natural language processing tools,
so that you can extract out these facts,
x is related to y, in some way, and then
put them into the graph form.
Right?
And psych, again, hand colored many of
these knowledge.
So, there are many efforts in which the
graphs were created.
Again, we are, I'm not going too much
into any of those.
I agree that these are challenges, but
I'm looking at a slightly different
challenge.
[COUGH] So just to continue with this
line and try to finish it quickly.
Queries are bigger, graphs are bigger.
And you can see hey why not use some
magic bullet like how to write.
Google users account for terabytes so 30
billion should be T right But the problem
is that, your graphs are not the same as
text tables, right?
Text pieces, which Google uses this one.
So your graphs have complex inter
connectivity, this is known as god knows
what are the notes.
Right?
What kinds of relationships are there?
That's one.
And today some connections may not exist,
but tomorrow you can just add one edge,
it seems like a very harmless piece of
edge saying Dolph Lundgren and Bruce
Willis acted in The Expendables.
They never acted before.
Suddenly, you put these two together and
form a connection.
So as you assume the doing the hard loop
you're actually partition in the nicely
hard all, the guys who works with Bruce
Willis.
I will put these two down separately.
And suddenly, expendables comes, all the
partitioning falls apart, right?
Which is not the case in the applications
settings where hard loop is used.
Your partitioning is fine.
You don't need to worry about it anymore.
Your partitioning logically means the
same.
But here things can get really messy,
even in a single static snapshot, as well
as you when have these dynamism in your
data set.
So therefore data partitioning solutions
will also need rethinking.
Okay, so given all that, it's not like
I'm the only guy who has thought about it
and teaching you.
There's a whole bunch of people who have
worked on it.
Okay.
There is huge research as well as
industry work that's going on for
developing graph data management tools
for very different kind of applications.
Both generic as well as in the analytic's
world.
So, for example, there is transactional
graph database systems, data management
systems, like Neo4J, Jena, HyperGraphDB,
RDF3x.
They're, they really focus on this LOD
kind of settings.
Right, well, you, until now, you never
had analytic s queries on there.
You just had more, just coming in, a
pattern, and you match it.
Right.
But we are saying now that SPARQL is
getting richer with recursive reasoning
kind of queries.
Then transactional GDM has to evolve into
which supports little more than just a
transactional pattern maxing place.
And then you have analytic GDM.
Analytic, graph database management, like
Pregel and Giraph, which, can be seen as.
Hadoop style processing for graphs, which
have [UNKNOWN] of reasoning.
You can compute page rank using Pregel.
In fact, this is the clean Pregel.
Paper also makes that, they design Pregel
so that they can do [UNKNOWN] on massive
graphs.
[INAUDIBLE]
>> Legal is not.
But it's open source implementation which
is on to of hall loop, called Giraph.
>> [INAUDIBLE]
>> Giraph is open.
>> Yea, it's actually bad at this
moment.
But, it's not as.
>> [INAUDIBLE]
>> Giraph lab, yes.
Graph lab I haven't put yet because it's
not really a GDI GD-ermium.
They are more designed for doing machine
loading applications on top of some
graphs, without really worrying about,
exactly.
So that's basically the focus.