sure
seen you do to my beloved to
Shinichi usual with a mob
T she combat the marquee Kobe GBB
top-seeded Tsonga g'day
fine particle BNP diesel from
line 32 GB she told plod along
280 yup from home that you come up with
the idea
d short simi clock Idaho
racial hang on I can tell you able from
each and whether they should you tell
beijing
yet casually abating and I'm a blog
which ones ambush
I G Hall doing Union you live elevating
a new share baby can t get away with all
my 10 mph oleanna
one now but you know what I would do you
have anything that would he be alien
heads
when you shop when you show no idea job
for the team meeting
courage a
a yes I see JG to implement a line 288
and veggie food allergy attack
jpg GG to head to SessionFactory
needy but the pay TV DJ cheeba mumble
TV cable entitle me Beijing home
feeding to hear about it be oceanfront
DT aliquam gordana teaches optional good
deeds on twenty
digital need to a tee time you
leadership the PLO
would you the Commission Heidi today
called he didn't immediately
and beachy to your judges William home
to johnnie the AC tumulty John Whelan
Martin
from Paul congratulations again for the
chanting
ship a that's a huge day II I know both
for Beijing and for yourself
but first of all describe to us a
the feelings for the last ten amid in
half
way west end of the court after the
fixed file
what are you surprised yeah I was
surprised because I didn't know that I
had
five fouls when I was standing on the
sideline I was just like oh my god I
cannot be out there with my teammates
right now to help them but
I had a feeling that we will we were
gonna be okay I just didn't know how
this is the longest million had my life
breakdown in you are not even looking at
them that couldn't believe that I was on
a call it an outcome was unfamiliar
me in on the Cylon at that time normally
I want a court
trying to make a play forced to wear in
this time I was
I was on silent watching wat
as is I just and I was on silent prayer
it
homes logo God we gotta win this game
you have to
no way we can go back to morrendo that
was a very
tight came 1 21 21 21 the wing
your sanity of the core a and very very
close
towards the end yooo Beijing
lost for myself being in those moments
and embracing those those challenges are
the best part of playing basketball
there's nothing better than that
and have an opportunity to to have
shared
that with magnitude this country size
all the people who wipes was like
although China a second
geared up and started to follow us
because we were
basin taken now janata China
Basle week with my body to me
material into the entity it in ya you
what you would in the twenty
on the I prison cool people and to to me
and the
you wouldn t 1g that the tag on him
mobley tangible to music
mucho moved to do it you to the among
them to one can you imagine
between home Thaci damage line but it's
always been sample
psalm go into the link up C&C be a dream
to learn from me
2011 will present at a little engine de
ghet
such time backseat decided to put it
mildly
actual team leader shouldn't affect
oftentimes turned on the party till date
Claudia
put on hold to cushion the delight teen
party
ET told to let song wanted the job the
pension
how long have you missed that
where last time I felt that
was when I was a Phoenix plan
playing in the playoffs I mean a player
is a test that's what you play for doing
the right thing
you play to position so in the playoffs
so you try to win the championship yeah
so that was a
there's a feeling that he had missed for
so long
yeah damage in and again from city Mar
22 with little
be cut to a tilde clicking not turkey
dismantled
fantasy duty in May a title from good
bottled up but the war your made from
real good to me
should have an 18k Sibanda you feel
miss understood when the Sports
Illustrated backand
2009 when they had this survey of
for would be the player they don't want
to play live and Laura
come on the topic okay I pay no mind to
I lack
I left dead human beings were going to
take the poll for it
jet to meet asked to meet with I also
you
really way this is with this is the
Lightning wanna you wanna put out so the
universe okay cool
okay with that I mean but I want to
strip that they were wrong
I don't wanna prove that they were wrong
because I knew I was right
so was a real improvement
wrong just said no more debate thing
said okay you still say names a rocking
I just know what I gotta do I gotta go
boom something
to me and stop talking our I was tired
bien what they call me lonely world
I hated that I and only will
hey I hated it but
you know I was okay because I knew I
wasn't that player or that person so it
didn't really bother me I just feel like
that people were asking about her
say that here in a min long yeah I heard
because that
that not with you you are no tests now
who I am
that's not how I play basketball I was
being defined by
plan in situations in the NBA
do RTT dome our bodies would immediately
DTD paint and a teasing 20t halter
glinting dental about 40 to contact 2014
to be
so long yup
John and Paul Martin to your mom
teaching Park 2gb said he should
Dhammapada gonna US you
the four GT Porsche the whole mobley
being retarded child
be would leave deeply attorney William A
to B to
mom would become so she fun in the
kitchen chill date on the 21
I noticed that you are kneeling down in
praying before your team players
lifted you up waterway in praying
I was just a good guy for giving me the
opportunity from
being through rising where so many
people
doubting category
kader up
what kind of category that occurred
where
and can win a championship completed
something different thing you know what
I've learnt
when you can never listen to say
doing take place
for a collaboration
whenever there's a groom everyone has to
be
saying reach
go have an opportunity to play with them
guys wanting I mean
in the coach that was like
this here all that was needed for
whenever you get opportune be apartheid
your aim to
mmm charger you're basically
in a position where Gover
governor something home if which is
move in the movement was trying to win a
championship
it took a lot it took a lot of a lotta
me
and everybody was on the same page
and/or
so when I think back to all the critics
in america
what they say you know why I came to
China
what I'm doing in China I mean is so
type of people
or even here speaking about something
like you're talking about something you
don't even know what you're talking
about going off
experiences 56 years ago
which is Connor to me is ninth
because now something brand new going on
in the present you're still talking
about
well known in the past to try to pull me
down so
I was is giving I was giving thanks to
God for
allow my mind to stay focused and at
do what was just died and
I was so humbled and appreciative
support
this whole season they knew
what I want goal and our
working toward because they were in see
it
laugh so much what's going on here
that's one moment here
ally hey but I could see that the whole
family shared
ditto this 2008 and reber's her yes
a person but I i would guess that you
a oh so wish to share that moment with
you all
late father yes that's possibly I was
after
but I believe the other hand I i believe
is his spirit was right there with me
and
I'm losing my father took Abril
took a really big toll on my life you
know
it was either gonna break me or was
gonna make because in the love that we
have
for for our Father and
you know doing their time when he when
Pastore
he passed on or what he loved to watch
his kids playing basketball wins and
stays white
game this these times where he which is
the same bag looking like that's my baby
that's my boy
what was the most important message that
he instilled into yourself if either the
winning
in that cable I know that he basically
coached you old through
your childhood my father engineer
my father he coached us
like my father really game
the brother were so did but my father
toward Earth never
give never give you know
generate if never give up you mean never
give up but never give
and give an answer
Sarwar majorities thought basically
I believe I know I didn't do something
it doesn't matter
a billion people say I did I know I
didn't do it
that doing argument on the army
said hello to India my body be I'm
patient on the surgeon use
ideas on the 20 t2 party is related to
deadly
multilateral interchange yesen him at
that point I went to a whole
oppression time as far as like was I
gonna stop playing basketball want
something that I love something I've
been doing since I was two years ago
already knew how you know how okay up
like can be
iraq but it was it was it was kinda
funny
amazin is stupid nonsense it was a
variety of different things in the lot a
different emotions at different times
and during that time as our room of a
van and started to understand how
people I started to learn how people
operated
who are conscious and you make them
this is Ian unconscious in is not
in a positive light it's only in a
negative light
thats wat thats was aggravating
internally not be anymore
internalize was the next that was my
next move staying patient stay is still
beat enable my dog ya ma petite ending
the season
JG team a she shoe shops in
mom Portland wt
to me by GDP to raag
occasionally deal to up from soho
GTG yup done by mobley million
side Beijing
does one have to travel 7,000 miles to
find peace
again in your hand that's what happened
I
thinking up you know where you are
packing for for a country called China
0 I don't mean to you very you know
little about
asked for it took me a month
took me a month I mean it was brought to
me about your own place channel two
we actually mine tooling had no idea
about china only thing I knew yeah I
mean
hit a great war and there was a lot of
people
so will you get em bowling on this
decision I was in gambling because it
was
you know spoken about was talked about
were
the pup with the possibilities were
actually all that was happening right
now
means adapting or will talk about as far
as what could happen
how do you convince your friends and
families who persuaded you
not going I mean my brother it didn't
know that no one can see the
no worker C division I'll what ASO
when I first came here was leap of faith
tony was a leap of faith when offers K
when I said I was told that that's when
everybody hola
you more back to china our way
yeah I'm going back to China when I
first
when I first got the China the first
time weeks I want to kill myself
hours ago craze why culture to form
on I mean it was just a variety of
things that I wasn't
I was like but this crap to describe to
me I mean I need more data
million I've never seen a big fish come
out and say one like
I they will even bring a big finish
second at this rate did everybody in the
pleasure was the oklahoma
in King up chicken head the whole
chicken now
I'm like I've never seen that before now
is
is know what's inside you know exist
life is normal for meetings and I'm
asking for serving
I mean I I was limitation she's so they
told me that I was probably the hardest
place to live
yeah where to people was so amazing
I mean when I first got it is showing
some ways love i jus
I was like man is love this is
incredible
hundreds of them was where the air you
like to see you
evan is just like the injured left knee
mea gotten way back onto my life
on my way it was some with the story is
so crazy
because it man I gotta when I was on a
plane I was depressed the whole time I
was coming hours a
flying on a player
oh my god this flatus so war
like where am I going or what am i doing
by I knew I was going to do something
once I made
season income that's when I knew details
on my way
I had no idea it would turn out the way
hours turnout
and had no idea the people
had no idea the coach I know I had no
idea
the Five Towns many instead guy sheer
had no idea
at from is so meaningful soulless
some guy i know i dare that Chinese
people be drinking is Mike danger I
never knew that by 200 ma
I maker I had no idea about all the
different names
and as activities in Roanoke College
Online
bid this is real life right here I
this is totally give her forward I'm
busy
Rd Union palatable simple Thomaston CT
portended Rd Union bonnet medici
up on the blog Glee coherent in the
Beijing mobley
deductions or lied Beijing he made
differential
to another which she took the plunge in
high-yield
by twenty Blacktown why was it important
for you
so it's not about winning the Champions
by winning the Champion
I'll definitely is always about I mean
now where did
we retain that people want to be that
way financing
find cuz you you have to do after were
you have to make sure you come ready
every game
is gonna be a fight name is going to be
a challenge never
team dinner always gear up and get ready
for bite back then
bag not I mean when I went there Beijing
wasn't saying that I wanted to play for
I was
going to see what my options or what my
situation turn out to be
when I came in at a whopping we wanna
win a championship everybody said that I
was crazy a raise
again that's a you know you gotta play
our the year I know I gotta play
I went to the finals to whites one
downplaying
I wanted this scene what the CBA fines
were were about
and I want to see how deeply when our
wives
ass then you can bill Empire
or and day of course it takes time take
the planarity
build his preparation being here
being a partner are today reminding
go allowed on
which is so having
eroding way to give back home
I was talking to my daughter now the %um
about to go back home shoes i which
saying about to go back that's our
apartment I
air others %uh stoller about to go back
to a park
she's actually speaking Chinese she's
learning
so glad my younger I want my older
daughter
she's she speaks Chinese seeing
up but you have to learn those words to
exchange with your teammates
a the game right I mean what are some of
the worst that
that you would use more frequently than
others
to be honest me reaches ages
they understand me an honest A&M is not
release
any specific were because we have a
translator trent death or importing
our trail the s get about
Chang having a really good translator so
vital
in the sea gave me you know you for
players good
I logged as being exchanged Basketball
Wives is
easy when I'm trying to get them to
understand is a
a really have to like
think about what I'm saying in
do it and is this is that
okay because going through some
me tellin
going go into
going to play so once be built their
connection
packages talk in a on a quedar kisses
talkin okay okay okay anomaly the same
thing
basketball good changed
once run normally sometimes it just one
look
is like some timely don't do that okay
your teammates certainly cherish what
you have contributed
to the team your inspiration your
leadership and you even
you worked like be a second coach would
follow the team
but then what have they part you
with they brought to your life Dave
Dave determine one beans yeah brother
those are my brother
brother together been together 6 with
them water
there with each other more
with them could lead to more than lunch
with a totality how my day some
mobley simple concluding on the net
Teddy mom
simple funds says union to protect
which uses Union time sorting the ending
in Jan
comedy and on that the until the coaches
can handle the hands of
to redline she'd run quite an amendment
21 PTI Mar 20 to lead a million donde
treatment will fight the whole time I'm
he met
happened LG judge insult one online %um
due to poor cool they told me to meet in
Italy
Martin abating obviously is another
metropolitan city that
his law similar to the life of New York
with the best part of the city that you
love energy
I mean this is his SS as a square box
in energy is
is amazing the people warming having
this opportunity in to share with people
who
I chance in amazement as something that
just happened
in new thing tears or
tears from people into staying
when I watch the video I just start
crying I'm like oh my god I can't
believe that
like derailing I mean just crying porn
out is people trying to hold back the
tears
like in amazement hope currently in
Phase cover in their face
seen at I'm
this is just amazing is so beautiful
like to witness the to witness people
feel nicer way about something that we
did
as a group there's something
for the city made the same proud me the
city happy
made them feel like you gave you made as
well
so it's not just about victory is not
even just about improving yourself that
you could do it
but it's also sensor sharing with no so
many we're told me
connections with people or a chorus
meaning being able to share the
connection
in love passionate will be put forth
to do something Foreign Affairs
is this incredibly not on 1g
the end of subtlety Tim temple Dr feel
I issue plunging mob unusual team mama
the
she agreed to hire a million helpful TT
shuttle back
yeah I don't mobley million by
Beatty
jerry can holder
she even hellish that
each Saluja to 4gb ends with the
Nationals
11 fun teaching me total porosity
Lee eat a dick them
line
deet Tim Donaghy was salty
City G-seventeen cuddle with a pic
to me Beijing touch it or so teachings
until someone could wardrobe
usual banya descending we done
tell 1892 times I seventy poignant with
ET Now
hartal shitty typical be to senior
should called see classes
Rd Union call me
that are you cool time daddy man army
from the initial
we went with the colors certainly water
passing the tires
did the comp to happened to you with
tonya
City you're going to need to fear pussy
to eat and eighty million that should be
fun
a union toward a party team paid 220 to
the city
lady Chitty our team city
team Shinya young man fun handle told
you do see eat beans
from medium eat with her to tell waiting
in junctional
you good
part
for the CBA to internet that'll plunge
into home made with the Meiji
you can identify him up with a title
ESPN
million huge implications municipal
labeled munchy
model company London the mall beneath
our feet into when this Indian
Italian sandwich and CC for the seeker
one soccer team
to clean my life hell and I started to
gain and pings
life when I came China my life begin to
change in Astana
the different and I started to move
different when I got when I will go back
home people
I don't know just different right wing
and
how are you doing pages like engines
marquardt I've lost the emotional
feeling
anything for sentencing
is in like a miracle i coming all the
way
to the other end of the earth to
when he is find yourself again in this
like Odyssey isn't it
is someone may self-discovery yes so
head
when I think about it i jus ads I may
not
acid back sometimes nazis these this
last week has been the business
down my life a little when I have my
chosen
I we cover my friend and I you never
stop us now in yet
yesterday Alyssa Alyssa late 19th her
know I'm like oh my job but I was
barrister my cell like Hazara
can I haven't felt like this I never
felt like this before
into bill is the lead is amazing I'm you
I keep his I keep my middle hang a right
on my light
I me and I sleep one engine today
I'm being my head to hear the matter I
was like are made
and I looked out as well okay the heavy
stuff s
what combativeness contrast of twenty
million dollars
and seven hundred thousand dollars that
you're earning now
it's not even about the wine my mother
told me she's as tough on you can have
all the money in the world
but I'm you a happy means Lapan
one can buy happiness can't buy
happiness
came by lower in love that our learn
that I have received from
this country is beyond belief
I can't even explain it mean I remember
I will never got the love that I have
been it
i doin CBA that it hoped you'd like to
the ocean and now under
reach and whether the issue 1 July shot
to shot on goal kicking the pgm
people here show up before the alarm on
me solution me
i doing out the National Jewish Health
said hi for Google
I told him don't tell a dude ranch only
trends we did you achieve
I'm watching a deal GD NT News Hindi
Julie
it thanks for joining laxatives me
welcome to the other
should have a chilling John Daly John
they added didn't have a teacher's house
was in a gym on
love Islam I Joshi as usual come into
the Alabama
kinda am
it