HEY THERE, STRANGER. I MISSED YOU.
LOOKS LIKE YOU MAY HAVE MISSED A SPOT.
YOU'RE NAKED.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHERE ARE YOUR CLOTHES?
UM, WELL,FIRST STEP IN SHOWERING
IS USUALLY TAKING THEM OFF,   WEIRDO.
NOW WHERE WAS I?
(grunts) YOU KNOW, I CAN'T
DO THIS WITHOUT MY COFFEE.
-OKAY, WHY ARE YOU COVERING YOUR EYES?
-I'M NOT.
ARE YOU JOKING?
YOU'RE NOT JOKING.
I JUST... I GOTTA...
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'VE BARELY SEEN YOU THIS WEEK.
YOU WORK LATE EVERY NIGHT.
OKAY, WE DON'T EVEN HAVE TO TALK
ABOUT OUR ENGAGEMENT PARTY.
ENGAGEMENT PARTY?
YEAH, WITH EVERYTHING  GOING ON AT WORK,
YOU'D THINK YOU COULD
HELP ME OUT FOR FIVE MINUTES.
JEEZ, SCOTT, I-I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU LATELY.
YOU WERE HER FIANC?
KIND OF A "QUANTUM LEAPER,"  HUH?
DID YOU HEAR WHAT I SAID? WE WERE NAKED.
I-I HAD TO LOOK AWAY  SO I DIDN'T, UH...
WELL, I MAY HAVE GLANCED.
I AM HUMAN.
BUT WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
IN GREEK MYTHOLOGY,
GODS OFTEN DISGUISE THEMSELVES
AS MORTALS SO THEY COULD SPY   ON THEIR SUBJECTS
AND TEST THEIR LOYALTIES.
WELL, NOT THAT I MIND
BEING COMPARED TO ZEUS,
BUT I DON'T NEED TO SPY ON MAGGIE
TO KNOW HER LOYALTIES.
ZEUS PLAYED THESE GAMES
WITH WOMEN FOR WHOM
HE HAD SPECIAL AFFECTION.
OH, DON'T START.
WHATEVER HAPPENED LAST YEAR
WITH ME AND MAGGIE,
WHICH WAS NOTHING,    BY THE WAY,
IS OVER, DONE WITH AND FORGOTTEN, OKAY?
ANY AFFECTION I HAVE FOR HER   IS PURELY PROFESSIONAL.
WELL, MAYBE IT HAS SOMETHING
TO DO WITH A CASE.
IF YOU HAVEN'T NOTICED,    THESE VISIONS USUALLY DO.
IT HAS TO DO WITH HER.
THIS IS TWO MAGGIE VISIONS IN A ROW.
LAST WEEK SHE'S AT THE SUPREME COURT
WITH--WITH POSNER & KLEIN
AND THIS WEEK SHE'S IN THE SHOWER WITH ME.
MAYBE POSNER MADE HER
AN OFFER AT HIS FIRM.
WELL, IF GOD IS  SENDING YOU VISIONS
ABOUT WHETHER OR NOT    MAGGIE IS CHANGING FIRMS,
WHICH, YOU KNOW,  GIVEN HIS BUSY SCHEDULE
AND SEEMINGLY MORE PRESSING  PRIORITIES, I HIGHLY DOUBT,
ONE THING WE'VE LEARNED IS
YOUR VISIONS OF THE FUTURE CAN BE ALTERED.
YOU CAN CHANGE DESTINY. DON'T LET HER GO.
IT'S A COMMON MISUNDERSTANDING
THAT A PUBLIC INTEREST FIRM
CAN'T BE PROFITABLE, BUT I ASSURE YOU
WE WILL SUCCEED.
AND THE BENEFITS?
THE FIRM'S TAHOE SKI RETREAT
WILL BE MADE AVAILABLE
TO SUCCESSFUL ATTORNEYS.
CLIENTS YOU CARE  PASSIONATELY ABOUT.
BLUE-CHIP CLIENTS OPERATING AT THE FOREFRONT OF GLOBAL COMMERCE.
OUR MISSION WILL BE TO USE THE LAW
AS THE HIGHEST FORM  OF SOCIAL ACTIVISM.
A DIFFERENT GUEST CHEF WILL BE
FLOWN IN EVERY MONDAY.
WHAT YOU GIVE UP
IN SIMPLE DOLLARS AND CENTS
YOU WILL MORE THAN MAKE UP   IN QUALITY OF LIFE.
THIS IS GOING TO BE
THE SINGLE LEAST SUSPENSEFUL  MEETING OF MY DAY.
ACTUALLY, I HAVEN'T MADE UP MY MIND YET, SIR.
REALLY?
BECAUSE MARCI AND I   WOULD LIKE YOU TO CONSIDER
JOINING OUR FIRM   AS A FULL PARTNER.
CAN YOU BELIEVE    HOW EASILY PEOPLE ARE BOUGHT?
THE EXODUS HAS BEGUN.
ONLY THE MORALLY BANKRUPT
AND WEAK-MINDED.
NO ONE LIKED   YOUR WIFE'S BANANA BREAD.
WE ONLY ATE IT TO BE POLITE!
HOW ARE THE ASSISTANTS
AND THE JUNIOR STAFF HOLDING UP?
NONE OF MY ROOSTERS ARE GONNA FLY THIS COOP.
YOU'RE THE BEST, PATTI.
I ASSUME THAT WILL BE REFLECTED
IN MY CHRISTMAS BONUS?
HEY.
GOOD TO SEE YOU...
CLOTHED... NICELY.
HOW ARE YOU?
HORRIBLE.
LOOK, I KNOW THE FIRM'S SPLIT
HAS LEFT SOME PEOPLE
WITH SOME VERY STRESSFUL DECISIONS.
YOU'RE TELLING ME.
SO POSNER DID MAKE YOU AN OFFER.
HE DIDN'T EVEN ASK FOR A MEETING.
-OH, THAT'S GREAT.
-GREAT?
HE'S MET TH EVERY SINGLE OTHER ASSOCIATE HERE.
MY ENGAGEMENT PARTY'S FRIDAY, ELI.
THE TIMING OF ALL THIS COULDN'T BE WORSE.
LITERALLY HALF MY GUEST LIST CALLED
IN THE LAST FEW HOURS  TO CANCEL.
GUESS THEY FEEL AWKWARD
ABOUT DOING THE MACARENA
WITH SOON-TO-BE EX-COWORKERS.
I DON'T KNOW WHICH TERRIFIES ME MORE--
THE FACT THAT WE'LL BE DOING
THE MACARENA AT YOUR PARTY
OR THAT YOUR GUESTS ARE
ALL PEOPLE WHO WORK HERE.
WELL, LET'S FACE IT.  I WORK 80 HOURS A WEEK.
MY LIFE IS SCOTT AND YOU...
THIS FIRM.
WELL, THIS PLACE IS--
WELL, WAS--MY FAMILY.
AND WE STILL WILL BE, ONLY SMALLER.
YOU CAN'T LEAVE, MAGGIE.
WHY WOULD YOU EVER THINK I WOULD?
POSNER IS LIKE   DARTH SIDIOUS.
WELL, THEN BEWARE THE DARK SIDE.
MISS DEKKER?
MR. POSNER WOULD LIKE TO SEE YOU.
THANKS.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
THAT I COULD CONVINCE MATT
NOT TO LEAVE OR THAT I WOULD WANT TO?
HE JUST NEEDS A GENTLE PUSH.
WELL, HE'S YOUR BOYFRIEND, TAYLOR.
DID YOU TRY  THE RED NIGHTIE THING?
THAT CERTAINLY   CONVINCED ME TO, UH...
THAT'S INAPPROPRIATE. NOTED.
JUST PUT HIM ON A CASE  WITH YOU, YOU KNOW?
SHOW HIM ALL THE GREAT THINGS
ABOUT PUBLIC INTEREST LAW,
HOW AMAZING IT FEELS TO REALLY HELP PEOPLE.
SHOW HIM SOME OF THAT STONE MAGIC.
THIS IS MATT DOWD.
YOU DON'T EVEN BELIEVE IN THE STONE MAGIC.
PLEASE, ELI?
I NEED THIS.
HE'S GONNA SEE   RIGHT THROUGH ME.
YOU NEED ME?
FOR WHAT?
MY ANALYTICAL MIND?
MY INNATE  COMMAND OF CIVIL PROCEDURE?
-OH, MY DEFT--
- YOU HAVE AN EDGE.
SOME MAY CALL IT OBNOXIOUS,
BUT THAT ADVERSARIAL EDGE
IN COURT CAN SOMETIMES--
OH, SHUT UP, STONE.
I KNOW TAYLOR PUT YOU UP TO THIS.
YOU CAN'T LET HER KNOW I TOLD YOU.
YOU DIDN'T.
YOU'RE AS TRANSPARENT  AS WINDOWPANE.
THEY'VE OFFERED ME PARTNER.
I'VE MADE UP MY MIND.
I JUST DON'T KNOW HOW TO TELL HER.
IS THERE A GOOD WAY
TO TELL YOUR GIRLFRIEND THAT
YOU'RE GONNA WORK FOR THE PEOPLE
WHO POLEAXED HER FATHER?
PROBABLY NOT, NO.
SO DON'T SAY YES YET.
YOU OWE HER TO AT LEAST
PRETEND TO MULL IT OVER.
BESIDES, YOU KNOW, YOU MAKE
POSNER & KLEIN SWEAT OVER THIS FOR A WEEK,
THEY'LL PROBABLY   RAISE YOUR OFFER.
WELL, I DO WANT A CORNER OFFICE.
ME--SENIOR ASSOCIATE?
IN CHARGE OF YOUR PRO BONO DEPARTMENT?
AT DOUBLE YOUR CURRENT SALARY.
COME ON.
I NEVER KID ABOUT MONEY
OR ABOUT FOUR WEEKS   PAID VACATION TIME
TO DO SOME   OF YOUR SPECIAL PROJECTS--
MOTHER TERESA'S NEXT JUNKET.
I THINK MOTHER TERESA'S DEAD, SIR.
WELL, THEN SOMEONE ELSE  ALIVE AND WELL
AND WHINING  ABOUT THE RAIN FOREST.
BUT I THOUGHT YOU AND MS. KLEIN
DON'T EVEN LIKE PRO BONO WORK.
DON'T LET MY DISDAIN  R ALL THINGS TIE-DYED FOOL YOU, MS. DEKKER.
EVEN I UNDERSTAND THAT
MAKING MONEY AND DOING GOOD
ARE NOT MUTUALLY EXCLUSIVE.    IT'S GOOD P.R.,
AND THERE'S ALSO THIS.
$20,000 TO THE ECO PRESERVATION LEAGUE?
A GESTURE OF GOODWILL
TO SHOW YOU HOW SERIOUS  I AM ABOUT THIS.
JUST CONSIDER IT   AN EARLY ENGAGEMENT GIFT.
ALL I ASK IS YOU TAKE A FEW DAYS.
JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:FRM@ÏÄ·ç
Sync:FRS@Ç³
elis 204
PATTI,
YOU KNOW THAT BOX   YOU'VE BEEN KEEPING FOR ME
WITH ALL THE FAXES AND LETTERS
FROM POTENTIAL CLIENTS?
YOU MEAN THE WACKADOO FILE?
I MEAN THE BOX   WITH ALL THE FASCINATING,
COMPLEX LEGAL DILEMMAS
THAT COULD ONE DAY
END UP IN THE SUPREME COURT.
WELL, WHAT I HAVE IS A BOX FULL OF CASES
FROM THE NUT BALLS
THAT SAW YOU ON THE NEWS--
THE WACKADOO FILE.
COULD I JUST HAVE IT?
HERE'S ONE,
AND I HAVE
THREE MORE IN THE SUPPLY CLOSET.
NOW...
SOME OF THESE CASES
ARE QUITE SIGNIFICANT.
IT'S ALL ABOUT FINDING   THE DIAMOND IN THE ROUGH.
SNOOZE.
THE ENVIRONMENT MAKES YOU  WANT TO NAP. I GOT IT.
WELL, HERE'S A FIRST AMENDMENT ISSUE.
MAN WANTS TO SUE HIS LANDLORD
FOR CLEARING OUT MOLD
WHICH LOOKS LIKE JESUS.
JESUS MOLD... PASS.
OH, WE MAY HAVE SOMETHING HERE--
TWIN SISTER FLIGHT ATTENDANTS.
SEE,   NOW THIS SOUNDS PROMISING.
THEY WANT TO SUE THE AIRLINE   THAT FIRED THEM
WHEN THEY TURNED 60.
PATTI!
CAN WE GET ANOTHER BOX IN HERE?
YOU SURE YOU WOULDN'T
RATHER SEE A LIVING CLIENT?
THIS IS HOW MY CASES  USUALLY COME IN.
MR. STONE?
-YEAH.
-HEY, I'M WILL SONNEBORN.
HI. UM, THIS IS MY ASSOCIATE,  MATT DOWD.
WHAT CAN WE DO FOR YOU?
I NEED YOU TO HELP MY GIRLFRIEND.
HOMELAND SECURITY ARRESTED HER
AND HER HUSBAND YESTERDAY.
I REALIZE    THESE ARE CONFUSING TIMES.
POSNER'S PROBABLY  MAKING SOME OF YOU OFFERS--
SUBSTANTIAL OFFERS.
BUT AS THE ASSISTANT
WHO'S BEEN HERE THE LONGEST,
I WANT TO REMIND YOU
THAT JORDAN AND ELI CARE
FOR EACH AND EVERY ONE OF YOU.
THEN WHY IS IT THE FIRST THING THEY DID
WAS FREEZE  NEXT YEAR'S WAGE INCREASES?
THAT'S A LOT TO DEAL WITH
IN THIS ECONOMY.
JORDAN'S VISION   FOR THIS FIRM IS REAL.
HE AND ELI WANT TO CHANGE THINGS
TO MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
NO OFFENSE, PATTI,
BUT ELI'S A LITTLE ECCENTRIC.
ELI MAY BE... UNORTHODOX,
BUT I'VE SEEN WHAT HE CAN DO,
AND BELIEVE ME WHEN I TELL YOU
IT'S MEANINGL,  IT'S INSPIRATIONAL.
THIS NEW FIRM  WILL BE A PLACE
THAT WE CAN BE PROUD   TO COME TO EVERY DAY.
HOW OFTEN DOES THAT HAPPEN?
GET THEM TO LIFT THE WAGE FREEZE
AND WE'LL THINK ABOUT IT.
YEAH.
GREAT.
I'LL TALK TO ELI, WORK  SOMETHING OUT FOR ALL OF US.
COULD YOU  EXPLAIN THAT AGAIN?
WILL IS MY BOYFRIEND.
HE GIVES HER SEX, BUT I GIVE HER EMOTIONAL SUPPORT
AND SOMEONE TO WATCH "PROJECT RUNWAY" WITH.
CARTER, CAN YOU PLEASE   BE SERIOUS? HE'S KIDDING.
SO WHO IS HE TO YOU?
CARTER IS MY BEST FRIEND,    ALSO MY--
GAY GREEN CARD HUSBAND.
OH, THAT CLEARS IT RIGHT UP.
SANA AND CARTER WERE IN
THE SAME PUBLIC HEALTH PROGRAM  AT BERKELEY.
AND WE'VE BEEN B.F.F.s  EVER SINCE.
HOW DID I.C.E. GET INVOLVED?
WHEN MY STUDENT VISA RAN OUT.
I WAS SUPPOSED TO RETURN   TO PAKISTAN,
BUT WILL AND I    WERE JUST GETTING
TO REALLY KNOW ONE ANOTHER.
WE WERE FALLING IN LOVE
I COULDN'T JUST LEAVE.
I HAD NALLY FOUND HAPPINESs
I TRIED TO EXTEND MY STUDENT
VISA,
GET A WORK VISA.
NOTHING WORKED.
I MARRIED HER
SO SHE COULD
STAY HERE AND FALL IN LOVE.
WHY DIDN'T YOU   JUST MARRY WILL?
I WOULD HAVE. I WANTED TO.
IT WAS TOO EARLY IN OUR RELATIONSHIP.
I DIDN'T FEEL COMFORTABLE
ASKING HIM TO DO THAT.
HOW DID HOMELAND SECURITY
REALIZE THAT THE MARRIAGE   WAS A FRAUD?
I HAD AN UGLY BREAKUP  WITH THIS JACKASS
WHO KNEW THE WHOLE STORY.
MY REMOVAL HEARING  IS THIS WEEK.
AFTER WHICH YOU FACE
UP TO FIVE YEARS IN PRISON.
YOU HAVE TO HELP THEM.
THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO.
YOU COMMITTED FRAUD,
AND IN POST-9/11 AMERICA, THAT
MEANS YOU'RE GOING TO PRISON,
AND YOU'RE GOING BACK TO PAKISTAN.
THAT CAN'T HAPPEN.
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE.
TELL 'EM, SANA.
UH, SHE WAS SUPPOSED TO RETURN
HOME TO AN ARRANGED MARRIAGE.
BUT I COULDN'T   GO THROUGH WITH IT,
NOT AFTER I MET WILL..
NOT AFTER I KNEW REAL LOVE.
IF SHE GOES BACK TO PAKISTAN,
HER FAMILY WILL KILL HER.
LET'S GET A MOVE ON,  MACARONI.
THOSE CATERERS ARE NOT
GONNA WAIT AROUND FOREVER,
AND WE ALREADY  RESCHEDULED TWICE.
I'M COMING.
HEY!
LOOKIN' FORWARD TO   THE FESTIVITIES TOMORROW.
I'M GLAD YOU GUYS CAN BE THERE.
THERE'S A LOT TO CELEBRATE.
BESIDES YOUR ENGAGEMENT, YOU MEAN?
WELL, MAGGIE GOT A VERY INTERESTING OFFER TODAY.
SCOTT.
HEY, COULD I HAVE A WORD WITH
YOU FOR A SECOND IN PRIVATE?
YEAH.
WHAT'S HE TALKING ABOUT?
DID POSNER MAKE YOU AN OFFER?
WELL, HE... HE GAVE ME A REALLY HARD SELL.
SO YOU TOLD HIM NO.
I-I DIDN'T WANT TO BE RUDE.
I TOLD HIM I'D... I'D THINK    ABOUT IT FOR A FEW DAYS.
WHAT DID HE OFFER?
ENIOR ASSOCIATE IN CHARGE
F THEIR PRO BONO DEPARTMENT
WITH LOTS OF SUPPORT FOR
THE ENVIRONMENT AND STUFF.
HOW MUCH IS HE GONNA PAY?
-TWICE MY CURRENT SALARY.
-WE'LL MATCH IT.
HOW CAN YOU?
I'M NOW A PARTNER AT THIS FIRM,
AND IT'S WHAT YOU DESERVE.
TRUST ME, I'M GONNATAKE CARE OF THIS, MAGGIE
NO WONDER MARTIN POSNER
WAS ALWAYS SO PRICKLY
HANDLING W.P.K.'s FINANCES.
IT WAS A HUGE TASK
WHEN WE HAD REVENUE.
MAYBE WE SHOULD CONSIDER PUTTING
THE BUILDING ON THE MARKET,
DOWNSIZING.
WHAT KIND OF STATEMENT WOULD THAT MAKE?
-DAD--
- SWEETIE, PLEASE STOP TAKING   THE STRESS ON YOURSELF.
I'M FINE.
I'M JUST NOT SLEEPING.
OR HUNGRY. THERE'S JUST A LOT
OF LIFE CHANGES AHEAD, YOU KNOW?
YES, I HAVE A FEELING  I DO KNOW.
HONEY,IF THERE'S EVER ANYTHING
YOU'D LIKE TO TALK TO ME ABOUT...
MAGGIE DEKKER JUST RECEIVED
AN OFFER FROM POSNER & KLEIN--
A SUBSTANTIAL ONE.  WE HAVE TO MATCH IT.
ELI, WE CAN'T AFFORD TO.  AND BESIDES,
MAGGIE'S THE LAST PERSON
WHO'S GONNA GO WORK FOR THEM.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.SHE'LL LEAVE. I KNOW IT.
ELI, I UNDERSTD YOU HAVE  A SPECIAL AFFECTION FOR MS. DEKKER.
WHY DOES EVERYBODY   KEEP SAYING THAT
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
SHE'S A FRIEND,  A PLATONIC ONE.
SHE BELIEVED IN ME
BEFORE ANYONE ELSE DID.
I REALIZE THAT,
BUT WE HAVEN'T  MATCHED POSNER'S SALARY OFFER
FOR ANY OTHER ASSOCIATE.
WELL, IF WE WANT  TO KEEP THEM--
YOU'RE A PARTNER NOW, ELI.
YOU'VE GOT TO START THINKING    LIKE ONE,
WHICH MEANS NOT ALLOWING SENTIMENT
TO CLOUD YOUR JUDGMENT.
IT MEANS WORRYING ABOUT HOW WE
FUND OUR QUARTERLY CONTRIBUTIONS
TO THE ASSOCIATES' HEALTH INSURANCE PLAN,
HOW WE KEEP OUR OFFICES LIT
AND WARM THIS WINTER
AMIDST SKYROCKETING  ELECTRIC BILLS.
BUT IF YOU TRULY THINK MAGGIE'S
PRESENCE AT OUR FIRM JUSTIFIES
TREATING HER DIFFERENTLY
¢TTHAN ALL THE OTHER ASSOCIATES
AND PLACING OUR OBLIGATIONS
TO THEM AT GREATER RISK,
IT'S YOUR CALL.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE TAKING THE DAY OFF
TO, UH, PREPARE FOR YOUR ENGAGEMENT PARTY.
OH, JUST STOPPED BY  TO PICK UP A FEW THINGS
BEFORE THE PARENTS ARRIVE.
LOOK, I SPOKE TO JORDAN,
AND THE THING IS,
WE'RE LOSING NEARLY ALL
OUR REVENUE-STREAMING CLIENTS.
AND I TRIED TO FIGURE OUT
A WAY AS BEST I COULD
TO MATCH POSNER'S OFFER, BUT--
ELI, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
-IT DOESN'T?
-  THIS FIRM CHANGED MY LIFE.
AND YOU--WELL, THE FIRM--
MADE ME SEE FOR THE FIRST TIME
I COULD MAKE A TRUE DIFFERENCE.
I COULD NEVER LEAVE.
I CAN'T TELL YOU HOW HAPPY  I AM TO HEAR THAT.
STONE, WE'RE LATE FOR COURT.
LISTEN, DEKKER,UH, THIS, UH, PARTY OF YOURS--
IS THAT MORE LIKE A GIFT THING,
OR IS A WEDDING PRESENT ENOUGH?
IT'S A DIFFERENT WORLD OVER THERE.
IN PAKISTAN, I AM CONSIDERED MY FATHER'S PROPERTY.
HIS HONOR IS DEFINED BY MY PURITY.
BY ENTERING INTO A SEXUAL
RELATIONSHIP WITH A MAN
OTHER THAN THE ONE CHOSEN FOR YOU...
I BECAME KARI--
AN IMPURE WOMAN.
AND WHAT IS THE PUNISHMENT
FOR BECOMING KARI?
THE ONLY WAY FOR MY FATHER TO RESTORE HIS HONOR
IS TO KILL THE ONE WHO DAMAGED IT--ME--
PREFERABLY PUBLICLY,  SO ALL CAN WITNESS
HIS HONOR BEING RESTORED.
OBJECTION--WHAT HAPPENS
TO CERTAIN WOMEN IN PAKISTAN
IS HORRIBLE, OF COURSE,
BUT IT'S NOT AT ISSUE HERE
UH, IT IS WHEN YOU'RE TRYING TO SEND HER BACK TO PAKISTAN.
I AGREE.   OBJECTION OVERRULED.
MISS BOOKER SEEMED   TO IMPLY JUST NOW
THAT HONOR KILLINGS  ARE RARE IN PAKISTAN.
HUNDREDS OF GIRLS ARE MURDERED EACH YEAR.
MY FRIEND WAS BURNED BECAUSE  SHE KISSED THE WRONG BOY.
HER BODY LAY IN THE STREET FOR TWO HOURS.
NO ONE DID ANYTHING.
THANK YOU, SANA.
NOTHING FURTHER.
I GUESS YOU'RE UNAWARE THAT
HONOR KILLINGS IN PAKISTAN
HAVE BEEN OUTLAWED
FOR THREE YEARS NOW.
ONE LAW CANNOT CHANGE  ANCIENT CUSTOMS.
AND EVEN IF IT COULD, THE LAW MUST STILL BE ENFORCED.
BUT ALL THE PROSECUTORS ARE MEN.
ALL THE JUDGES ARE MEN.
NOT EVERY PAKISTANI GIRL
WHO DISOBEYS HER FATHER
IS MURDERED, AM I CORRECT?
THERE ARE LUCKY ONES.
BUT SOME FATHERS ARE MORE
CONTROLLING, LIKE MY FATHER.
YOUR FATHER ALLOWED YOU
TO COME HERE AND STUDY.
THAT DOESN'T SOUND PARTICULARLY CONTROLLING.
-HAS HE EVER LAID A HAND AGAINST YOU?
-NO
-THREATENED YOU?
-NO.
BUT YET YOU THINK HE WOULD KILL YOU
IF YOU RETURN TO YOUR COUNTRY.
DO YOU HAVE ANY PROOF?
NO, I... I DON'T.
SO WE ARE TO JUST TAKE YOUR WORD--
THE WORD OF A WOMAN WHO STOOD IN FRONT OF ANOTHER JUDGE
AND PROMISED  TO LOVE, HONOR AND CHERISH
TILL DEATH DO YOU PART
A GAY MAN?
OBJECTION.
NOTHING FURTHER.
YOU REALIZE THIS   COULD ALL BE BULL, RIGHT?
LIKE "BECOME A U.S. CITIZEN FOR DUMMIES"--
WHEN MARRYING  YOUR GAY BEST FRIEND FAILS,
CRY HONOR KILLING.
GEE, MATT, CYNICAL MUCH?
I'M JUST SAYING CLIENTS LIE, EVEN YOUR CLIENTS.
GOOD NEWS.
11 LEGAL SECRETARIES, 6 PARALEGALS
AND FIVE CLERKS--THEY ALL SIGNED TO STAY ON WITH US.
THAT'S NEARLY EVERYONE.
NOW ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS CONVINCE JORDAN TO UNFREEZE
THEIR RAISES FOR THE NEXT YEAR.
IT'S AMAZING THAT YOU   CONVINCED THEM, BUT AS OF NOW
THERE ARE TEN AND A HALF
ACTUAL LAWYERS STAYING.
SO HOW CAN I JUSTIFY  KEEPING 22 STAFF
WITH OR WITHOUT RAISES?
CAN YOU JUSTIFY LETTING THEM GO?
THE FIRM IS SPLITTING IN TWO.
WHICH IS WHAT I MIGHT DO
TO YOU IN A FEW SECONDS.
I PUT MY ASS ON THE LINE.
IF YOU DON'T COME UP WITH THAT MONEY,
WE'RE GONNA LOSE EVERY ASSISTANT, EVERY PARALEGAL--
PEOPLE WHO BELIEVE
IN THIS PLACE WILL STAY.
THIS IS THE REAL WORLD.
PEOPLE HAVE OBLIGATIONS.
I REALIZE THAT,
BUT MY HANDS ARE TIED.
YOUR HANDS ARE TIED?
LISTEN TO YOUELF.
YOU SOUND LIKE POSNER.
IS THAT THE KIND OF BOSS YOU WANNA BE?
IF SO, MAYBE THEY ALL SHOULD LEAVE.
PATTI, COME ON. I'M TRYING.
DON'T "COME ON" ME!
I AM GOING TO TAKE A RIDICULOUSLY LONG LUNCH.
YOU CAN ANSWER YOUR OWN
DAMN PHONES.
GOODNESS GRACIOUS.
WHAT MY COUSIN DID IS UNFORGIVABLE.
I SHOULD NOT EVEN BE HERE.
THEN WHY ARE YOU?
SANA TOLD US  THAT YOU TWO WERE VERY CLOSE
WHEN SHE FIRST ARRIVED HERE,
AND THEN ONE DAY YOU JUST
STOPPED RETURNING HER CALLS.
WHY?
I LOVE SANA, OKAY?
BUT I COULD NOT WATCH HER
BECOME A WESTERN WOMAN.
YOU'RE WEARING J. CREW AND NIKE.
DOESN'T SEEM LIKE YOU HAVE MUCH
PROBLEM WITH WESTERNIZATION.
MY FAMILY EXPECTED ME TO LOOK OUT FOR HER.
AND YOU GOT TIRED  OF BEING A SPY.
LOOK, THIS IS THE WAY IT'S BEEN FOR CENTURIES.
SANA'S FATHER WAS DISGCED.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOPAINFUL IT IS FOR A MAN TO LOSE HIS HONOR?
WELL, MAYBE THERE'S A WAY THAT,    UH, YOU COULD HELP
WITHOUT ANYONE KNOWING.
MAYBE THERE'S A LETTER
OR AN E-MAIL
FROM SANA'S FATHER INTIMATING
HIS PLAN TO HARM HER.
YOU'RE ASKING ME  TO SACRIFICE MY HONOR.
LOOK, I UNDERSTAND THAT
SOME PEOPLE ARE VERY STRICT
ABOUT THEIR CUSTOMS,
BUT YOU'VE LIVED HERE  LONG ENOUGH
TO SEE THINGS A DIFFERENT WAY.
CAN YOU TELL ME  THAT YOU STILL BELIEVE THAT
BECAUSE A WOMAN  LOOKS AT A MAN THE WRONG WAY
OR REFUSES TO MARRY SOMEONE  CHOSEN BY HER FATHER
THAT SHE SHOULD BE KILLED?
YOU HONESTLY BELIEVE THAT
BECAUSE YOUR COUSIN IS A WOMAN
THAT SHE SHOULDN'T BE ALLOWED
TO DECIDE FOR HERSELF   WHO E LOVES OR MARRIES?
SHE'S LIVING HER OWN LIFE
IN THIS COUNTRY JUST LIKE YOU.
SHOULD SHE HAVE TO DIE
BECAUSE OF THAT?
AND CAN YOU JUST  STAND BY AND WATCH?
SO WHAT ABOUT YOUR... HONOR?
OKAY, I'LL ADMIT IT.
I DIDN'T THINK YOU'D TURN HIM.
HOW'S IT FEEL WORKING ON A CASE
YOU'RE ACTUALLY INVESTED IN?
DON'T GET AHEAD OF YOURSELF.
I'M STILL VERY INVESTED
IN KEEPING UP MY MEMBERSHIP    AT PEBBLE BEACH.
ADMIT IT, DOWD. YOU'RE HOOKED.
OH, COME ON. AGAIN?!
SCOTT?
WHAT IS IT  WITH THESE TWO AND THE SHOWER?
ARE YOU COMING IN HERE?
I'M ALL LATHERED UP.
NO, I'M JUST GONNA G   UH..:
TO THE BEDROOM    AND--AND--AND GET DRESSED
WITH THE DOOR CLOSED AND LOCKED, MAG...
..NIFICENT WOMAN   WHO IS NOT MAGGIE.
COME ON.
WE DON'T HAVE THAT MUCH TIME
BEFORE YOU'RE A MARRIED MAN.
WE NEED TO TAKE ADVANTAGE.
WE KNOW EACH OTHER...
INTIMATELY?
OH, GOD. YOU'RE FREAKING OUT AGAIN.
ARE YOU GONNA END THINGS AGAIN?
SHOCKER.
WHAT IS THAT, THE FOURTH TIME THIS MONTH?
SORRY, NO TIME TODAY.
GET YOUR BT IN HERE.
?
?THERE--
SANA'S FATHER ASKING AMIR TO JOIN HIS COUSINS
IN DEFENDING HIS HONOR.
AND WE ALL KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
IT'S VAGUE AT BEST, HEARSAY,
AND THERE'S NO WAY TO
AUTHENTICATE THAT THIS LETTER ACTUALLY CAME FROM SANA'S FATHER.
IT'S A DEATH SENTENCE,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
YOUR CLIENT BROKE THE LAW, AND DESPITE THIS LETTER,
I AM OBLIGATED
TO HAVE HER REMOVED.
WERE YOU BORN WITHOUT THE COMPASSION GENE OR SOMETHING?
HOMELAND SECURITY DOESN'T PAY ME FOR MY COMPASSION.
THEN WE'LL TAKE THE LETTER TO JUDGE KETTLEMAN.
I THINK HE'LL BE INCLINED TO SAVE HER LIFE.
HMM. SEE, I THINK HE'LL BE
NCLINED TO ENFORCE THE LAW,
HIM BEING A JUDGE AND ALL.
WHICH IS WHY HE WILL NOT SEND A YOUNG WOMAN
TO HER OWN LYNCHING.
I AM WILLING TO CUT YOUR CLIENT A DEAL.
BUT IT IS THE ONLY DEAL I'LL PUT ON THE TABLE.
IT'S INSIDIOUS.
WE'RE OBLIGATED TO PRESENT IT,
BUT THE OFFER SUCKS.
IF I GO BACK TO PAKISTAN,
THEY'LL HAVE ALL CHARGES
aGAINST CARTER DROPPED?
-I'M JUST AS GUILTY AS SHE IS.
-YOU'RE AN AMERICAN.
BOOKER'S A BUREAUCRATIC HACK.
IF SANA ACCEPTS,
SHE CAN TELL HER BOSS
SHE SENT ANOTHER ONE BACK.
IT'S ANOTHER VICTORY FOR NATIONAL SECURITY.
WELL, DON'T WORRY. SHE WON'T ACCEPT.
WHAT WILL BOOKER DO IF I DON'T?
THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
THEY'LL PRESS FORWARD WITH THEIR
CASES AGAINST YOU AND CARTER.
BUT, SANA, WE CAN WIN THIS.
YOU CANNOT TAKE THIS OFFER.
I'VE ALREADY GOTTEN YOU
IN SO MUCH TROUBLE.
I CAN'T LIVE WITH THE CHANCE
YOU'LL GO TO JAIL.
OH, YES, YOU CAN.
I DIDN'T SPEND THE LAST TWO YEARS EXPLAINING
TO EVERY SINGLE DATE I BROUGHT HOME
WHY THERE WERE BRAS HANGING IN
THE BATHROOM SO YOU COULD BAIL.
I LOVE YOU.
I DID THIS TO SAVE YOUR LIFE.
AND NOW I WANT TO SAVE YOURS.
YOU CAN'T GO BACK THERE.
I SEE NO OTHER CHOICE.
I'M TAKING THE DEAL.
POOR MAGGIE.
NO ONE IS HERE.
MATT?
SORRY.
YOU'RE BARELY EVEN HERE TONIGHT.
IS IT THE CASE?
I JUST CAN'T STOP THINKING,
WISHING THERE WAS SOME WAY
I COULD STOP SANA FROM TAKING THIS DEAL.
I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU GET
THIS UPSET OVER WORK BEFORE.
NOT SURE I'VE BEEN THIS UPSET BEFORE.
I'M SORRY.
IT IS NICE TO SEE YOU CARING
SO MUCH ABOUT A CLIENT, THOUGH.
WHAT?
SUBTLENESS ISN'T EXACTLY YOUR FORTE.
THINK I DON'T KNOW
YOU HAD STONE SET ME UP?
YOU COULD HAVE JUST PASSED ME
A NOTE ASKING IF I WAS STAYING
WITH BOXES FOR YES OR NO AND "I"
DOTTED WITH A LITTLE HEART.
OKAY.
IT WAS IMMATURE. I JUST--
I DIDN'T WANT TO PRESSURE YOU.
COUPLES HAVE SURVIVED WORKING
AT DIFFERENT FIRMS BEFORE.
I JUST...
THERE'S ONLY SO MUCH STRESS
A RELATIONSHIP CAN TAKE.
NO PRESSURE THERE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.I'M NOT GONNA ASK YOU TO STAY.
GOOD.
'CAUSE, TAYLOR, YOU MEAN SO MUCH TO ME.
IF YOU HAD ASKED ME, THERE'S NO WAY I COULD HAVE SAID...
NO.
WHY ARE YOU SMILING?
I THINK I JUST FIGURED OUT A WAY
TO GET SANA TO CHANGE HER MIND.
THE OTHER THING ABOUT MOJITOS IS
THEY MAKE YOU FEEL ALL BETTER,
LIKE A TROPICAL BEACH PARTY IN YOUR MOUTH.
I MEAN, LOOK AT ME.
I'M HAVING A GREAT TIME.
ARE YOU SURE?
'CAUSE YOU'RE SITTING
OVER HERE ALL ON YOUR OWN.
IT'S A DISASTER.
IT'S JUST BAD TIMING.
doT TAKE IT PERSONALLY.
ELI, IT'S MY ENGAGEMENT PARTY.
IT SHOULD BE...
SHOULD FEEL DIFFERENT.
LIKE ALL THESE PEOPLE WHO DIDN'T
SHOW UP KNEW WHAT I DIDN'T.
SCOTT AND I HAD A HUGE BLOWUP THIS MORNING.
HE DOESN'T UNDERSTAND WHY I TURNED DOWN POSNER.
POOR GUY.
HE'S SO WORRIED AND CONCERNED
ABOUT OUR FUTURE.
HE'S SO GOOD TO ME.
AND I...
I CAN NEVER HURT HIM.
MAGGIE, I HAVE TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT SOMETHING.
THOUGHT YOU MIGHT BE HUNGRY.
BROUGHT YOU A PLATE--SUSHI.
OH, NO, THANKS.
A LOVELY BRIE.
I'M OKAY.
-CHAMPAGNE?
-NO.
HOW ABOUT THIS EMMENTALER?
HAVE YOU TASTED THIS? COME ON.
YOU'RE PREGNANT.
I KNEW IT.
YOUR MOTHER HAD A THING FOR EMMENTALER
WHEN SHE WAS PREGNANT, TOO.
ok COLUMBO, YOU GOT ME.
PLEASE DON'T SAY ANYTHING TO ANYONE. MATT DOESN'T EVEN KNOW.
OF COURSE NOT. THAT'S COMPLICATED. I UNDERSTAND.
YOU COULD HAVE TOLD ME, THOUGH.
I'M SORRY.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
PRETTY OVERWHELMED, TO BE HONEST.
IT'S A LOT TO THINK ABOUT--A BABY.
I NEVER REALLY SAW MYSELF AS A MOTHER.
I'M NOT SURE I DO NOW.
I SEE.
SO YOU MIGHT NOT BE KEEPING IT?
I'M SORRY IF THAT'S NOT
WHAT YOU WANT TO HEAR, DAD.
I MEAN, THINGS WITH MATT AND I ARE GOOD,
BUT WE'RE NOT EXACTLY SERIOUS.
CAN I RAISE A BABY ON MY OWN?
I MEAN, WOULD I EVEN WANT TO?
SWEETIE, THE DECISION IS YOURS, OF COURSE.
BUT JUST SO YOU KNOW,
YOU ARE NEVER ALONE.
THANKS, DAD.
WELL, I DON'T UNDERSTAND.Y-YOU WERE IN MY BATHROOM?
WELL, YEAH. I WAS IN YOUR SHOWER FIRST.
UH, IT'S-- IT'S, UH, VERY NICE.
IT'S A GREAT SELECTION OF SHAMPOO.
IT'S A LITTLE GIRLY FOR MY TASTE, BUT, UH--
BUT WHAT WERE YOU DOING IN THERE?
) YOU SEE, THE THINGS IS, UM...
I WASN'T... ME,
AND, UM, I WASN'T...
ALONE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
MAGGIE, I WAS--
-SCOTT!
-THERE YOU ARE.
HI, HONEY.
SHOULD'VE FIGURED WHEN I
COULDN'T FIND HER ANYWHERE,
SHE'D BE HERE WITH YOU.
MAGGIE, YOUR PARENTS
ARE LOOKING ALL OVER FOR YOU.
PARENTS. I BETTER GO.
I'M ONLY GONNA SAY THIS ONCE. BACK OFF.
LOOK, WE'RE GETTING MARRIED.
WHY CAN'T YOU RESPECT THAT?
WHY CAN'T YOU?
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
IT MEANS I SAW YOU
WITH A CERTAIN, UH, NAKED MARRIED WOMAN.
WHY DON'T YOU MIND
YOUR OWN BUSINESS, BRO?
WHY DON'T YOU TELL HER, BRO,
BEFORE I DO?
BEFORE SHE MAKES THE BIGGEST MISTAKE OF HER LIFE
AND MARRIES A PIECE OF CRAP LIKE--
ELI! WHAT-- WHAT'S GOING ON?
JUST... GO TELL HER.
YOU TELL HER, OR I WILL.
GO CLEAN UP YOUR FACE. WE'LL TALK LATER.
AND YOU...
PLEASE LEAVE.
now
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE   SO EARLY?
IS IT CARTER? WILL?
NO, NO,  IT'S NOTHING LIKE THAT.
LOOK,   YOU CAN'T TAKE THIS DEAL.
CARTER DOESN'T NEED    YOUR SACRIFICE.
HE NEEDS YOU.
GOING TO JAIL WOULD DESTROY HIM.
LIVING WITH THE GUILT OF YOU
DYING WOULD DESTROY HIM...
NOT TO MENTION WILL.
WILL'S A STRONG MAN.   HE'LL BE FINE.
TELL HIM THAT.
ALL RIGHT, STEP IN, PLEASE.
SANA, TELL WILL EXACTLY
HOW HE'LL BE FINE
LIVING THE REST OF HIS LIFE
NOT KNOWING WHETHER THE WOMAN
HE LOVES IS ALIVE OR DEAD.
AND, WILL, YOU TELL SANA
EXACTLY HOW YOU AND CARTER
WILL BE ABLE TO GO ON WITHOUT HER,
THAT A DAY WILL COME
WHEN YOU TWO WON'T WAKE UP
THINKING ABOUT HER,
WONDERING,
HATING YOURSELVES.
IF YOU TWO CAN ACTUALLY CONVINCE
EACH OTHER OF THOSE THINGS,
THEN, SANA,   YOU SHOULD TAKE THIS DEAL.
BUT MY GUESS IS YOU WON'T.
MY GUESS IS YOU'LL STAY.
YOU'LL STAY   FOR THE MEN WHO LOVE YOU.
SANA MADE SOME MISTAKES,
BUT THE QUESTION BEFORE YOU,  YOUR HONOR,
IS WHETHER THOSE MISTAKES
JUSTIFY PUTTING HER TO DEATH.
THAT'S WHAT SENDING HER  TO PAKISTAN WILL DO.
THE LETTER FROM SANA'S FATHER
TO HER COUSIN PROVES THAT.
MS. BOOKER CALLS THE MARRIAGE
BETWEEN SANA AND CARTER  FRAUDULENT,
YET SANA WAS WILLING TO RETURN
TO PAKISTAN AND FACE DEATH
FOR CARTER.
THAT...
THAT IS SACRIFICE
AND A LOVE MORE REAL
THAN WHAT'S BETWEEN
MOST MARRIED COUPLES I KNOW.
I'LL SAVE YOU   ALL THE SUSPENSE.
MISS KHAN HAS NOT DEMONSTRATED
RESPECT FOR OUR LAWS.
SHE KNOWINGLY ENTERED
INTO A FRAUDULENT MARRIAGE
IN ORDER TO OBTAIN A GREEN CARD.
I CANNOT REWARD   NOR CONDONE THIS BEHAVIOR,
AND I CANNOT EXTEND TO HER
THE PRIVILEGE  OF U.S. CITIZENSHIP.
I AM CONVINCED, HOWEVER,
THAT MS. KHAN WOULD BE
IN GRAVE DANGER   IF SHE RETURNS TO PAKISTAN.
I THEREFORE GRANT THE WITHHOLDING OF HER REMOVAL.
SHE'LL BE ALLOWED TO REMAIN HERE
AS LONG AS THERE IS  A THREAT AGAINST HER.
SORRYTHINGS DIDN'T WORK OUT.
WE'LL SEE HOW SMUG   YOU ARE TOMOOW.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
YOU PUSHED ME TOO FAR.
I SPOKE TO MY SUPERVISOR,  CANDACE BONNEVILLE,
TOLD HER ABOUT OUR LITTLE GREEN CARD SITUATION.
RECOMMENDED TH SHE EXPEDITE PROCEEDINGS
TO GET CARTER THE MAXIMUM-
FIVE YEARS.
WHAT? NO.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
WHY WOULD YOU THINK
I'M SO SORRY
FOR MYEHAVIOR...
FOR EVERYTHING.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE HAD TO
FIND OUT ABOUT SCOTT THAT WAY.
ARE THINGS, UH... HOW--HOW ARE THINGS?
THE ENGAGEMENT'S OFF.
THE WEDDING'S OFF.
IT'S ALL... OFF.
IT'S FOR THE BEST.
IF THERE'S ANYTHING THAT I CAN DO...
IF YOU WANT ME TO PUNCH HIM   AGAIN, I WILL.
I'M A GIVER THAT WAY.
HE'S NOT ENTIRELY  TO BLAME, YOU KNOW.
HE HAD GOOD REASON.
SCOTT'S NO DUMMY.
HE KNEW.
HE KNEW IT  BEFORE I EVEN DID.
I WAS COMING HOME EVERY NIGHT,
TALKING ABOUT WORK,
WHAT YOU HAD DONE IN COURT
OR WHAT WE TALKED ABOUT.
-MAGGIE--
-   YEAH, I THINK HE PROPOSED TO GET ME TO FORGET YOU.
I THINK I ACCEPTED FOR THE SAME REASON.
I KNEW.
I KNEW YOU DIDN'T FEEL  THE SAME WAY AS I DID.
-I WISH--
-  YOU DON'T.
I GET IT, ELI.
ANYWAYS,
TURNS OUT SCOTT WASN'T THE SAINT
I THOUGHT HE WAS, WAS HE?
HE AND CANDACE HAVE BEEN   GETTING IT ON FOR MONTHS.
CANDACE?
LUCKY I WASN'T ON YOUR
GREEN CARD CASE, BY THE WAY
TURNS OUT SHE'S BOOKER'S
TEAM LEADER AT I.C.E.
TALK ABOUT   CONFLICT OF INTEREST.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
I HAVE YOUR BOXES,   MISS DEKKER.
OH, COULD YOU PLEASE PUT THEM BY MY DESK?
SO YOU'RE... FINALLY
GETTING YOUR OWN OFFICE?
WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE
WE'RE SHORT ON SPACE ANYMORE.
I CAN'T STAY HERE, ELI.
I CAN'T  LET MY FEELINGS FOR YOU
COST ME MORE THAN   THEY ALREADY HAVE.
NOT POSNER & KLEIN.
DON'T DO THAT.
YOU--YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
I DO.
I LOVE YOU, ELI.
BUT FOR ONCE...
I'M ACTUALLY GONNA PUT MYSELF FIRST.
MISS BONNEVILLE?
HI.
I'M ELI STONE.
YOU'RE REPRESENTING  CARTER JAMESON, RIGHT?
I, UH, PULLED HIS FOLDER
AFTER I GOT YOUR MESSAGE.
YOU MUST HAVE REALLY PISSED
CHARLOTTE BOOKER OFF.
I GET THE FEELING
SHE'S A BIT OF A SORE LOSER.
SHE'S PASSIONATE ABOUT HER WORK.
BUT YOU'RE HER BOSS,  AND, UH,
I KNOW FOR A FACT THAT
THIS OFFICE HAS HANDLED   DOZENS OF CASES EXACTLY
LIKE CARTER'S WHERE YOU HAVE SIGNED OFF ON DEALS
WHICH
INVOLVED ZERO PRISON TIME.
I'M SORRY, MR. STONE, BUT THIS
ISN'T GONNA BE ONE OF THEM.
I HAVE TO ACCEPT CHARLOTTE'S RECOMMENDATION.
MY PEOPLE NEED TO KNOW THAT I TRUST THEM.
I FEEL AWFUL
PLAYING THIS CARD,
BUT, UM, CONSIDERING
WHO DEALT IT TO ME,
I DON'T SEE HOW
I HAVE ANY CHOICE.
I KNOW ABOUT YOUR...
EXTRAMARITAL ACTIVITIES
WITH SCOTT CLAUSON.
PARDON ME?
I KNOW IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS,
BUT I WAS...
I THINK I WAS MEANT
TO KNOW ABOUT YOUR AFFAIR
SO THAT I MIGHT ENCOURAGE YOU  TO HELP MY CLIENT.
ARE YOU BLACKMAILING ME?
NO. I AM JUST STRONGLY SUGGESTING
THAT THERE IS A SOLUTION
OPPOSITE TO MS. BOOKER'S...
WHICH YOU SHOULD SERIOUSLY CONSIDER.
UPON FURTHER EXAMINATION   OF HIS FILE,
I DO SEE SOME   AMELIORATING FACTORS HERE.
500 HOURS OF COMMUNITY SERVICE
AN2 YEARS PROBATION.
SOUNDS LIKE WE HAVE A DEAL.
SURELY YOU JEST, MS. DEKKER.
OUR OFFER OF LEGAL EMPLOYMENT
IS STRICTLY NONNEGOTIABLE.
NOTHING'S NONNEGOTIABLE,  MR. POSNER,
NOT WHEN BOTH PARTIES   HAVE LEVERAGE.
I'M WELL AWARE OF MY UNIQUE
VALUE TO YOU AND MS. KLEIN.
PRAY TELL, MS. DEKKER.
YOU RELISH THE THOUGHT OF HOW
MUCH YOU THINK IT WILL HURT ELI
IF I GO WORK FOR YOU.
DO YOU REALLY HAVE THAT LOW
AN OPINION OF ME?
LOWER, ACTUALLY.
AND YET YOU'RE WILLING   TO WORK FOR ME
IF I MEET YOUR TERMS.
IF I CAN USE YOU TO HELP
THE PEOPLE I WANT TO HELP,
YES.
THESE ARE MY TERMS.
TAKE THEM OR LEAVE THEM.
VERY SAVVY ASKS...
T WE CAN LIVE WITH THEM.
WELCOME TO POSNER & KLEIN.
I SUSPECT WE'RE GOING  TO DISCOVER STILL MORE
HIDDEN DEPTHS IN YOU, MS. DEKKER.
THE PROSECUTION IS GIVING CARTER A PASS.
I KNOW. SANA JUST CALLED   TO THANK ME.
HOW DID YOU DO IT?
FRIENDS IN HIGH PLACES.
YEAH.
WE DID GOOD.
WE DID. SO WHY ARE YOU PACKING?
WHAT WE DID THIS WEEK,
I HAVE NEVER FELT SO...
GRATIFIED,
SO RELIEVED BY A WIN.
WHICH MEANS THAT TAYLOR'S
?HALF-BAKED PLAN WORKED
AND YOU'RE SUPPOSED   TO STAY NOW.
STONE,
I HAVEN'T SLEPT  IN THREE DAYS.
I'VE BEEN WEARING THE SAME   STINKIN' SHIRT SINCE TUESDAY,
AND I HAVEN'T SWEAT THIS BAD
SINCE I RAN   THE BAY TO BREAKERS MARATHON.
THAT'S BECAUSE THE CASE MATTERED TO YOU, MATT.
THAT'S WHAT IT FEELS LIKE.
THAT'S EXACTLY MY POINT.
I LIKE A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP,
AND THE ONLY OCCASION
WHERE I ENJOY SWEATING
ISN'T IN THE COURTROOM.
NAH. THIS ISN'T ME, ELI.
YOU SAVED SANA'S LIFE.
YEAH,   AND IT NEARLY ENDED MINE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW I WOULD HAVE LIVED WITH MYSELF
IF WE'D LOST THAT.
LISTEN, MAN,
I ADMIRE WHAT YOU DO.
IT'S JUST NOT WHAT I DO.
WHAT ABOUT TAYLOR?
SHE'LL BE FINE.
YOU SHOULD BE WORRIED  ABOUT YOURSELF.
WHY?
BECAUSE THE NEXT TIME
WE'RE IN COURT TOGETHER,
IT'LL BE MY JOB  TO SHRED YOU.
I'M SORRY.
DON'T BE.
YOU MADE YOUR OWN DECISION.
THAT'S WHAT I WANTED YOU TO DO.
PLEASE DON'T  TAKE IT PERSONALLY.
YOU SAW WHAT THIS TRIAL DID TO ME.
I JUST... I DON'T DO EMOTIONAL,
TAYLOR. YOU KNOW THAT.
I DO.
ANYWAY,
THINK HOW MUCH  MORE FUN SEEING EACH OTHER
AT NIGHT'S GONNA BE WHEN WE HAVEN'T SEEN EACH OTHER ALL DAY.
I MADE RESERVATIONS   AT MASA'S.
8:00 OKAY?
GREAT.
HI.
HELLO.
SO RUMOR HAS IT
THAT POSNER MADE EVERY MEMBER
OF STAFF HERE AN OFFER,
INCLUDING YOU.
JUST SO YOU KNOW, UM,
OUT OF ALL THE PEOPLE HERE,
YOU'RE THE ONE  I COULD NEVER LOSE.
I MEAN THAT, PATTI.
WELL, I MEAN, LORD KNOWS
YOU'D BE USELESS WITHOUT ME.
LOOKS LIKE, UH, YOU'RE  NOT THE ONLY ONE, TOO.
I SAW JOHN IN THE ELEVATOR,
BETTY IN THE KITCHEN.
WHATEVER YOU SAID TO THEM   MUST HAVE WORKED.
I GUESS WE GOT A LOT
OF SAPPY IDEALISTS AROUND HERE.
I GUESS.
WELL, YOU CAN TELL THOSE SAPPY IDEALISTS
WHO STAYED ON THAT
WE WILL  UNFREEZE THEIR RAISES  FOR NEXT YEAR.
. YEAH, IT'S NOT  AS MUCH AS WHAT POSNER OFFERED,
AND IT'S NOT   WHAT YOU ALL DESERVE,
BUT WE'RE GONNA DO WHAT WE CAN.
I'LL TAKE IT OUT OF MY OWN
SALARY IF I HAVE TO.
REALLY, ELI?
THIS IS A NEW FIRM, PATTI,
AND WE MAY HAVE TO IMPROVISE,
BUT WE'RE GONNA FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO BE THE BEST FIRM THAT WE CAN.
NOW IF YOU WOULD BE SO KIND,
MAY I HAVE MY WACKADOO FILE?
OF COURSE.
JUST THE MAN   I WAS LOOKING FOR.
I TRUST IT WASN'T TOO DIFFICULT TO FIND ME.
OUR RANKS ARE CONSIDERABLY THINNED.
THINNED...
BUT STRENGTHENED.
CERTAINLY THERE ARE PLENTY
OF ETY OFFICES NOW
IF YOU WANT TO MOVE OUT OF THE LIBRARY.
OH, THANK YOU, SIR,
BUT, UH, I THINK I'LL STAY.
SENTIMENTAL REASONS,  YOU KNOW?
THAT I DO.
WHAT'S THAT?
NEW CASES. NEW CLIENTS.
I WAS JUST BRINGING IT  BY YOUR OFFICE.
OR WE COULD START FRESH
TOMORROW IF YOU LIKE.
NO, NO. NOW WOULD BE FINE.
BUT FIRST THERE WAS SOMETHING
I WANTED TO GIVE YOU.
TO NEW BEGINNINGS...
PARTNER.
NEW BEGINNINGS.
welcome to www.1000fr.com