[Music]
hi there everyone I have had the
pleasure of talking to Shin behind stage
and you are in for the most incredible
story as we're talking and as I
introduced you should thank you for
being here thank you they're showing
some of the pictures so for those who
don't know Shin she's been called the
woman who built Beijing she's a
self-made billionaire Shin didn't grow
up like this she grew up in the Cultural
Revolution and I'll let you tell the
stories but ended up as a factory girl
when she was 14 somehow ended up at
Goldman Sachs and next thing you know
she has I mean look at these buildings
in Beijing right now we're showing some
of the most extraordinary buildings but
let's start I don't want to spend too
much time on your your growing up years
but it's so incredible for us here in
the u.s. to hear that at 14 years old
you were working in a factory right so
tell us about those guys so I was born
and grew up in Beijing during cult
revolution and the days the years that
China open the door when some of the
Chinese were allowed to get out my
mother who was a Burmese Chinese was the
first to leave China and went to Hong
Kong so when we went to Hong Kong I was
14 and it was hard to think about what
else can do but basically need to make a
living so I we ended up me and her both
working the factory I was 14 and so we
worked together in factories and were
you going to school were you learning i
i i went to evening schools and so i
wanted to continue the education but
mainly it was you know in hong kong
first i didn't even speak Cantonese
that's a local language so I needed to
learn that and working but working you
know I naturally just pick it up so I
continue the evening education for a few
years and till I finished high school
high school level you make it sound so
easy I worked in a factory and I went to
school and what it couldn't have been
what you know I would try to make it
into the in the context of us it's like
a new immigrants right you come in - we
went to Hong Kong we're like a new
immigrants right so
what's there that we could do it was a
very basic manual work you can pick I'm
sure some of the new immigrants coming
to this country had a similar experience
so that was the life for me and my
mother but you knew you had it in you
you knew there was more out there right
so I was of course desperate relief
right I didn't want to spend the rest of
my life in factories and by the time you
know after five years I may save a
little bit money I saved about 3,000
English British Pound I decided to leave
and try at Hong Kong then was still the
British colony so then that the place
naturally to pick to go to study was
England so I went so you pick up by
yourself
mmm get on a plane to England you don't
speak any English no and you don't know
anything about England I'm nothing know
so you land in London I'm here and what
happens so I got to England well before
I went to England I went to British
consul in Hong Kong and I wanted to go
to a school to study English the only
place I've heard in my life was Oxford
in England so I said is that a school at
an Oxford they say oh there's a language
school you can go so I went there I
think that was the first moment in my
life I am probably the only moment in my
life I felt quite scared because
suddenly I arrived to this place I did
not know a single person I didn't speak
the language and he just felt really
scary and my mother wasn't even there
right it wasn't even Hong Kong there's
still Chinese however I was 19 but I was
more scared the first day in England
then when I was 14 first day went to
Hong Kong well you had your mother with
you I had my mother and and you were
surrounded
I presume by other people who spoke your
language and tell me about the the story
you saw one other Chinese person amma so
I I was scared I said down I just
started crying so I feel like after five
minutes I thought this is not gonna hold
for too long so I just went on the
street and then there was the first
Chinese looking person I just grabbed
her I assume she's Chinese gonna had no
idea but she could have been Japanese
laya but I just assume she's Chinese so
I spoke to her in Chinese and say are
you Chinese you know and she said yes
and I said oh great I just arrived here
you know where's the supermarket I can
get some food and she she was really
nice she took me good supermarket she
said you want to come to join me for a
party we have a Chinese gathering
tonight so from that moment onward I
found my way you said rather fearless
even though you said you were scared it
sounds I was scared but for an hour and
then you found a friend I was gonna sit
there just cry for the rest of my life
does it come from your parents right
they they lived through the cultural
episode
yeah you know if you grew up in China
and culture evolution you've been
through so much in life and you know
just it just gave you that much more you
know strength and so you guys know I
really pressed her on this backstage
like you move to England you you move
back to China and you'll hear about this
in a second you've built this company
that is so incredibly successful that's
the only moment you were scared that's
the only mom give me another one give me
another everyone asking me and that is
it and it must be that you went through
so much as a child plus whatever you had
in you that nothing could be nothing
seemed scary you had already done the
scary parts well no no they're plenty of
moments that feel very challenged it was
difficult I was struggling but it was I
wasn't scared I just know that you know
things will work out and it was more
focus on getting things worked out okay
so you you land in London you sell fish
and chips oh I told you that story right
so I got to a box where I started
studying English language and I could
speak a few words and somebody I needed
to make a living right because I only
had 3,000 pound and that wasn't gonna
last for too long so somebody told me
there's a chinese couple opened a fish
and chips store they're looking for
someone part-time for Friday and
Saturday evenings so I went I said you
know can I have a job and they say yet
do you know very simple English and I
said yeah I can speak very simple they
say all you need to say is one there's a
long line of people buying fish and
chips all you need to ask them
is salt of vinegar salt of vinegar so I
can say salt and vinegar so Dominica
so the whole night I would just add salt
or vinegar salt and vinegar did you
dream something funeral I gotta saw the
video and then you know after the
evening they would they're so nice they
would ask me to pack some fish and chips
and go home and I had for like two years
I was having fish and chips so much I
can't eat it I can't look at it so so at
this point you're studying English
you're selling fish and chips I wonder
if that guy who hired you knows where
you are now I don't know right when does
that be funny and and how did you get
from there to college and then yeah so
that from there moment it was relatively
easy because I was already in this
system right so I learn English that I
want went to Sussex University from
there I went to Cambridge University and
that I'd ended up having a job with
Goldman Sachs so once you you know went
into that education it became relatively
smooth so I worked at Goldman Sachs for
a few years and I but my heart was in
China I always wanted to go back so back
in 95 now how many years almost you know
20 23 years ago I decided you know I'm
gonna quit Goldman Sachs I'm gonna go
back to China and that's what I did did
you and we'll get to that a sec but did
your eyes continue to open or once you
got to London then you were you you were
in this world now and everything seemed
normal because the first time you saw an
escalator was that in Hong Kong that was
in Beijing and bear was backing when I
haven't even gone to Hong Kong got it
but right so I mean increasingly you
started to be in a much fancier world
yes and so by the time he went to
college was it just this is my world now
no no it was never my world college was
another struggle right because everybody
was 17 and I was older by the time I got
there and so and also I didn't
understand I could speak basic English I
was still not able to really
I understand everything and then you
know the kids in college you know what
did they want to do they want to get
drunk they want to go to parties and I
didn't understand any of that why would
people want to do that right like just
get drunk and go to parties her what's
fun about that I was there to study
mm-hmm
so I just said you know I was one of
those nerdy Chinese girl just start the
study study right and of course I needed
more time to study than the others
because I had bad education before and I
couldn't speak much English so that was
most of my college I was I never felt
quite fitted in right cuz I just always
fell I don't know like every room I walk
in and I feel like oh what's this all
about you know let me figure it out how
do I feel confused by this beer-pong
face I ended up having a job selling
beers in the bar that was your entree
into that at Goldman how long were you
Goldman 2 years 2 years and your job was
I was with IBD which is innocent banking
division okay investment okay so you're
so you're at Goldman and but what need
to know like the interview for Goldman
job what what's your strengths so you're
you left Goldman why did you after you
have this life in London here why did
you decide to go back to China I because
China then became really interesting you
know it's the it's the mid-90s China
began this journey of opening building
private sector building the market
economy and I was trained as economists
you know at Sussex in Cambridge so my
master's thesis was on privatization of
Chinese economy so I was always thinking
this is a really exciting moment you
know I was just not gonna be you know
doing a banker job and sitting on the
side to watch it I just want to be part
of that so I moved back to Beijing was
your mom still there my mom stayed in
Hong Kong
she said yeah and when you went back did
you know what you wanted to do did you
go there with a job did you go there
with gold man no no no I met my husband
before you moved back right so that was
the link right sorry I met my husband
four days later would
I did get married four days four days
took quite a while wait so you were in
China just visiting you met him and four
days later he said marry me and you said
sure let me give up my Goldman job and
move to China and we'll be part of this
again I don't know it's I met him and
then four days later he's yeah we kind
of noticed it should we get married I
said well I need to fix a few things but
yes why not and the way you describe
your husband as I read it they'll read
it was he was a country bumpkin oh but
yes you have called him a country
bumpkin when you got back but you'd had
this life overseas he'd never left China
right Neil I've never left trying
doesn't speak English still doesn't
speak English now and any was from one
of the poorest prophet he's from one at
the pros brothers is and but he's the
one who had this dream of real estate
that's right
yeah and so tell sister I bought into
his dream you know so he I met him and
then he said you know at first he
proposed and said get married on I say
yes so I said okay but I better get to
know this guy and then he said you know
let me show you what I do and so he took
me to this construction site at the time
it was a massive hole on the ground so
he said this is what I do I build
buildings I was like wow I've never seen
such a big hole on the ground and I and
then he said you know look at this right
it's gonna this is gonna be the
Manhattan of Beijing I would say you
know this guy who's never been to
Manhattan he's dreaming about something
this is not possible how could this
thing be building took Manhattan
actually today if you go to Beijing and
Shanghai it is such a modern Manhattan
that with high-rise skyscrapers and many
of the buildings of course were built by
me and you know my husband and and our
peers our fellow developers at that
point you're talking to this guy who's
never seen anything you've been to
Manhattan he has these dreams how what
did you
leave in him and what did you believe
about China at the time that you felt
like okay this is this is worth joining
not only is it worth being a part of but
I think we can make this work I think
China in the mid 90s was in such a
beginning of everything so everything
felt possible like there's no building
somebody said don't build a building
there's no stores someone needs to open
the store there's no restaurant so money
it's just that everything seemed to be
possible they all you needed to do is to
go ahead and do it and it wasn't you
know there was no the business community
is so like not formed yet it's in the in
the process being formed so then I think
that the few of us were early ones were
just really we're actually part of the
force of building the whole community
building the whole industry well I think
you could go into a situation like that
and look at it two ways
either there's no infrastructure here
and so I can't get anything done or get
it done your own way here's a building
but I mean I can't there were no banks
right you weren't getting a mortgage on
build in there there are some banks
there were Chinese banks but the banks
were just not lending to mortgages right
that's why many you didn't have a
banking system in the same way so where
did the money come from so we had to go
to the banks to convince them that you
know in order for us to sell condos you
have to have mortgages with our
mortgages the buyers don't have that
much money and they need to borrow some
so it took a while to convince the banks
to start trying out that's a new
business for them too because they
haven't done any mortgage business so
everything was new building a building
was built new selling apartments was new
for the banks to provide mortgages was
new everything was new was it scary at
all you know it was exciting so there
were I know going back to the scary part
but but there was there any point in
there where you thought this isn't gonna
work
right oh yeah the NT of times plenty of
times almost every day NFL this is not
gonna work this is not gonna work
to start with you know my husband and I
we got married on a very short you know
to say the least so we we did not know
each other that well right so out of
sudden we're husband and wife were
business partners were in the new
venture together everything new right so
you can imagine the conflict the
challenges the the problems right there
any problems and differences that we had
in the office naturally carried forward
home right so it just felt really
intense and two years later I thought
this is really not gonna work right we
should really just went separate ways
and he felt the same because we were
just fighting almost every day every
minute how big was the company at that
point uh still small it was I don't
remember small early they still trying
to you know take it off the ground but
we we we we thought this is not working
maybe not just a business but also the
marriage was right working so we I went
back to England for two weeks and he
went with his friends somewhere for two
weeks and but by the end of the two
weeks I decided to go back because I
thought well it's hard but I have to
make it work so I went back I told him I
think the problem is the two of us
working together why don't you work I
say at home how about that and he said
oh that's sounds good so the next thing
I knew is that I got pregnant and then
halfway through the pregnancy the
business because we're not fighting
anymore at the business took off and
then he said oh I actually need you to
come back to work this is too much what
I can't deal with this anymore
and then so I went back to where I got
my job back I brought my baby to the
office later hurt so that's how do you
think you could have if he had never
said come back to work I need you do you
think he would have been okay staying at
home no I would have asked to go back
you would have submitted an application
what about that I think this this needs
more than one person right and you were
itching to get back to work
I imagine at that point I love your
stories about having to convince people
about beauty and buildings and why it's
important because the way you guys grew
up it wasn't like that it wasn't this
sense of we need to build something that
looks different than everything else and
beautiful and so how did you do that so
we start a building and very soon I
realize a big component of building is
architecture you can build very ugly
building you can build very beautiful
buildings and so I threw just my own
curiosity I fell in love with
architecture I started visiting a lot of
Architects studios around the world
going to a lot of exhibitions art
exhibitions that's just to see how the
architects present their work and then
when I see something really nice you
know I was right away I was thinking can
I bring this person to China can she and
him come into China the word you know
they haven't oh then I found out this
person has never really built anything
more than an Art Center I said well
think can this person come into building
an office building a condo building so
that's how I it just didn't happen
overnight it's just a gradual thing and
then I started inviting people to come
in first are doing small aperture than
then become bigger and bigger and bigger
and then in the end but the idea of let
me go back to that for one second you
took all of these architects who were
basically building things drawing things
on paper but no developer would hire
them there were in most of the
commercial developers eyes they are a
little too creative too imaginative and
I now I know more about how conventional
developers think they think this is too
costly and they think these artists are
too hard to work with because they're
too much of a character
none of those you know things that I
didn't think that matters because I was
more drawn attracted by the beauty of
their work and I was more thinking about
how can I bring this to my work but what
about then bringing that to China and
and convincing customers and people who
are investing you it is worth spending
money on something beautiful to a
generation of people who had grown up
during the Cultural Revolution right
where that wasn't honored the the beauty
was so natural that I never I knew that
is going to be accepted by the market so
that was never the issue it was more of
an issue of bringing the architects to
China as many of these people never been
to China and you know of course never
done the project in China so how do you
bring someone who likes aha Hadid in
London
to Beijing and then not only she hasn't
done a building in China she hasn't done
a big building install so then how do
you how do we work with her and bring
her you know bridging that with whole
local communities of designers
architects to really make these gigantic
developments happen so that's just you
know so our whole company and office
just you know build the the capacity to
do that over time and in the beginning
days I also remember reading that people
would come with suitcases of cash and am
i right you're looking at me like I'm
crazy
Oh to buy the condos oh yeah they would
come with suitcases of care this is
remember what the time or that we're
going backwards right this is a time
when we had to convince the banks to
lend mortgage anyway so mortgage so
people many of people don't even have
checking account in the banks right so
then they all want to buy or these
people can want to buy an apartment and
some came with cash what now we can go
back for it again but what I find really
amazing is here we talk so much about
women having to break the glass ceiling
right and and get to the same point as
men and in China you had an entirely
different experience at least in the
private sector I grew up with not
knowing any women staying at home you
know my mother would her friends worked
there's no such thing as staying at home
because and everybody worked for the
government so growing up in that culture
women are just naturally think that you
would study you will go to have a job
you would work right so I think that has
created a and then when China opened to
be
more commercialized you know build the
market there was no tradition of a you
know male-dominated business society
there was no such thing so everything
you know men and women are pretty much
on the level playing field to start so
you see many women in the private sector
do well and I think it's partly because
there was no tradition holding back and
started from a clean sheet I'm gonna ask
the question from the audience but I
think it follows exactly from what
you're saying but as women become
increasingly financially successful
studies show that many women actually
worry about being more successful in
their career than their partner at this
from an entirely different perspective
I'm guessing yeah it's not an issue no
it's nothing yeah why should we be
thinking we should be less successful
than our partners no and your husband's
not worried about he's the one who
brought you back no no he's not worried
about that
but you don't need a husband who doesn't
worry about that and right now in China
you you have co-working spaces some of
the most co-working spaces in all of
China yes right and and what is that
because I don't know if we all have a
sense of what the entrepreneurial spirit
feels like in China and what barriers
there are versus barriers here I think
China was just because you know China's
the whole business history is just
recent three years right it's really
short so I think the the there's no
really sad ways of doing things so I
think it opens up the possibilities and
opportunities to anybody who just wants
to take the risks and do it as a result
you have this amazing amazing spirit of
entrepreneurship and I think it
continues to be there is very dynamic of
the society I think here is the same
it's like the tag the startups and you
know that culture is there so back to
your question on the co-working so we
build buildings for so long right for
20-something years we've been building
buildings now the cities in China are
largely built
so then we're asking ourselves what's
the next so we want to start building
the contents inside the building and
that's why we started that the business
of co-working just really providing it's
called Soho 3q and it's really providing
an office space for startups and laws
and laws hundreds of startups are in our
cell 3q it's pretty unusual for a family
that's it yeah so those are the pictures
it's beautiful but it's unusual for a
founder though we've had quite a few
here at this conference to start
something small uh-huh and then still be
at the helm of it as it's grown so much
larger what is it do you think about you
that was able to take something from the
startup phase where you're all sitting
in the same room together you're all
talking to each other to now when you
have all these employees all around the
world to still be able to maintain the
excitement about it and the and to grown
the leadership that it takes to run such
a big company did you ever drive
yourself around this way I just feel
like I love what I do and I still love
what I do so I think maybe the days that
I don't love what I do and I don't have
that excitement you know I just continue
to feel excited about going to work and
but but the leadership that it takes if
you don't start with that I don't think
when you have a three-person company you
have to learn how to maintain your
culture and maintain this big office and
make sure everyone has the same values
and become a real leader of many many
people did it come naturally or did you
but I think the leadership is you start
with the little and then you bro into it
you know the more you do it the more you
know how to do it I don't know I mean I
I was always the one who wanted to lead
who wanted to do something different I
was not afraid of doing that and I
continue to do that and I feel a lot of
people want to do something exciting
do you have any friends from your Hong
Kong days who you still keep in touch
with yes I'm good and what is what do
they all do know from the factories yeah
that's what I meant actors no no no no I
really have lost touch with them you
have yeah but through the rest of your
life but from England days from the
ragland's right so once you've gone on
once you got on this trajectory yeah and
do you ever um sort of go home at night
through all this time and think I have a
great responsibility
right I have I've helped build this city
and now I have a great responsibility
because I run this big company mm-hmm
what I always I don't feel not quite in
those sense but the way I feel
responsibilities for instance every
building I built I feel I feel the
responsibility I know these buildings
gonna be there for over a hundred years
and I know I need to do something more
than a building needs to be more than
just because I need need an office
building okay I need to lease an office
building I need to sell the office oh I
know it needs to be more than that
that's why I went into architecture
because I also always knew a building is
not just an office just not a condo
building it's also a face of the city
and we were building the modern face of
the city do you feel like you or someone
I mean you're called the woman who built
Beijing do you feel like it you feel
like you have been one of those core
people who really helped to change China
what I fell that I was one of those core
people who you know really build Beijing
all right we have another question oh
this is from you I believe or oh it's
one more name yeah okay as a tech
founder I often hire a very creative
team members who have great ideas but
don't work well on a team how do you
bridge work style and cultural
differences not just across teams but
across countries who don't work well
well then some don't belong there right
they need to work well if people don't
work well you need to find out why cuz
there may be one or two people they just
don't like it or what it's just I think
if they don't work well that's a problem
is there anything very clear-cut to you
just it's we've got this we'll just do
this that's going to work but I'm very
created making decisions if I see
there's a room of ten people in a team
right like two people is always making
you know the arguments and so on is
making this whole team slow down this is
not working so we need to do something
and is that how you run your life for
your kids your marriage your business oh
yeah everything just here this is what I
think let's go with it let's not fret no
analysis paralysis let's keep going
yeah well analysis no what's that
and what do you think your team what do
you think the people who were closest
with you how do you think they described
you I don't know some of them that here
you should ask them wait where's Ashley
she's right there yeah are we right in
saying she's just that decisions or
decisions they come pretty easily and
then they're done well you know the
other thing that Ashley told me is that
you are the kind of person that if I ask
you something today and you don't know
it
tomorrow you will know more than I do no
I'm very curious right you know you know
you know something I don't know I would
want to know and I'm gonna be stay up
overnight Google go everything read
everything and you've been like that
your whole life I'd be like that woman
and do you think because a lot of people
would think that you had to be
laser-focused on your business at a
certain point and not spend all this
time learning so many other things but
I'm guessing you think it all feeds back
into the session I feel yeah if he's
back to what I do and what do you hope
for the future continue to feel excited
for what I do and you know continue to
build and and now I'm spending also more
time working with younger people because
we started a charitable project called
Soho China scholarship we have we would
provide financial aid for Chinese
students go to Ivy Leagues we have 44
scott soho scholars at harvard yale this
year so I also spent time with them and
I wanted to just because I remember how
I was you know from factory to a
university from university to this right
so I wanted to share my own experience
with this younger generation so that's
also something I really enjoy doing when
you look back on your life and think of
yourself as a factor girl or living in
Beijing with your mom does it seem to
make sense
your trajectory or do you feel like wow
how did I get here I really I mean I
just felt like life has taken me to a
lot of surprised places and I was able
to always find a fun part of it
and get on with it and so that's how I
do that's how I see life is just deal
with it and go on yeah well I mean this
was so incredible speaking with you you
have said we didn't get to touch on your
whole story but it is it's amazing for I
believe us who grew up in the United
States you know even if we didn't have a
lot we still had a lot more than then
you did I mean working in a factory when
you were 14 years old and so it's just
amazing to get to hear the story of
someone who had the inspiration and
ambition at that age to end up where you
are now and then to give back well thank
you thank you so much
you