-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
Hung
Season 01 Episode 06
sync:Ö¥Ê¿µ°¸â
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Just because we've lost,just because
the past is not what we wanted it to be,
doesot mean we cannot change.
In an instant,we could.
What do you want to think tonight when you replay
this in your head with the lights out,trying to sleep?
I'm sorry I'm late.
No problem.
Nice scarf.
Oh,really? You like it?
Looks good on you.
Thanks.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
What are we doing?
Don't ask me that.
Okay.
Are you nervous?
Um,should I be?
Yes,I'm nervous.
Well,don't be.
Come on.
Thank you for coming,jim.
it's okay to feel a little uneasy.
This must be difficult for you.
it means a lot to me that he's here.
Of course it does.
It does mean a lot,
because you have to understand I'm gonna confront
you head on and most men would run from that,
so thanks for being here.
You're welcome.
So what did you want to confront?
Should I just jump in here?
If you want to.
I want to say to you,jim,that-- that your
money destroys you-- your father's money.
I-it's like-- it's like
you're choking on his vomit.
It makes me want to weep,
because sometimes I picture you without
him and his money¡ªand the money¡ª
and you're a completely
different human being.
You don't do what you did,jim.
Not to me. Not to anyone.
You just--
you just don'T.
I don't know what to do with him!
He's like a stone wall.
I don't-why did he even-- why
did he even agree to come here?
Do you-- does
she want--
don't talk to him.Talk to me.
Explain to me why it happened.
Maybe you went for
the wrong kind of guy.
Just tell me,for fuck's sake!
Jemma.
Swear the fuck out!
I don't know why!
Jemma,I don't know why things
happen in my life or-or your life!
If I had to take a guess,I'd have to say
something about you is a big,fat turn-off!
Oh,like now?
Am I a turn-off right now?
No.
Are you okay?
Yeah,I'm fine.
So,uh,what was that about,exactly?
It doesn't matter.
That's it?
What am I supposed to do now?
I don't care what you do.
- Jemma paid me.
- Paid you?
Yeah,your cut's in my desk.
Don't worry. I locked it.
Paid you? For what?
It's a long story.
She booked me for a session.
When?
It's over already. Just now.
I-I-I saw her on
my lunch break.
She called me late last night.
What was I supposed to do?
If a client calls you
directly,you tell me immediately.
It's not cool.
There's a protocol.
She paid me $500.
What wrong with that?
Look,last week you went to
her house behind my back.
Now she's calling you at
all hours of the night.
It was a decent hour.
I'm going to have a
little talk with her.
I-don'T. That's not a good idea.
Why not?
She-she's having a hard time.
And you know this because...
She took me to see her therapist.
Yeah,I think that's why she hired me.
I think I'm supposed to help
her,you know,work shit out.
A million things come to
mind,but I'm not gonna say them.
I'm just gonna keep my mouth shut.
Leave her alone,okay?
I'll talk to her about the rules.
Okay.
I've gotta go.
Are you drinking enough water lately?
What?
You look dehydrated.
What's that? Some kind
of dermatology put-down?
No,baby,water's excellent for the skin.
Yup. It's also good for depression.
You lost your dog-- he
died-- and that's rough.
I'm sick of water,ron.
I want to talk about money.
What about it?
Do we have it?
Are we rich or are we poor?
I can't tell.
We drive a mercedes,and we pay for
natasha,and on the other hand doris is dead.
Well,we're not rich or
poor,jess,but we did lose a lot--
- 30%,maybe 40%,so--
- 40%?
Yeah,I've got to get to the office.
40% of what,ron?
This is what is so frustrating.
Ron,you don't tell me anything.
Is there something you want to buy?
Is there?
Are you feeling neglected?
Are you feeling deprived?
Because say the word,I'll buy it.
And if I can't afford
it,I'll hock my jaeger.
I'll wash dishes.
I'll eat hot coals for you,baby.
I don't want you to eat hot coals,ron.
I just... need to know the numbers.
I don't know the exact numbers,jess.
But if you want to help,you can make a
list of potential household cutbacks or...
you could always get a job.
I still haven't heard
anything,so good luck with that.
- Thanks for meeting me here.
- What?
I left you a message about us meeting.
You guys go ahead. I'll catch up.
I'm sorry. What are you doing here?
I know you're busy because
you haven't called me back,
but I was in the neighborhood¡ªI
was nearby,so I thought¡ª
terry,I'm working.
This is my place of work.
It's tanya.
Okay,why don't you just
tell me why you're here?
Oh,listen to me. I thought I made myself
pretty clear in our initial interview.
Now what you wanted
was a little unorthodox
and I said,"fine,as long
as you respect our rules."
and one of those rules is you do
not contact or pay a client directly.
Hold on.
hey,Yeah. Yeah,I'll be right there.
Don't let him see it,brad.
It's pretty simple what--
so that's the way it goes.
I know,as a businesswoman,you understand after
years of working that there are certain systems...
that keep the trains
running on time that...
I will be right up.
I-what are you talking about?
Our parameters.
What if I just ignore you
and do whatever I want?
What?
What's stopping me from-- I don't know--
just not bothering to listen to you?
Well,I would stop you.
It's my service.
I'm the one who makes the rules.
Jemma. Jemma,I do not
suffer fools gladly.
Now look,ray--
ray is my employee.
Now you cannot get to
him except through me.
We are inextricably linked.
Who's ray?
You mean randall?
No,I do not mean randall.
I mean,there is no ray.
You know what? You're fired.
That's right. I'm
firing you as a client.
You know,I've had enough
of you and women like you.
Good riddance!
It's pretty good,huh?
I mean,check out the new panel.
It still smells a little wonky,though.
It's normal.
Anyway,I'll fix it...before
we move you guys back in.
Cool.
Great.
Let's choose some wheels.
All right. I circled the
ones I think are good.
You tell me which one's
got your name on it.
An '89 mustang?
Yeah,vintage-- it says so right
there in the ad.Heck of a car.
It's got 120,000 miles.
So?
Those are highway miles.
I talked to the guy selling it.
all right,whatever. You guys decide.
Hey,where are you going? I
thought we were buying a car.
She doesn't give a shit,dad.
All she cares about is
her fat-ass boyfriend.
Hey hey,give it a rest,damon.
Maybe she sees something you don'T.
What are you talking about?
I'm saying people are complex.
They're like... onions.
You peel a layer and sometimes you
find something you weren't expecting.
No,you don'T. You just find more onion.
holy cow,ray.
This place is really coming along.
It still really smells though.
so it
this your--
You must be ray's¡ª
yeah,tanya,this is my kid.
Damon,tanya.
I think I see the resemblance.
Yeah,the eyebrows,right?
Damon,we'll be right back.
Take a look at the '89 mustang,huh?
You can use this time to get excited.
Nice meeting you.
Oh yeah,you too.
Thanks,tanya.
Now my kid thinks you're my girlfriend.
What? Just because I
show up at your house?
Don't be infantile.
What do you want?
I've got great news.
I caught up with molly and she wants
to book you again for saturday night.
This saturday?
Yeah,you can go on the early side and then
come over and meet me and download after.
I got a bunch of netflix films.
We'll all pop some
popcorn,you can come over.
Tanya. I've got a life.
I've got a game this saturday.
Okay,so maybe we'll make it friday then.
No,jemma mentioned she wanted friday.
Don't worry. I'll make
her book through you.
Okay,it's too late for that.
I made an executive decision.
What are you talking about?
I'm an executive too. She's fine.
No,she's rude and I fired her.
I fired her.
I lost my temper.
Well,unfire her!
Jesus,tanya. Why did you
have to go mess this up for?
I'm not messing this up.
I'm fixing it,okay?
I'll-I'll fix it.
I-I-- just
leave me alone.
Mom,I'm not-- I do not
feel comfortable with this.
Ronnie's a private person. I
want to respect his privacy.
So? You go.
What about you?
I stay and not respect his privacy.
look-credit card bills.
Visa.
Mastercard.
More visa.
What does it prove?
Poor people don't spend so much.
Only rich ones.
make sure you put everything back.
He's gonna notice if
things are disturbed.
You are wife.
You have right to know
when husband is liar.
He's not a liar,mother.
He is worse than liar.
Treats you like child.
Worse than child.
He treats you like
pet,like your dead dog.
What are you talking about?
You want little needle in your face?
Too much wrinkle here.
Too much pimple there.
He takes care of me,mother.
He takes care of you.
How much money he has?
Do you know?
Of course not,because he
doesn't want you to know.
that's enough. You're driving me crazy.
Put it away.
Stock exchange.
I find the most important file.
Now you tell me he's not rich.
$833,000.
Why is it in parenthesis?
It's a loss,mom.
It means he lost $833,000.
Okay,so maybe I wrong.
Maybe he lost money.
You hungry? I make something to eat.
this is jemma. Be patient.
You'll get an answer eventually.
no. Hey,jemma. It's tanya.
Listen,I've got some terrific news.
Despite our previous miscommunication,I
had a discussion with randall
and we've decided to allow you to keep your
membership,provided you respect our rules.
Just please give me a call
at your convenience,okay?
you should call her back.
I'm sorry.
I've been swamped.
But really,randall,all that talk
about regulations and parameters?
She is a trip,your tanya.
She's not my tanya.
Well,she's your madam,isn't she?
I thought I was a book editor.
Oh,book editor.
That's so yesterday.
What's your real name?
I can't tell you that.
Why not?
Take a leap of faith.
And if you can't,just make something up.
I'm not gonna know the difference.
My name is ray.
- More? Tell me more.
- No.
- Please.
-  No.
I'll pay you... lots.
What do you think I am,a whore?
Yeah. Yes,you're a whore.
You're so funny,you're so
hot and I'm very into you.
But you're going to tell me.
Is this all you do?
Are you a fireman?
No.
Policeman?
A plumber?
No.
Stop torturing me.
You're making me want to fk you.
I'm gonna charge you double.
Tell me what you
fucking do for a living.
I'm a coach.
I'm a high-school basketball coacH.
I want to see you do it.
I mean coach.
come on! Defense!
Oh,come on.
It was looking like another losing game.
So many teams were having us for
lunch,I barely remembered how to win.
He didn't touch him!
Come on,ref. Call it both ways.
Ref's making bogus calls all night.
what are you looking at,ray?
Get your head in the game.
That's the half.
Wolves 26,tomahawks 36.
Oh my god,I love that lip gloss.
Hi,can I have one ticket for
the wolves and two buttons?
You mean the game.
Right,the game.
Thank you.
Damon,right?
How are you?
I'm good.
Fight,wolves,fight!
Are you-- do you-do
you go to the games?
Oh,no. No,I just-- I was
home,I'm having a moody night,
so I thought I should
be around human beings.
yeah,well,there's human
beings here,I guess.
If you kind of like that thing.
You're funny,aren't you?
Yeah.
I guess I-- I guess I kind
of have a funny personality.
Oh,hey,sweetie. Are you ready?
Mom,this is a friend of dad'S.
A friend of dad'S.
I'm jessica.
Tanya.
- Nice to meet you.
You're darby,right?
Uh,yeah.
Great.
Well--
so let's get back to the game,huh?
Where are you sitting?
Me? Oh,I don't know.
Anywhere. I don't know.
51 is killing us out there.
Yeah.
I knew I should've paid more attention.
My heart just wasn't in it.
Pazderka,box his ass out,okay?
This is varsity. Come on.
In two years,no one came to my games.
Now here we were in the worst losing
streak of my life and my ex-wife,
my two kids and my pimp were all
sitting up there side by side.
Let's go! Come on!
What's wrong with dad?
He seems kind of out of it.
I don't know.
Has he been putting on weight?
I think he lost weight.
Must be all that camping.
Do you have any idea how
much of an idiot you are?
I mean,you don't even
have a personalitY.
I do too have a personality.
No,you don'T.
Even the goth kids
think you're a poseur.
Kids,please.
I know what you mean.
How old are yours?
Oh no. I-I just teach kids.
I mean I used to teach kids
poetry before the budget cuts.
So do you come to ray's games often?
Who,me? Never.
I mean,I did when we were married.
I was head cheerleader back in my day.
But no,tonight I
figured "what the heck?"
My husband's working late.
I'm an adult.
I'll just go have a great night with my two lovely
kids and watch the wolves like we used to,huh?
Right,kids? Isn't this fun?
That's nice.
How do you know ray again?
We're friends--
good friends.
It's complicated--
me and ray.
How so?
Nice shot!
Go,wolves!
No,that was for the other team.
We're the white team.
They're the red ones.
Time out,time out,time out. Time out.
Bring it in,bring it
in. Let's do it. Come on.
This team is not seven points
better than us. All right?
All we've got to do is
we've gotta make more shots.
It's a simple game,guys.
And then she came.
She made me tell her,but I
didn't think she'd really show up.
And then suddenly I felt
it-- I wanted to win.
I wanted to win while she watched.
All right. Mike,I've got this.
Listen,guys,it's not about shots.
It's not about them.
This is about you-- what's inside
of you-- what's inside of you.
What do you want to think tonight when
you replay this game inside your heads
with the lights out and
you're trying to sleep?
That you gave it 70%?
Or 80%?
If we don't give it our all,if we
don't give it everything we've got,
then it don't matter what
the scoreboard says-- we lose!
If we believe we're better
than others believe we are...
if we play with our hearts,the
box score doesn't matter.
The scoreboard...
doesn't matter.
We win.
"Defense" on three.
All right,guys,one two three.
Defense!
come on,ref!
Don't let that big street zip code
affect the way you ref the game!
Sit down and shut up!
You sit down!
let's go,wolves!
Let's go!
Let's go,wolves!
She wanted to see me coach.
I wasn't going to let her see me lose.
She was gonna get her money's worth.
And this losing streak--
this streak was gonna end.
Trap! Trap!
no fouls. No fouls.
And the final score is the wolves
scoring 56 points to the tomahawks' 55.
- Who is that?
- I don't know.
just great.
Nice.
That's what I like to see.
It was a good game,mike.
Thanks for keeping it
together,you know,until--
until what? Until your blonde
walks in and turns you around?
Who is she?
Uh,she's-- she's
my good-luck charm.
Hey,hold on a second.
Hey,wait up.
What do you want from me,ray?
Look she paid me to come here.
I tried to make her book through
you,but-- what are you doing here,anyway?
I-I thought you didn't like sports.
You told her where you work.
You told her what you do.
You told her who you are.
You let her into your life.
Are you crazy?
We could go to jail for this.
Relax.
I trust her.
You tr-- you
trust her.
Hey,coach.
that's some leap.
Yeah.
A long time ago.
You look the same.
You look happy.
Yowant to go steady?
Well,like,you want to take me to your
house and play "seven minutes in heaven"?
You know...
maybe I won't charge you anymore.
Oh,but then it wouldn't be as fun.
drecker makes game changing
catch-rallies wolves to finals
Hung S01E06
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-proudly presents
sync:Ö¥Ê¿µ°¸â
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-