Welcome back to Logic Language and
Information.
And to this, the final in a series
of lessons on sequential digital systems
and their logic.
First, we restate the multiple roles of
logic here.
We can formalize system specifications and
prove
they're equivalents of different versions
of specifications.
We can formalize system descriptions of
next-state and
output in terms of current-state and
current input.
And then, using the work we did last
lesson on validities of temporal
logic, we can reformulate the system
description into an equivalent past
focused form.
Characterizing current state and output in
terms of previous state and previous
input.
Formal verification in the logic then
amounts to showing validity status for
formulas of the form Box D sys only if Box
A spec.
To begin with, an exercise for you in
translating specifications into the
language of temporal logic.
Consider a clocked sequential system with
two 1-bit inputs,
p1 and p2, and one 1-bit output, z, such
that.
For all times n, the output z is 1 and
time
n if and only if time n is at least 3.
And the inputs p1 and p2 are the same
value at times
n minus 1 and n minus 3, and are the
opposite value at times, time n minus 2.
So, which of these formulas express this
functional description?
Have a go.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
So, how did you go?
Formula a is not correct.
Because the conjunction p1 and p2 does not
capture
the meaning that p1 has the same value as
p2.
The biconditional is needed here.
Formula b is also not correct because we
need previous,
previous p1 if and only if not p2 to get
that, p1
has the opposite value to p2 at time n
minus 2.
Formula c is correct.
And so is formula d, which gives
the equivalent future-focused formulation,
using an instance
of the validity scheme from last lesson
relating next and previous across three
time steps.
Our main job for the rest of this lesson
is to
work through the formal verification of
the triple one detector system, T1D.
We will finish off with a brief, but more
general
discussion, of the enterprise of verifying
and validating digital systems.
So, here is the T1D circuit diagram, which
is
summarized by the next-state and output
formulas as shown.
Where we've made explicit the initial
conditions that q1
and q0 must have value zero at time zero.
Now, we'll give the A spec in future focus
form.
Next, next, next z if and only if p and
next p and next, next p.
And for my work last time on fluencies in
logic relative to the flip flops.
We're going to use the past focused
version of the system description.
So let T1D.
T1D, be the conjunction of q1 if and
only if previously p and q 1 or p and q 0.
q0 if and only if previously, p and q1,
or, p
and not q0, and z if and only if q1 and
q0.
For the formal verification of the T1D
system, we then need to prove the validity
of the formula box DT1D, only if box A
spec.
To piece
together the verification we're going to
go
back to the state transition output table.
Since, this was how we derived the formula
DT1D in the first place.
Remember that this table contains all the
content needed to
produce the circuit and the description
formula for the system.
Back in lesson 9-3, we stepped through the
next state entries of that table,
and we did so by assigning meaning to each
of the four state configurations.
Back in lesson 9-3 we had not
yet formalized the semantics of temporal
logic formulas.
So we used a mix of sort
of temporal formulas with previous, the
previous operator
and the time conditions like N equals
zero, N equals one, or N equals two.
We can now fully formalize these state
meetings.
So the got nothing state 00 is expressed
by
the formula, previous not p, or not
previous true.
Since not previous true picks out time n
equals 0.
The got one 1 state, code 01, is expressed
by previous p and previously, previous
p or not previous true, which is another
way of saying, previously in state 00.
The third state, got two ones, is
expressed by previous p and previous,
previous p, and previously previously in
state 00.
And the third state 11 the success state.
Is got three ones is expressed by
previous p and previous, previous p and
previous, previous, previous p.
Finally the output z is expressed by the
conjunction q1 and q0.
Let CT1D be the conjunction of these
current-state output formulas.
So notice that this formula CT1D expresses
our design intention,
but it doesn't come for free, we have to
prove it.
Clearly if we could prove that box DT1D
only if
box CT1D is a validity, then we would be
done
because box CT1D implies the past focused
version of the specification.
However, this is proving more than we
need,
and it would take more time than we have.
So what we really want to pull out from
the formula CT1D is just the last two
conjuncts.
Since these two equivalences give us what
we want.
So it is clear that we're going to have
the validity of the formula box B
T1D only if box A star spec where first
a star spec is the past focused version of
the specification.
And B T1D is the conjunction of the
success state equivalents q1 and q0 if and
only if previous p and
previous, previous p, and previous,
previous, previous, previous p and
the output equivalence z if and only if q1
and q0.
Assembling what we've already got we have
that box
BT1D only if box A star A spec is a
validity.
In the previous lesson 9-4, we show the
validity of box A star spec only if
box A spec, where A spec is the future
focused version of the specification.
So to prove the validity of the
verification
formula, box DT1D only if box A spec, it
remains to
prove the validity of box DT1D only if box
BT1D.
To fill in this last piece, first observe
that there is a valid equivalence
between the description formula D T1D and
the formula D star T1D as shown.
Which is simply obtained by distributing
the previous operator over conjunction and
disjunction.
And applying the tautology expressing the
distribution of, and of/or.
Next note the validity of box D star T1D
only if box
ET1D where this new formula ET1D says
q1 and q0 if and only if previous p and
previous q1.
Now this validity can be shown either
directly, using the
semantics, or else by a short series of
equivalent validities.
So, we've reduced our remaining task to
proving the
validity of box D star T1D implies box
BT1D.
And we're going to use this auxiliary
formula ET1D to accomplish the task.
From the past-focused system description D
star T1D,
we can fully unwind the state signal q1.
The series of equivalences here start with
the q1 formula from D star T1D.
Then on the second line, we substitute
what we know, from D star T1D, into
the q1 and the q0 slots, in the formula
and then
start distributing, the previous operators
over, conjunctions and disjunctions.
Then note that a or true is equivalent to
a, and that a and true is equivalent to a.
In this way, with a few steps, we end up
with the equivalence,
q1 if and only if previous p and previous,
previous p.
Which says, q has value 1 exactly when the
previous two input values of p were 1.
Note that this formula is fully unwound
characterization of q1, because
there are, is no longer, any circular
dependence of q1 on previous
q1, or previous q0, so we have unwound,
the feedback loops.
So summarizing previous slide, we have the
validity of box D star T1D
only if q1 if and only if previous p and
previous, previous p.
And also from previous slide, we have box
D star T1D, only if box ET1D.
Now applying the substitute,
substitutivity of equivalence
principle to the formula ET1D, we get.
In a few steps to the desired conclusion
that q1 and q0, if and only if,
previous p and previous, previous p and
previous, previous, previous p.
So, finally, we are done and we have now
established
the validity of box D star T1D only if box
BT1D.
Putting all our pieces together, we've
done it!
Congratulations, you've made it all the
way through
the formal verification of the triple one
detector system.
High five!
Excellent.
As promised it does take a bit of effort
to
formally verify even a small sequential
system with four state configurations.
Before we finish up, we'll briefly look
more generally
at the enterprise of verifying and/or
validating digital systems.
The most common approach is validation via
simulation and testing.
This involved simulating the system
response to test input
signals to validate that the expected
output is produced.
While computer engineers have developed
extensive principals for the
strategic selection of useful test input
signals, this approach is
still fundamentally limited by the fact
that it only considers
a small sample of the infinitely many
possible input signals.
In contrast, formal verification gives a
rigorous
proof that the system design implements
the specification
and produces the expected output in
response to
all of the infinitely many possible input
signals.
In practice, formal verification is
particularly
valuable, in detecting subtle errors, in
the design that would be difficult to pick
up, via simulation and testing.
Formal verification of logical
correctness, then
needs to be supplemented, with a separate
timing analysis, to ensure real time
constraints
on synchronous memory components can be
satisfied.
For the correct behavior of basic memory
components like the D flip-flop, there are
constraints on what is called the setup
time and the hold time for the device.
The setup time is the minimum amount of
time the
data signal should be held steady before
the clock tick event.
So that the data is reliably sampled by
the clock.
While the hold time is the minimum amount
of time the
data signal should be held steady, after
the clock tick event.
While these times are much smaller, than
the
real time period of the clock, they're not
zero.
So the accumulated propagation delays
through the next
state combinational subcircuit do have to
be analyzed carefully.
This sort of analysis is beyond the scope
of
direct, discrete time temporal logic, and
of us here.
The first three methods can be used all at
the design stage, before the computer chip
is fabricated.
After physical construction, the final
task is hardware testing,
to search for fabrication errors resulting
from layout defects.
As we've seen with triple one detector
system doing formal verification by hand
for even a quite small digital system
requires a non-trivial amount of effort.
Clearly, some computer assistance would be
helpful.
There are a number of both commercial and
educational open source software tools
that can be used for the formal
verification of digital systems using
temporal logic.
Many of the same tools can be used for the
formal verification of computer software
using temporal logic, as well.
Leading hardware industry companies, like
IBM, Intel,
Samsung and Motorola, regularly use formal
verification methods.
Particularly in the design of critical
components whose failure could
have catastrophic consequences for human
life, property or financial loss.
The most common approach goes under the
name, model checking.
And model checking merely is a verb phrase
to describe
the task of determining truth in a model
or valuation.
All the hard work goes into representing
models or valuations.
Within state of the art model checking
tools, explicit model
checking can be done for up to 30 state
signals.
Two to the power 30 state val, values.
While implicit or symbolic representations
of states, allow up to 100
state signals or more, so 2 the the power
100 state values.
So this brings us to the end of this
series of lessons on the logic of
sequential digital systems.
We have seen how sequential systems build
on combinational systems
by adding memory components, digital
clock, state signals and feedback.
And we've seen how to specify, describe,
and
formally verify sequential digital systems
in temporal logic.
We hope we've achieved the modest aim of
providing a basic
understanding of digital systems by
building on your knowledge of core logic.
This series ended up longer than intended
because getting through the formal
verification of
even a simple system like the triple one
detector, takes a fair amount of effort.
So I do hope this has not been off-putting
and that you found the effort worthwhile.
And you can now head off as an educated
person of the twenty first century.
So bye for now.