Is it bad tonight?
Bad. That's one way to describe it.
Insane seems a little more appropriate.
It feels like he's breathing down my neck, man.
It is my professionaI opinion
we should get the hell out of here. Now.
Noted.
Clean this place up, then locate our guests.
I just need to take the edge off.
You know the routine.
I need you clear-headed.
First things first.
Now, where is he?
Show me where he's hiding.
Son of a bitch!
You said he only killed nine people.
There are 40 victims here.
Nine when he was alive.
He's added a few since then.
Now where is he, Dennis?
All teams go to alpha. Bring in the cube!
How did this guy get the name
"The Breaker"? Is he a truck driver?
Simple folkIore.
The locaI color exorcising its demons.
Maybe it's because he broke his victims
into as many pieces as possible.
I hate being rushed.
This one isn't like the others.
- I'll give you a bonus.
- You don't have that kind of money.
After tonight you'll be surprised.
Now, get to work.
CarefuI, Dennis.
Don't get too curious.
Son of a bitch!
How can you justify what you're doing,
Cyrus? It's out and out slavery!
You are persistent, Damon.
And what about you, Kalina?
Still carrying around
those ridiculous quicksilver flares?
You still have that quaint little magicaI book?
These aren't animals you're capturing,
they're human beings.
They are dead human beings.
Maybe you should join Greenpeace.
Throw blood on old women's furs.
Who are you to play God?
- Playing is for children.
- You'll never pull it off.
Not without the right spells.
That, and the thirteenth ghost.
Thirteenth ghost?
Get them out of my sight!
We've wasted too much time already.
Why did he say thirteenth?
Move the cube into position.
What's he talking about, 13 ghosts?
You contracted me for 12 ghosts!
The Breaker is 12!
I'm done after tonight, Cyrus.
Yes. Twelve and then one more.
I thought you were psychic!
That's not how it works, and you know it!
There's no time to argue.
Release the bait!
What bait? We never needed bait before!
A truck full of blood?
You've got to be shitting me.
Oh, boy.
Now...
...power up the cube.
Start transmitting.
Come.
Come!
Help me! Help me!
Oh, shit!
Put him down!
Cyrus, I hope you're happy.
You've got your twelve now.
Help me! He's dying!
Hang on, Damon. Somebody help!
God damn you, Cyrus!
Somebody help me, please!
Help me. Do something!
Oh, Cyrus.
Oh, God.
- Swing me!
- Come on, Bobby.
Faster, Kathy.
Let me get your arms.
Try to drag me.
You're the best little brother.
I love you. Let's go!
I'm going to get you! I'm going to get you!
Look at those two. She's got him
on the run now, but pretty soon...
...he's going to be picking her up
and throwing her over his shoulder.
They're perfect.
Watch them. Watch them.
They really love this place.
I love you.
Surprise!
My heart! My heart!
Happy birthday, Dad!
Happy birthday, Arthur.
Here's my present, Dad.
We love you. Make a wish.
Blow out the candles.
What did you wish for?
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
What's that? Why is the smoke alarm on?
It's the fire alarm.
I'll get the kids. Call the fire department.
Dad! Help, Mom!
Get the kids. Get the kids!
Mom! Dad! Help me!
Where's your mom? Where is she?
I don't know where Mom is.
Bobby, come on! We have to get out. Oh, my God!
Jean! Jean!
Mom's still in the house.
We can't leave her there.
Bobby, go outside. Go wait outside.
You can't go back in there, sir.
I'm sorry, sir. She didn't make it.
I should have gone back in.
We are gathered here today,
to honor the memory...
...and life's work of Jean Kriticos...
...a devoted mother and loving wife...
...who was too quickly taken from this life.
Jean, you will be forever missed,
but never forgotten.
I miss you, Mom.
Why did you have to leave us?
I can't do this without you.
I don't want you to go.
Mom, I love you so much.
Please watch over us.
I'll love you always.
Dad, it's...
It's almost 8:30.
Shake a leg or you'll miss your first class.
Today on Death in America:
"Cancer rates are down...
"... but suicide is sky-high.
"We have a speciaI treat for you today.
"A body was found this morning,
decolopolated. "
"Decapitated. "
Bobby honey, find a healthier hobby.
Leave me alone, you guys, I'm recording.
Good morning, everybody.
Something smells interesting.
Dad, they found a guy without a head
behind Dunkin' Donuts.
I love Dunkin' Donuts.
- Ow, shit!
- Kathy, kathy...
Why don't you let Maggie make breakfast for once.
Honey, that's why we hired her.
Dad, have you tasted Maggie's cooking?
Just that one time.
Hey, I heard that. Hell, I cook better than you.
We have to try to get along here.
Dad, will you tell Kathy that keeping
a record of death is healthy?
Kathy, "Keeping a record of death
is healthy. "
Because she's being a reaI slut about it.
Bobby. Don't call your sister a slut.
Thank you, Maggie.
I prefer the term "bitch. "
See, sluts are girls with loose sex--
Mr. Edgar Allan Poe,
did you do your homework?
Because Mr. Peterson-
Damn it! Bobby for the the third time
I've tripped on that stupid scooter!
- Sorry.
- If we had a bigger place, we wouldn't have this problem.
Well we don't have a big place anymore, do we?
This is the best I can do for now...
...so let's all try and keep our shit
off the floor.
All right? Now, Bobby,
put away the damn tape recorder.
Can you do that for me?
And get ready for schooI.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Must be the lawyer. I forgot.
Lawyer, what lawyer? Dad, our credit
was all cleaned up.
No, I don't think it's about that.
They won't make us move again, will they?
It's gonna be all right.
Whatever it is, we'll deaI with it.
Mr. Kriticos?
That's right. You are?
Ben Moss. How do you do?
Please, come in.
Is now a good time, or...?
As good a time as any.
Please, just give me one minute.
Sorry. I'm ready.
I represent the estate of your uncle
Cyrus Kriticos.
We have an Uncle Cyrus?
Had. I only met him a couple of times
as a kid.
He wasn't too popular.
My dad said
he squandered the family fortune.
We have a family fortune?
No. Cyrus squandered it.
Bobby, isn't that great?
You got a late uncle.
- What is he late for?
- His next birthday.
You mean, he's dead?
- Now we get his attention.
- Pipe down.
Cyrus recorded this message
six weeks ago.
He asked that it be played for you
in the event of his death.
Arthur...
...it's good to talk to you.
Sadly, if you're watching this now,
it means I am no longer among the living.
Happily, that makes you and your family
my sole beneficiaries.
I've instructed my lawyer, Mr. Moss...
...to deliver the essential elements
in my last will and testament.
Give it to them, Ben.
A key?
A key to what?
A key to your new house.
What?
This house is the fruit of my life's work.
Bathrooms.
Everyone gets their own bathroom.
Is this for reaI?
It is a one-of-a-kind home.
It's my home, actually.
My home.
I have no complaints.
I've led an interesting life.
I have seen some amazing things.
But the only regret I have, is that
I never got to know my nephew Arthur...
...nor appreciate the love of a family,
like you have.
This house is my attempt
to make up for that.
Enjoy.
Perhaps we'll meet again...
...in another life.
- Wow!
- When can we see it?
The house is yours whenever you like.
I'm heading up there after work.
If you want, you, your wife and kids-
Time-out. I am not the missus here.
My wife...
My wife is...
- Our mom got burned to death in a fire.
- Bobby!
What? It's true.
That's enough, Robert.
Mr. Moss, exactly where is this place?
A couple hours drive from here,
a town called Willow Grove...
...just up the parkway.
It's in a gorgeous area. But I have to
warn you, your uncle liked his privacy.
There isn't a neighbor for miles.
Come on. Hurry up.
S-U-F.
Suffocate. I got it. I win.
So what? You think you're so slick.
Come on, you guys. We're almost there.
- Excited?
- Yeah. Mom would have freaked over this.
Looks like things are
starting to get better, right?
Yeah.
That's strange.
Dad, it's beautifuI.
My God. I've never seen anything like it.
CooI!
So futuroic.
It's about time somebody showed up.
Is this your place?
- Who are you?
- I'm the power guy.
Don't touch.
Your house is knocking out the power
of the whole tri-quad area.
I need to get inside
and check the breakers.
Could you come back tomorrow?
Is that maybe a possibility?
Tomorrow? Let me see.
Oh, there's about 5,570 houses
right now without power.
My bosses kind of frown on that, so...
Right, well that's not really our problem, is it?
Look, buddy, I've been doing this job
for about three weeks.
Is there any way you can give
me a little bit of a break here?
Sure.
No problem.
Thank you.
Mr...?
Kriticos. Arthur Kriticos.
It's quite a place you've got.
Yeah. We're moving in.
One step at a time.
- That's odd.
- Dad, you broke it.
Bobby, give it a rest.
Hello.
Wow! You can see right through it.
What, you guys couldn't afford any walls?
How weird.
Guess Uncle Cyrus wasn't too keen
on privacy.
I sure hope the bathroom's in the basement...
It's like a funhouse.
It's Latin.
Everything's so beautifuI.
Family, just so we're all clear,
Miss Maggie does not do windows, O.K?
Wow!
What an incredible wealth of knowledge.
- A samurai sword.
- Bobby!
In your dreams, paI.
Dad, this stuff must be worth a fortune.
Yeah, that occurred to me, too.
Oh, Cyrus.
You crazy son of a bitch, what did you do?
Goodness.
It's like a cathedraI.
All right, first rule: No throwing stones.
It's marvelous, though, isn't it?
A living work of art.
The sooner you show me
where you hid the basement...
...the sooner I can get my ass out of here.
I believe it's down the hall.
It's two doors on the right.
Excuse me.
The construction is amazing.
I'm getting dizzy.
Bobby.
Don't touch anything. Okay?
At least untiI we get property insurance.
Arthur, we've got some papers to sign
in the library.
After that, I'd love to give you
and your family a tour of the house.
Great. I don't want you guys to move
from this spot.
We'll be right back.
Dad, you're being paranoid and overprotective.
Yeah, of all this stuff.
I know you guys too well. Stay...
...right here. I mean it.
What the...?
Where'd you hide your money, old man?
Oh! Shit!
What the hell was that?
Oh, no.
Oh, Cyrus.
Alright, now I know I'm dreaming.
Was Cyrus a hunter?
You could say that.
Your uncle was quite a collector
of many things.
I've marked where
you're supposed to sign, Arthur.
Okay, look.
I didn't want to bring this up
in front of the kids...
...but this place is beyond amazing.
I'm just a math teacher.
The taxes alone must be...
I have nothing set aside.
To be honest, a fire took away everything.
Arthur, you don't need to worry.
Cyrus was a genius
when it came to finances.
Basically, you and your family don't
ever have to worry about money again.
Son of a bitch.
Lookee here. Look, y'all.
Look, look!
Sign.
Arthur?
Arthur, we've got to...
We have to talk.
What is the deaI with the breakers?
There's nothing wrong with the breakers.
I'm not the power guy. My name is Dennis Rafkin.
- You're Dennis Rafkin?
- Who's Dennis Rafkin?
My office warned me about this guy.
I know this will sound completely
whacked, but just stay with me.
I used to hunt displaced spirituaI energies
with your uncle.
I'm sorry?
PK agents. Revenants. Wraiths. Wraiths?
Do you have any idea
what I'm talking about?
That's okay, I'll do this the easy way: ghosts.
Arthur, I used to...
I used to hunt ghosts
with your Uncle Cyrus.
Goats?
Ghosts! Ghosts, goddamn it!
Listen to me!
Race you to the end of the hall.
No, Bobby, I don't think this is the place-
Come on, slowpoke!
Is that the best you got?
My grandma scoots better than that.
Ghosts. As in disgruntled spirits
trapped on earth. Ghosts.
As in Halloween? Boo?
As in Demi Moore
and Unchained Melody. Ghosts.
Ghosts. Okay, I get it. I'm scared.
Don't laugh at me. Don't laugh.
I'll explain everything...
...as soon as you get
you and your children outside.
- What's taking you so long?
- Out of my way.
- I don't think scooting is your game.
- Come on.
- I won.
- You cheated. That wasn't fair. I didn't get a start.
Got to be on your toes, man.
This has to be my room.
There are toys everywhere.
- I wonder what my room's gonna look like.
- And now entering the coolest room in the house.
I'll be in here.
This place is awesome!
Look, Cyrus has containment
cubes all over the basement.
I don't know why they're here...
...and I am not staying around to find out.
- So, if I were you-
- Well, he isn't you.
This guy has been harassing my office
since your uncle died.
I see this all the time.
Some rich guy passes away
and all the nuts come out!
Next thing, he'll be claiming
Cyrus owned him money or-
He did owe me money.
He owed me a shitload of money!
These are some funky-looking specs here.
- What do you think? Do I look cooI or what?
- Let me see.
Not so fast. You gotta cater to my ego first:
"Maggie's the best babysitter
you ever had. "
- Come on!
- All right.
I'm getting my ass
out of the big glass house!
Grab your children! Do the same.
Are you all right?
Jean! Jean!
We'll go get you some help. Okay?
Don't touch me.
Oh, my God!
We've struck gold.
- Easy.
- Don't.
How's your head?
Not good.
Where's the suit?
Power guy. Idiot.
Whoa, cooI!
Better have a pair of those in my room.
Bobby, where are you going?
What are you staring at?
Hey, kiddo.
He thinks I'm going to duck.
Hey... nice tits.
What's the matter, honey?
Bad representation?
Not bad for an hourly wage.
It's time to leave.
I'll take your word for it.
Kathy?
Come on. This way.
Shit! What the hell? Kathy!
Maggie? Bobby!
Hey, I uhh...
I was just kidding before.
A little lawyer humor.
Really?
Kathy?
Bobby!
I don't believe it.
Believe what?
- I told them not to leave this spot.
- They're kids, what do you expect?
Thank you, Dr. PhiI. You check downstairs.
I'II look up.
Bobby, come on! It's time to go!
Kathy? Where are you guys?
Bobby!
I'm sorry.
What are you doing up here?
I told you to wait downstairs.
Yeah but Dad, come on.
This bathroom is unbelievable.
Great house. BeautifuI bathroom.
Now, where is your brother?
He's with Maggie.
Was with Maggie. We were racing
and we saw all the glass-
That's good. You're supposed to
watch him. That's what I pay you for.
Bobby.
Down here.
Maggie?
Come on down and play.
Is that you?
Maggie?
Stop playing games.
Bobby? I have something for you.
We'll have lots of fun.
Don't come down, Bobby.
Stay upstairs.
Don't follow her.
Down here, Bobby.
Bobby, don't come down, honey.
Bobby? Around the corner.
Don't come down here!
That's it.
You guys, I'm gonna tell Dad!
Bobby!
I'll find Bobby.
But I want you both out of here.
- But, Dad-
- No "buts"!
I want you both to wait in the car.
I'll be out as soon as I find the kid.
- Why are you freaking out?
- Just this once, don't argue with me.
What happened to the door?
Son of a bitch!
I cannot believe this.
I'm going to have to break it down.
Back away!
It's quite dramatic...
...but you're wasting your time.
It's all sealed up.
- Weren't you in an orange jumpsuit?
- Don't go there.
What do you mean, "all sealed up"?
What part of that code
are you having trouble cracking?
The entire house is sealed up.
- There must be another way out.
- I've looked.
We'II look again, right after I find my son.
Now get up.
That's all right, I'll wait right here.
I don't know what the hell is going on here,
I really don't know who the hell you are.
And my son is missing.
So, untiI those questions are answered,
I'm not letting you out of my sight.
Now, get up!
All right. Breathe.
Did the lawyer split?
Bobby.
Come on, guys! Stop hiding!
Bobby!
- Bobby.
- Come on out now, paI!
Stop screwing around.
Glass family Robinson,
you're wasting your breath.
This is ectobar glass. He's not gonna hear you.
This is shatterproof and soundproof.
What are these?
That's a little harder to explain.
They're containment spells.
Ghosts can't cross those.
- Ghosts?
- Yes, ghosts.
The supernaturaI realm has its own
set of laws. For ghosts, it's spells.
Written or spoken, the ghosts
have to obey whatever the spells say.
The entire basement is filled with ghosts.
In this basement?
Of course, in this basement.
What is it with you people?
If it was next door, I wouldn't give a shit!
Dad!
- I can prove it.
- Hey, I gave a pair of those to Bobby.
SpectraI viewers.
You can see ghosts with these.
Bobby, come on.
- I don't see any ghosts.
- Because they're locked downstairs.
Dad!
There's more of this crazy spell shit
on the floor.
Let me see those.
Bobby! Come on out, paI!
Hidden barrier spells. You gotta be kiddin' me.
Why would he need more protection?
All right, that's enough.
This is not helping.
I want you to do me a favor and stop
with all the haunted house nonsense...
...at least untiI we find the kid
and figure a way out of here.
Bobby, come on.
I don't know where he could be.
Wait, no, no, no, no!
Wait, no!
What are you doing? What did I just say,
that there was a petting zoo downstairs?
No!
There are ghosts downstairs, Arthur.
Right, right. But you also said...
...that they're all locked up. Right?
- No. No way.
- Wait.
Listen.
I'll make a deaI with you.
I'll pay you whatever Cyrus owed you...
...if you just help me...
...find my son.
Unbelievable. Get out of my way.
Bobby.
Get out of the basement.
You need to go upstairs.
You need to put on those glasses.
Leave me alone!
That's it. That's a good boy.
Bobby.
Go upstairs and find your father.
Mom?
Go on.
Go upstairs!
Go find Kathy.
Watch out.
Bobby! Come on!
You don't have to scream, all right? Just...
...chill.
- This way.
- Hold on. Listen to me.
This will take forever.
This place is just too big.
Kathy and I will head up this way.
You two check down there.
- No, I don't think we should split up.
- It's okay.
Go in a straight line, turn around.
We'll meet back here in five.
Five. Back here.
Don't touch anything.
- I don't want to go with him!
- Go ahead.
Wait a second.
Let's go back to the ghost thingy.
There are ghosts in the basement.
If you don't believe me, look for yourself.
I told you, I can't see any ghosts.
What the hell? Give me those.
Let me see. Why are these open?
I was down here before.
They weren't open.
- Oh, God! I hate it when they do that!
- Do what?
They wait for you to stick your face
right up against the glass, then give you...
...a big, fat "boo"!
Don't do that!
God.
You see it?
- It's, it's...
- A ghost. It's a ghost!
Just like I've been saying all night!
Finally, a believer! Thank you O Lord Jesus!
There are ghosts around us all the time.
Most of them can't hurt us.
Most don't even wanna hurt us. A little
ghost here, a little ghosts there, no one cares.
But there are exceptions,
like this badass behind me.
The ones who die violent deaths stay in
a tortured realm, so that's all they know.
What is he doing?
I don't know. I can't see.
I don't have the glasses.
Okay, I've had it with this. It's time to go.
- Now! Please!
- Don't touch me.
Will you come on?
Come on, ghost boy! Move your ass!
It's time to go.
Dad, slow down. We're going to get lost.
Dad! Aaahhh!!
Dad.
Listen to me.
He's going to be okay.
We're going to find him.
I am so ready to leave this place.
- Oh, boy.
- What?
- That's the symboI of The JackaI.
- What's The JackaI?
The JackaI is the Charlie Manson of ghosts.
And if The Jackal's out, screw the kid.
We've got to get out of this basement.
Maybe Rafkin was right, and maybe there-
Kathy!
Think about what you're saying.
There is no such thing as ghosts.
Kathy.
Kathy!
What is it? I can't see it!
Tell me where it is!
Get off!
Hold on! Stay with me!
Come on, pull!
- Who are you?
- Never mind, just pull, god damn it!.
Shit! Don't speak. Don't move.
Somehow...
...we got behind enemy lines.
Hurry!
Please, hurry!
Hey, little guy.
- How.
- I don't think you should be teasing the ghosts.
- Will you shut up?
- You shut up. You're the one that keeps pissing them off.
Go.
- Maggie!
- What?
Where?
I can't see shit without the glasses, idiot!
Well, I can see.
And I think you should go this way!
Go, go!
It's all right. I've got you.
Look at me.
Daddy.
It's okay.
Who the hell are you?
And what the hell was that?
My name is Kalina Oretzia.
I'm in the spirit reclamation business.
What?
I free trapped souls. Cyrus-
Forget Cyrus and trapped souls
for a goddamned second.
What are you doing here?
Looks to me like I'm saving your ass.
Oh, my God!
It's over there! It's over there!
Give him your glasses.
Come on!
Oh, my God.
Unbelievable.
Another one of Cyrus's victims.
I hope to God the barrier spells hold.
Victims?
Cyrus had a nasty habit of enslaving souls.
That's why I'm here.
I intend to set them all free.
Listen to me.
I need to know...
...how you got in here.
I slipped through an opening in the house
when it shifted.
- An opening where?
- Don't get your hopes up. It's closed now. It won't happen again.
Let me show you. This is the Arcanum.
Many people died
in the quest for this book.
It was written in the 15th century
by an astrologer named Basileus.
In it, he describes
the making of a certain machine.
One that can see into the future.
He wrote it while he was under
demonic possession.
I can't believe Cyrus built it.
Built what? What are you talking about?
Basileus's device.
We're in the middle of a machine, designed
by the deviI and powered by the dead.
Listen to me.
I don't give a shit about any machine...
...or deviI or Basileus or anything...
...except getting my family
the hell out of this place.
I came here
to set the souls in this house free.
You want help, you have to help me first.
Kathy, can you walk?
Kathy! Oh, no. This can't be happening!
- We have to get out of here.
- I'm not going anywhere without my kids.
Try telling him that.
Come on.
This way. Come on.
Stairs. Let's go.
Go. You go!
Don't touch me!
Wait! The glasses!
You'll need these! Catch!
- Good job.
- Sorry.
Perfect. Another dead end.
Okay, genius, we found the stairs.
How do we get to them?
- Get away.
- What? What do we do now?
Get away from the glass.
- Why?
- Just do it.
Glasses.
Duck!
Move! Go left!
Do something, for Christ's sake!
We're running out of corridors!
Duck! Go left! Go right! Move!
Get down!
Here. We've got to get to the library.
It has spell protection all around it.
Where is that from here?
Can I rely on you not to get me killed?
I guarantee nothing.
See anything?
- Anything?
- No.
Come on.
I think they're just downstairs.
Nothing.
If we get out of this alive,
I've got to get a pay raise.
That's a big "if. "
Give me the flare.
What's wrong?
Don't start freaking out now. Come on.
What?
- Okay. What?
- Shut up.
Give me the book.
Just back up.
Go. Slow.
- I'm going slow.
- Slow.
Go! Go!
Fast!
- What the hell?
- Who the hell?
What the hell are you doing here?
Shit!
Remember me?
Thanks for taking your time.
Go down the hall. Turn left, then right.
- Where are we going?
- Trust me, okay?
- Arthur?
- Trust her.
Okay, let's go!
- Who the hell is she?
- I'll explain her later.
What happened to Kathy?
I don't know, she disappeared.
How do you lose an entire family
in a glass house?
Arthur!
Kalina, give me a flare!
Get him! Go! Get up!
This is not the time to be a girI! Run!
Stop dragging your ass, man! Go!
Oh, my God! Go! Run!
Now is not the time
to sit around, Arthur! Run!
Get the door. Close the door!
Arthur, are you all right?
God, what's going on here?
Fucking ghosts.
I hate this job.
They don't seem to like you, either. I wonder why.
You got something to say, say it.
All right. Let's start with:
This is all your goddamn fault!
If you hadn't caught them,
we wouldn't be running from them.
It was his uncle that built the house!
You helped him. How could you help him
without knowing what he was doing?
- I had my reasons.
- Money, you parasite.
You stole people's souls for money!
How depraved is that?
If you haven't noticed, I'm a little bit of a freak!
I come within 10 feet of anything dead,
I go into seizures.
I touch somebody, a whole life full of shit
flashes in front of my eyes.
So, yeah, I'm depraved.
But Cyrus was my friend,
and he accepted me.
He didn't accept you. You're so pathetic!
- He used you.
- Shut up, both of you.
Cut him some slack.
What difference does it make?
You didn't tell him, did you?
Oh, God, tell me what? What now?
About the fourth ghost.
Don't do this. I didn't tell him.
He has a right to know.
What about the fourth ghost?
St. Luke's HospitaI. Six months ago.
You're saying my wife's spirit...
...is trapped in this house?
I didn't know you.
I didn't know her.
I didn't know she had a husband.
Why? In God's name, why?
Tell me, why her?
I don't know. Cyrus handpicked them,
including your wife.
I figured out who you were
and I've been trying to help you.
You call this help? She's right!
This is all your goddamn fault!
Son of a bitch!
You can save her. And your kids, too.
Just listen to me and believe me.
This house is not a house.
It is a machine.
A complete and faithfuI re-creation
of Basileus's design.
According to this, there should be
12 earth-bound spirits trapped inside.
See these?
They represent the black zodiac.
They represent the ghosts that
Cyrus needed to catch: The First-Born Son.
I don't want to play.
The Torso.
The Bound Woman.
The Withered Lover.
Jean.
Bobby. I love you.
The Torn Prince.
The Angry Princess.
I'm sorry.
The Pilgrimess.
The Great Child and the Dire Mother.
The Hammer.
And here, the sign of Hell's Winter:
The JackaI.
And The Juggernaut.
According to Basileus, the machine required the energy...
...of these specific spirits
in order to bring it to life.
Once it engages,
the spirits are released one by one.
The house then draws them to its center.
Each one adds its energy to the machine,
powering it up.
Powering it up for what?
To open the Ocularis Infernum.
What's that?
It's Latin.
Ocularis Infernum. The Eye of Hell?
Very good.
The Eye of Hell. I'm stuck in a glass house
with crazy white people...
Go on.
In hell, there is an eye
that sees everything, the past, the future...
...heaven and earth,
the blessed, the damned.
If knowledge is power,
then the man who controls the Ocularis...
...would be the most powerfuI
man on earth.
Your uncle.
Great.
So...
...how many ghosts have been set free?
Eleven. And the house needs twelve.
No. Damon said something about thirteen.
That there are thirteen ghosts.
The thirteenth ghost is a faiI-safe.
To stop the process, the house needs
a sacrifice of life instead of death.
A willing, human sacrifice.
A sacrifice of the broken heart.
The only ghost to be created
out of an act of pure love.
You're the thirteenth ghost.
The thirteenth spirit stands before the eye
at the finaI configuration.
As the eye opens,
the spirit uses the power of life...
...to short-circuit the system.
Uses the power of life how?
By leaping into the eye.
And Arthur's supposed to take this leap?
No fucking way, lady.
That's suicide. I won't let you do it.
You need to come up with something else.
That's not working.
Love is the most powerfuI energy.
Meaning?
In order for you to save your children,
you must trade your life for theirs.
Let me see this.
There's got to be a better way.
I don't read Latin.
Well, we can try it the old-fashioned way,
my personaI favorite.
Nobody will be here
to brag about it afterwards.
We need to come up with
a game plan soon. Time's running out.
Are you going to blow the place up?
The last ghost is about to be released.
- I know why you feeI you have to do this.
- Get away from me.
Psychics call it a "linking. "
We linked earlier. I saw everything...
...about Jean, about you.
Shut up.
I'm not going to listen to this from you.
Kalina is talking about suicide.
Whatever I have to do to save my kids.
It doesn't add up.
It doesn't make any sense.
There's got to be a better way.
"Doesn't add up"?
What does add up here, Dennis?
How much of this equation
makes any sense at all?
Goddamn it. Goddamn it.
AII I can think about are my kids.
I don't even know if they're alive.
Then let's go out there and find out.
One last time,
while there's still time, you and me.
Kalina...
...no matter what I decide to do,
or what happens to any of us...
...are you sure
you can you stop that machine?
I've got enough explosives
to blow us back to the 15th century.
Okay.
- How many flares do you have left?
- One, why?
We're going out again.
No fucking way, Arthur.
You're going to get yourself killed.
Not if we take that.
We got about ten minutes
untiI the ectoplasmic shit hits the fan.
Go.
We'll go downstairs to try
and buy you some more time.
After you, Captain America.
Damn. I just got my nails done.
Here. Put these on.
Come on, let's go!
"There's no place like home. "
"There's no place like home.
There's no place like home.
"There's no place like home. "
Knock it off, Dennis.
Just keep your eyes open.
I sure as hell hope I don't bleed to death.
That would suck.
Rotate.
Is that half the lawyer?
Here, take this. Move it.
Oh, my God. He definitely looked better.
Oh, my God. Shit.
GirI, hurry up!
- Ram him!
- He's swinging for the fences!
Kalina, get over here!
This flare shit ain't working! Hurry up!
Where is it?
Kalina?
Why are you so mad at me?
I did everything you asked me to do.
I killed Damon, I stole his spells.
I even made sure your pathetic
nephew didn't get himself killed!
Kalina!
Where are the spells?
You're not mad at me, are you?
Of course not.
- What is it?
- Oh, shit.
There's only room for one of us back there.
What are you doing?
Don't worry about it, Arthur. I've been looking
for a reason to like myself for a long time.
Dennis, don't do this!
Hey, bro. You ain't nothing but a bitch!
Dennis, no!
Oh, my God.
What do we do now?
Your nephew believes
that sacrificing himself will save his kids.
But he won't do it unless he's
convinced his kids are in jeopardy.
- Well, put them in jeopardy.
- What?
- Why not?
- But they're kids.
Greatness requires sacrifice.
Now, I have a job to do.
And so have you.
Do it. Do it!
Yes.
And now to finish this.
Oh, my God. Jean.
I loved you so much.
I miss you.
Miss you.
I'm nothing without you.
Don't go.
Fetch the book.
Cyrus! What are you doing?
You just can't teach some people.
I thought I told you,
greatness requires sacrifice.
- Kathy!
- Bobby, don't look.
I wanna look!
Kathy, I'm scared!
Kathy!
Kathy! Bobby!
Daddy!
Bobby!
Dad, help!
Oh, my...
Make it stop, Dad! Make it stop!
This house is not a house. It is a machine...
...designed by the devil...
...and powered by the dead.
According to Basileus, there should be
12 earth-bound spirits trapped inside.
They represent the black zodiac.
They represent the ghosts
that Cyrus needed to catch:
- The First-Born Son.
- One.
- The Torso.
- Two.
- The Bound Woman.
- Three.
- The Withered Lover.
- Four.
The Torn Prince.
The Angry Princess. The Pilgrimess.
The Great Child and the Dire Mother.
The Hammer. The Jackal.
And The Juggernaut.
Twelve.
You're the thirteenth ghost.
If I'm the thirteenth...
You son of a bitch!
Release my kids, you bastard!
Damn you! You're nothing, Arthur!
Do you hear? You loser!
I've dedicated my entire life to this.
Every waking moment, for years.
Have you ever shown
that kind of dedication? Have you?
The world has no time
for little people like you.
It needs people
who are willing to do anything!
Anything for greatness.
You don't have a choice this time, Arthur.
You will make that leap.
The machine requires
a ghost to be created...
...out of an act of pure love.
That's why I chose you, nephew.
You and your pathetic family.
Make it stop, Dad!
Congratulations,
you get to become the thirteenth ghost.
Now, get on your feet!
Come on!
Trust me, Arthur. It's not over yet.
You can finish this.
You still have the power in you.
It's just a matter of how you use it.
Go to your kids. They need you.
Dad! Help!
Daddy, don't! Don't do it!
Oh, fuck!
Dad!
Don't move!
Keep your heads down!
Hold on tight!
Everybody okay?
You okay?
How did you know we'd be safe here?
I didn't.
I just wasn't about to leave you guys.
I love you both so much.
Mom?
I love you guys.
I love you.
This is it for me.
I am on the first fuckin' plane back to Newark.
I am sorry, family, Kathy,
Bobby, Uncle, ghosts...
...I am sick of this nanny shit.
I've had it.
This was not in the job description. I quit!