Finally l saw the status of Yokogawa
and Tokyo in bomb
l stared the view of
both side of the road.
And the expression of the men
and lady on the road.
my impression is...
the factories in Yokogawa
and Tokyo are disappeared in the bomb.
This time l felt the truth meaning.
whatever men or lady
they and what l saw
before 22 years in Japan.
already so much difference.
Who changed it?
it cannot do not let them take it...
Who we are going to judge.
they disturbed the world.
tormented China.
And ruined the future of their country.
a state had good future.
therefore result in the fate.
Do evil by themselves.
this is a tragedy in the history
Also an retribution
We affirm that,
as members of the lnternational
Military Tribunal for the Far East,
we will duly administer
justice according to law,
without fear, favor or affection,
according to our conscience,
and the best of our understanding,
and that we will not disclose
or discover
the vote or opinion of any
particular member of the Tribunal
upon finding or sentence,
but will preserve the inviolate secrecy
of the counsel of every member.
We swear to God.
Please sit down.
Before we start, there are a few things
l would like to clarify
First of all,
we don't need to be overly polite
among ourselves.
Please just call me William.
We should treat each other as equals
and consider ourselves one big family.
l hope this would be a pleasant experience
for all of us.
As this trial will be conducted
on the basis of the Common Law System,
the seating of the judges
will be as follows:
The United States, Britain,
China, the Soviet Union, Canada
France, Australia, the Netherlands,
lndia, New Zealand, and the Philippines.
l will not accept that arrangement.
Pardon me. What do you mean?
l believe the seating order of the judges
in this trial should follow the order
of signatures on
the Japanese lnstrument of Surrender.
China was second on the list.
Therefore, the judge from China should be
seated right after the United States.
My dear Mei, this is a courtroom,
not a reenactment of surrender.
Then perhaps,
Sir William could explain his reasons
for this arrangement?
Dr. Mei, this is has been
the common practice.
What common practice? Whose practice?
lsn't following the order of signatures in
the lnstrument of Surrender a common practice?
Dr. Mei, we are here to
judge war criminals.
Why are you making fuss
over such a trivial matter?
This is no trivial matter.
Besides, Our concern here is what's
right and what's wrong.
There's nothing trivial about it.
Dr. Mei, then please suggest a fair method.
lf we are not going to follow the order
on the lnstrument of Surrender...
Maybe... it might even be the fairest...
we'll put ourjudges on the scale,
and the seating arrangement
will be determined by weight
Dr. Mei, the method you suggest
is eminently fair,
but would only be appropriate
for boxing matches.
This is a courtroom, not a boxing ring.
lf the seating arrangement is
not to be determined by weight,
then the only fair method
is to follow the order
on the Japanese lnstrument of Surrender.
l have no wish at all to allow
this international tribunal
to become a boxing ring.
Stop!
Chinese pig! Get out of Japan!
We were beaten to American,
Not China! Get out!
Cooperate with US.
Gendarme, finished the enquiry.
driver was kept back temporarily.
For the further enquiry
xiao Nan and
l was both ashamed to the driver.
Also sigh with emotion.
Come in.
Dr Mei,
there will be a rehearsal for tomorrow's
opening ceremony at 4:00 this afternoon.
Please be there on time
and wear yourjudicial robe;
photographers will be present.
Thank you
Good afternoon, sit down.
Since the lnternational Military Tribunal
for the Far East formally
begins hearing its cases tomorrow,
l will announce the seating order of
the judges for final dress rehearsal today...
The seating order
of the judges is as follows:
United States, Britain,
China, the Soviet Union, Canada,
France, Australia, the Netherlands, lndia,
New Zealand and the Philippines...
Dr. Mei, please let me explain.
Please calm down and listen
l'm listening
The main reason l placed the American
and British judges on my left and right
is because they have a better
understanding of the Common Law,
which would make this
trial fun more smoothly.
This decision absolutely does not reflect
any prejudice against China...
Forgive me for being frank.
We all know that this is
an international tribunal,
not British or American.
l don't see any need to seat the American
and British judges in the center.
Dr. Mei,
please look at this problem
from a different angle.
With this arrangement,
you will be seated between
the American and French judges,
instead of next to the Russian general.
l would imagine that would please you.
Sir William, that's insulting.
As a Chinese,
it is my solemn duty to remind you
that l didn't come to Tokyo to be pleased.
My homeland China has been invaded
and plundered by the Japanese
for over fifty years.
To the Chinese people,
trying Japanese war criminals
is a heavy responsibility,
a grave responsibility.
We are not here for pleasure.
Doctor Mei, l would like to
solemnly remind you as well that.
this seating arrangement
originated from an order given
by the Supreme Commander,
General MacArthur himself
lt would be extremely unfortunate if your
refusal to accept this seating arrangement
were to cause friction
in Chinese-American relations.
Your government might not
agree with your decisions.
l refuse to accept this arrangement
that has ground at all in any law or reason.
ln this war against Japanese aggression
China has suffered the most
and fought the longest,
the hardest.
The Britain, on the other hand, has been
retreating and surrendering time and time again.
lt's unthinkable that
China's place in this trial
should be relegated to
a spot below Britain.
l do not believe the government of
China will agree to this arrangement...
ln addition,
l don't believe that this seating arrangement
came from the Supreme Commander himself
Hold on. Let me discuss this
with the otherjudges first.
l'll have an answer for you in ten minutes.
Dr. Mei, l'm sorry to disappoint you,
but my colleagues unanimously see today
just as a dress rehearsal
and nothing more.
Why don't we just take
a few pictures at the rehearsal now,
and then tonight we'll open
a full discussion regarding
the actual seating order of
tomorrow's court?
Sir William,
l have to disappoint you as well.
l definitely will not participate in
the rehearsal for this seating arrangement.
The whole world's photographers
and reporters in rehearsal
are now out there in the courtroom.
They are going to take photos
and write reports on this seating arrangement.
When these reports and photos reach China,
do you know what's going to happen?
The entire Chinese people will all
reproach me for my weakness
and my incompetence.
lf l agree to this arrangement,
l'll be insulting my country.
l'd be insulting
all my countrymen's suffering,
sacrifice, and perseverance
in resisting the Japanese aggression.
Everything.
Sir William, can you understand?
lt is for this reason that
l will not take take in this rehearsal.
As for myself, l will report the matter back
to my government to see if they support me.
lf they don't, l shall resign immediately
and ask them to replace me.
Please do not leave. How about this?
l'll get our colleagues' opinion
on this again
l absolutely don't want you to go.
l'll be back in no more than ten minutes.
Alright, l'll wait another ten minutes.
Dr. Mei, you win.
Your country should be
proud to have a fighter like you.
l'm not a fighter.
l'm ajudge, a Chinese judge.
My dear Mei, can you do me a little favor?
Of course.
Call me William.
William.
Good evening, please give me some wine.
Yousuko,
come here and join us
What's a pity, maybe next time will be ok.
For Japan's failuer, cheers!
Mr Shino,
we have promised that we don't talk
bout the War any more!
Don't talk about the War
For our friendship, cheers
But Japan failed in the war
Japan really failed?
What's the purprose for your coming back?
With the prond of a winner,
to display your strength to us?
Or to talk about the past with Yousuko?
Do you know how Yousuko survived
in the American army's bombs?
American army throw out 2500 tons of bombs,
Tokyo's 35 sections were blowed down,
80000 people losed their lives
ln Hiroshima
and Nagazaki,
10000 people were died
They were all common people
Did they have any fault?
But do you konw hao many people died
in Shanghai and Nanjing?
Wuhan bomb, Chongqing bomb,
Huabei butcher,
Do you konw how many Chinese common people
died in Japan Army?
Do you know how
many Chinese women were raped?
That's a lie!
That's a lie for your political purpose!
Were there any turth
in your newspaper?
Youiqi!
You care about him?
The family
due to the war.
lost happiness.
Fangzi talk to xiaoNan.
brother and ZhengFu
were back from the war,
drunk everyday.
Nobody know
what happen in china.
Fang Zi and her sister YingZi.
since they have left school,
for responsing the Dong Tiao council.
joined the battle service group.
Have never been heard of since.
xiao Nan is the journalist
who was sent to Tokyo
by Dagong Newspaper
before the war starting
he was studying at Tokyo,
Fangzi and xiaonan were his classmate.
xiang, try to look
a little more enthusiastic.
Don't forget this is a historic moment.
The whole world is watching us!
This whole situation just makes me
a little uncomfortable.
What's that?
l feel like l'm putting on a show here.
Court.
Please sit down.
The lnternational Military Tribunal
for the Far East is now in session.
All the defendants of this case
were once leaders of Japan
for the past several decades
when Japanese power was at its peak.
They include prime ministers,
foreign ministers,
treasury ministers, chiefs of staff
and military high commanders.
No matter how high they once stood,
their treatment now is no different from
that of the lowest of ordinary soldiers.
We will assure the defendants
that a careful examination will be made
before this court regarding
the number and nature
of the prosecution charges filed
against them in the indictment,
along with the declaration of
all the applicable laws.
Honorable presiding judge
and members of the court,
l am Joseph Keenan,
the chief prosecutor for this lnternational
Military Tribunal for the Far East
and for the United States of America,
The charter of the lnternational Military
Tribunal for the Far East clearly stipulates
five separate charges with which
the defendants have been indicted,
as listed:
premeditation, organization,
initiation, and
or execution of a war
in violation of international law,
treaties, agreements or assurances.
ln addition to these charges,
participation in a common plan
or conspiracy for the accomplishment
of any of the foregoing is also
an offense against humanity...
Toujyou, l'll kill you
l'll kill you
Bring this people out of the court.
Next,
the lnternational Military Tribunal for
the Far East will hear the defendants' please
to the charges brought by the prosecution.
l ask Mr Web for blench this justment.
Anyone with any objections
on how this courtroom
is ran should put them in writing.
The defense's oral argument
is completely out of line.
This is an despicable ambush comparable
to the sneak attack on Pearl Harbor.
l insisted on my request.
and l challenge
the qualification of all judges.
Control yourself.
He's provoking you on purpose.
This trial totally base on
the haughty and bias of the Kultur.
base on the nongovernmental spirit that
winner is king and the loser is thief.
judging the civilian life
who exert their utmost effort
for asia peace and co-prosperity.
l doubt the court's equity.
also feel sorrow
for the dignity of the law.
Silence! Mr. Defense attorney,
the courtroom is not preaching grounds for
your theories or for your to set conditions.
Your first point concerns me personally.
Therefore, l withhold myself
from the decision the otherjudges will
make in a conference later.
l also don't think the other ten judegs
have the qualification of
the lnternational Military Tribunal.
So l think the conference ofjudges
will not be fair, too.
l object!
Then in your opinion,
what do you think would be fair?
Super court in United States of America.
That's completely out of question!
Court is adjourned.
How could an international court
compose of eleven judges appointed by
their respective democratic governments
and organized by the best
minds of international law
lack the decorum of one
federal court?
This is absolute provocation.
Since l've been the target,
l'm willing to abide by
the ruling of a conference ofjudges.
Ougawajyumei which seemed crazy at court
was theorist of the Japanese
racialism and militaristic.
And the September eighteen
incident's direct organizer.
after identified by allied
forces' legal medical expert.
identified he had syphilis
cephalitis and anoia.
Lose ability that identify yes or no.
in this trial
Only one escaped from war
criminal depend on malinger.
a senior reporter say--
Ougawa is a craze
adventurer, typical ruffian.
fancy of great empire filled
with his brain.
After our discussion, the ten judges
unanimously agreed
with the second article of the Tribunal,
specifying the Allies's Supreme Commander's
ability to appoint judges to this court
on the basis of recommendations from
their respective national governments.
Therefore, we do not possess the power
to decide appointment, dismissal,
or withdrawal of any judge.
That means the guilt or
innocence of the 28 defendants
must be based on the final
verdict of this military tribunal.
Next, we will hear
the defendants' plea to the charges.
The 28 accused shall now state whether
they plea guilty or not guilty to the charges
the prosecution brought against
them in the indictment
of the lnternational Military Tribunal.
Defendant Sadao Araki, how do you plea,
guilty or not guilty?
l petiton the court to let
my lawyer answer the question.
Petition denied.
The court requires you to speak for yourself.
l'm not guilty.
l objected the indictment,
Japanese criminal defend
team's vice leader,
Who was also Hideki Tojyo's attorney,
Named Hirose itiro,
Built a defend team composed of
over one hundred people.
They used Long-term stratagem,
Never stop to make incident,
ln order to throw the court into confusion,
Which made the trial get along.
lt was no so bad as you thought,
l think we must win in first section,
Mr. Kinan and l have prepared two weapons,
They must recive applause.
The fish was finished,
Landlady,
Your Chinese was so perfect!
Mr. Kitano,
Your brither Gunni was died in the war,
lf you have time tommorrow,
Please come to the police office
to affirm the reliquary.
Hello
Gunni died.
lt was your Chinese who killed Gunni.
Go away.
l'll kill you
lt is you who killed my brother.
Kitano's brother Gunni
Was sent to China together with Hideo,
Hideo came back Japan now,
But Gunni was died.
Kitano's animosity to Chinses,
Was increased by Gunni's death,
Which made us anxious.
ln that time,
Tokyo was involved into the animosity,
Which was derived from the war to Chinese.
When was the beginning of
the Japan-China war,
That was the most
important point we concerned
On China in the Tokyo trial
After the Guandong Army
entered the Northeast China,
Their frequently defiance action,
Made China-japan relationship
in this area tense up.
ln the end, the China-japan war began with
Guanggutun lncident,
which was premeditated by Japan Army.
Mr. District attorney
arbitrarily accused that
the Huanggutun accident were the begining
of the Japanese aggression towards China,
it against the truth,
obviously,
it also confused the partly conflict
and formal war.
At the time, the Beijing government
was the only Chinese government recognized
by the international community
and as such it had diplomatic
relations with other countries.
And, Zhang Zuolin was
the head of that government.
l would like to ask the defense,
when one country plots
and succeeds in the assassination
of the head of another government,
if that is not an act of war between
the two countries, then what is it
Dose Mr. District attorney have
any evidence to proof that
The Huanghutun accident
was done by Japanese army?
This is a deposition given by the former
Japanese Navy Minister Keisuke Okada.
Mr. District attorney
How could we believe the words
a navy officer said?
Then who could give evidence
that these events took place?
Of course the lieutenant officer.
Your Honor,
the prosecution would like to call the former
lieutenant general of the Japanese Army
and former head of the
Japanese Army lnternal Affairs Office
Ruykichi Tanaka as a witness.
Bring the witness in.
Bring in the witness Ruykichi Tanaka.
Witness, please state your name.
Tanaka ryuuguqi.
Your nationality?
Japan.
Your profession?
The former lieutenant
general of the Japanese Army
What was your rank and post
before your military retirement?
The former lieutenant general,
and former head of the
Japanese Army lnternal Affairs Office
Are you familiar
with the Huanggutun lncident
which occurred in China on June 4, 1928?
Yes
Do you know who killed Zhang Zuolin?
l had researched the files,
lt was planed and carried out
by the former brainman of the Guandong Army,
lwamoto ousaku.
Order! Order!
On June third, 1928,
At the across of Nanman railway
and Jingfeng railway,
lwamoto ousaku and his understrappers,
Bombed out the train came from Beijng,
Which one just Zhang zuolin was sitting,
And the next day,
Zhang zuolin was reported for his die.
Mr. Tanaka,
according to what you just testified,
l want a direct answer
to the following question:
Do you think the Huanggutun lncident,
the Shanghai lncident,
the September 18th lncident,
and the July 7th lncident
which all occurred on Chinese soil, were
planned, instigated and carried out by Japan?
Yes
Please tell the court
the names of the persons
who planned,
instigated and
carried out these acts of war.
l can
Some of them were sitting over there.
Please point out the individuals for us.
Hideki tyoujyou.
Dohihara kenji
ltagaki siro
Order! Order!
Mr. Defense attorney... Mr. Defense attorney
Mr. Hirose,
please don't waste our time.
lf you have a question, then ask it.
lf not, please sit down.
Witness,
Are you Japanese?
Mr. Defense attorney. l'm warning you...
l have no questions any more...
August-10-1946
who has been detained at
Boli prison in Russia,
China last emperor - PuYi.
came to Tokyo via Haishenwei
accompanied by Russia army.
PuYi attend to the court and bear witness
lt made
the trial like a drama.
PuYi attended the court,
it shocked Tokyo.
attracted all of the world's focus.
Asaki News Paper said,
This is a epochmaking date
in the period of Tokyo trial.
by Japan empire in the past.
nominated him to
the Kangde emperor's son emperor.
actually attended the court
and bear witness
Never in the past.
When you were emperor of Manchukuo,
what rights did you have?
l don't have any right,
everything was determined by Japanese Army.
Absolutely everything?
Yes
Oh, l have only one right,
What was that?
The right they ask me
everything to do.
During this period,
did you have freedom of movement?
Freedom?
During the these years,
l didn't have any freedom,
Just like a monky!
Mr. witness,
The words you said to the brother
of the Japanese Emperor,
ls said by yourself, is that right?
That was prepared by them.
My question was is that said by yourself?
You just need to answer me yes or no.
Yes
Why there were tears in your eyes?
Why were you crying?
Was that because the help
of Japanese Emperor?
Was that because the fervor
of the Japanese people?
Please answer me.
Why were you crying?
That was a act.
You are lying.
You are a lier.
You put all your crime on Japanese,
but you actually a criminal.
Finally you will be judged
by Chinese government
as a war criminal
8 whole days.
PuYi made it in the Tokyo trial.
the longest witness record.
fight against the Guang Lai Yi Lang
Criminal's lawyer group
threatened and terrified
27-Aug
after the last time witness,
PuYi left the court under
the protection of Russia and U.S.
PuYi's witness
proved that Japan invaded ManZhouLi,
directly.
lt is a unlawful aggression.
because Japan carried out
the news forbiding
and forbidden the Japanese army
contacting to home.
cannot mention the criminal
and wrongdoing actions
during the war period.
civilians in Japan
to the action butchering captive
and civilians
few people know it.
even many Japanese,
Do not believe the Nanjing massacre.
l suggested
judger meeting approve
take the Nanjing massacre
Be a unit to judge.
There was no butcher in Nanjing,
Like procurator Kinan said,
what Japanese army did,
to Chinese common people and women,
the accusation which organized
and inhumane butcher and rape,
were all libel.
Further more, the accusation
which over military necessary,
and wrecking building
and wealth were all lies.
My name is Robert Wilson.
l'm an American doctor.
l lived in Nanjing from January 1936,
until August 1940.
ln 1937,
l was a professor of history
at Jinling University.
From 1912 to 1940 l was pastor
of the Episcopalian Church in Nanjing.
l'm Wu changed.
l'm Wu deyi,
my home was at No 11,
Zhongshan road, Nanjing.
l'm a farmer.
Please tell me what you saw
on December 13, 1937,
after the Japanese Army entered Nanjing.
Nanjing became hell on earth!
the Japanese army went into a killing
frenzy burning everything in sight.
Endless looting and rape.
Honorable court,
This was came from witness Jon Maggie,
Which was shut
on 22th Dec, 1937.
l ask for the court to let me show it here.
Witness, what's your name
l'm Wang defu.
Your profession?
l don't have any profession.
Then how do you make a living
l'm living in Banruo Temper in Nanjing now.
Before that, what did you do
A Thief.
Please say that clearly.
They always call me thief.
Where were you on December 13, 1397
when the Japanese Army entered Nanjing?
Did you leave the temple at any time?
We leaved.
How many monks went out with you?
Four monks.
Three real monks and l.
We meet some Japanese solider,
and then they caught us.
How many of them were there
and what were they doing?
They had over ten persons,
they were raping a Chinese girl.
What did they want you to do
They asked us to rape the Chinese girl too.
Did you rape her?
No
What happened next?
They used bayonet,
And ask us to put off our clothes
They ask us to rape that Chinese girl.
Otherwise, they will kill us.
And then...
Mr. Mingxin didn't answer their request,
What did they do to Mingxin?
They cut off Mingxin's
sexual organ.
Did Mingxin die?
He was rolling in the grond
The blood was all around his body
What about the Japanese soldiers?
What did they do?
Laughing, they were all laughing.
Then what happened to the rest of you?
Mr. Mingkong and Mingfa also
didn't answer their request,
Did the Japanese soldiers also
cut off their sexual organs?
Yes
Did they live?
No
You just said that,
The Japanese soldiers ask you
and three teal monks
To rape that Chinese girl
Yes
They all didn't agree,
so at last they died, is that right?
Yes
And you? Why were you survive?
Were you agree?
Answer me.
Did you rape the girl?
Yes, l raped her.
Were you really forced to do
Or yourself also want to do this?
How can you proof yourself
were forced to do?
How can you proof you were not willing to?
Damn it!
Asshole! Damn it!
The war between Japan and China,
Just as the bust up between
the brothers of the Asia Big Family.
Japan have no choice
but to use some strong measure.
This is just as after the brother keep
his temper for a long time
he'll drive his little brother away.
This is in order to make
China change his view.
Maybe our attitude was a little wildness,
But the original purpose was
to do some good things,
The elder brother was loving
the little brother.
And might l ask
how the younger brother responded to
his older brother's solicitude?
The little brother didn't
understand our purpose.
He still didn't enjoy this love.
Don't talk about the Brothers any more!
Totally bullshit!
Bullshit!
ln the last verdict of
the international tribunal,
To the Nanjing Butcher in China,
This cognizance was made,
ln the first six weeks
of the Japanese aggression,
The number of innocent people
who were butchered
Was over two hundred thousand.
This was the most discreet estimation
Of the international military tribunal.
The number Chinese government
announced later
Made it clearly that
ln Nanjing
There were three hundred thousand people
were killed by Japanese Army.
Sakurako,
Sakura was Fangzi's sister,
she came back from China,
She joined battle service group
for the enthusiasm of dedication
to Japanese Army,
but finally become sex tool for them.
Welcome!
Hideo, is this Mr. Hideo?
That's very fine! You are still living.
Please sit down,
You'll be free drinking today.
lt's so good to see you alive.
Mr. xiaonan,
Do you familiar with that person?
He's the brother of one of my friends.
That's fine!
An old friend come here,
free drinking today.
Mr. Hideo, don't you really remember me?
Do you know each other
Hideo,
Please forgive me.
Don't believe Chinese people.
l believe my own judge only.
Yousuko, don't forget that you're Japanese.
Yousuko Yousuko
Mr. Hideo.
What happened to my brother?
Your brother is in the pothouse now
Brother, what's wrong with you
You Chinese people are still
so savage in our country.
l'll kill you
Hideo,
Kill these Chinese.
lt's them who make Japan
become a humiliator.
lt's them who make us become orphan.
Japanese devil!
No.
Brother!
lt had been one year when l came to Tokyo,
Not only the Chinese government
But also l, the party judge,
Was never thought that
A legality trial
Which the winner country
to the defeat country
Became so difficult and complex.
Here also has joy,
But not to me
lt belong to other people
l'm just a visitor.
The criminals'individual defendance started,
What made the pressure of Mr.xiang
Was the trial to
Doihara kenji and ltagaki siro.
These two criminals was the leader of
The Japanese-Chinese aggression.
Which made the Chinese people
into pain and suffer.
lf we were beaten by them in the court.
The result will not image.
The situation was that
Doihara kenji kept silence until the end.
He tried to get rid of the trial with
the loophole of Common Law System
ltagaki siro was crankiness.
He wrote a 48-pages long apologia,
Said that he would fight with
The Chinese prosecution team.
Mr.Ni zhengao was the leader of this team,
He came Tokyo to help Mr.Mei.
For all of accusations.
My party-
Mr. Doihara denied all.
further more he also think
that facing all accusation,
He absolutely think it
scorn to argue with accuser.
therefore for a Japanese army's reverence
He gave up justification for themselves.
l denied all accusations.
Can Japanese government
seeing the Northeast people
live in tribulation and scuffle?
We help them out of pity and friendship.
ls it the guilt?
Since l was charged of landtied officer.
l always persist in withdraw,
peace, armistice.
whatever what accusal will be
sentenced by prosecution team
l always be one of Japanese
who love peace!
l'm not guilty.
You just said that
the September 18 lncident,
also known as the battle
on September 18, 1931,
was never premeditated,
nor a conspiracy. ls that correct?
Yes
However, you admitted earlier that
the Kuandong Army did formulate a battle plan
before the Huanggutun lncident.
Did you not agree to do it?
l have to explain
this battle plan to you.
l don't want to hear your explanations!
My question is,
Did you report the battle plan
to the central command,
and did they approve it?
Yes
Then, how can you perpetuate your
statement of no premeditation
and conspiracy for
the September 18 lncident?
Because comparing our Guangdong army
with Chinese Northeast army,
for military strength,
we are in inferior position by 1:20
Therefor we must prevent their attack.
we just self-defence.
How did you know the Northeast Army
was going to attack you
We received some information,
After that we start making this plan.
The information on hand? What information
Mr. ltagaki,
don't forget you're in a courtroom.
Only the evidence matters.
So, if you are going to testify
that the Northeast Army
was about to launch an attack
on the Japanese Army,
then you have to provide proof.
ln your defense brief,
you stated that during
the negotiations for
the Three Power Accord between Japan,
Germany and ltaly
you didn't advocate expanding the war.
ln addition,
when the Changgufeng lncident occurred
on the border between China
and the Soviet Union,
you tirelessly sought a peaceful solution.
ls that right?
Yes
As a result,
your emperor punished you for your actions.
ls that correct
lsn't that right?
How did you know this?
l'm the one asking questions here,
not you.
Answer me, lsn't that right?
That's not true.
This document was found
by the Chinese prosecution team
in the archives of
the Japanese Army lnternal Affairs Office.
lt is ajournal kept
by Saionji and Harada.
lt records in detail
how the emperor severely
reprimanded ltagaki for
both these incidents.
And you have the nerve to deny
this ever happened?
Your Honors, l now submit
this evidence to the court.
please examine it and have it recorded.
Near the end of your term
as minister of the army,
you sent an emissary to China to meet
with two individuals...
the first premier of the Republic of China,
Tang Shaoyi,
and the former head
of the Northern Warlords, Wu Peifu
ls that correct?
Yes
Your emissary's purpose was to
entice them to participate
in a puppet organization you were
trying to set up. ls that right?
l don't know.
Well, do you at least
remember whom you sent?
Was that person none other than the one
who usurped the position
of mayor of Shenyang,
installed the puppet emperor Pu Yi,
fraternized with
the Japanese Kuandong Army,
plotted to bring self-rule to North China,
instigated the independence movement
in lnner Mongolia,
incited traitors everywhere to set up puppet
governments and traitorous organizations
never hesitated to do evil,
and now sits in the defendants' table,
namely Kenji Dohihara?
ls that him?
Answer me.
This is the most brilliant victory of
china's prosecution team
During the 10 days heckle with itagaki
Nizheng'ao rebuted
and required those things
He mentioned in the refution.
Finally, by the method
that approaching the topic indirectly,
He beat the Doihara who not say a word.
The war which was launched
and enlarged by Hidekitogyo
Brought the Asia a very severe disaster,
Also, brought Japan
a far-reaching secret anguish.
This secret anguish,
Pervaded several decades
after the war finished,
Makes the young of that age full of
Being at sea, despair and even crazy,
The pain of lose destroy
many people's spirit
At the very beginning,
the holy war to the Asia Paciffic,
And the worship to Hidekitogyo
To where should Japan go?
During the time that the young of
Japan thinking of the question,
Also worry about their
own's destiny and future.
War is just like a beast, who licked up
life, honor and country,
As well as blood and ideal.
Thank you.
Japanese people are all good people,
But why they all had
blind faith to the emperor?
So why the Chinese people
had blind faith to the Huangdi?
But why the emperor had to start a war?
So why Chengjisihan had to
crusage towards to the west?
Why your Tang Empery start war
in Chinese western areas,
And fight broad to Korea?
Emperors all want to start wars.
So we must send revolutions.
Revolution?
Miss Chiba
What happened?
Help!
Hurry! Help!
This became a unsettled case in the end,
The killer was not found.
From that day,
xiaonan and l had never went there.
any more.
The trial to Hideki Tojyo
Would be another fierce fight.
At that time, different public voices
came up all over the world.
There was request ofjudging the emperor again.
lt was a controversial issue in judges's meetings.
But after the secret discussion
between MacArthur and the emperor,
The issue was left unsettled.
Later on, Sir William showed his standpoint
of not charging the emperor and the imperial family.
Brother, l wanner go to eat noodle.
Welcome.
This way please.
YingZi, go and serve the customers.
Welcome.
Give me a bowl of noodle
and a bunch of fish.
Sakurako, go to help your father,
Little child, never mind please.
What happiness.
Dong Tiao government called 100 million
citizens to go into battle.
The temporary council passed 3800 million Yen
according to the request of
Prime Misinter Dong Tiao.
Don't change the channel.
Temporary budget for supplement of military expense
firstly l announce here,
delegating my party
Hideki Tojyo
My party - Hideki Tojyo
he except be evidence by himself,
He will not require any
other attestor on the court.
ln addition,
he will not submit any evidence.
over
Next, my party will readout his affidavit.
finally, maybe this is the last opportunity
on the court permit.
l would like to repeat here.
Japanese empire's national policy
The policy was pursued by the officer
who occupy the position legally
at that year.
Not aggression and not exploitation
We just pursued according to constitution
and law regulation.
But still met the rigorous reality.
We took the national fate to be ante,
but we lost
l insisted on that this was
a war of self-defence.
Not a war of disobeying
the lnternational Law.
About the responsibility
of the war's failure
This is my fault.
lt means that l'll take on all
of the responsibility.
Hideki toujyou.
19th, Dec, Syouwa 22 year, Tokyo.
Now, according to your reasoning,
on the one hand you carried out
peaceful negotiations
between Japan and China,
but on the other you occupied China
with a powerful military force.
Aren't those two contradictory?
They didn't contradictory any more.
Did you ever contemplate
that the invasion of Manchuria
might turn the Chinese public against Japan?
Chinese public antipathy against Japan
was existing long before.
But Japan have never aggressed China.
Silence!
How many people did
the Japanese Army kill?
l don't know.
This document
was published by the
Japanese lmperial General Headquarters
lt reports that between the period
July 1937 and June 1941,
the Japanese Army killed two million
and fifteen thousand Chinese people...
lsn't it logical that must slaughtering
two million Chinese lives
could rouse the fury of the Chinese people?
Please answer the question.
l also think it was a misfortune.
Many of those you butchered
were innocent civilians.
Why was the treatment
to these non-involved
innocent civilians so atrocious?
What is called there is no relation
between people and war
China is same as we Japan.
As the captain of China regime,
direct people to
oppugn Japan and insult Japan.
so draw on killing.
this is the wrong of China regime.
no relation to us.
So l insist donot withdraw from China.
Further more keep extending the war.
ls it right?
l don't like answer yes or no.
This is a courtroom. Your wants are
irrelevant and an answer is mandatory.
So, yes or no
Object
The procurator didn't have
right to ask like that.
Objection overruled!
The witness must answer
the prosecutor's question
with yes or no.
Answer me! Yes or no?
No
No? Did Japan evacuate troops from China
after you received instructions to
form a cabinet in October 1941?
No, but that was
You already answered my question.
l don't need an explanation.
ln your statement,
you said that Japan's decision to go to
war with the United States,
Britain and Holland
which was the direct result for those countries
freezing Japan assets on July 26, 1941, correct?
Yes
You already told the court that
the emperor loves peace, didn't you
Yes
Furthermore, no Japanese
official or commoner
would dare to disobey the emperor's orders,
is that correct?
What l said was a national sensibility,
That was different from
the Emperor's responsibility.
But as a matter of fact,
did you not initiate hostilities
against the United States,
Britain and the Netherland?
That was decision of our council.
lf the emperor opposed the war,
would it still have happened?
l have already said lots of times that
the Emperor didn't have any responsibility,
Japan had no choice but initiate the war.
Do you think initiating
hostilities is morally
and legally acceptable?
l think it is acceptable,
whenever past now and future,
l still think it is acceptable.
So if you and your colleagues
were acquitted,
You would go out
and do it all over again?
You would continue to allow
Japan to launch invasions
and start wars?
Yes
Dear honours,
the procecution'd like to announce that we've
completed our cross examination of Hideki Tojyo
YingZi
All be sitted.
The 817th session of lnternational
Military Tribunal for the Far East
is now in session.
Next, the prosecution
will make its closing argument.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Honorable judges,
and members of the court...
all of the accused,
joined in a formulation
and execution of a plan
a conspiracy whose publish
was to establish Japan's
military, political,
and economic domination over the countries
within the Pacific and lndian Oceans!
ln order to achieve this goal,
Japan alone
or working with liked minds,
embarked on a war
of aggression to subjugate all
who stood in its way.
My prosecution team and l
have produced more than enough evidence
to prove the participation of the accused
in the above summarized criminal actions.
Throughout the history of civilization,
no one has ever seen
such a peak of cruelty
and barbarity.
Countless people died horrendous,
unthinkable deaths to feed Japan's
insatiable appetite for domination.
By their actions,
they have challenged human civilization,
challenged peace,
and challenged the whole world!
Their mutual delict intent.
in order to be sure the reign
position of Japanese king.
No worth guilt than start
the aggression battle.
the safe of all world people
be threatened by this intrigue.
be wrecked by the war
only result of the intrigue.
is taking world people to
undergo dead and pain
Therefore, l, Joseph Keenan,
on behalf of my colleagues
on the Allied prosecution team,
solemnly request the honorable judges of
the lnternational Military Tribunal
for the Far East
to severely punish those responsible
for this horrible war of aggression,
in the honor ofjustice
in the spirit of compassion,
and in the honor of humanity.
The presentation of the cases
before the lnternational Military Tribunal
for the Far East is now concluded.
The verdict will be announced after
the judges' final deliberations.
Until that time, the court is in recess.
Yuiqi, what are you doing
Revenge, for my brother
For all persons who died in the war
lt was me who killed your brother
Why? why you killed him
Have you seen a child kill persons?
Yuiqi, what a chastity boy
But he became a devil in the war
l had to killed him
Japanese devil!
Brother
l have said that
l can accept you not to love me
But
l can't accept you
to love a Chinese!
l love you.
Yousuko!
Are you alright?
Please say something to me
Please say something to me!
l won't go back China
l won't go back China,
Please say something to me!
Yousuko, Please say something to me
Please say something to me
Far east international military tribunal
entered the final stage.
judgers from 11 countries have
huge difference for the judgement.
and appeared opposed emotions.
especially for the Hidekitojyo
and other 24 criminals.
on the question ifjudge them gallows
Occurred feud.
is it the problem that how to condemn?
a reporter of English Times News,
whose forecast is very surprise
on the problem whether use death penalty
He said, there are 2 splits
among eleven countries.
further more it is the most number
which disagree with dead penalty...
do not ask me any more.
l can say nothing to you.
people cannot identify the devilishness
of the war and crime,
until suffer the harm
l have never regret, but today...
l regretted.
chose to come to Japan.
Thinking of xiangyu's tragedy,
l want to commit suicide.
Mei,
you want to learn xiangYu?
And do you want to die?
if you died, then the judger
could stand by you.
could punish the war criminal
you could jump down from the window,
l do not hold you.
Do you think you can help by doing so?
Bullshit.
l think you are probably a coward.
do you think you can move god,
depend upon your emotion?
do you think the judgers
will stand by you,
depend upon your temper
and your complaint?
action, show me your action!
there is a logion in Hunan
as long as you can not fight me died,
l will stand up!
l will stand up.
lf no one has anything new to add,
we can begin voting...
Alright, since no one has anything
left to contribute,
let's get started.
Sir William, would l say a few
more things before we start voting?
Of course
Thank you
Please give me a glass of water
We all agree that the criminals
are guilty.
But we cannot agree
if they should be hanged for what they did.
A lot of innocent people died for the war.
They can only rest in peace
when these criminals are
punished by the death penalty.
Mr. Bernard
your objection to the death penalty is
because you believe a civilized country
should have abolished the death penalty.
Am l right?
absolutely right
ln general, l agree with you
but in this case, l have my doubts...
Mei, l'd be happy to discuss it
According to your logic,
civilization should be respected
but what about life?
Shouldn't life be respected?
l don't think l need to answer
that question
You should already know
the answer perfectly well
l'm sure you wouldn't deny the preciousness
of life because everyone only lives once
Because everyone has one life.
Suppose this cup represents humanity
and the water representscivilization
Please excuse my crudeness
Civilization is created by human being
lf people were ruthlessly murdered,
how can we talk about civilization
Mr. Bernard
Mei, pls. Seat down.
Mei, you want to discuss Buddhism with me
l don't know a lot about Buddhism
but l have a great
deal of respect for it...
when l was a child,
l learned from my parents
l've known that Buddhism
encourages people to do good
and avoid doing evil. Correct?
That's a fundamental idea
Besides the teachings to promoting goodness,
isn't there also punishment of the evil
Yes. But Buddhism says that punishment
is carried out the next life.
You mean
if someone does evil in this lifetime,
he'll pay for it in the next. Right?
That's right
But who will prevent
the crime this lifetime?
Could Buddha prevent Japan
not to start wars again?
Dose Hideki Tojyo believe Buddha?
Buddha will help him believe
Buddha will love him
and forgive him for everything he's done.
ln the end, Buddha will embrace everyone
That's how his power works
we are side with Buddha hoping that
in the future, there are no war anymore.
No crime or evil.
But expectation in spirit can affect
what's happen in realism.
Those unbearable ugliness
and trample on humanity
l don't have any doubts
about the power of Buddha,
But l doubt that if the people
can reach light
under the direction of Buddha.
Buddha says believe makes the dream come true,
But what if these criminals
do not believe in Buddha at all?
l agree to the ancient Greeks' proverb
What god has will belong to him at last.
Mr. Pal
Why we come to here,
the judges from 11 countries,
have come to Japan, for what?
so
we msut punish the criminals
according to law.
Mei, don't try to persuade me anymore
l still think my viewpoint is correct.
Mr. Pal, l won't try to
persuade you any further
The ancient Greeks had a proverb
Fate sees the world more
properly than we do
l can see that l'm next.
Please...
Lao Wei, my dearjudger
All of you here are legal experts
from all over the world
l want to ask you
what is law
and what is the function of it
Throughout the 817th long tribunal
between the two years,
We finally confirm that they are guilty
But now we were talking about
the civilization and the religion
Gentlemen,
This is not classroom of collage,
This is not temper
This is court!
What we need to talk about
is how to punish the criminals
l think the role of religion
is to tell people
what can be done,
to tell people to do good and to forgive.
On the other hand,
Law prescribes what cannot be done.
Otherwise, you will be punished by law.
You will have to go to the guillotine
and the scaffold.
This is law
This is why l insist on imposing
the death penalty on the war criminals
Besides robbing the resource
of other countries
and expanding his territory
Japan also killed thousands
of innocent people
Japanese army's plundering raping
backfiring and killing,
They had killed numerous innocent people-
the Chinese, the Koreans, the Filipinos,
the Singaporeans,
the Americans, the Englishmen...
These crimes are not enough
to bring them to justice
lf neither Japan
nor the war criminals receive
the severest punishment
who can assure that they will
never wage war again?
Who can assure that Japan
will never invade other countries?
Who can assure that
the Japanese militaristic spirit
will never revive?
anyone of you here is able to
make an assurance like this
What l wanted to say,
what l should've said, it's done
We can vote now
for all those who died in the war...
for closing eyes in death
pls. Think it over.
They are watching us, watching
the pens we hold in our hands...
No for the death penalty
No
Yes for the death penalty
Yes
No
Gentleman
as you see this 5 to 5
This is the last ballot...
This one last ballot
will decide everything
Yes
l will now read the verdict...
the court believes
that there is no need to consider whether
or not the accused are guilty of
the conspiracy to violate treaties
and accords Japan had
with other countries
because charge of executing a plot along with
other countries to wage an aggressive war
is already the gravest
crime one can commit.
The court finds all the Japanese
defendants guilty as charged!
international military tribunal concluded,
ln the end, seven criminals
were punished to death.
until now, l can't call to mind,
on this morning,
if the judges who agreed death sentence
were not reach six,
what will happen to me
what will happen to all the Chinese people
what will happen to the whole world
otherwise,
all the judges had pledged
in the beginning
we would never disclose that
who agree the death sentence
and who not agree,
what l what to say was that
l have tried my best...