公众号：VC星球英语
微信：VCPlanet
Hey there, De'Graft here.
Welcome to Newsround.
First up schools in Scotland
and Wales are to close from Friday
because of coronavirus.
It's also expected that schools
in England will also close -
but we're waiting for an annoucement
from the UK Government
about that soon.
It's the best way to make sure
we can all stay safe and healthy.
We know that lots of you will be
worried or upset by this.
Please head to Newsround
online where there is lots
of advice to help you.
We're all here to look
after each other.
Now, across the world people
are limiting their socialising
to help them keep safe
from the virus.
In some countries - like Ireland -
schools are closed too and parents
are working from home.
So what's that like?
Well, meet Eabha.
She's from Dublin and told us
what her life's like and how
she's spending her time.
I'm Eabha, I'm 11
and I live in Dublin.
Because of the coronavirus I'm off
school, and my mum and dad
are working from home
on their computers.
I got schoolwork set by my teacher
and I got a novel to read.
My sports also is all cancelled,
and the playgrounds
and libraries are closed.
During the day, I might walk my dog.
I do sports with my
sister, but I'd stay...
Social distancing,
so I only do it with her.
But all the shops are still open.
But even if you see someone, you can
speak to them from a distance.
It's good because you don't
have to go to school.
It's bad because the reason
like you are off school
is because of the coronavirus
and that's not a good reason.
I'm a bit worried about it
because vulnerable people
like grandparents or people
who are sick could get it.
I'm not worried for myself because I
don't think I'd get very sick.
I think it's a good idea to close
the schools because then you can't
get it from other people and give it
to vulnerable people
like your grandparents
or people who are sick.
We're sure you have loads more
questions about all of this.
Well, Doctors Chris and Xand
from Operation Ouch have come
to the rescue and answered loads!
So take a look.
Now, lots of live football may
have been postponed.
But that's not going
to stop some clubs.
League Two side Leyton Orient have
set up a Fifa tournament -
which they've called
Ultimate Quaran-TEAM -
which sounds a bit like quarantine.
It involves 128 professional clubs,
including Manchester City,
Ajax, Roma and Benfica,
with each club chosing
who represents them.
The draw was made last night -
one of the biggest names
involved is Andros Towsend,
representing Crystal Palace.
Next to Your Planet -
where we've got bears
coming out of hibernation,
trees being planted and the amazing
benefits of sea grass.
Hi, Hayley here with the latest news
affecting your planet.
First to Russia, Finland and Canada,
where there have been
lots of sightings of bears.
That wouldn't seem too unusual,
but this is their normal
hibernation time.
It's been an unusually warm
winter in many places.
And the bears are awake
from their deep sleeps
and on the prowl for food much
earlier than normal.
But the problem is that
at this time of year,
it will be much harder to find
the plants and small
animals they normally eat.
Next to the UK, where forestry
workers are responding to a call
to plant millions of trees
to tackle climate change.
This is Canadian Shelby Barber,
who can plant more
than 4,000 trees a day.
Sounds like hard work,
but she takes it in her stride.
I've personally in three
years planted just over
half a million trees.
Environmentalists, though,
are concerned that governments
and industry think that planting
trees is an easy option
and they think those measures
alone are not enough.
Finally, staying in the UK,
we had to Pembrokeshire,
where scientists are planting
seagrass seeds under the sea.
The seeds have been collected
by volunteers from around the UK
and divers are planting
over1 million of them.
And divers are planting over
one million of them.
Seagrass is an amazing
plant because it helps
prevent coastal erosion,
provides habitat for wildlife
and collects carbon,
which it can store 30 times faster
than land forests.
Well, that's it for this week.
See you next time for more news
affecting your planet.
Finally, there is so much stuff
on Newsround's website that has
nothing to do with coronavirus!
Hooray!
Why not try a quiz about pandas?
Or check out the unicorn dog!
But most of all, keep smiling
and keep watching Newsround.
See you tomorrow!
公众号：VC星球英语
微信：VCPlanet