Hi, I'm De'Graft.
It's Thursday,
and this is Newsround.
Here's what's coming up
in the next few minutes.
The Prime Minister announces big
changes to schools that
will affect you guys.
And we catch up with the unusual
sports still going on!
And the footie stars
with a new type of training.
公众号：VC星球英语
微信：VCPlanet
First up, the government have
announced big changes - meaning that
most of you won't be
going to school next week.
Here's more on why.
Yesterday afternoon
the Prime Minister stood up
with his scientific advisors
and announced a big change
to children's lives
all over the country.
From tomorrow schools will close
right across the UK and children,
like many of their parents,
will have to spend
their time at home.
However, some schools will stay open
for children of key workers,
like parents who work
for the emergency services,
along with children who need extra
support, and some school staff
will look after them.
After schools shut their gates
from Friday afternoon,
they will remain closed for most
pupils, for the vast majority
of pupils, until further notice.
The objective is to slow the spread
of the virus and, as I say,
we judge this is the right moment
to do that.
And it's not just lessons.
Exams like SATs, GCSEs and A levels
will no longer happen this summer.
The Prime Minister promised that
pupils' learning wouldn't be
affected and those taking exams
would get the qualifications
they've worked for,
although he didn't say how.
The government's chief scientist
was keen to say that children don't
seem to be badly affected
by coronavirus and schools
are still safe places to be but this
big step is aimed to stop germs
spreading more widely.
We're sure you have loads more
questions about coronavirus -
well, doctors Chris and Zand
from Operation Ouch have come
to the rescue and answered loads!
So, take a look.
Schools closing may seem really
disappointing for you,
but the same thing happened
to students in China
a few weeks ago - and now they've
had some great news!
For the first time they've
reported NO new infections
since coronavirus began -
and some schools are even reopening!
Martin's been taking a look.
But they're back
at school so yippee!
Now, most sports in the UK are off -
so it's a chance for us to check out
some more unusual ones.
Take a look at banger racing!
Despite hardly any crowds watching,
these drivers are speeding around
the tracks in old cars with windows
- and even doors - missing -
they're trying to win the race
and also not fall apart!
Last up - with most of the sporting
world on hold - lots of stars
are twiddling their thumbs at home.
It's caused some footballers
to start off a new craze -
the loo roll challenge.
Here are some of them in action.
I will not be trying that one at
home.
Right, guys, that's all for now
but don't forget to head over
to the website for loads more -
including where you can check out
the Spongebob Squarepants hotel,
take our quiz about strange
celebrity food and read how Wales
is going to ban single-use plastics
next year.
I'll be with you guys right here,
live on CBBC tomorrow morning.
See you later!
公众号：VC星球英语
微信：VCPlanet