The bright moon sends my longing through a thousand miles
People reunion at the Mid-Autumn Festival
The 10th year of Sing! China in 2021
During these 10 years
Those beautiful songs accompanied the audience through every weekend
At the same time, these people who love music from all over the world find a common home
This year is the 10th year of Sing! China
It is very rare for a show to last for 10 years
It's a miracle
Sing! China is definitely an indispensable show for the entire Chinese music industry
Many amateurs who have never had any audience
After a period of time, they became superstars
It is a very good platform for people who love to sing
It’s also a great show for the audience
Not only for the development of C-pop
But also for the cultivation of talents
Sing! China has made a great contribution to the promotion of the music market
So I am looking forward to this show
It's the 10th years of Sing! China
I think I also witnessed the competitors become famous singers
I hope it can encourage the competitors
Today is the Mid-Autumn Festival
The previous tutors and students gather together
They are ready to review Sing! China together through a special awards ceremony
To see what happened in this big family in the past 10 years
Dear audience and friends in front of the TV
Good evening
Welcome to Zhejiang Satellite TV 2021 Sing! China Mid-Autumn Festival Special Show
First of all, let us give a round of applause for Bi Xia, Chen Bing, Guo Qin, Xing Hanming, Liu Xuejing, Zhao Lu, they will sing "Beneath The Stars"
Next, let's give a round of applause to the tutors
Hello everyone
Welcome
Mid-Autumn Festival is coming
I saw you all came to the stage with moon cakes
Next, please give the blessings of the Mid-Autumn Festival to our audiences
I brought red bean paste mooncakes
Then I wish all friends across the country a happy Mid-Autumn Festival
This one is a multi-nuts mooncake
I wish the students from all over the world
I hope they will have a colorful performance on the stage of the 10th season of Sing! China this year
Nice
This is called Xylitol Almond mooncake
I wish everyone good health
With big bright toothy smile
Thanks
Wang Feng
This is ham mooncake
I wish everyone a happy life
Eat well
Especially wish you eat a lot
Thank you Wang Feng, come on, Xiaoyun
This is a strawberry mooncake
I want to wish everyone a happy Mid-Autumn Festival
I wish all the girls are cuter
And more and more beautiful
Thanks
Here are some very delicious egg yolk mooncakes
I want to wish the boys to be successful in their careers
Everything goes well
Thanks
Very heartfelt blessing
Next, I want to ask, are you hungry?
Let’s share these mooncakes with our students
Staff, please come over and help
Yeah
At the same time in Langjiu Manor, we also have another segment of the show
Tutor Hacken Lee and Bichen will send blessings to everyone
Let's take a look
Everyone, welcome to the 2021 Sing! China Mid-Autumn Festival special show Langjiu Manor segment of the show
I am Chang Geng, greetings to you all
Today on our stage
The two tutors and the students are already here, and they want to spend the Mid-Autumn Festival with everyone
Let’s ask the two tutors to say hello to everyone
Please send your Mid-Autumn Festival blessings
Hello everyone
I am Zhang Bichen
Then I am very happy to spend the Mid-Autumn Festival with everyone here
Then what I bring to you is
Lotus paste mooncake
I wish you all have good luck in the Mid-Autumn Festival
All wishes come true
What I brought is the Cantonese Char Siew mooncake
Char Siew mooncake, I have never had it before
That means the moon is full in the sky
Then people are reunited
Because I also wish you all a happy Mid-Autumn Festival
Thanks
Thank you two tutors
Thank you too
Please get some rest
Thanks
Let's continue the award ceremony of the main venue
At this moment, for the Mid-Autumn Festival night of Sing! China's 10th anniversary
Students are going to send their most sincere blessings
Let’s keep up with their speed
Go to this exclusive audio-visual feast of reunion
On Mid-Autumn Festival, I will make a crispy and delicious fried lotus root box on behalf of the team for our dear tutor Li Ronghao
Welcome to the 2021 Sing! China Mid-Autumn Festival special show
Not only there are members of this year’s team
But also many of our old friends are already here too
Welcome
Then we will invite our tutors to take their places
Please
Tonight's Sing! China Mid-Autumn Festival special show has nothing to do with ranking
Or competition
It's a special award ceremony for the 10th anniversary of Sing! China
According to the data on various platforms each year, for example the number of comments,  reposts and the popularity, we will nominate and present the awards.
A lot of new music styles appear on the Sing! China stage every year
It makes niche music attract more audiences on this stage,
It Successfully broke down barriers
Next, we are going to present “The most barrier-breaking performance award”
Of 10th anniversary of Sing! China
The guest of honor, Liao Changyong and his assistant Zhang Bichen
Welcome
Tutor Liao, when you came to this show
It caused a huge sensation on the Internet
Why?
Because all the netizens think that your coming to this show
It's something you have never done before
And everyone didn't expect you to come
So the netizens are looking forward to it
What do you think about being a tutor?
Actually there are many types of music
Whether it is classical,
Folk music
Or pop music
In fact, they all learn from each other and respect each other
They should try to incorporate all kinds of music in
Sing! China is a very inclusive stage
I came here
It is also because of Sing! China is a inclusive show
So I feel very happy
I was wondering: "Why are you so surprised?"
All right
Then let’s take a look at the shortlist of Sing! China’s 10th anniversary “The most barrier-breaking performance award”
Please look at the big screen
“The most barrier-breaking performance award” for the 10th anniversary of Sing! China
I'm so embarrassed
Congratulations to Dean Liao
This is a performance by us
Tutor Bichen was also in that season
Right
It's destiny
We Class 2 got together again in this way
Yes, indeed
Guo Qin, you come back to our big family today
You feel different, right?
Especially today, Dean Liao came to present you the award
Yes, I feel honored
This performance, because of the injuries
so
It has been very impressive to me
Everyone helped me
I think this award is actually
Not just for me
But for all the staff and tutors on the stage and behind the scenes
Next, the 2019 Sing! China champion Xing Hanming and Guo Qin sing "Big Fish"
Xing is here too
Thank you Guo Qin
Thank you Xing Hanming and Guo Qin
In fact, the year Guo Qin came to Sing! China
She also officially became a student of Shanghai Conservatory of Music that year
So just now when Liao Changyong presented the award to Guo Qin
Guo Qin calls you Dean Liao
You didn't expect it too, right?
Yes, this student sang such a song
What do you think?
Keep working hard
Thank you, Tutor Liao is too strict
It's a big holiday!
Yes, it is
You must keep working hard
Because the road ahead is still long
We are just starting now
I'm not saying you didn't sing well
I mean you need to keep working hard
There is still a long way to go in the future
It needs us to explore
OK
Thank you Dean Liao
Next, Ronghao, you can have a good talk with Xing Hanming
I haven’t seen you for a while, Xing
I haven't seen you for a year or two
-Last time I came here
-Last year, you came to see me, I remember, right?
Xing is my champion student in 2019
Sing! China's championship
When Xing sang just now
It's like my daughter married to someone who lives far away
I can only see her once a year
It's a feeling can't be verbalized
You are not that old
Yep
No, just got into the state in advance
It's a rehearsal
Since the end of the competition
Xing has insisted on making her own music
Right
Music with a lot of your own ideas
She actually sent something to me
I wish Xing can be better and better on this road
It is what I said a few years ago
You are still young
Never stop being adventurous
This is very important
I'm sitting here again today
Then Xing Hanming was singing there again
I feel like I've traveled through time
And it feels like nothing has changed
Anyway, this is how I feel today
-Tutor for one day, father for life
-Not that serious
We are friends
What does Xing want to say to your tutor?
Tutor Li
I said before "I will laugh all the way to the bank"
Yes
You can
Thanks
Let's give a round of applause to Xing Hanming again
Thanks Guo Qin
Thanks
Welcome
Next, we are going to enter a very artistic and fairy-like world together
Zhang Bichen brings us a song
She wrote this song all by herself
Please enjoy
"Life"
Next, we are going to present "the most popular cover song" of the 10th anniversary of Sing! China
Li Ronghao and Jike will present awards
Welcome
As a tutor
What is the most important thing when you cover a song?
I think no matter you cover a song or you are the original singer
The most important thing is this song is suitable for you,
I think this is the most important
Ok
Then let’s take a look at “the most popular cover song” for the 10th anniversary of Sing! China
The shortlist
Please look at the big screen
The 10th anniversary of Sing! China
The most popular cover song nominations are
Sing! China's 10th anniversary most popular cover song
The original singer is Zhou Xingzhe "The Love That Never Lost Connection"
Thank you Zhou Xingzhe for writing such an excellent song
But because of work and pandemic
He didn’t get the chance to come to our 10th Anniversary Awards Ceremony
But he recorded a VCR to express his gratitude and excitement
Let's take a look
Hello everyone
I am Zhou Xingzhe
Congratulations on the 10th anniversary of Sing! China
Thanks to Sing! China
So many singers with dreams have a stage of their own
And I hope you can keep people who love music on this stage
Thanks Sing! China
I wish you a happy 10th anniversary
Thanks, bye bye
I want to tell everyone that the data is really amazing
This song has been played 1 billion times so far
More than 10 million people added this song to their "favorite"
And many people who love this song covered this song
-I am the 1%
-You did?
Yes, I did
I really like it
There are many people like you
One of them at the moment
She's sitting there too
And after watching Sing! China, she covered the song
Her version is currently the most popular cover version
I already know who it is
Whose team is she from?
From Li Ronghao’s team
Wang Jingwen
Next, Wang Jingwen will sing
"Love That Never Loses Connection"
Nice
Thanks
Great
You just finished singing
Jike cheered for you right away
Beautiful
Do you like Jingwen's singing?
Yeah
She is adorable
And this song is also very nice
So after watching Sing! China
You immediately covered this song on that social platform
What kind of reason made you cover it?
Take it easy
Because this song is very beautiful
I have always loved this song
Then the version sung by Shan Yichun
Which is very beautiful too
It's beautiful
I really wanted to learn it right away
Ronghao, as the tutor of Jingwen
What do you think?
I saw her raise her head to sing for the first time
It’s nice to sing with your head up
Try to sing with your head up next time
This song is good
I actually sang your version of this song, right?
Thanks
Really? Did you cover the version she covered?
Yes, I realized when I heard the prelude
It turns out…
Thanks
Jingwen, this song was like her own song
No, it is an ability
Because she sing the songs she likes in her own unique methods for
Some very delicate transpositions, it is her style, I think it’s very good
Thanks
Sounds like we are back to the competition again
Isn't this Mid-Autumn Festival?
No
Today is the Mid-Autumn Festival
Okay. Say hello to your family
Say something to your family
Ok
Hello my families, you are doing great
The family members also wish you success in the competition
Get good grades
Happy holidays
Happy holidays, everyone
Happy holidays to you
You too
Over there
Does she look sleepy every day?
She has been in a trance; we both are in such a state
No, your head was in the clouds
She is in a trance all the time
From 2012 to 2021, in these 10 years
There were 1596 songs in Sing! China
Last year,
Sing! China also added an original track
A lot of good quality songs have been sung
So next, what we are going to present is the "Most Distributed Original Song" for the 10th anniversary of Sing! China.
Let us invite guest of honor, Li Ronghao and his assistant Jike Junyi
Welcome
Since last year, we have added this original track
It enriches the whole stage
Our tutor has a broader consideration of each student
I also hope that
In the future, more singer-songwriters can come to Sing! China and bring their songs to this stage
Ok
Then let’s take a look at the "Most Distributed Original Songs" of Sing! China
Please look at the big screen
"The Most Distributed Original Song" nominated for the 10th anniversary of Sing! China
Congratulations to these five students who won the Most Distributed Original Song Award
Next
The 10th Anniversary of Sing! China, the most popular original song, "Time for a Drop of Tear" from Zhao Zihua
Congratulations, Zhao, it seems you have experienced a lot of vicissitudes in this year
You have experienced a lot
Congratulations to Zhao Zihua , "Time For A Drop Of Tear"
Thanks
Ronghao, do you think it stirred up memories of last year
Because you were the first to turn around for Zihua
And
You know
It has been played 100 million times since it was sung on this stage
Over 1 million people add it to their "favorite". It is a masterpiece of Sing! China
Congratulations again to Zhao Zihua
Thanks
Zihua, you come back to Sing! China's big family again
What’s on your mind right now?
I am back on this stage today
It's heartwarming
And then it's quite familiar
It’s like going back to my alma mater during the Mid-Autumn Festival
When you sang
Tutor Ronghao turned around first
Then Tutor Li Jian also turned around too
Can you tell us what caused you to turn around?
Ok
Actually, it’s the memory of last year, not a long time ago
Zhao is the same as many singer-songwriters I like
He not only writes good lyrics and music but also sings well
Because he has his own characteristics
No matter what kind of song he is writing
It will always be Zhao Zihua’s style
So I like him very, very much
I am very grateful to Zhao for coming to our Sing! China last season
He possessed great charm on this stage
Though it was only after one year
I find that there are too many memories
There is a very important fragment
The Zebra Forest of your team was in the finals last year
And the last song was the final song of the 9th Sing! China
You chose Zihua’s "Time For A Drop Of Tear"
Because actually Zhao
He was in my team during the blind selection
Then because of the competition system, he switched to another team
It has been a very regrettable thing in my heart
So I hope
My students can sing Zhao's song on the stage of the finals
For me
For our team
It is also a very perfect ending
Today is a perfect day
There is a different kind of feeling
On this mid-autumn night
We will enjoy a brand new version of "Time For A Drop Of Tear"
Zhao Zihua, Zebra Forest will sing "Time For A Drop Of Tear "
Thank you Zhao Zihua and Zebra Forest
It seems to be back to last year again, right?
Tutor Ronghao
I said that when they showed up on the stage
I got goose bumps
I see this picture because of these three, do you know?
They picked Zhao
Which almost drove me crazy last year
You saw that, right? Do you understand?
I understand
I really didn't know what to do
All right
After discussing, we decided to challenge Zhao
After a year
The 4 people who drove me crazy are back here at the same time, it is even worse
Finally I know why Harlem can’t stop crying before
-You know why we cried when we came back now
-I understand now, that feeling
When I saw the previous students
You three, are you all okay?
Pretty good
I think we have to get together tonight
They are all here
All four of them
Tutor Li is really touched today
He doesn't know what to say, there’s no logic at all
-He was simply moved,
-Yes, I was a talkative person
When I saw these kids come back
I am really touched
Zebra Forest, today you can sing this song that we all like with Zihua on the stage
What's on your mind right now?
It’s like last summer again
And when I was in this recording studio
I have never felt this way
Each scene flashed before my eyes,
Then I almost cried when I heard it
Zihua
I just felt that we were going to battle again
Last year, Hacken paid particular attention to Zihua, and he liked his songs very much.
They are really good
I really want to say I like your songs
Thank you guys
Thank you both for the wonderful performance
This is a classic song by Anita Mui
I want to ask Hacken
What do you think about their performance just now?
So beautiful
Isn't Wu Keyue a student in my team?
She sings mostly Cantonese songs
I think this time she sings Mandarin song.  It feels very different
When you heard a different version, it feels different
Yeah
I met Pan Hong for the first time
I saw your performance last year too, they were both very good
OK
Thanks
Are their minds in sync?
When we two look at each other
I feel that We are on the same page
You can communicate by eyes
We met for the first time
It’s our first cooperation
But on this stage today
We really get each other
Yep
Great
It was fate that brought us together
You have bond of understanding between you
Wu Keyue also got 8 turning-around
Right?
Hacken
How did you feel when you heard Wu Keyue's song on the stage?
I have to press it
I have to press the button
It is a very firm attitude
So what's on your mind when you come to Langjiu Manor Today?
I feel so special when I came here
I sang "Manju Shahua" on the blind selection stage, it is very classic
Actually it was a song released in 1985
It's just like Langjiu
It feels that although it has existed for a long time
But it's like a good wine
The longer it stays, the stronger it gets
No matter how many years have passed, it is still a classic song
Time to test the standard of beauty
Thank you both again
Thanks
In the past 10 years, many outstanding singers have been on the stage of Sing! China
After the competition
They didn’t stop working hard and writing songs
They have delivered a lot of good works for our Chinese music industry
Next, we are going to present the "Golden Record Award" for the 10th anniversary of Sing! China
Welcome to guest of honor, Hacken and Bichen
You are the champion of the third season of Sing! China
Right?
Does that champion mean anything special to you?
The champion actually made a mark on me
The best result
So it makes you
So it makes you go to get better results
It is a great encouragement for me
I want to know
What is the difference between the tutors that year and tutors of this year? Which one will be more handsome?
I was joking
Let's take a look at the VCR
Take a look at who will win the "Golden Record Award" for the 10th anniversary of Sing! China
Please look at the big screen
Sing! China,10th anniversary
Golden Record Award
Once they came with a dream
My name is Liqi
I will let more people know that I am Li Qi with a Bob haircut, who can sing love songs
My name is Jiang Dunhao
I really like this song
Then I just want to express it simply and beautifully
My name is Zhaxi Pingzuo
I'm so happy
Give me a hug
My name is Danzi
I have a wish
This kind of folk song can be incorporated into popular songs
Then I show it to everyone
They shine on the stage
When they get together, it's a fire
When they are scattered, it is a starry sky
Along the way, they didn’t change their original intentions
They are still young when they meet again today
Sing! China 10th Anniversary Golden Record Award
Awarded to the 10th Anniversary Student Collection "They Are Still Young When They Meet"
But when talking about maturity and transformation
I have to mention one of you
That's Bichen
I believe everyone still have a deep impression of her who was standing on the stage
Wearing a blue hat
She said now she has her own new song
She is also getting more and more confident
Her aura is getting stronger and stronger
But what remains unchanged is her dedication to music
Next, Bichen will sing
"The Midnight Toward Morning"
This song is from my first album
I haven't sung for a long time
As soon as I got there
Because I am very willing to sing this song when I am happy
I hope this song can bring strength and happiness to everyone
Let's wave our arms together, OK?
Thank you all
Thanks
Talking about music style
You personally prefer lyrical songs?
Or the songs which can get you energized
I like both
I think this is actually the same
Just like people have different emotions
When you have fun
When you are sad
When you are in love
Maybe you will also be very lively
Are there any stories in this song?
This song is very simple
It says we don’t want to besiege ourselves
We should dare to innovate
Dare to improve yourself
Unveil a new stage of better life
Make breakthroughs in music and life
It’s great to open up our horizons
I believe everyone will have different feelings about this song
Thanks
Please take a seat
On this Mid-Autumn Festival, we gather together at Langjiu Manor
Let's raise a toast
To the dream chasers who keep walking on the road of music
Next, Let’s go back to the award ceremony of the main venue
Now let's go back to our awards venue
Next, Jike Junyi brings a song "Kapok"
Thank you Jike Junyi for the beautiful song
Just like the song "Don't Be Afraid" on the Sing! China stage for the first time
This "Kapok" is also a Yi song
As the only Chinese artist invited
The song was sung at the "Looking to the Future Action" event at the UNFPA headquarters
Thank you again
Thanks
We also feel the love in the song
Because she has been singing "our love, come back" repeatedly
We also hope to pass on this love to more friends who love music on the stage of Sing! China
Next,
On the Sing! China stage
When the tutors turned around,
They have formed an indissoluble bond with their students
So this tutor-student relationship is particularly unique and beautiful on this stage
The next award we are going to present is the 10th anniversary of Sing! China "the most tacit understanding of tutors and students"
I would like to invite the guest of honor Hacken, and his assistant Wu Mochou. The 10th Anniversary of Voice of China, the most tacit tutors and students
Let's take a look at the VCR
Sing! China 10th anniversary of the most tacit understanding of tutors and students, shortlist
Summer of 2012
A northeastern girl with her unique voice was on the stage of Sing! China
Here
She met her tutor in life
I have nothing to say
She is the type I like
-I choose Harlem
-Let’s rock together,
Every performance, her passion rekindles his persistence in music
I'm recording an album recently
I think there seems to be a song that suits the two of us
What do you think?
Love is like the breeze and rain
Teaching benefits tutors as well as students
To cultivate fragrant peaches and plums with your love
We sing together on the same stage
I came to Sing! China because of Harlem
I think he is the one that can communicate with me
I came to Sing! China
I just want to find someone like Wu Mochou
She is a gift from God
I met a tutor who understood me and supported me so much
This is the happiest thing in my life
Thanks Wu Mochou
She made me reinvigorate the courage and persistence for music
Sing! China, 10th anniversary
The winner of the most tacit understanding of tutors and students is
Harlem, Mochou, my goodness
The winner turned out to be myself and Harlem
For this year, there are many reasons
There are many other students
Including Harlem, who are not able to come to the 10th anniversary awards ceremony.
What does Mochou want to say to your tutor?
I'm okay, I didn't cry
10 years ago
When I laughed, it was like I was crying
When I cried it was like a laugh
Now I am still learning and improving myself
But the person I have to thank for the rest of my life is
Harlem Yu
Then I hope that on the road of music in the future
I can still meet him
I also hope that my lovely tutor Harlem will always be healthy
Always be very happy
Thanks
Next, Wu Mochou will sing "Superwoman"
Thanks Mochou
Thank you all
Next
Hacken and Mo Chou will present awards
And it is also a very loving award
Sing! China, 10th anniversary
"The most loving class"
Please continue to present the awards
It's the first time that Hacken came here to be a tutor
How is your relationship with all your students?
How do we get along?
In my team, everyone shares his favorite music
We learn from each other
Because I think
There is no good or bad music, just whether you like it or not
I hope on this stage
Let's sing more music we like, OK?
Come on
They are really great
Then do we have to watch the VCR again?
Ok
Let’s take a look at VCR, there are nominations for Sing! China's 10th anniversary "Most loving class"
The third year of Sing! China
Na Ying’s “Class 2" team,
Every cruel battle made the tutors and students shed moving tears on the stage
I think in our "Class 2"
There is no competition. For us, it is cooperation
We don't want anyone to leave this stage
No matter who is leaving
We are all in the “Class 2”
The 7th year of Sing! China
Jay Chou, "the wildest on the earth" team
I'm going to invite students to dinner today
I cook by myself
Nicholas has 12 flavors
I have one more, 13 dishes
From table to stage
Don’t be "the strongest on the earth"
To be "the wildest on the earth"
The 7th year of Sing! China, Li Jian, Siberian Tigers team
The road is long , let's explore music together
Sing well onstage
Enhance physical fitness offstage
Drink more hot water
Congratulations to Danzeng Nima
He share the glory of the annual championship with his tutor Li Jian
The 8th year of Sing! China
Li Ronghao's "Babe" team
There are many pitfalls in life, you know
With me, I can help you fill up a lot of pits
When you go out, you don't need to make that much effort
I think it's pretty good
Members of our team, don’t take it as a separation
Everyone has stayed in my team
They are teammates but also friends
They fought side by side and became each other's warmest friend
Summer will pass
But the friendship of the "Babe" team will never end. In my heart, it’s like a family
A lot of talented people were shortlisted
Come on
My mandarin is just so-so
You read it
Ok
Sing! China's 10th anniversary "most loving class", Li Ronghao's team, “Babe”
Congratulations, Ronghao
Mr. Li Ronghao, please come to the stage to accept the award
Only two people came
So you come to accept the award in behalf of other students
Thank you
Excuse me
I just forgot to put that trophy
-It's the thought that counts
-Could the staff take the trophy here?
Thanks
Here comes the trophy
Oh my goodness, such a great trophy
My goodness, what are you doing here?
My goodness why are you all here?
Have you been here for a while?
Here we go again
We have been here for the whole day
Didn't you expect it?
I didn't expect it
Did you really think I forgot to bring the trophy?
I didn’t expect it, not at all
Help
I'm gonna cry
I know why you won, there is a very important reason
Because they really have a very good friendship
They keep in touch and interact a lot
I actually know
We have a group chat for three years, they never stopped chatting there
Including their "moments" on Wechat
I often saw these two get together, and the three get together
They have kept in touch for three years
At the end of the competition
There were some classmates who left first
But since then, they have been in touch for three years
Because of this
I am touched too
So special
Yeah
Thanks to the show for letting me know these young musicians
I hope they get better and better
I can't talk too much
Li Ronghao, if you were a girl, you would have burst into tears
I won't
They also prepared a small gift for you
You Bowen, what is this?
My friends and I prepared a fried lotus root box for you
Why fried lotus root box? Every time the gift is so sloppy
This is a more meaningful gift
I hope you can be harmonious with your family
Doesn't it sound like…
"Occasionally harmonious"?
I got you, special harmony
Last time they gave me a self-portrait
Which shocked me
I haven't used this word "shock" for a long time
You know
It shocked and embarrassed me
You sent a lotus root box today
Let's eat together when we finish recording
Once again we wish all the students
Have a bright future
Again
Thanks Li Ronghao
Next, Huang Xiaoyun will sing "Take Me to A Place Far Away"
Thank you Huang Xiaoyun
Embrace your tutor like the first time on the stage of Sing! China
It feels like I’m here for the test
So happy
The smile of Wang Feng in the picture was particularly brilliant
I had a beard back then
Yep
She told me that she wanted to go to the conservatory
This is always her dream
Because she thinks she can sing forever
But she hopes to learn more
And when she was about to graduate
At that time, I had heard some friends around me talking about her
When her "The Stars and the Sea" came out
More people know Huang Xiaoyun
I am really happy for her
She was my student
About the Central Conservatory of Music
Actually I took the exam twice
There was a little mistake the first time
I didn’t dare to bother Wang Feng
Until a year later
After I was admitted
I told Wang Feng
I was admitted to the Central Conservatory of Music where you graduated
It's true
This stage of Sing! China is so beautiful
Thank you Sing! China for giving us such a wonderful fate
In Sing! China's previous battles, there were many classic duets
In order to choose a song suitable for the students, the tutor worked hard
Next, the last award tonight
Sing! China's 10th anniversary "Most Unforgettable Duet"
Guest of honor Wang Feng and his assistant Huang Xiaoyun
Liao, you know the "competition system” used to be crueler,  there was "internal PK"
-I know
-In the case of internal PK, we decide who wins by one song
And in this "internal PK", there are so many wonderful songs
Now let’s take a look at the VCR
Shortlist for the 10th anniversary of Sing! China "Most Unforgettable Duet"
Wang Feng's team "Hey Jude"
I have seen this before
Na Ying’s team
-Lake Baikal
-This is also good
Nicholas Tse's team "Light Years Away"
Li Jian’s team, "Water Flower + La Vie En Rose"
Wonderful
I think it's possible
Sing! China's 10th anniversary "Most Unforgettable Duet"
Wang Feng' team
Congratulations to Wang Feng's team, "Hey Jude"
"Most Unforgettable Duet", Wang Feng and Bi Xia come together to accept this honor
Bi Xia, please come to the stage
And accept this award with Wang Feng
In fact, this honor belongs to the entire Wang Feng’s team, belongs to Bi Xia and Zhong Weiqiang
We want to send the blessing to Zhong Weiqiang, because he is also watching our show
We are very grateful to him as well
Thank him for making so many beautiful memories on this stage
Thanks
Then Xiaoyun will give this trophy to your tutor and Bi Xia
I think Bi Xia should be the most suitable one to hold it
And also to all my students of 2013
This is the honor of our team
I really want to
I have to break this in half and give it to Simon
I will give him more than half
Because when you played the video just now
I really miss Simon
As I mentioned before, I thought
The one with the helmet was Simon
There is one behind
That's an alien
And his body shape is quite similar
Then I thought it was a surprise again
Then I found out
I seemed to think too much
But I think, Simon, no matter how far apart we are
Like what the tutor said before
His spirit, old naughty boy
8 years have passed
He's almost 70
He had his birthday two days ago
I sang a birthday song to him
Then he went out to play and post videos
And he plays in a band
Live performance
Now he plays in a band, Rock and Roll
Yes, full of energy
So there is actually no real separations on the stage of Sing! China
Although summer will pass
The competition will end
But friendship lasts forever
We are best friend forever
We will always be a big loving family
We also invited all our tutors to come to the stage together
Let's toast together
Happy Mid-Autumn Festival everyone
This Friday at 8:20, Zhejiang Satellite TV 2021MC Sing! China "Tutor Decisive Battle"
We will see you soon