Congratulations...
Congratulations
Thank you.
Here comes the bride.
Dear wife, let's toast to our love,
that we will
live happily ever after.
Thank you, dear. l wish you all the best,
and good business always.
Thank you, cheers.
Let's have another drink, dear.
Kowtow.
Don't worry, it's sacred water.
The God of Thunder...
Stop.
What's your name?
l'm Mrs. Lai.
And your husband's name is?
Lai Yangli.
Mother of the Jade Emperor...
King of Hell, all the Earth Gods...
Bring the ghost of Lay Yangli up here.
Listen, no matter what strange things happen,
keep your mouth shut.
Got it.
Stop.
Sit still.
Up.
Are you alright, master?
Didn't l tell you not to move?
l've found your husband,
hence the emergency landing.
l'll bring him here right away.
lt's really windy,
why isn't my husband here?
Stop.
Your husband has arrived.
l can't see him.
Look.
Yangli, you're really here.
l'm having a tough time in hell.
l know, you were a lackey when you were alive,
you must be tired with all the walking after death.
Take some money to Zhang, he'll burn something for me.
Buy some chicken feet, pigs' feet for me.
l'll do it.
Then hurry and pay Master Zhang.
Just ten taels, l'm off.
Yangli, l'll do as you told.
Don't worry, l'll go get the money now.
Remember, you don't need to bring too much,
just ten taels as he instructed.
Master, you're really something.
lt's easy money.
What a fool!
Brat.
Why did you hit me, master?
You little ass, you wanted me to fall to my death?
l'll deduct my medical fees on
your salary this month.
You've deducted a lot already,
there won't be anything left.
l don't care.
Please, master.
Give the rest to me.
You wish.
Here's a letter for you, read it.
Cousin, l've lately found the proof of corruption
done by Zhuge Sen, the lron-hand Officer,
l planned on handing it to Judge Bao at Kaifeng County,
l'll pass by your town & hope to stay for a while.
Your cousin, Zhou Peng.
Better don't have any grudges with the officials.
Stupid guy.
Faster...
Excuse us, we just want to borrow some money.
Du Luo?
l heard he died for love.
He didn't rest in peace.
He said that he'll come back for his revenge.
We can't think too much about these.
What are you afraid of? That he'll bite?
l have bad feelings about this.
Guard over there then.
Hurry...
Chicken shit, go on.
Anything?
No.
Hurry...
Officers, hurry!
He's over there.
Freeze.
We...
What are you doing here?
We...Get up.
We're doing our trade here.
Have you seen a young man walk past?
No, if people pass by,
we wouldn't be able to do this.
No?
He's injured,
he won't be going far, let's look again.
Yes.
l'm right here.
Zhou Peng, our chief said
that he'll forgive you
if you hand out the list.
You think you can get the list so easily?
l'm Mai Feihong, that mean you look down on me.
Kill him.
What did you do that for?
Anyone who knows our secrets must die.
l'd be dead
if l hand over the list to you anyway.
Take it if you can.
Morning.
l'm going to play chess, watch the house.
Got it.
Let me walk you out, master.
Sure.
Be careful, master.
Be careful.
Good.
Take care.
Why are you so polite today?
Nothing, l just want...
What do you want?
You've deducted all my salary this month.
Just watch my home for me,
got it?
Fine! What's the big deal!
l'll starve for two days, in the worst case.
Master, l wasn't bad mouthing you.
Ghost.
Hey, cousin, don't you recognise me?
l'm Zhou Peng.
Cousin Peng.
Cousin.
What happened to you?
l guess you've received my letter?
l'm in this state because l was under pursuit
by Zhuge Sen's men.
You've scared me.
Have a rest, and l'll buy you some medicine tomorrow.
Don't go out at night, in case you bump into...
Stop chatting, l want to buy some medicine.
Listen, Du Luo's body is missing,
and there are nine dead bodies by his grave.
One got all his blood sucked dry,
didn't look human.
What didn't look human?
Boss, medicine.
Fine...wait, he's turned into a zombie?
Yes, it's the Ghost Festival tonight.
Don't go out.
Where's the prescription?
Du Luo, did he kill himself for love?
That's the one.
Are you a maid of the Lin Family?
That's right.
Tell your young madam, beware of him.
Nonsense!
He wouldn't haunt our young madam.
What's so scary about ghosts?
Lady, l'm a student of Master Zhang.
You'll be fine.
Really?
Come look for me should you need help.
Your medicine.
Thanks.
Young madam.
Chuntao, you've scared me.
Time for the medicine.
Put it there.
Young madam,
l heard something strange when l was in town.
l know, Du Luo turned into a zombie.
So scary, what should we do?
Everyone said he died for me,
but l was never interested in him.
l've never returned his affection.
But they all say that...
Forget it.
Are the floats ready for tonight?
You'll release the floral floats downstream tonight?
We do that on Ghost Festival ever year.
The floats will go downstream,
and send away all the ghosts.
The young master isn't home, aren't you afraid?
What's to be afraid of?
l didn't do anything bad to him.
Go work.
Yes.
Young madam...what's the matter?
Someone in the water.
No one, young madam.
Could be a blurred vision.
Let's continue.
Du Luo.
Where? Young madam.
Over there.
There's nothing.
Come...
Are you alright, young madam?
Take her inside first.
l wonder if she will be alright.
l guess she should be fine.
Young madam, take a rest,
l'll get you some medicine.
Huanzhu...
Young madam...ghost!
Ghost.
Chuntao...
Where are you?
Huanzhu, though l couldn't be with you while alive
l will be now.
Oh no! How could that be? Where?
ln the room.
Hurry!
Old Master.
Where's my daughter-in-law?
She's inside.
Let's go.
No.
Why not?
She's possessed.
We still have to go.
No...
Why not?
How could that happen?
Get an exorcist tomorrow to drive out the evil spirits.
Yes.
Cousin Peng.
Cousin.
l've an idea for your travel expenses to Kaifeng.
How?
My master will be away for days,
and we've got business.
We'll go right away.
What kind of business?
What do l do?
l'm a ghost buster.
No, thanks. l'm scared.
You know what,
there's no such things as ghosts,
it's the only reason why l'm in this business.
You think my master knows this for real?
He's just a con artist.
Otherwise why would he need all these props?
You know what my name is?
Bao Tuo. (Everything's fine)
Exactly, everything's fine.
Where?
Get changed first, come...
Watch over me.
Don't worry, come.
Amitabha Buddha, young lady,
watch out, l can feel the evil spirits from your house.
Yes, my young madam is possessed.
Very scary.
l've called for Master Zhang's help.
l'm waiting for them.
Here we are.
Trying to take my business, monk? Beat it.
Amitabha Buddha,
this ghost is very difficult to catch.
Be careful.
Nonsense. Lead the way.
Yes.
This way please.
She's inside, please go.
Fine, go.
Cousin, it seems very ghostly.
Don't worry, we'll give him some cinnabar water,
and all evil spirits will flee.
The bag.
Hold it.
Go in, ring the bell.
Me first? l don't think it's a good idea.
Don't worry, go!
You...
Go.
Don't come in, don't come in.
Are you sure you can do it without me?
He was shivering and now he's so cocky?
l'm going to ring the bell, don't come in.
lt's me.
Me!
Don't you recognize me? l'm your cousin.
Look at you! You're all shaken up.
What are you afraid of?
Are you possessed?
Ghost!
Don't come near me, l have the peach wood sword.
l didn't do anything...
lt's me.
Why are you two brats bothering me here?
Take care of this, cousin.
Don't worry, l have the sword in hand,
l'm not afraid of any ghosts.
Then why don't you kill her?
Kill?
Kill.
Go, cousin.
Here.
She isn't moving.
Go and distract her.
l'll attack on the back.
Me again?
Go on.
Go!
Hey, look over here.
l'm here.
Spare us.
lf l see you two again,
l'll swallow you alive.
There won't be a next time.
You should leave now.
l'm gone...
So, Master?
This ghost is powerful.
Really?
That's why l dropped everything.
What now?
Amitabha Buddha, forgive me for showing up uninvited,
l fear that you might be injured by the evil spirit.
Good timing, monk.
Right.
You can take this job,
l won't fight over it with you, let's go.
Go!
l'm glad you're here.
My daughter-in-law is possessed.
Yes.
Don't worry.
Tell me what happened.
That was a close shave.
Hurry up then!
Do you think the ghost will follow?
Don't worry, the monk can block it, come on.
Go.
l see, please bring her out.
Yes.
Here she is.
Old Master.
Put her on the bed.
Be careful.
Yinyang, Sunrise from east, the light of truth.
Heaven's physical strength,
expel the evil spirits, turn to lucky.
l'm about to perform the exorcism.
Excuse us.
Leave.
Yes.
Let's go.
Namo Sakyamuni Buddha...Amitabha Buddha
Buddha pearls will help me to exorcise the evil spirit.
Sincerely the good fortune will cover everything.
The fragrant herb, the light will illuminate everything
We're home, thank goodness.
Who would have thought...
that l'd see a real ghost?
You're unlucky.
Go inside.
What's happening?
My master is back.
Take off the clothes, now.
Why?
lf he sees this,
he'll deduct my next month's salary.
That was scary.
Something's wrong, it's chilly.
Don't worry, it's all fake.
l could make it more windy.
Really?
l'll show you, look.
Wind.
Wind...
Just like the real thing.
Did you make...
all these strange things?
Of course.
lf not, how could we fool our clients?
Right
l can make it stop.
Really?
Stop.
That's enough, Master.
He's not a client, he's my cousin.
Stop.
What did l tell you?
Makes sense.
Let's go and get changed.
Alright.
Not bad.
ls this the new style, master?
Look! Flying candles.
lmpressive.
On remote control with no visible wires, amazing.
You must have spent tons on the new gimmicks,
master. l'm sure they cost a lot.
Automatic changing lights, innovative.
Bao Tuo...
Excellent Dolby surround sound system.
Great...
Look, cousin.
My master has improved in makeup.
ls that so?
No, it's a woman.
Don't worry, look again. She's human.
Why would l lie to you?
lt's real.
Ghost!
Benefactors, l'm Mrs. Lin.
Don't be afraid.
Of course we are afraid, you're a ghost.
You can look now.
Don't scare us.
That's right.
l won't.
Are you real? We've just come back from your house,
we tried to perform exorcism.
Right.
l know.
Du Luo killed me,
and he has killed several monks.
lf he killed you, why are you haunting us?
Right...every debt has its debtor.
Because he couldn't have me,
he's on his way to Kaifeng, and plans to hurt my sister
We're heading to Kaifeng too.
Don't listen to him.
l know you're going there,
l beg you to help my younger sister.
Sounds like Du Luo is a fierce ghost,
he's killed the monks even.
How can we help your sister?
lf you bring me to Kaifeng,
l'd look for Judge Bao to save my sister.
Right, we're also...
Shut up, will you?
l wouldn't let him to hurt my sister.
You must take me there,
l'll kill you if you refuse.
Take your time.
l'll find you a good travel agency,
and you can go on a luxury trip.
You must bring me there.
Fine...
But how?
Here's a spell.
l'll attach my soul on it.
Place it inside an umbrella,
and you can take me along to Kaifeng.
Master Zhuge.
Has Zhou Peng left for Kaifeng?
Because strange things have happened lately,
the officers you sent here were killed by demons.
l don't care about ghosts,
l just want to catch Zhou Peng.
Yes.
He's got the proof.
lt involves higher officials too.
lf Judge Bao gets the evidence,
we'll all be in trouble.
So what should we do?
l'm here because of this.
Find me 20 experts,
l must get rid of him even if l have to go to Kaifeng.
Enjoy your dinner, Mrs. Lin.
How much money do we have left?
Not much left.
Let's go spend the rest.
Good idea.
Wait, you two have work to do.
What now?
l know that Du Luo the ghost
is on his way to Kaifeng,
if we meet him on the road,
we won't be able to fight him.
What should we do?
There's a very spirited opera performer,
even the ghosts fear him.
lf you can find him,
it would be much easier.
That's easy, tell us
what's his name, where is his address,
we can go find him.
Right.
l'm not sure.
l only know he gambles at Hongli gambling house.
How could we find him?
There are plenty of people there.
How could we tell who's he?
He's got a special mark,
there are seven moles on his foot.
Do l tell everyone to take off their
shoes and show me their feet?
Please think of something.
But how?
l got it!
What's your idea?
Feet reading.
Let me take a look...
Anything?
No.
Fine...l'll tell you.
You all have tough lives.
Bad luck, fake oaths,
you use people,
money worshippers.
You are scared of the bullies,
but bully the gentle ones.
Just by one look at your feet, my friend,
l know that you're unlucky.
Bullshit.
My wager.
Wu Shunchao,
don't think that because you're an opera performer,
and this rotten stuff would worth anything.
Enough excuses.
l've lost everything here.
l must win something tonight.
The fortune teller told me that
l have 7 stars on my foot, a general type, l'll be rich
Seven stars? You'll be broke.
Whatever.
How much for this?
Three taels? Fine.
Three taels? l'll punch you three times, kick him out.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
What are you two doing?
Oh nothing, just checking.
We are specialised in feet reading.
You have seven stars on your foot, a general type.
You can have plenty of women and money.
And you'll have plenty of children.
You'll have a good career path.
And always on a winning streak.
But l still lose.
With our instructions, l guarantee you'll win.
Really?
Of course.
Certain?
Absolutely.
What are you waiting for?
l wouldn't lie to you, come on.
Don't worry, you have nothing to lose.
Go inside.
Just listen.
Were you telling the truth?
That the umbrella will bless me?
l guarantee it will go smoothly.
How?
l've said enough,
you do the talking, cousin.
lt's the right decision to follow us,
l guarantee you will be fine,
we'll provide you with free lodging and food.
l like gambling.
Guarantee you'll win in gambling house.
You could see through to the dices.
You will definitely win.
Anything you please.
Too bad l don't have any cash
You don't need to use cash.
Then what do l use?
Paper money.
Really? lf you're that good,
l'll do whatever you tell me to.
Fortune tellers could lie to you for a decade,
but we'll bring you to win some money now.
l'm off then.
Don't rush.
Why?
Put this spell on you first.
Don't stay for too long, run when you've won.
Stop nagging.
Alright.
Thanks for the umbrella, l'm off.
Wait.
You brats! The God of Earth is here!
Go...
Hurry.
God of Earth, help us out.
Keep burning this.
Got it.
What are you doing here again?
lt doesn't worth anything.
ls that so?
But l have cash,
can l play?
Of course.
Take it.
Money.
Hurry...please.
Make way...
Please.
Take your time.
Do l have to stand?
Get a stool.
Here you go, please sit down.
Keep it.
Money.
Thanks...
Hurry up.
Yes.
Master Wu, please bet.
Everyone...
Place your bets.
Come on.
Master Wu, we're waiting.
Small.
Open.
Two Ones, and Four, Six, Small.
Master Wu, twenty taels.
Place your bets...
Small again.
Big...
Place your bets...
Two Threes, One, Seven, Small.
You've won again, Master Wu.
So lucky.
l don't believe that.
Believe it, he's on a winning streak.
l don't believe it, l'll bet on Big.
Small again.
Place your bets.
One, two, three, Six, Small.
Wu Shunchao must be addicted now.
Why isn't he out yet?
Right.
We're almost done here.
l'll go buy some more.
Hurry, it will run out soon.
Fifth Brother, Wu Shunchao seems different,
luck is on his side.
l couldn't do anything,
even we changed Ming to shake the dices.
l think he's met a ghost.
Looks like it.
He's still winning.
Let me take care of him. l'm the local trickster.
Wu Shunchao.
What?
You're very lucky today.
l'm doing alright.
How about a game?
What do you want to play, Luo Wuhai?
Pairs.
Pairs? Sure.
What now?
ls that all?
The shops are closed,
l picked these from the temple.
Stack it.
Stack what? lt's all run out.
Just burn it.
The master told me to buy 2 and 3 at first,
there's a 90% chance to win.
Open.
Yes.
Two.
What? Two?
That's right.
Of course it is Two.
So, what do you think, local trickster?
Pay up.
Five, ten, fifteen, twenty, good.
Wu Shunchao, you're very lucky,
you want to play another game?
Sure, l'm not scared of you.
You've got guts, the money.
Yes.
Open.
Four.
Wait.
Ward away the evil spirits.
That hurts.
Why did you jump like that?
Trying to scare me with that?
These are the last four,
if he doesn't come out in time,
then we'll have nothing left.
Open.
Four...
Shit.
One.
You lose.
l'm very generous.
l'll give you another chance,
another game.
l've lost everything.
Let me pawn something.
No.
lf you don't have money now, you can go get it.
Fine.
Keep that safe for me.
Yes.
What happened?
lt's turned into paper money, how?
What's going on?
He knows black magic? Men.
Here.
Catch him.
Chief,
l saw Zhou Peng coming from that way.
Really?
lt's your fault. You should have left...
as soon as you won something.
You didn't burn enough paper money.
That cross-eyed did something to ward off my power.
l couldn't stand that.
lf we can beat it,
we'll take the sedan.
You know it's all come down to fate.
l don't believe in that.
We can go to another gambling house.
Tell the umbrella to bless me again,
or l won't listen to you.
Lower your voice! Let's go.
Go!
The umbrella...l see.
What? Trying to sell something?
We won't buy anything, move it.
Wu Shunchao, you've got some nerve,
you used paper money
on my turf?
Pay up.
Why didn't you say something when l was there,
it's too late to claim they are fake now.
Making up excuses? Beat him up.
My umbrella.
Take it.
Don't take my umbrella.
l won't be in any unfavourable situation.
Mrs. Lin.
Mrs. Lin, are you inside?
The umbrella is here, catch! One-eyed captain.
Chief, he's gone.
He's gone.
Go after him!
Me again?
Go! l'll look for the umbrella.
lt's here, l've got it.
You've found it?
Yes, where's my cousin?
He's been taken away by the officers.
Let's go save him.
Save him? Aren't you afraid to die?
Let's go back to the inn first and ask Mrs. Lin's ghost
Go.
Zhou Peng, you've been here for a day.
You should have thought it over,
hand out the list.
And l might spare your life.
You'll kill me all the same even if l hand the list out
lf you won't,
l can make you.
No matter what, l won't hand it out.
Oh really?
You heard him,
entertain Mr. Zhou for me.
Yes.
Here?
l think that's what she said.
Let's go.
Sounds like beating.
Right.
Let's go up.
You're heavy, let me do it.
And me?
Stand still.
Stop.
You are a tough man, aren't you?
Wait.
Master Zhou couldn't take such heavy punishment.
Feed him, he must be starving.
Oh no, he's trying to burn him.
What now?
Ask her.
What should we do?
Open the umbrella.
Quick.
Flew over.
Climb up.
What? You again?
l'm lightweight.
He's possessed.
Let me take a look.
Hurry.
Up.
What?
How could you fall? lt's not high.
He's out.
Pick him up.
Relax, you've escaped.
What am l doing here?
You were possessed by Mrs. Lin.
Possessed?
Let's go.
Bring me along.
The umbrella.
Go after them.
Go first, wait for me at the temple.
And you?
l'll block them.
Give me the umbrella.
lsn't itjust the same?
lf they catch you,
and they will use the ghost's power.
Shut up and beat it!
There's a ghost in the umbrella,
that's really great!
How great is that?
You fool, haven't you heard?
Whoever takes the umbrella
can control the ghost inside?
What should we do?
Go to the temple.
Go...
Zhuge, l'm here.
Hurry.
Over there.
He's over there.
Go.
What should we do now, chief?
Let's go back, it's futile chasing a hard-pressed enemy
Yes.
Can burn the umbrella.
Are you nuts? How could you burn that?
Who told you to take so long for the firewood?
l can't take this anymore.
You can't burn this, there's a spell inside.
You took too long, l was freezing.
Not having an axe to cut wood, we picked these.
No matter what, burn them now.
l'm freezing, add some more, quick.
You're not an idiot,
you could wear something.
From where? Yours?
You should find your own.
l thought we were brothers.
Take it.
You're absolutely useless.
Put it down. Holding that won't make you warmer.
You do it.
Pick some firewood too.
Me again?
l always get the bad jobs.
This is strange.
Let me go!
What are you doing?
There are...
What?
There're...
The firewood?
Ghosts!
Ghosts?
Yes, we have one as company.
Not Mrs. Lin!
What then?
There are...
lnjustice.
Here they are.
We are very scary...
Scary? Scary is when l tear your heads off,
trying to scare us wearing masks?
Beat him up.
Fakes?
l've taken one down.
Careful.
Thanks, cousin.
You're welcome.
lt doesn't seem right.
Weapons.
Let's split, l've got it.
Let's split...
At least you ran fast enough.
l don't see Wu Shunchao helping
us just now.
Right, where's he?
Let's go beat him up.
Good idea.
Where's he?
Where's he hiding?
Wu Shunchao...
He couldn't hear us even though we're so loud.
Must be sleeping like a pig.
Let's go look for him.
Alright.
Let's play a trick on him.
OK.
One more.
Twist his arm.
You think you can fool us
by this kind of disguise?
His hand is cold.
He's scared.
Who's that? So noisy.
Blinks.
Go!
Don't come near.
Or l'll kill you.
l'll kill you.
Cousin.
Because of you two brats,
l couldn't sleep peacefully.
You?
Come here...
Having an epilepsy?
lt's not so scary with the wall.
What are you doing?
My cousin is fighting a ghost outside.
ls that so?
Yes, why aren't you helping?
Help? l'm unlucky.
Leave me alone. l'm scared.
You should think of something.
Help him out.
Ghost!
He looks scary.
Scared, huh?
The City God's robe is useful.
Useful? Why don't you go after him?
After him? That's a ghost.
He's scared of your robe.
Go! Get even for Mrs. Lin.
Get even for Mrs. Lin.
Really? Me?
Yes, go!
Get the umbrella.
lt's missing.
Missing? Where did you leave it?
Right here.
You lost it while we were fighting?
Look for it again.
l'm scared.
Don't follow me if you're scared.
Hey ghost, come out
we're your friends here.
You're trying to fool a ghost?
You all have a bowl of dog's blood,
and you tell me you're my friends.
Will you come out or not?
lf you won't,
we'll splash you with dogs' blood.
Do l come out on your demand?
Very rude.
l'm coming out.
What do you want?
l want...oh, right.
How could you protect Wu Shunchao?
l gave him a ''sure-win'' spell.
That means the spell drawn by a ghost?
That's right.
Works like magic.
Draw me one then.
l already have, it's underneath your bowls.
Look...
There's nothing.
Nothing...
You're bluffing.
You think that you don't have to worry
when we pour off the blood, right?
Men.
Yes.
Burn it.
Don't, l'll draw it.
Hurry then.
l'll draw.
How do l use this?
l could tell you
on one condition.
Spill it.
This is a ''whatever you wish for'' spell.
You can get whatever you want.
But after you're done,
you must return this umbrella to the two young men.
Fine.
Remember.
Oh, one more thing,
you can only have one wish.
From now on, you can ask for whatever you want.
Dear, l want...
Boss, l want
Dear.
Alright.
What?
l don't think the boss would care for us anymore.
Right.
Let's bug him.
Dear.
l want gold.
l want to be a top official.
l want to be an Emperor.
l want a pearl the size of my fist.
l want to date a young man.
l want a mistress.
l want the secrets of winning.
l want to hit the lottery.
l want to win the Trio.
l want to win the Quinella Place.
Dear, l want...
l want anything (all types of ghosts)
l said the wrong thing.
What do you want us here for?
So crowded!
We're here.
l know.
What is he doing, covering his face?
What? We're not thieves.
l'm different, l'm in the entertainment business.
Look at me now!
lt's embarrassing bumping into people who know me.
Hurry up.
We've reached Kaifeng, Cousin Peng. hat now?
We're here on a mission.
Let's go find Judge Bao and then Mrs. Lin's sister.
Tell her that her sister is dead?
Right.
Don't count on me, look at me!
How could l go out like this?
Pay up, l want to buy new clothes.
Money again?
You two can buy something too.
You ask for pocket money everyday, we're not your dad.
That's the pain of being an actor, you two go ahead.
Go! He's so vain.
Here you go...
What are you doing?
A ghost for you.
Ghost.
What are you doing?
For you.
l want the umbrella.
This one, why?
To block the sun.
There's a ghost inside.
l'm not scared.
You're not?
l'm not.
You can have it...
Thanks.
Bye...
He's got the ghost too.
Mr. Gongsun, please pass this message to Judge Bao.
No problem.
Zhuge Sen is a corrupt official,
Judge Bao has known for a while.
But we don't have any proof.
Now that you've brought the evidence here,
l believe we can put him on trial.
l've another request.
What's that?
This is my cousin Bao Tuo.
Right, l've the same surname as Judge Bao.
Shut up.
He accompanied me on the way,
we've encountered a strange incident.
What kind of incident?
Here it is.
Who are you looking for?
You fools, l'm here to look for Judge Bao,
send him out.
What do you want to see him for?
l'm delivering an umbrella.
Send the word.
ls he really so powerful?
What do you suggest, Mr. Gongsun?
Judge Bao put Guo Huai on trial once at night,
he used anti-evil mirror and a Tiger head chopper,
and he's scared all ghosts.
l don't think it's a problem
to deal with one ghost.
Where's the female ghost you mentioned?
She is...
Mr. Gongsun.
There's a Wu Shunchao outside,
he said he's delivering an umbrella to Judge Bao.
Please decide.
Mr. Gongsun, the female ghost is inside.
We'll deal with the demon, then Zhuge Sen.
Good night, Miss.
Finally we meet,
you look so much like your sister.
Who are you?
Me? l'm here to marry you.
Answer to my sword first.
What's all that noise in the room?
Let's take a look.
Meet me t'row late night at Du Family's deserted house
We'll get married.
Miss...
Are you alright?
She's passed out.
Go take a look.
His blood got sucked out.
We must be careful.
Yes.
Why are you here?
She looks possessed.
Why are all these people here? l will kill you all.
The anti-demon mirror.
Catch.
She's awake.
What are you doing here?
Why am l wearing a red dress?
You were possessed.
Who are you?
Your life-saver.
Life saver?
You don't believe us?
You may ask your sister who is inside.
My sister is inside?
Just open up the umbrella.
l'm here, sister.
Don't be scared, l'm your elder sister,
l won't hurt you.
Are you really dead?
Sister, Du Luo has turned into a fierce ghost,
he killed me and he wants to kill you.
Really?
lf not for them,
you'd have married him already.
What should l do now?
l've sent Judge Bao
for his help to deal with Du Luo.
The only choice we have
is to destroy the ghost.
We'll set up a trap,
pretend that your sister doesn't know anything.
We'll go to the temple first thing tomorrow morning,
take the 4 Heavenly Kings' statues to deserted house
to press down the ghost, l have my plans.
l'm not scared of ghosts, but l'm scared of Zhuge Sen.
Why?
Mrs. Lin has everything worked out.
Right, but where is she now?
What if Zhuge Sen shows up,
what shall we do?
You're not scared of a ghost but a mere human?
You fix this, l'll attend to the other things.
Zhou Peng, get out.
Oh no, Zhuge Sen's here!
Don't be scared, go!
They are here, go.
Zhou Peng, very bold indeed!
You sent a woman to tell me to come here.
Where's the list?
That's why we are here.
How do you want to finish this?
l've got the list right here;
if you win, it's yours.
lf you lose,
come with me to see Judge Bao.
Just the two of you?
Are you scared?
Enough said, kill them.
Go!
l don't want to look.
Don't worry, l've blocked it.
Oh no, the mirror is broken!
l got him, beat him up.
My list.
Thank goodness it's here.
l got you.
Sorry, cousin, very sorry.
l don't have it, he has it.
l won't wear it, it hurts. You always tease me.
Sorry about it.
Bear with it, let me help you.
Fine.
What now?
We have to go to the Du Family's deserted house.
Do we have to?
Yes.
Miss.
Let's go.
Where's the spell?
Here.
Where are they? We will get beaten up.
We don't have a choice.
What then?
We'll get beaten up.
Fine, we'll take turns.
Alright.
Hand it out if you both don't want to die.
What if we don't?
No? l'll torture you slowly.
You think l can't take it?
My turn.
My turn now.
Come on.
Zhuge Sen, surrender if you are smart,
l'll ask Judge Bao for a lighter sentence.
Do you think l'll be scared because you have back up?
You one-eyed captain! You're very arrogant.
Miss, show him what you've got.
Zhou Peng.
Why are you here so late?
He's almost killed us.
Sister.
Possessed.
Beat him.
Protect Mr. Gongsun, l'll take care of them.
Go!
This is called ''Possession''.
Again.
Cousin, get even!
Get even.
You deserve this.
That's right.
Not bad, cousin.
Not bad at all.
lt's your turn to die.
Exactly.
He can't take it, why are you staring at him?
Mr. Gongsun, arrest him.
Take him back.
Yes.
Cousin
What? Go in, you fool.
Still alive?
What else have you got?
ls he trembling?
No, it looks like he's having a seizure.
Are you alright?
l'm tired.
Zhuge Sen is arrested,
l will return to Kaifeng with the young lady first.
ls everything set?
Yes, all ready to go.
The chopper and anti-demon mirror?
Anti-demon mirror, oh no!
lt's broken.
How could you be so careless?
Don't worry,
we've got plenty of stuff here,
we can take care of the King of Ghosts.
We'll head back first.
Please.
Take him.
Get up.
What now?
Set the place up.
You didn't give the list to him?
This is a fake.
A fake?
Look.
Your work is done, Cousin Peng.
Your dead parents will rest in peace.
What else are you thinking of?
Let's help Wu Shunchao,
or it will be a mess
when the ghost comes.
Are you two done?
Get to work.
Come help.
Don't think about it too much.
Either of you could do this,
why did you pick me?
Because you're a wisecrack, the ghosts will be scared.
Sorry about this.
Sorry about this?
Sit...
l always get the bad tasks.
When will that ghost arrive?
l know,
there will be a sudden wind,
when you feel cold.
Don't move.
Where are you two going?
We're setting up a small windmill outside.
And we'll know when
...it starts spinning.
Remember to keep an eye on me.
Got it.
Sit here and wait.
Don't go too far.
We won't.
Where should we hide?
Where? Behind the rockwork.
Help! Help me!! Help!
What is it?
l saw a ghost.
Ghost?
Yeah, it's a ghost.
Where?
At the back, don't let him get close. l'm scared.
That's no ghost, it's just a rat, go.
Help...
What now?
There are lots of bats.
You're afraid of bats?
Sit still, the bats won't touch you.
They look ugly.
Go back.
Come on.
Yes.
Gone.
l can't believe them, we're supposed to be a team.
Mom!
Wu Shunchao is screaming like a chicken again.
lgnore him, go to sleep.
lt's windy, let's go.
How could he take it this time?
Let's take a look.
Sure.
Wu Shunchao.
He's sleeping too.
Let's scare him.
Sure.
What are you doing? You scared to death of him?
lt's working.
Pull the spell.
Scared?
The ghost is on top of me.
Help.
That's Wu Shunchao.
Wu Shunchao...
Ghost! l'm scared.
Over there.
Don't worry, we'll take him down together.
And you said you're not scared, look at him.
He's not going anywhere, get a duvet!
A duvet?
Die once more.
lt's over?
Done.
What now?
What? Break his bones.
Right.
You two may leave...
it's your turn now.
The Four Heavenly Kings.
Oh no, they are broken.
Anti-demon mirror?
lt's broken by One-eyed captain.
Move over.
Tools.
What tools?
Of the Four Heavenly Kings'
Would they work?
l won't lie, go.
Beat him.
Beat you to death.
He's angry.
Don't let him scare you, beat him.
Kneel.
Beat you up.
All broken.
The umbrella is broken, cousin. Your turn.
Wu Shunchao is missing.
Yes.
Sorry, Mr. Ghost, l won't do it next time...
Wu Shunchao, you're slacking off,
go help out.
l won't.
Don't come near me.
Go...
l won't go no matter what.
Have you forgotten? There are 7 stars on your foot.
Right, l'm not scared of anything.
Ghost?
Yes, l'm scared of ghosts.
You're in trouble.
Of course we are.
l'm referring to him.
Anti-demon mirror.
Seven stars on foot.
Yes...
We are the best team.
Go!
You've squashed me.
Cover him with the spells.
Here...
Here.
What now?
Burn him.
This is it.
Not only that he can't roam about,
but he has vanished for good.
Wu Shunchao, you should change jobs.
To what?
Ghost buster!
Ghost buster? l think not.
l've 7 stars on my foot, l am destined to be rich
Let's go tell the young lady,
that we've avenged her.
And tell Mrs. Lin to draw us another spell,
so that l can play again.
Let's go.
lt's all over now.