春秋风月字幕站
http://gdyfdjg.blog.163.com/
^_^=== 春秋风月 原创翻译 ===^_^
Nurse?
Brought you  your
sleeping  medicine    honey
ls  it  night already?
lt's  9: 30
What about the  day?
What about  it?
Was  it a  beautiful  day?
Was the  sun  out?
Was  it warm?
Kind  of warm
Clouds
Were there  clouds  in  the  sky?
l  suppose there  were
l  never  was  much
for  staring  up...
at the  sky all  the time
l  used  to  look  up
at the  clouds  a  lot
lf you  stare  at them
long  enough...
they  become things
you  know?
Ships    people...
Anything  you  want    really...
if you  stare  at them
long  enough
lt's time to take
your temperature  now
Just one  other thing?
Well?
When    nurse?
When  will  they take
the  bandages  off?
How  long?
Until    uh...
Until  they decide
it's  safe for your face
l  know
lt's  pretty  bad    isn't  it?
l've  seen  worse
But  it's  pretty  bad
isn't  it?
l  know  it's  pretty  bad
Ever  since  l  was
a  little  girl...
people  have  always
turned  away from  me
l  can  remember
a  child  screaming...
when  she  looked  at  me
l  never  wanted
to  be  beautiful
l  just wanted－－
l  just wanted  people...
not to  scream  when
they  looked  at  me!
When    nurse?
When  will  they take
the  bandages  off?
Please?
Easy    easy
Let  me take
your temperature
Maybe tomorrow.
Maybe the  next day
You've  been  waiting
so  long  now...
it  really doesn't  make
that  much  difference...
whether  it's  2  days
or  weeks    now    does  it?
Paging  Dr.  Stateman.
Dr.  Stateman    please
Dr.  Bernardi
Evening  report
on  patient  307
Resting  comfortably.
No temperature  change
Thank you    nurse.
l'll  be  right down
Ever  see  her face?
307?
lf  it were  mine
l'd  bury  myself...
in  a  grave  someplace
You  have  been  introduced
to  Miss Janet Tyler...
who  lives  in  a  very  private
world  of darkness...
a  universe  whose  dimensions
are the  size    thickness...
and  length  of the  bandages
that cover  her face
ln  a  moment    we'll  witness...
the  removal
of those  bandages...
and  we'll  see
what's  under them
Keeping  in  mind
of course...
that we're  not to  be
surprised  by what we  see...
because this  isn't
just a  hospital...
and  this  patient
Janet Tyler...
patient  number  307
is  not just a  woman...
because this
happens to  be...
the  Twilight Zone
You're traveling
to  another  dimension...
a  dimension  not only
of sight and  sound...
but of  mind
A journey
into  a  wondrous  land...
whose  boundaries
are  only that...
of the  imagination
You're  entering...
How  about
her  blood  pressure?
1 20  over  80
Good.
Any thyroid  reaction...
since the  latest  round
of  injections?
Nothing  out
of the  ordinary
All  right.  Nurse    you
can  come  back  at  1 1 :00...
and  give  her
the  usual  sedative
All  right    Doctor
Warm  this  evening
Miss  Tyler?
l  thought  it was.
Very warm
You  can  take
my word  for  it
We'll  have those  bandages
off you  very shortly
l  expect you're
uncomfortable
l'm  used  to  it  by  now
l  have  no  doubt.
This  is your...ninth?
ls this
your  ninth  procedure?
The  1 1th
Sometimes  l  think  l've
lived  my whole  life...
inside  of a  dark  cave
There's  kind  of
a  comfort    though...
living  in  a  cave
lt's  so  private
No  one  can  ever  see  me
lt's  hopeless
isn't  it    Doctor?
l'll  never  look
any different
Well    that's  hard  to  say
Up  until  now
you  haven't  responded...
to  any of our  procedures
But there's  no  way
of telling...
not  until  we  get
the  wrapping  off
Your  1 1th  visit
No  more  after this    either
No  more tries
l  don't  know
what else  we  can  do...
not without
endangering  your  life
You  very well
may  have  responded...
to this  last treatment
We just won't
know for  sure...
until  l  take
those  wraps  off
But  if  l  haven't
responded    then  what?
There  are  alternatives
Like?
Don't you  know?
l  know
You're  not alone    Miss  Tyler.
You  realize that    don't you?
You're  hardly alone
Many others  share
your  misfortune...
people  who  look
much  as you  do
Now    one
of the  alternatives－－
should  this  last  procedure
prove to  be  unsuccessful－－
the  state  will  allow you
to  live  comfortably...
among  those
of your  own  kind
My own  kind?
lt's  a  haven
for  people  like you
Now    who  knows?
You  might even  like  it there
But  it's  not fair    Doctor!
l  don't want to  live
among  freaks!
l  want to  live
among  normal  people
Look    Miss  Tyler
we  are  not  unsympathetic...
to your  condition
Your  presence  here  in  this
hospital  attests to that
We're  gonna  do  everything
we  can  for you...
but you're  gonna  have
to  be  realistic
l  could  wear  a  mask
or this  bandage
l  wouldn't  bother  anyone.
l'd  just go  my own  way
l'd  take  a  job    any job
Who  are you  people    anyway?
And  what gives you...
the  right to  decide  where
l  live  and  how  l  live?
l'm  just a  doctor
Only the  state  can
determine  social  policy
All  we  can  do
is follow the  rules...
that they  lay down  for  us
But  it's  not fair    Doctor!
The  people  who  are  different
having  to  stay away...
from  the  people
who  are  normal
Who  decides  what's  normal?
The  state  isn't God    Doctor!
Miss  Tyler    please!
But the  state  is  not God!
lt  hasn't the  right to－－
to  punish  people...
for  an  accident of  birth
lt  hasn't the  right
to  make  ugliness  a  crime
Miss  Tyler!
Now    l've  gotta  ask...
that you  stop this  kind
of talk  immediately!
Do you  understand  me?!
lmmediately!
l  can  feel
the  night out there
l  can  feel  the  air
l  can  smell  the flowers
Mmm
Please take this  off of  me
Please take this  off of  me!
Take this  off of  me!
Please    take this  off of  me!
Miss  Tyler.  Nurse!
－No!
－Got  her  legs!
No!
lt's  all  right
Please!
The  doctor's  decided  to
remove the  bandages  in  307
He  wants to  have
the  anesthetist stand  by
Anesthesia    please.
Wanted  for  307
Yes    when  she  sees
what she  looks  like...
she  may get violent
You  look tired    Doctor
l  suppose  l  am
You've  been  under  a
great deal  of tension
l  know  how  much
it  means to you...
this  case  in  307
Well    you  try and  be
impersonal  about these things
You  do  everything
medically  possible...
everything
humanly  possible
Then  in  the  end
you  cross your fingers...
and  hope for  a  miracle
But you  know
once  in  a  while...
a  miracle  does  happen...
just often  enough
to  let you  know...
that you're  not wrong
or foolish  to  hope for  one
But you're
destroying  yourself...
getting
so  personally  involved
l  know
Don't you  think
l  told  myself that?
l've just seen  that woman's
real  face    nurse...
the face  of  her  real  self
lt's  a  good  face
lt's  a  human  face
l  understand
but  l  must confess...
it's  easier for  me
to think  of  her  as  human...
when  her face
is  covered  up
Why?
Why shouldn't  people
be  allowed  to  be  different?
Why?  Doctor    please!
Be  careful
－What you're talking  is－－
－ls treason?
This  case  has
upset your  balance...
your  sense  of values
l'll  be  all  right
once the  wraps  are  off...
once  l  know  one  way
or the  other
She  keeps  complaining
about  her  legs
Yeah    l'll  be  down
to  see  her  soon
And  now
ladies  and  gentlemen...
our  leader
The  leader's  speech
is  about to  begin
Good  evening
ladies  and  gentlemen
Tonight  l  shall
talk to you...
about glorious  conformity...
about the  delights
and  the  ultimate  pleasure...
of our  unified  society
You  recall    of course...
that directionless
unproductive...
oversentimentalized  era
in  man's  history...
when  it was  assumed
that dissent was...
a  natural  and  healthy
adjunct to  society
You  recall  that during
this  period  of time...
there  was  a  strange
oversentimentalized  concept...
that  it  mattered  not
that  people  were  different...
that this  world  could  exist...
in  some  sort
of crazy  patchwork...
glued  together
in  a  fragmented  society
We  know  now
that that was  wrong
Now  as  l  unwrap...
l  want you  to  keep
your  eyes  open
l  want you
to  describe to  me...
the  different shading
of  light as you  perceive  it...
as  each  layer  of those
bandages  come  off
All  right
Now    if you  make
any  movement...
or  if you  start to  get
emotional  on  us  in  any way...
l'm  gonna  have the  nurses
hold  you  down...
and  have the  anesthetist
put you  under  sedation
ls that  understood?
l  promise...l  won't
All  right
Do you  see  any  light  now
Miss  Tyler?
Just a  little
lt  looks...
lt  looks  gray
How  about  now    Miss  Tyler?
lt's  bright    very  bright
Good
l'm  at the  last  layer  now
Miss  Tyler
l  can－－
l  can  see your  outline
Just vaguely...
but  l  can  see you
Now  l'm  gonna  remove
the  last  bandage    Miss  Tyler
Do you  want a  mirror?
No
No    thank you
No  mirror
l  want you  to  remember
one thing    Miss  Tyler
Are you  listening?
Yes    l'm  listening
We've  done  all  we  could
lf we  were  successful
all  well  and  good...
there  are  no  problems
lf    however
this final  procedure...
has  not achieved
the  desired  results...
keep  in  mind
you  can  still  live...
a  long  and  fruitful  life...
among  people
of your  own  kind
As  soon  as  we  discover
these  results...
we  can  either
release you  or－－
Doctor?
Yes?
lf...if  l'm  still－－
if  l'm  still  so  ugly...
is there
any other  alternative?
Could－－
could  l  be  put away?
Well    under  certain
circumstances    Miss  Tyler...
the  state  does  provide
for the  extermination...
of certain  undesirables
There  are  many factors
to  be  considered    though...
that  bear  on  that decision
And  under the  circumstances
considering  your  age...
and  your  general
physical  condition...
l  doubt very  much  if
we  could  permit anything...
but your transfer
to  a  communal  group...
of  people  with  your－－
your  disability
You'll  make  me  go    then?
That'll  probably  be the  case
All  right    Miss  Tyler    now
remain  very quiet    please...
and  keep your  eyes  open
All  right    Miss  Tyler
Now  here  comes
the  last of  it
l  wish  you  every good  luck
Oh    hideous
No  change.
No  change  at all!
Oh    no
Ahh!  Poor thing
No!
Needle    please.  l  knew
this  would  happen
Turn  on  the  lights!
Needle    please
Stop that  patient!
Stop  her!
There  must  be
a  single  purpose...
a  single  norm...
a  single  approach...
Aah!
A  single  philosophy
of government
That  is  why we  must
no  longer  permit...
the  ugly to  exist
within  our  society!
－They  must  be  removed!
－No!
lt  is  essential
in  this  society...
that we  not only
have  a  norm...
but that we  conform－－
Conformity we  must worship
and  hold  sacred
Conformity  is  our  key
to  survival
Don't  be  afraid    Miss  Tyler
This  is  a  representative
of the  group...
you're to  live  with
Oddly enough
you  came  right to  him
Come  on    now.
He  won't  hurt you
Janet...this  is  Mr.  Smith
He's  in  charge
of the  village  group...
you're to  live  with
You'll  be  able to  live
among  your  own  kind
Miss  Tyler?
We  have  a  lovely village
and  wonderful  people
l  think you'll  like  it
where  l'm  gonna  take you
You'll  be  with
your  own  kind...
and  after  a  little  while－－
you'd  be  amazed
at  how  little  a  while－－
you'll  feel  a  sense
of great  belonging
You'll  feel  a  sense
of  being  loved
And  you  will  be  loved
Miss  Tyler
Please
Miss  Tyler?
Would  you  get
your things  now?
We  can  leave  anytime
Mr.  Smith?
Yes?
Why are  some  of  us
born  so  ugly?
l  don't  know    Miss  Tyler.
l  really don't  know
But you  know  something?
lt doesn't  really  matter
There's  an  old  saying...
A  very    very old  saying
Beauty  is  in  the  eye
of the  beholder
When  we  leave  here...
when  we  go
to the  village...
keep that  in  mind
Try    Miss  Tyler
Say  it over  and  over
in  your  mind
Beauty  is  in  the  eye
of the  beholder
We'll  get your things
and  we'll  leave
Good－bye    Miss  Tyler
Now the  questions
that come to  mind :
Where  is this  place
and  when  is  it?
What  kind  of world  is this
where  ugliness  is the  norm...
and  beauty the  deviation
from  that  norm?
You  want an  answer?
The  answer  is  it doesn't
make  any difference...
because the  old  saying
happens to  be true
Beauty  is  in  the  eye
of the  beholder
ln  this year
or  1 00 years  hence...
on  this  planet...
or  wherever there  is
intelligent  life...
beauty  is  in  the  eye
of the  beholder
Lesson  to  be  learned
in  the  Twilight Zone