－Hey    Ali.
－Hey
Coffee    black    shot of espresso
Oh    you  better  make  it
a  double  shot
One  of those  days    huh?
Why would  today
be  any different?
－The  usual    Dev?
－Chai  tea    no  sugar  added
Aw    that's  my  boyfriend
the  health  nut
“Family of  hobbits found  living
near  Mendocino.”
How  pathetic!
l  don't  know
why  people  waste their  money
Me    neither.  l  mean
does  anyone  believe this  crap?
lt's  not crap.  lt's funny
Then  why aren't  l  laughing?
Obviously
you  don't get the joke
-You  act  like you  wrote this.
－She  did
－Poor thing.
－Pays the  bills
Thanks
l  had  better  get to  work
Yeah.  l'll  see you  at  home.
l  love you
Love you    too    babe
Hi.  Can  l－－
There's  no  reason
for you  to  be  ashamed
So    you're  saying
he'll  forgive  me?
Tonight
you  will  have your  answer
That's－-that's  wonderful
l  don't  know  how to thank you
Are you  sure
l  can't  pay you  or…
No.  No    no.  Keep your  money
Thank you
Really
Sir    are you
some  kind  of fortune-teller?
Each  of  us  has  a  path
we're  meant to travel
l  can  help  show the  way
And  you  don't charge  a  fee?
l  was  born  with  this  gift
l  choose to  share  it
How  noble
What's the  catch?
There  isn't one
Oh    that would  be  a  first!
OK
Let's  see  what you  got
春秋风月字幕站
http://gdyfdjg.blog.163.com/
^_^=== 春秋风月 原创翻译 ===^_^
You're  unhappy at work
Who  isn't?  Come  on.
You  can  do  better than  that
All  right.
Any chance  l'll  get a  new job?
l've  been  sending  out  resumes
for  weeks
An  opportunity awaits you
but you  must seek  it out first
That's  it?
That's  enough
Thank you
You  get what you  pay for
The future－－
we'd  all  like to  know
what's  in  store for  us
Ali  Warner  has just  been  given
a  glimpse  into  hers
Now  she's  about to  go
down  a  path…
that will  lead  her  deep
into the  Twilight Zone
You  are traveling
to  another  dimension－－
a  dimension
not only of sight and  sound…
but of  mind
A journey
into  a  wondrous  land…
whose  boundaries  are  only
that of the  imagination
You're  entering…
Now  we  come to  Pisces!  Health
You're  not a  Pisces    are you?
How  many times  have you  asked
me that?  l'm  a  Sagittarius
Well    lucky you    because
the  cold  and  flu  season…
is  going  to  be  hitting  Pisces
with  a  vengeance  next week
－Or  so  say the  stars.
－Stars?  What stars?
You're the  only astrologer  in
the  world  who  uses  a  dartboard
Oh    darts    stars.
They're the  same thing
At  least they are
at the  National  Bystander
Thank you
You  know    you've  had  that  phone
glued  to your  ear  all  day
l'm  not working  at this  rag
forever
You  sent those  resumes  out
what?  Weeks  ago
You  never  even  got a  nibble.
Now just  because…
some  coffee  shop  con  artist
says that opportunity awaits－－
Yes
You're  with
the  National  Bystander?
That's  right.  Allison  Warner
OK.  We tried  contacting  you
via  e－mail
－Really?
-Yeah    a  few  days  ago
You  know    my e－mail
was  down  for  a  couple  of days
－Can  you  come  in  tomorrow?
－Tomorrow
Yeah    yeah
you  bet  l  can  be there!
－2:00  p.m.
－Thank you
－Tell  me.
－That was  Brash  magazine
They  read  my  resume
and  they want to  interview  me
No  way.  For  a  job?
Get outta  here!
The  guy  in  the  coffee  shop
He  was  right
Ooh!
All  right.  Scorpio
Hey!
l  have  a  job  interview
this  morning
Congratulations
Thanks
Can  l  buy you  a  cup  of coffee
or  a  pastry or  something?
l'm  sorry.
l  don't even  know your  name
lt's  Kanayo
And  thank you    but  l'm
quite  content at the  moment
l  feel  like  l  owe you.  l  mean…
l  don't  know  if  l  believe
in  all  this  prediction  stuff…
but  if  it wasn't for you…
l  would  have  never followed  up
on  all  those  resumes
Well    l'm  glad
l  could  be  of  help
The thing  is
l  really want this job
lt's  with  Brash  magazine
Have you  ever  read  it?
No    l  don't think  so
Well    it's…  Trust  me
lt's  a  great opportunity.
Like you  said
lt's  a  chance for  me to  write
something  smart for  a  change
And  you're  concerned
you  won't get the job?
Oh    really
l  just came to  say thank you
l  didn't come
for  another  reading
l  know.  l  know
But you  have just  begun
to follow your  path
Don't you  want to  see
where  it  leads you?
All  right
l  can't  believe  l'm  doing  this
You  have  nothing  to  worry about
You  mean  l'm  gonna  get the job?
How  do you  know?
lt's  not what  l  know
lt's  what  l  see
What do you  see?
A  secret admirer
Ali
Ali  Warner
Remember  me?
Brad  Holman
－From  Carson  High?
-You're  lookin'  at  him!
Wait    we  were  on  the  school
newspaper together    right?
Yeah.  Even  back then
you  were  a  terrific  writer
Really?  You  never  said  anything
Well    that's  because
l  had  a  real  crush  on  you
No    no.  Don't worry.
That's  not why you're  here
l'm  married.
We're  expecting  a  child  in  July
Oh
So    l've  been  reading  some
of your  stuff  in  the  Bystander
Don't tell  me.  You  read  it
in  the  checkout  line
No    no.
lt's  actually very funny
-You  think?
－Absolutely
ln  fact    l  think
your  sense  of  humor…
would  fit  in  perfectly with
what we're  doing  here  at  Brash
Are you  saying
that  l  have the job?
Well    there  is
one  potential  problem
Chicago?
You  can't  move to  Chicago
Why  not?
'Cause you  can't  leave  me  here
all  alone  is  why  not
l'll  come  back  and  visit
Oh    that  is  so  cold
Oh    my God.  You've  already
made  up your  mind    haven't you?
You  can't get out of  here
fast enough!
Do you  blame  me?
Can  l  come    too?
Maybe  Brash  needs
a  new  astrologer    you  know?
－l  can  bring  my own  dartboard.
－l'll  ask
Oh    l  take  back  everything  bad
l  ever  said  about you
－So    when  do you  leave?
－l  fly out  in  a  day or  so…
but  l  won't actually
make the final  move…
-for  a  couple  weeks.
－Man
Which  is  good  because there's
no  way  l'm  leaving  Devin
l'm  not sure  how  he's  going
to feel  about the  move
Hey    l  could  always
consult the  stars
But you'd  probably
rather talk…
to your  psychic  friend
over  at the  Mocha  Junkie
－What's  his  name?
-You  mean  Kanayo?
He's  not  my  psychic
But you  do  have to  admit…
he  was  right
about  my job  interview…
and  my secret admirer
Ali    sweetie    let  me
fill  you  in  on  a  little  concept
OK?  You  might  have  heard  of  it
lt's  called  coincidence
as  in  lucky guess
Well    l  wouldn't  mind
a  few  more  lucky guesses
You  don't  really  believe this
guy's for  real    though    do you?
l  never  said  l  did    but－－
Hey    why don't you  meet  me  at
Mocha  Junkie tomorrow  morning…
and  you  can  judge for yourself?
All  right
lt  looks  like
l'm  going  to  be  moving…
to  Chicago
for  a    you  know    a  new job
And  l'm  just worried
about  my  boyfriend
He's  not sure  whether
he  wants to  move to  Chicago…
and  l  don't want to  lose  him
We've  been  together
for  almost a  year  now
Do you  think there's  any way
that  he'll  come  with  me?
The  eyes  closing.
That's  a  nice touch
l'll  tell  you
if  he  starts talking…
in  my Aunt  Ruth's  voice
l  am  out of  here!
Shh!
Go  home…
and  you  will  find  your  answer
That's  it?
ls that the  best you  can  do?
lt's  enough
Devin!
Well    l  know the  answer  now
Anyone  who  still  listens
to  heavy  metal  music…
doesn't deserve
to  go to  Chicago
Devin－－
Devin    you  bastard
OK    so that's flight  355…
and  it  leaves tomorrow  night
at 7:45
-Yes    that's  correct.
－All  right    great.  Thanks
What  is  it?  l'm  only going
for  a  couple  of days
That's  not  it
Oh    l  get  it
You're  pissed
because  Kanayo  was  right again
l  just don't think
you  should  see  him  anymore
Why  not?
'Cause  at some  point
he's  going  to  be  wrong…
and  you're  going
to  have to  pay for  it
－ls that a  prediction    Seth?
－l'm  not joking
lf  he's there
when  l  get  my  morning  coffee…
l'll  talk to  him
lf  he's  not    it's  no  big  deal
You're  here  early
Can't get enough  of your  coffee
－Thanks    Tony.
-You're  welcome
－Hey    man.
－Hey
Get the  usual?
Cool
Hi    Kanayo
Thank you
l'm  flying  out to  Chicago
tonight…
to  meet with  my  new  bosses
and  l  just wondered…
if there  was  anything
l  should  know
What  is  it?
What's  wrong?
l  would  not do  any traveling
at this time
Are you  saying  that
l  shouldn't go to  Chicago?
lt  is  not your  path
But  l  have to  go
l  may  never  get
another  offer  like this
l  can  only advise you.
The  decision  is yours to  make
－Hello?
－Ali?  You're  still  there
l  know  it sounds  crazy
but  Kanayo told  me  not to  go
Well    thank  God  you  didn't!
Turn  on  the  news
…received  an  update
There  appear to  be  no  survivors
To  repeat once  again
flight  355  has  crashed…
ninety  miles  outside  of Chicago
Sources  at the  National
Transportation  Safety  Board…
Flight  355?
Focusing  on  engine failure…
as the  probable  cause
of the  accident
－That was  my flight.
－Ali    are you  seeing  this?
Ali    are you  there?
Ali?
Ali    answer  me.  Are you  there?
Ali
l  still  can't  believe
that you  were  so  right…
about  me  not taking  that  plane
But what  l  really  need
to  know…
is  how  long
l  should  avoid  travel
l  mean    my car
isn't ever  going  to  make  it…
all  the  way to  Chicago
but what about a  train  or  a  bus?
l  mean    what's  important…
is that  my  path
still  leads  me there    right?
－What?  Don't tell  me  it's－－
－Shh!
－l  can't  help you.
－What?  Why  not?
-You  must clear your  mind.
－OK    fine.  How  do  l  do that?
Maybe you  should  come  back
tomorrow
No    l  cannot come  back tomorrow
l  need  to  know  now.
l  have  so  many questions
lf  l'm  not going  to take
the job    then  l  have to  know…
because  l've  already given
the  Bystander  my  2  weeks  notice
Please    please.  Come  back  later
No!  l  need  to  know
And  you  will…
later
He's  all  yours
Like  a  moth  to  a  flame
You  just can't stay away
can  you?
Well    look  at those two.
l'm  sure they're  asking  him…
what  movie
they should  see tonight
Those  dilettantes!
l'm  glad
you  can  laugh  about this
Ali    believe  me
l  am  not  laughing
Look  at you
Look  at you    honey.
You're  a  mess
OK    come  on.  You  and  l
we're taking  a  walk.  Let's  go
Do  not  make  me  drag  you
out of  here.  Let's  go.  Come  on
OK    Seth    enough  already
Look    l  know you
had  a  bit of a  rough  night－－
Rough  night?
lf  it wasn't for  Kanayo…
l  would  be  dead    along  with
those  people  on  the  plane
All  right.
Let's just say this  guy…
really does  have the  power
to  predict the future－－
－The  man  saved  my  life.
－OK.  He  saved  your  life
But  it's  still  your  life
isn't  it?
l  mean    come  on    you  can't  let
this  guy decide your  every  move
Even  if what  he  predicts
is true?
No    especially  if  it's true
Sweetie
if you're  not careful…
you  won't  be  able
to  cross the  street…
without getting  his  OK
Oh    God.  Come  on
Am  l－－do you  really think
l  look that  pathetic?
Look    it's  simple.  Kanayo  says
each  one  of  us  has  a  path
l  just  need  to  make  sure
that  l  am  on  the  right one
Ali    do you  hear yourself?
l  have
a  lot of  important questions…
that  need  to  be  answered
l  need  a  new job.
l  need  a  new  boyfriend
You  don't  need!
Honey    you  don't  need  Kanayo
to  do  any of those things
Yeah    yeah    yeah
l  don't  believe this.
l  don't  believe this!
After  everything
that  l  have just said…
you're  still  thinking
about going  back  in  there?
Shh!
You  know  what?  That's  right
And  it's  my decision
Well    fine    then.
Get your fix    OK?
l'll  visit you  in  rehab
－Hey    where'd  Kanayo  go?
-You  just  missed  him
Do you  know  where  he  lives
or  where  he  works?
Not a  clue
Well    what about a  phone  number?
l  really  need
to  get  in  touch  with  him
Sorry    Ali.  They come    they
drink their  coffee    they go
What about a  last  name?  Come  on
help  me  out  here    please?
Look    he told  me  once    but
don't ask  me to  pronounce  it
Yeah
Ali    it's  closing  time
Hey    he's  usually  here
first thing  in  the  morning
Come  on
Hi    this  is  Ali
Flying  cockroaches
invade  Cleveland
Read  all  about  it
in  the  National  Bystander
And  leave  a  message
after the  beep
Ali?  Ali    pick  it  up.
l  know you're there
lf you  don't want to  pick  up
that's  OK
l  just want to  say  l'm  sorry
all  right?
l  was－－l  was
a  little  harsh  today
l  have  no  right to tell  you
how to  live your  life
You're  a  strong  person
You  always  make
the  right decisions…
and  l'm  sure
this time you  will    too
l'm  at  home  if you  need  to talk.
Bye
Oh    my God!
Kanayo!
－Kanayo.  Where  is  he?
－He's  already come  and  gone
No    no    no    no    no!
That can't  be!
He just walked  out the  door.
You  should  be  able to－－
Kanayo!
Kanayo    wait!
Hey
No!
Kanayo!  Kanayo    please!
Oh    God.  Oh    God
Hang  on    Kanayo.
You're  gonna  be  OK
You  have to  be  OK.  l  need  you
l  need  you  to  help  me
get  me  back  on  my  path
l  can't find  it without you
What  is  it?
What are you  trying  to  say?
No!  You  can't die!
Don't  leave  me!
Please!  Kanayo!
What am  l  supposed  to  do?
l  don't  know  what  my  path  is!
What's  going  to  happen  to  me?
Where  am  l  going?
Oh    God    where  am  l  going?
By seeking  a  path
to  her future…
Ali  Warner  put  her  destiny
into the  hands  of another
And  now that  path
has  become  a  dead  end…
filled  with  helplessness
despair    and  boundless  dread
Ms.  Ali  Warner    facing
the  bleakest of futures…
in  the  Twilight Zone
Where  am  l  going?