Yeah    yeah    yeah.
Hold  on    let  me  speak    OK?
Listen    look
you  bozos  asked  me…
if  l  wanted  to  increase
my credit  limit
l  mean    what the  hell
was  l  gonna  say?  No?
Yeah    well
how  was  l  supposed  to  know…
l  was  gonna  get  laid  off?
No    listen    l  don't  know－－
l  don't  need  you  tellin'  me
how  much  l  owe    OK?
What do you  want to  know?
How  much  l  owe  my ex－girlfriend?
Or the three  grand
l  owe  my  brother?
No    no    you  can't cancel
my credit card!
l  got  bills  up the yin-yang!
Yeah    well
sorry doesn't cut  it    pal!
Uhh!
Yeah?
Hello    Vince
Do  l  know you?
l'm  Muriel.  This  is  Michael.
May we  come  in?
Look    if you're
sellin'  somethin'    l'm－－
We're  not selling  anything
Good.  'cause  l  don't
have  any  money
You've  been  chosen
For  what?
We're  here to  offer you  a  chance
at a  whole  new  life
Ha  ha.  l  knew  it.  Good－bye
You're  not  listening    Vince.
You've  been  chosen
l'd  hate to  see those
pretty  little fingers…
get smashed  in  my door    OK?
We're  here to  help you
Look    you  wanna  help  me?
l  need  a  job
l  could  use  some  money
in  my  pocket
And  while you're  at  it…
why don't you  help  me
get  my girlfriend  back?
What we're  offering  you  is
a  little  bit  more  substantial
And  what  l'm  offering  you
is  a  chance to  get  lost…
before  l  come  out there
and  kick your  ass
l'm  gonna  count to three
One…
two…
What's this?
lt's  a  gift
Yeah    well    whatever  it  is
l'm…not  buyin'
Don't  be  so  sure    Vince
春秋风月字幕工作室
http://gdyfdjg.blog.163.com/
^_^=== 春秋风月 原创翻译 ===^_^
Hey there    Vince
Now    we  know you've  had  some
disappointments  recently
l  guess  lookin'  back
on  your  life…
there's  not  much
to  be  proud  of－－
problem  kid    barely  made  it
through  high  school…
petty thefts    all  those  DUls
ls  it any wonder
that  Lea  dumped  you?
But you  don't  need  me
to  remind  you…
that failure  sticks to you
like  gum  on  a  shoe
l  don't  need  to  listen  to this
But you  and  l  both  know
there's  more to  Vince  Hansen…
than  the  record  shows
There's  something  inside you
Vince    something  worth  rescuing
That's  why
you've  been  contacted
That's  why you've  been  chosen
We'll  be  back for you  soon
That's  a  sales  pitch…
Vince  Hansen  doesn't  hear
every day
But what exactly
did  they  mean  by chosen?
ln  the  Twilight Zone…
Vince  is  about
to find  out the  answer…
whether  he  wants to…
or  not
Wha…
You're traveling
to  another  dimension－－
a  dimension  not only
of sight and  sound…
but of  mind
A journey
into  a  wondrous  land…
whose  boundaries  are  only that
of the  imagination
You're  entering…
lf you  do  drive
the  Ahman  freeway…
it's jammin'  up from  Avenue  50
all  the  way  into  down－－
Hey    hey    red
Hey.  How's  it  hangin'?
To the  left
Not that  it does  me  any good
in  this  wheelchair
What do you  got for  me    slick?
The  essentials.  What else?
lt's  up to  sixty  million
Feelin'  lucky today
Ah    mmm.
Nighttime  reading
-Just what  l  like.
－Heh  heh
Tuna  fish  again?
What am  l    a  cat?
lt's  healthy
Come  on
All  right.  Hmm
What do  l  owe you    kiddo?
A  can  of  brew
will  call  us  even
You're  a  good  neighbor.
You  know that?
－Drop  dead.
-You  first
So…how's
the job  search  comin'?
Ah    well    l'm  supposed  to  see
Doyle this  afternoon
He  says  he  may  have  somethin'
lined  up for  me  at the  shop
Doyle?  Doyle's  a  surly  bastard
Yeah.  Well    so  are you
That's your  problem    man
You  hang  out with
the  wrong  kind  of  people
Damn    are they still  around?
You  mean  Michael  and  Muriel?
“  Gimme that
old  time  religion  ”
They come  knockin'  here    too?
“  lt's  good  enough  for  me  ”
They're freakin'  wackos
They even  left  me
some  video to  watch
Had  my  name  engraved
on  it and  everything
Yeah    they  left  me  a  DVD
Oh    yeah?
Did  you  watch  it?
Why the  hell  would  l  watch  it?
Yeah
l  don't  know    it's  weird
Mine－－mine    uh    it－－it…
－had  all  this  stuff on  it.
－What  kind  of stuff?
l  don't  know.  Like    uh
you  know    like    personal  stuff
Like  my  life  and    uh…my  past.
They even  knew  about  Lea
Get  used  to  it    buddy
This  is  what  happens
when  this  old  time  religion…
meets the  information
superhighway
You  can't  keep  nothin'
a  secret  no  more
Yeah.  What can  we  do    you  know?
We  can  have  another  beer.
That's  what we're  gonna  do
That's  good  enough  for  me
What do you  mean
there's  no job?
You  told  me there's  work  here
l  was  being  optimistic
What the  hell  good
does that do  me?
Well    l'm  sorry about that
What    l  can't  have  a  lousy fry?
May  l  remind  you?
Things  are tough  all  over
Yeah    but you're
the  one  sittin' there…
with  all  the  French  fries
And  they're  good    too
Do  me  a  favor?
Let  me finish  my  lunch
in  peace
Thank you
They're  among  us
They  may  look  normal
like you  or  me…
but don't  let that fool  you
They  may  look  like  missionaries
but they're  aliens
They're  gonna  wipe  us  out
We  have to  stop them
They've  locked  out
our  satellites
Now  we  can't see their  ships
And  now they're  here
They're  gonna  take  us
back to their  planet…
turn  us  all  into  slaves
Would  you  get  lost?
God    save  us from  them
The  sudden  failure…
of the  Global  Satellite  Network
has  increased  world  tension
We're  approximately
fifteen  minutes  away…
from  the  start
of an  emergency session…
of the  U.N.  Security Council
And  the  latest opinion  polls
show the  american  public…
Turn  this  crap  off    would  ya?
l'm  depressed  enough  as  it  is
What the  hell
are you  doin'  here?
lt's  nice
to  see you    too    Gordo
l'll  have  a  vodka  tonic
hold  the tonic
Have  it someplace  else
You  forgettin'    man?
You're  barred  from  here
ls  Lea  around?
Heh
You're  a  regular  glutton
for  punishment    aren't ya?
l'm  a  romantic    is  what  l  am
Here you  go
Just when  l  thought
it was  gonna  be  a  nice  day
l'm  not  loanin' you  any  money
Well    that's  good    'cause
l'm  not  here to  borrow  any
lt's  awful  lonely
out there  without you
Well    try gettin'  a  job.
Maybe you  won't  be  so  lonely
Look    l'm  tryin'.  l'm  tryin'
l  don't  understand
how you're  able…
to just go  on  with  your  life
like  l  never  existed
You  just don't get  it    do you?
Well    maybe  l'm  not
as  smart as you  are
No  argument there
Vince    l  want to  make  something
of  my  life    you  know?
l  don't want to  waste  it
hangin'  out and  partying
lt's time to  grow  up
Does  any of this
ring  a  bell?
Baby…l  love you
And  l  love you    OK?
lt's just…
that's  not enough  anymore
Y-you  don't  mean  that
Vince    you're  not  listening
all  right?
That's  why you  never
get the  message
Lea    you  gotta  give  me
another  chance  here    OK?
Just  let  me  explain
There's  nothin'
to  explain    man
Stay out of this    Gordo.
lt's  got  nothin' to  do  with  you
You  know    you're  right?
He  never  gets the  message
－Hey    don't  hurt  him!
－Too  late
Ohhh…uhh…
Have you  watched
the  DVD yet    Vince?
Who  are you  freaks?
What do you  want from  me?
We're  here to  help you
Help  someone  else
Time  is  running  out
l  don't care!  Leave  me  alone!
You  don't want that    Vince!
You've  been  chosen!
Hey    neighbor!
Turning  from
the faltering  negotiations…
at the  United  Nations
to  local  news…
police  are  issuing  an  appeal
for  anyone  with  information…
about the  disappearance
of Wendy  Robins to  come－－
No freakin'  way
Speed!
Speed?
Uhh
'Cause there's  somethin'
inside you    Speed
Something  worth  rescuing
That's  why
you've  been  contacted
That's  why you've  been  chosen
We'll  be  back for you  soon
l'm  telling  you    Speed
couldn't  have  gone  anywhere…
without  his  chair.
The  guy can't walk
Then  where  could  he  be
Mr.  Hansen?
Beats the  hell  out of  me
Who  are you?
Richard  Schultz
Homeland  Security
lf  l  could  have  everybody
step  outside    please
Why?
Right this  way    Mr.  Hansen
Do you  know  if Mr.  Moorcock
had  any visitors  lately?
Uh    yeah.  Yeah
l  was just tellin'
the  officers  inside
Uh…Michael  and－－and  Muriel
At  least    that's  what
they called  themselves
They're  some  kind  of
religious  nuts    l  think
Were you  visited
by them  as  well?
Well    yeah    they  hit
the  whole  neighborhood
There's  more  of 'em
out there    too
Who  are these  people?
And  what would  they want
with  a  guy  like  Speed?
Mr.  Hansen
l'd  be  extremely careful…
who  l  let  in  my  home
if  l  were you
Heh.  What are you  sayin'…
they're  gonna  try
and  disappear  me    too?
There's  a  pattern  forming
So  Speed  wasn't the first
There's  been  others?  How  many?
You  call  me  if you  see  Michael
Muriel    or  any of their friends
Wait    wait    wait.
Just  between  you  and  me
Are－－are  we talkin'
aliens  here?
You  have  my  number
Diplomats  at the  United  Nations
Security Council…
have traded  threats…
over the failure  of
the  Global  Satellite  Network
ln  other  news
the  mysterious  wave…
of  missing  persons
around  the  world…
has  baffled  the  international
scientific－－
Look    Lea    l  didn't come
to  make trouble
l  just want to  warn  you－－
l've  been  tryin' to  call  you
Oh…that's  great
Um    listen    there's  somethin'
you  need  to  know
l'm  not exactly sure
but  l  think  we're  all  in  danger
Where  is  everyone?
Didn't you  see the  sign?
We're  closed
Listen    you  don't  know
what's  been  goin'  on
People  have  been  disappearing
Oh    Vince
No    it's true.
You  gotta  come  home  with  me
We'll  lock  ourselves  in    and  if
anyone  we  don't  know  comes  by－－
Vince    can  l  please
say something?
What?
l  just feel  so  much  love
for you  right  now
l  just…
l  want  us to  be
together…forever
And  we  will
And  l'll  do  a  lot  better
l  promise
-You  mean  that?
－Oh    you  know  l  do
Well    you  could  start
by watching  the  DVD
What  DVD?
The  DVD that Muriel
and  Michael  left you
Lea－－
We've  been  chosen
OK    Lea    listen  to  me
There's  no  need
to  be frightened
We  can  still  get away
Don't  be  silly
They're  waiting  for  us
l'm  supposed
to take you  to them
Oh    my God
They've  already turned  you
into  one  of them
Vince    you  still  want
to  be  with  me    right?
Well    we  can  be together
lsn't that what you  want?
l  owe you
Hey    hold  on  a  second.
The  least you  can  do…
is tell  me
what you  need  it for
What  if  l  told  you  Speed
was  vaporized  by aliens?
American  lntelligence  Services
report…
that    for the first time  since
the fall  of the  Eastern  Bloc…
every  nation
with  nuclear  weapons…
is  at their  highest state
of  readiness for  war
The  president will  be  addressing
the  nation  tonight…
to  call  for  calm  in  the face
of this  growing  crisis
Come  on
Oh    come  on    come  on!
Go  away!
l  mean  it!
Vince!
Uhh!
You  shouldn't  have  done that
l'm  sorry    Vince.
lt's  clear  now…
you  were  never  meant
to  be  chosen
Bye    Vince
l  really did  love you
l  came  back for you    buddy
Sorry you  won't
be  with  us    man
ln  a  world  about to  end…
Vince  Hansen  was  given
a  chance for  salvation
But  leave  it to  Vince－－
one  of  life's  perpetual  losers－－
to  make the  wrong  choice…
and  to  wind  up
just another  cinder…
on  an  ash  heap  somewhere
in  the  Twilight Zone