Ellen
we're  going  to  be  late
We're  right on  time
Besides...
the  babysitter's
not  here yet
l'll  get  it
Hi.  l'm  Miranda  Evans
Danielle
come  meet Miranda
Come  on  in.
l'm  Pete
This  is  Ellen
Miranda    meet  Danielle
Hi    Danielle
Hi
Come this  way
The  agency tells  me you're
studying  child  development
Yes    Mrs.  Randall
l  hope to  make
child  care  my career
Well    Danielle  should  be
easy to  care for
She'll  probably spend...
most of the  evening
in  her  room
OK.  Just a  few things
Danielle's  allergies...
are  listed  in
the  blue  section
Acceptable foods  are  in
the yellow  section
The  pink  section  contains
approved  TV  programs...
and  phobias  are
in  the  purple  section
No  problem
Emergency  numbers
are  in  the  book
Just call  our  cell
if you  have  any questions
Now  we're  late
Good  night    Pet
Have  a  good  time
OK    you    too.  Be  good
Bye    Mommy.
Bye    Daddy
See you    honey
So  l'll  bet your  room
is  pretty cool
l  picked  the  colors.
Do you  want to  see?
l'd  love to
Miranda  Evans
has  a  bond  with  children
She  understands
their  problems    their fears
But tonight she  will  meet
a  special  little  girl...
with  a  very
unique  problem...
that will  stretch  Miranda's
bond  with  reality  itself
That over there
is  Ursula  Unicorn
And  this
brown  horse  is  Hans
l  got  him  for  Christmas
And  do you  want
to  know  a  secret?
My  mom  doesn't  know
l  know...
but for  my  birthday...
l'm  getting  the  little
girl  who  rides  him...
a  bridle    and  a  saddle
Wow
These  dolls
are  beautiful
Do they fit  in
your  dollhouse?
They're  not
to  play with
Why  not?
They just aren't
We  could  play a  game
l  have  Clue
and  Eloise  Monopoly...
uh    Girl  Power...
Name  That  State－－
it's  educational
Oh    and  l've  got
Herd  Your  Horses
l  love that game
sounds  great
What are you  doing?
One  of the  dolls fell.
Don't you  want  me to fix  her?
－ls there  a  key?
－l'll  do  it
You  have to  be
really careful
春秋风月字幕站
http://gdyfdjg.blog.163.com/
^_^=== 春秋风月 原创翻译 ===^_^
Ow!
l'm  bleeding!
Maybe you  cut  it
on  the  glass
No    she  bit  me!
What    the  doll?
She  couldn't  bite you
Danielle
She's just a  doll
l've  got a  Kleenex
You're traveling
to  another  dimension
A  dimension  not only
of sight and  sound...
but of  mind
A journey  into
a  wondrous  land...
whose  boundaries
are  only that...
of the  imagination
You're  entering...
l  think  Shelley's  mad  at  me
Shelley?
And  why would
Shelley  be  mad?
'Cause  l  want
to  play with  you...
and  not with  her
Do you  get  mad
when  someone...
doesn't want
to  play with  you?
No    but  Shelley does
She's  very jealous
That  must  make  it  hard...
when  you  have friends
over to  play
Shelley  must get
angry a  lot
l  had  a  friend
but she  moved  away
And  Shelley's  a  new friend
She thinks  l  should
just  play with  her...
and  the  other  girls
The  other  girls?
The  dolls?
Yeah
But you're  my  newest friend...
and  l'm  going  to  play
with  you...
downstairs
where  Shelley can't see
OK.  Let's  go  downstairs...
and  make  some  cocoa
and  popcorn
l  can't  have  sugar
after  7:00
Well    this  is
a  special  night
Let's  make  an  exception
Can  you  do that?
Let's  go  crazy
Cool
l  love  chocolate
l  do    too
Shelley doesn't
－Really?
－Nope
But  Katie  loves  chocolate
the  Belgian  kind
And  Katie  is?
She's the  one
next to  Shelley...
in  the  ski  outfit
She  went to the  snow
with  us
Katie's  afraid
of the  dark...
that's  why  l  have
to  have  a  night－light
So you're  not the  one
afraid  of the  dark
Well    l'm  mostly
afraid  of spiders
Angie's  afraid
of the  water
lsn't that weird?
Jenny's  not afraid
of anything
We  used  to  watch
Buffy  together
She  wanted  Buffy and  Spike
to  hook  up
Do you  even  know
what that  means?
No    but Jenny
really wanted  it
Wow.  Your  dolls
sound  like fun
Sometimes
Sometimes they aren't
Anyway    you're  my
new  best friend
Oh    l  forgot  my game.
l'll  be  right  back
"The  child  is  not always
the  root of the  problem
"Sometimes
the  child  is  gifted...
"and  thinks  differently
than  his  or  her  peers
"The  child  can  be
subject to fantasies...
imaginary friends
and  anti－social  behavior."
Aah!
Danielle    what's  wrong?
Oh    no
Shelley.  She's  gone
Did  you  take  her  out?
She  got out  by  herself
lt's your fault!
You  left the  key  in!
Why don't you  get
the  horse  game－－
But  Shelley
could  get  hurt!
OK.  Where  do you
think  she  went?
She  likes the  dark
Then  let's  go  look
in  the  dark
Lock the  case first
Where's the  key?
lt's  not there?
l  bet  Shelley took  it
Let's  go find  where you－－
let's  go find  Shelley
Where  should  we  look?
Mom  and  Dad's  room.
lt's  really dark  in  there
She  can  hide
l'm  not allowed
to  go  in  there
You  want to  wait
in  the  hall?
l  think  she's  downstairs
Let's  go  see
Shelley doesn't  like
chocolate
This  could  have
hurt someone    Danielle
l  know
Why would  Shelley  be  mad
when  l  love  her  so  much?
Sit down    OK?
Danielle    l'm  your friend
Do you  feel  like...
l'm  not  paying  enough
attention  to you?
l  didn't  break  anything.
Shelley did
l  told  you
She's  mad
and  l  don't  know  why
l  take  really good
care  of the  girls
Do you  think they're  mad
at  being  locked  up?
But that's  where they  live
lf they get out
they could  get  hurt    or  lost
l  have to take  care  of them
l'm  like their  mom
Have  any of them  ever
gotten  out  before?
When  you  were  upset
maybe?
Shelley got out once  before
She  broke  my  mom's
Chinese teapot
Did  you  tell  your  mom...
that  Shelley
broke the teapot?
l  told  her
it was  an  accident
So    when  your  mom's
not  here...
you  don't  blame things
on  the  dolls
You're  psychologizing  me
You  think  l'm  making
all  this  up
l'm  not stupid
l  don't think
you're  stupid
But  maybe
if you  told  your  mom...
that you'd  rather
take the  dolls  out...
to  play with  instead
of  locking  them  up－－
l  can't take them
out of the  case!
l  told  you!
Why don't you  believe  me?!
Uhh!
lt  hurts.  lt  hurts
Shelley tripped  me
Stay  here.
l'll  call  your  mom
No.  We  have to  put
Shelley  back
You're  hurt    Danielle
l  have to  call  your  mother
We  have to  put  her  back  now!
ln  a  minute    Danielle
Mrs.  Randall?
lt's  Miranda
No    it's  not
an  emergency
l  just  need  to  know  where
the first－aid  kit  is
Danielle  cut  herself
No    no    she's fine.
lt's just a  little  cut
All  right    honey
let's  go  upstairs
Don't  leave  Shelley
She'll  do  something  else  bad
She's  right  here
OK.  All  done.  Better?
We  have to  put
Shelley  back
Oh    no
They all  got out
Danielle    where  are they?
l  don't  understand.
l  love them
Danielle    sometimes  people
even  parents...
don't always tell  you
that they  love you...
but they  really do
lf you  tell  me  where
you  put the  dolls...
then  we  can  talk  about  how－－
Don't you  see?
Shelley  hid  the  key...
and  then  made  sure
we  would  go  downstairs...
so  she  could
come  back  up  here...
and  let them  all  out
Shelley's  a  doll
not  Sydney  Bristow
We  have to find  them!
This time    you  tell  me...
what you  did
with  the  dolls
We  can  put them  back
and  then  go  play a  game
l  didn't do
anything  with  them!
Shelley  let 'em  out!
They  never  all
got out  before
OK.  We're  going
downstairs
l'm  going  to  do
my  homework－－
We  can't!
We  have to find  them...
before they do  something!
Let's  go    drama  queen
Look
Very clever
but  it won't work
How  did  you  do this?
Look  out!
That wasn't  nice
Shelley
That's  mine
lsn't that a  little
grown－up for you?
No    it fits.  See?
l'm  phoning  your  parents
They  moved
l  told  you
Mrs.  Randall    it's  Miranda
Look    there's  some
weird  things  going  on  here
So    l'm  going  to take  Danielle
and  go to  my  house  until－－
What's  wrong?
lt's  OK.  l'm  going  to  call
your  parents  on  my cell  phone
My  battery
Damn  it!
Danielle?
"Young  children
who  play alone...
may  be  at  increased  risk
for  later  problems."
Shelley
l  don't  know  what you...
and  your freaky  little
friends  are  up to...
but  l'm  taking  Danielle...
and  getting  out of
this  horror  movie
Miranda    help!
You  stupid  bitches!
Help  me
Danielle
are you  in  there?
Open  the  door
l'm  scared
Danielle    you  have
to  let  me  in
l  won't  let them  hurt you
l'm  scared
We  have to  get
out of the  house
But they're  in  my  room
Yes    they are    but...
but we  can  get  past them
l  got  past them
didn't  l?
They're  not after you
l  don't get  it.
They're just dolls
They're  not just dolls!
l  can  carry you
They won't even
be  able to  reach  you
Where  did  you  get that?
That's  mine!
lt's  mine!  Give  it  back!
That girl  in  the  picture
she  was  wearing  this
l  just wanted  them
to  be  my friends
Katie...
you  said
she  liked  chocolate
Angie  was  afraid
of the  water
You  watched  Buffy
with  Jenny
You  shouldn't  have
looked  in  there!
Don't  be  mad.
l  didn't  mean  to
What did  you  do to them?
They said  they were
my friends...
but they always  left
when  my  parents  got  back
They were  babysitters
Your  parents  paid  them
to  look  after you...
not to  be your friends
l  begged  them  to  stay
but they wouldn't
They  left    and  they
forgot about  me
Oh    God
The  dolls  weren't
trying  to  hurt you
They were trying  to  warn  me
They told  me to  leave
All  the  clues
They're  still
trying  to  warn  me...
to  get away from  you
Don't  be  mad!  Don't go!
Let  me  go    Danielle!
Let  me  go!
Don't  leave!
Let go    Danielle!  Let go!
Stay!
Look    l  came  home...
and  found  my daughter
hysterical  in  the  closet!
She's  1 0!
Yeah    well    this  is
the third  time...
a  sitter from  your  agency...
has  walked  out
and  left  my  kid  alone!
l  want to talk
to the  manager!
Really    Danielle...
these  were  all  over
the  house
Just what were you  doing?
l  thought you  were
going  to  play quietly
lt's  no  wonder  we  can't
keep  a  babysitter...
when  you  behave
like  a  wild  thing
l'm  sorry    Mommy
l  know you  are
but you  know the  rules
You're  grounded  to your
room  for the  weekend
Good  night    Danielle
Turn  on  my  night－light
For  Katie
You  were  all  so  bad
l  have to  ground  you
forever
You're  never
getting  out again
l  wish  you'd  stop  hating  me
lt'd  be  nicer
if we  were  all  friends
But you  know the  rules
This  is your
new friend  Miranda
Now you  all  be  nice to  her
Miranda  Evans
thought she  could  help...
a  little  girl
overcome  her fears
Now    Miranda
will  be  able to  ponder...
the true  meaning  of fear...
from  inside  a  glass  prison
known  as the  Twilight Zone