Congratulations    Annie.
lt's  all  yours
lt's  hard  to  believe
Scott    that goes
to the  downstairs  bath
l  don't  know  how…
we're  ever  going  to
be  able to  afford  this…
but  it  is  perfect
There's  only one thing  missing
Get  me the  dolly    will  you?
l  remember that  photo.
Even  Czonka's  smiling
You  sent  it out
as  a  Christmas  card  last year
Mm...hmm
lt  belongs  right there
doesn't  it?
Mm
Mom!
Sean  says  l  have  dragon  breath!
You  don't  believe  me
go  ahead  and  sniff  her
l  hate that  photo
That dress  makes  me
look  chunky!
- What dress  doesn't?
- Mom!
So  much  for
my  perfect  moment    huh?
Hey    l  said
no  skateboarding  indoors!
Whoa!  Easy    Czonka    easy!
How  'bout  backing  me  up  here?
Come  on    honey.
lt's  moving  day
Czonka!  Czonky    bad  boy!
Help…please.
Someone    anyone?
You'll  be fine    Annie
Call  me  if you  need
anything    OK?
- Philip.
- Thank you
Annie    l  just  have to  say
that you  were  right
lt feels
just  like  home  already
Czonka!
What?  What?  What?
Oh    boy
Don't tell  me
it's  only  moving  day
Where'd  l  put
those  paper towels?
Honey    relax
Phillip    we've  been  here
fifteen  minutes…
and  already
the  hardwood  is  scraped…
and  the fireplace  is  stained
They're  kids    Annie.
The  dog  got excited
Phillip    this  is  supposed  to  be
a  fresh  start    a  new  beginning
Just  because
we  have  a  new  house…
doesn't  mean  we're  gonna
turn  into  a  new family
Sometimes  l  wish  we  could
Annie  had  it on  the truck
Does that  make  me
a  terrible  person?
Don't worry.
lt'll  be  our  little  secret
Czonka    you  bad  dog!
Go  give  Mommy some  love
Oh.  Very funny.
Don't tell  me…
Czonka's  already  made
a  new friend
What are you  talking  about?
Come  here    Czonk.  Come  here
Good  boy!  Who's  my champ!
That's  right    Czonka  is!
What's  wrong?
Stop  screwing  around    Phillip
l  mean  it.  This  isn't funny.
lf you  bought another  dog…
Do you  know  what Mommy
is talking  about?
Of course you  don't.
Neither  do  l
This  is the  wrong  day
for  silly games
Perfection
lsn't that something
we  all  yearn  for?
Annie  Macintosh  does
She  wants the  perfect  house
the  perfect family…
the  perfect  life…
but she's  about to  learn  that
perfection  is  an  illusion…
and  a  terrifying  one
at that…
in  The  Twilight Zone
You're traveling
to  another  dimension...
a  dimension  not only
of sight and  sound…
but of  mind
A journey
into  a  wondrous  land…
whose  boundaries  are  only that
of the  imagination
You're  entering…
Satisfied?
l  don't  understand
What  happened  to  Czonka?
l  really wish
you'd  stop  saying  that
You're  gonna  give  him
a  complex
That  is  not  my dog
Well    l  don't  know
what to tell  you
Look  at  his  AKC  papers
Look  at  his  ribbons
his  champion  certificate
- How  much  proof do you  need?
- lt's  not  my dog!
Annie    you  love this  dog!
Hell    there  are  days you  think
you  like  him  better than  me
Why are you  pretending
you  don't  recognize  him?
Go  away.  Phillip    get  him  away
Czonka    sit
Sean  is  stapling
his  posters to the  wall
You're  a  traitor
you  know that?
- And  they shoot traitors.
- Leave  me  alone!
- ls that a  new  zit?
- l  hate you!
That's  not  my dog
Annie    listen  to  me
very carefully
l've  seen  this  before…
and  buying  your first  home
can  be  very difficult
There's  escrow    inspections…
it's  a  lot of stress
So  what you're  saying  is
l've  owned  a  poodle…
for five years…
and  never  realized  it
l've  had  clients
forget their  own  names…
the year  it was
how  many children  they  had
l  knew this  one  guy who
every day for three  months…
drove  back to  his
old  apartment after  work
What's that got to  do  with  me?
l've  got two teenagers.
l  eat stress for  breakfast
Which  is  why
l'm  not worried  about you
Then  stop  looking  so  worried
l  just want you  to  remember
we  ran  the  numbers
You  are  not  in  over your  head
You  got a  great deal  here
Told  you  buying  a  model  home
was the  way to  go
What are you  really
trying  to  say    Yasmine?
l'm  saying…relax
Everything  is  gonna  be  OK
This  is your  home
And  that…
is your  dog
What's that?
French  champagne
Talk  about optimistic
l'm  so  sorry  it's  been
such  a  tough  day
l'm  sorry
if  l  freaked  you  out
Does that  mean  l  can
open  up the  champagne?
Down    boy!
Annie    l  just want to  say…
l  know that
l  was  reluctant to  move…
but  l  am  so  glad
that you  talked  me  into  it
Now    if  l  could
talk  you  into  something…
Just  pretend  he's  not there
l  can't
春秋风月字幕工作室
http://gdyfdjg.blog.163.com/
^_^=== 春秋风月 原创翻译 ===^_^
- Mom.
- Hmm?
You  forgot to  buy syrup.
You  know  l  hate  plain  waffles
l'll  go  shopping  today
Tess    l  made you
a  special  surprise for  lunch
- lt  better  be  egg  salad.
- How'd  you  guess?
Morning
Love you
Who...who  was that?
Mom    cut  it out
Tess…l  asked  you  a  question
Who  is that  boy    and  what's
he  doing  in  our  house?
Mom    come  on
First  it was  Czonka
and  now  it's  Sean?
Sean?  Wh...what are you
talking  about?
That  isn't  Sean
Dad!  Mom's  acting  weird  again!
Sean!
Get down  here  right  n...
Mom?  What's  wrong?
Phillip!
Aah!
Mom!
You'll  be just fine
Just get some  rest
We're  good  here
She's  gonna  be fine
Annie?
You  gave  us  quite  a  scare
What  happened?
You  took  a  little tumble
but you're  gonna  be  OK
The  paramedics  said  you  might
have  a  slight concussion
Ohh…
Sean…Tess…
where  are they?
Kids    your  mom
wants to  see you
No
Those  are  not our  children
Time for  school    you  two.
You're  late  enough  already
Come  on.  Bye    Dad
Bye    Mom
See ya  later
Sean  and  Tess…
Annie    sit    sit
Phillip!  Don't you  care?
Our  children  are  missing!
Listen  to  me    Annie
Our  kids  are
on  their  way to  school
l've  never  seen  those two
before  in  my  life
Don't you  know
your  own  children?
Of course  l  do!
You're  confused
No    l'm  not!
You're the  one that's  confused!
What's  wrong  with  you?
What's  wrong  with  everybody?
Annie    calm  down!
Oh    God!
What  if  it  happens to you?
- What  if you  vanish  next?
- l'm  not going  anywhere
How  can  l  be  sure?
l  don't want to  lose you!
You're  not going  to
Ohh…
No…
No
Annie…what's  wrong?
Oh    no    no    no
No…
Phillip...
or  whoever you  are...
just go  away!
Annie    it's  me
Yasmine
ls that  really you?
At  least you  haven't changed
Did  you  see  him?
Did  you  see  Phillip?
He  called  me
He  asked  me to  come
speak  with  you
But did  you  see  him?
Annie    he's  downstairs
And…
And  he's  very concerned
about you
And  you  didn't  notice
anything  different about  him?
Annie    l  know this  is  hard
for you  to  believe…
but…Phillip
is  still  Phillip…
just  like  Czonka's
still  Czonka…
the  kids  are  still  the  kids.
None  of them  have  changed
Oh…
- l  am  not going  crazy.
- No  one  says you  are
l'm  sure there's  a  perfectly
rational  explanation
Yeah    you're  right.  There  is
l  changed  them
You  lost  me
l  remember telling
Phillip  l…
l  wished  for the  perfect family
to  go  with  all  of this
And?
My wish…
it's  come true
Heh
Yasmine    this  is  not funny!
l'm  sorry.  lt's just…
You  trust  me    Annie?
l  want to
Then  come  downstairs  with  me
Why?
l  want to  show you  something
Look  at  me    Annie
l'm  still  Yasmine    right?
l  haven't changed
Come  downstairs
This  isn't  my furniture
Our  sofa  was ten  years  old
The  stereo
Phillip  wanted  this  stereo
but  it was  $10000...
OK    OK.  Let's just  pretend
for  a  second…
that everything
you've told  me  is true…
that...that this  isn't
your furniture…
and  this  isn't your family…
and  somehow
everything's  changed
Oh    Annie    don't you  get  it?
Don't you  see?
Any way you  look  at  it…
you  got what you  wanted
Honey    you've traded  up
So…how's the  new  school?
The  campus  looks  very  nice
l  love the tennis  courts
They  have  stadium  seating
and  everything
l  met  my  new  swim  coach  today
He  won  a  bronze  medal
at the  '88  Olympics
Well    it seems  like you  two  are
really going  to  love  it  here
How's  work    Dad?
Well    you  know that  biotech
company that  l  made  an  offer  on?
We  closed  the  deal  today
Cool!
That's  great!
lsn't that great    Mom?
Yes
lt's...it's  great
So    Mom    um
is your  head  feeling  any  better?
Hey    you  remember that time that
l  got  beaned  in  little  league?
You  played  little  league?
l  guess  l  forgot
l  think  l'll  get
some  more  wine
OK
This  is  what you  wanted…
the  perfect family
the  perfect  home…
To the  best  mom
in  the  world
We  love you
more than  you'll  ever  know
“Tess  and  Sean.”
And  you  love  me    too    right?
You're  a  good  dog
This  is your family  now
They  love you.
They  need  you
You're  gonna  have to try
to  make this  work
She's  not getting
any  better    Dad
lf anything
she's  getting  worse
l  know
What are  we  gonna  do?
We  have to  help  her
We're  gonna  do  whatever  it takes
to  make  her  better
l've  already  made  some  calls
Will  she  have to  go  away?
Just for  a  little  while
Don't worry.  l'll  be  here
Honey    is that you?
This  is Yasmine.
Please  leave your  name…
number    and  a  brief  message.
Have  a  great day
Yasmine    if you're there
pick  up!
Yasmine    please!
l  don't  know  what to  do
They're  gonna  send  me  away
Annie    where  are you?
Oh    God    they're  coming
Mom?
Where  are you?
Annie
What are you  doing?
No!
You  leave  me  al...alone
Help  me    please!
Ohh…
No…
No!
There you  are
Are you  OK    Annie?
l  was just  looking
at our  picture…
thinking  how  lucky  l  am
l  have  a  wonderful  family…
a  beautiful  new  home
lt's  perfect
Just  like you
Lizzie.  Dinner
l'll  be  right there
l  just finished  upgrading
my digital  family game
Just a  game?  Or  is  it?
How  do  we  know  we  aren't all
just characters…
in  some  computer  game
called  life?
And  at any  moment
each  of  us  could  be  replaced…
by someone
a  little  smarter…
a  little younger…
a  little  more…
perfect?