春秋风月字幕站
http://gdyfdjg.blog.163.com/
^_^=== 春秋风月 原创翻译 ===^_^
Hold  on    he just walked  in
There you  are.  Sound  magazine
lt's the third  time
they've  called
Where you  goin'?
Dress  shopping
for the  party tonight
Whoa    whoa    whoa
whoa    whoa    whoa
You  look too  good
just to  run  out on  me
-You're  all  sweaty.
－That's  OK    that's  OK
Come  on    now.
6:45    the  limo  will  be  here
Do  not forget
－l  won't forget.
－All  right
Yo    this  is  Marvin  Gardens
man    speak
What  up?  lt's  Darnell  Walker
We're  doing
our  annual  top ten  list…
for  most  influential
hip－hop  artists
Just wanted  to  check  some facts
if you  got a  minute
OK    so    where  do  l  rank
this year?
Number three.
You're  up two  places
l've  heard  so  many stories
dawg
How  did  you  really choose
your  name?
Well    it went down
like this    man－－
as  a  kid    l  loved  Monopoly
Everybody  loved  it
you  know  what  l'm  sayin'?
My family
we  played  it all  the time…
and  everybody wanted
Boardwalk…
Park  Place…
but  me
l  loved  Marvin  Gardens…
because  Marvin  Gardens
was  a  sleeper…
it was
a  primo  piece  of  property
lt was the  best spot
on  the  board  to  me
You  know  what  l'm  talkin'  'bout?
And  who  always  got they  hotel
first  but  me?
So that's  how  l  got  my  name
Well    is there  anything
to that  rumor…
that your  label  rejected
your first tape you  delivered?
Hell    no!  Ain't  noth－－
Listen
that's  exactly what  it  is    man
lt's  a  rumor
you  know  what  l'm  sayin'?
l  mean    listen    they ain't even
heard  the  record  yet…
and  when  they  hear the  record
they gonna  be  kissin'  my feet!
You  understand  that?
Look    listen
l  got Chuck  Amok  on  the track
l  got  Lil' Jolly on  the track…
l  got  Kid  Bang  on  the track.
This  record  is  a  monster!
Oh    man
that's  gonna  be  off the  hook!
Hey    yo    l  know you're  busy
Just one  more  question
lf you  lost  it all  right  now
what would  you  do?
l'd  probably  play
a  whole  lot  more  video  games…
you  know  what  l  mean?
Ha  ha  ha  ha  ha
No  doubt about  it
But  listen    man
holler  at  me  later    OK?
You  got  it.
Hey    thanks for your time
OK    Darnell.  Peace
We  shall  wait  here
until  the  part－－
That's  a  good  job    man.
OK    but what you  need－－
Uh－huh.
Hit the  red.  Hit the  red
Boom!  Oh!
Good  job    man
You  know  we  got youth  basketball
in  an  hour    though    right?
－Uh－huh.
－Good    good    good
Ten  more  minutes  on  this    OK?
When  you're  at the top  of
your  game  like  Marvin  Gardens…
the  only thing  left to  conquer
is fear－－
fear that your  success
won't  last…
that  maybe    just  maybe…
You  might fall  back  into
a  life you  once  escaped
Lighten  up.
You  trying  to  kill  him?
lt's  what this  scumbag  deserves
All  right.  That's  enough
l'm  sure you  can  appreciate
the  officer's  passion
You  capped  his  partner.
That's  like  killing  family
What are you  talking  about?
l'm  not a  cop  killer
No?  Well    right  now
you're the  only suspect we  got
Yeah
You  are traveling to  another  dimension...
a  dimension not only of sight and  sound...
but of  mind...
A journey into a wondrous land
whose boundaries are only that of the imagination
You're  entering…
So  l'm  in  Barney's…
and  they got these
new  pants for  white  girls…
with  padding  sewn  into the tush
Can  you  believe  it?
l'm  trying  to  burn  it off…
and  they're  paying  extra
to  put  it on
You  had  another  one
of those  visions    didn't you?
Marvin    you've  been
having  these for  weeks  now
Look    it's  nothin'
lt's just  pressure
from  making  this  record
You  mind
if we  stay  home tonight?
Whatever
But  l  really think…
that you  should  see
a  psychiatrist
l  am  not seeing  a  shrink!
Don't ask  me to
l  did  all  this  on  my own
l  don't  need  people thinkin'
that  l  can't  keep  it together
You  think you're  gonna  lose
your  street cred?  ls that  it?
Baby    listen
lt's  not your  image
that  people  love
lt's your  music.  lt's your  soul
Marvin    l  love you…
and  it  kills  me
to  see you  suffer  like this
All  right?  You  hear  me?
OK    then  smile
Did  you  hit this today?
lt's  on
Hey    let's  make  it  happen
Yo    yo    yo    yo    what's  up    baby?
－What's  up    man?
－Chuck    what's  happenin'    man?
l'm  all  right.  l'm  workin'
You  ready to  hit this?
Let's  do the  chorus    man
－Hey    let's  do  it.  Let's  go.
－Let's  make  it  happen
－Hey    yo    roll  it    man.
－“  l  can't  help  it…  ”
－All  right    here  we  go.
－“ Just give  me…  ”
Then  go  like this
“  When  l  die  l  wanna  be  high  ”
“  Never  worry    just  bury  me  ”
“  Along  with  my currency ”
“  When  l  die  l  wanna  be  high  ”
“  Never  worry    just  bury  me  ”
－Got that?
－l  got  it.  l  got  it
Hey    yo    yo    yo    yo
roll  it again    roll  it again
－“  l  can't  help  it ”
－OK    so this time…
Five    six    seven…
“  When  l  die  l  wanna  be  high  ”
“  Never  worry    just  bury  me  ”
“  Along  with  my currency ”
“  When  l  die  l  wanna  be  high  ”
“  Never  worry    just  bury  me  ”
“  Along  with  my currency ”
“  When  l  die  l  wanna  be  high  ”
“  Never  worry    just  bury  me  ”
“  Along  with  my currency ”
“  When  l  die  l  wanna  be  high  ”
“  Never  worry    just  bury  me  ”
“  And  that's forever    my  lord  ”
What's  goin'  on    man?
Driver's  license
and  registration
Damn    l  can't  believe this
Well    you  better  believe  it
We  got a  witness that saw you
running  from  the  crime  scene…
throwing  something
into that field
Now    we find
that something  was  a  gun…
you're  as  good  as fried
Unless you  come  clean  with  us
We're talkin' to you    scumbag!
l  don't even  know
how  l  got  here
This  must  be  getting
very  painful  for you
How  about
you  tell  me the truth?
Maybe  l  can  help you
All  we're  asking  for
is your  cooperation    Dwayne
Just tell  us  what you  know
Dwayne?  Who you  callin'  Dwayne?
Y'all  got the  wrong  man
Bastard's  screwin'  with  us
Do you  know  who  l  am?!  Do you?!
l'm  Marvin!  l'm  Marvin  Gardens!
Sorry.  l  didn't  recognize you
lt's  all  right.  Damn
Listen    man
what's  going  on  around  here?
Where's the  other  cops?
What's  going  on?
－Mr.  Gardens?
-Yes
Think  l  can  have
your  autograph…
for  my  little  sister?
Sorry about what  happened
No    no    no.  That's  OK    man.
l'm  just  havin'  a  hard  day
Thanks
Apologies  again
The  way you're  describing…
these  shifts  in  consciousness
Marvin…
it sounds  like
what we  call  a  fugue  state
Whatever  it  is    it ain't  real.
lt's  like  a  nightmare…
but    you  know    like    l'm  still
awake    and  one  second    bam!
l'm  in  this  life
and  then  another  second…
l'm  in    like
a  whole  'nother  life…
and  l'm  gettin'  grilled
about shootin'  some  cop
You  said  these  cops
call  you  Dwayne?
Yeah.  Yeah.  What's  up  with  that?
Was  it a  nickname
from  your  childhood?
Or  an  old  friend
you  might  have forgotten  about?
No
You  mentioned  that
you  grew  up  in  the  projects
－Were you  in  a  gang?
－No
l  was  not  in  a  gang.
My  mother  would  have  killed  me
Fair  enough
Were you  ever  arrested?
Or  maybe you  were  involved  with
a  crime that you  got away with
Look    l  don't  know  where you're
going  with  these  questions
l'm  trying  to find
a  suppressed  memory    Marvin
Something  from  your  past－－
a  reason
why you  might  have  created…
this  elaborate fantasy world
Well    l  thought fantasies  was
about good  stuff    not  bad  stuff
Usually they are
l'm  curious    Marvin
You  ever fear
losing  everything  you  have?
And  ending  up
back  on  the  street?
Hell    yeah.  Every damn  day.
That's  what  keeps  me  so  hungry
l  mean    l  worked  too  hard
to  get where  l  am…
and  l  am  never  going  back－－
never
Junior
Junior    it's  not funny
Where  did  you  get this  gun  from?
Huh?  l'm  talkin' to you!
Cousin  Trey  left  it  here
l  was  gonna  give  it  back
Man    l'm  sorry
l'm  yellin'  at you  like that…
but you  know  how  l  feel
about guns.  l  don't  like  guns
Guns  are  not for  playing  with
They're  very serious things
you  understand?
People  get  hurt with  guns
every day
People  get  killed  with  guns
Daddy    have you  ever  seen
anybody get shot?
J    there's
another  world  out there…
that  l  worked  hard
to  leave  behind
And  l  don't want guns…
or  any  part of that world
in  our  life  here
－Got that?  Yeah?
－Mm－hmm
-You  understand  me    right?
-Yes    daddy
-You  do?  Well    guess  what.
－What?
“  l  love you  so  much  ”
－“  My  little  boy ”
－l  love you    daddy
Good.  All  right
So  it's  bedtime for you
Here.  Make this  comfortable
Oh    yeah    right
Get  under the  covers    man
you  ain't funny
Good  night    OK?  Sleep tight
－Night.
－Night    daddy
You  know    l'm  proud  of you
l  didn't actually think
you'd  talk to  Dr.  Sinclair
Well    l  can't  have
those  visions  anymore    so…
Marvin…
you  worry too  much
Oh    baby
Yeah    l'm  a  worrier    l  guess.
You  know    it's just  my  nature
The  doctor  gave  me  some  pills
Said  it would  help  me focus
better  on  the  here  and  now
－Oh    sounds  good.
-Yeah
Feels  like
they're  working  to  me
Don't you  pass  out on  me
you  punk!
l'm  not through  with  you
Your time  is  running  out
Dwayne…
and  so's  my  patience
Here.  Let  me  help you
Jazmine?
Here.  Drink  some  water
Doesn't  have to  be  like this
Dwayne
Stop  calling  me  Dwayne
My  name  is  Marvin－－
Marvin  Gardens
And  l'm  Jazmine
That's  right.  You're Jazmine
my wife  in  my  real  life
What  real  life
are you  talking  about?
Come  on    Jazmine
l'm  a  millionaire.  l'm  famous.
l  live  in  a  mansion
You  live  in  the  projects
Dwayne…
with  your  mother
and  your  sister
That's  a  lie!  That's  a  lie!
Come  on.  You  know  how  it works
Good  cop/bad  cop
Now    if you  don't
write  out a  confession…
l  can't  help you  anymore
Look    l'm  not gonna  confess
to  something  l  did  not do
l'm  not a  cop  killer!
l  really wish
l  could  believe you    Dwayne
l  really do
Jazmine    come  back!
Jazmine!  Jazmine!  Don't  leave!
-Jazmine.
－Relax    baby
l'm  just going  to  get you
some  water.  Come  on    now
Oh.  You  were there this time.
You  were there this time
What do you  mean?
ln  my vision－－
ln  my vision    you  were there
and  you  were  a  good  cop…
but you  were trying
to  get  me to  confess
And  did  you  confess?
What you  mean    did  l  confess?
No    l  didn't confess
'cause  l  didn't do  nothin'
l  never  did  nothin'
in  this  life  or  no  other  life!
How  come  nobody  believes  me?
OK    Marvin    you're  really
starting  to  scare  me  now
Oh    man.  l'm  sorry
Don't go.  Just…
lt's the  record
lt's just the  record.
l  gotta  get  it done
l'm  gonna  finish  it tomorrow
lt's  stressing  me  out
a  lot  right  now
Come  back  over  here    please.
Just come  back  over  here
lt's  gonna  be  all  right.
lt's  gonna  be  all  right
What are you  doing?  Come  here
l'm  gonna  finish  this  record
tomorrow…
and    oh    just wait.  You  just
wait.  lt'll  be  all  right
－OK.  OK.
-You  just wait and  see
lt's  gonna  be  all  better
tomorrow
“  Well    l  plan  to take
the  world  by  mysterious  ”
“  That  means feelin' this  ”
“  l  give  it a  while
before you  really  miss  ”
“  Off your tongue
ever  since  l  was young  ”
“  To  act slow
wanted  the  dough  ”
“  Don't you  know  ”
“  l  rip  scenes
and  leave  'em  bent ”
“  From  any state  or  continent ”
“  For  mad  dollars  and  cents  ”
“  And  then  advance
my thoughts  ”
“  And  l  arise    there's
a  grace  like  Arthur  Ashe  ”
“  To  put  me  six  with  my cash  ”
What's  up?  Y'all  feelin' that?
Yo    yo.
That was  off the  chain    dawg
Yo    dawg    that was tight.
Do that verse  again    right?
Cool    cool.  Let's  do  it again
“  Well    l  plan  to take
the  world  by  mysterious  ”
“  That  means feelin' this  ”
“  l  give  it a  while
before you  really  miss  ”
“  Off your tongue－－ ”
What the  hell
are you  stoppin' for?
－Oh!
-Yo    he fell    man
Marvin    what  happened?
Damn
l'm  telling  you    doc
these  pills  don't work
lt's  like they're  making
the  visions  stronger
We  could  increase the  dosage
No!  Forget  it!
l  want a  specialist
l  don't care  how  much  it costs
l  want the  best shrink
that  money can  buy    you  hear  me?
Oh    l  hear you    all  right
And  l'd  like to  help you…
but you're  not giving  me
anything  here    Dwayne
l've  given  you
every opportunity…
to  come  clean  with  me
But you  seem  incapable
of telling  me the truth
This  is your  last chance
Dwayne
Now    either you  tell  me
that you  killed  that cop…
or  me  and  the  detective  here
we're  gonna  leave this  room…
and  we're  gonna
let the  officer  here…
finish  up the  interrogation－－
his  way
This  ain't  happenin' to  me.
This  ain't  my  life
Hey!
Your  life  is  gonna  be  over…
if you  don't
snap  out of  it  right  now!
My  name  is  Marvin  Gardens
and  l'm  no  criminal!
Marvin    are you  OK?  You  have
had  a  real  breakthrough  here
－l  think  we  need  to  dig  deeper.
－No    no    no    no
We－－we  don't  need  nothin'    man
l  don't  need  you.  l  don't  need
your  stupid  questions…
or your  worthless  pills
l  don't  need  any of  it.
You  know  why?
Because  l  got everything
right  here
l  got the talent.
l  got the  will
l  made this  life
l  deserve this  life!
And  nobody's
gonna  take  it from  me!
Hey!  Hey!  Yo!
－Hey    there you  are.
－Hi
l  was  gettin'  worried
about you
Oh    don't worry about  me.
Give  me  my  kiss
That's  right
Finishing  up  my  record
Are you  really done?
Yeah.  Well    actually
l'm  just gettin'  started…
'cause  when  the  record
come  out…
we're  gonna  be  movin'
to  a  much    much  bigger  place
Twice  as  big  as this  one.
Really
Did  you  hear
what  l  just told  your  mama?
Put that down
Did  you  hear  what  l  just
told  your  mama    little  man?
l  gotcha.  l  gotcha
Are you  ready to  celebrate
with  mama?
Huh?  We  goin' flyin'
We  gonna  go  crazy.  We  goin'
all  over the  place    too
We  goin' to  Belgium  for  waffles
Baby    what about those  visions?
Come  here
From  now  on    the  only visions
l'm  gonna  be  seein'…
is  how fortunate  l  am  to  have
you  and  him  and  everything
lt don't get  no  better
than  this
Yeah
He's  alive
but  his  mind  snapped
You  went too far    Sinclair
Hey    did  what  l  had  to  do
You're  not gonna  believe this
Metro
just  picked  up the  shooter
Got a  confession  and  everything
－Dwayne's  innocent.
－Oh    man
Get a  paramedic  in  here
What the  hell
are you  lookin'  at  me for?
How  was  l  supposed  to  know
he  was telling  the truth?
－What  is  it?
－Looks  like  lyrics
When  l  die    l  want to  be  high
Never  worry    just  bury  me
along  with  my currency
For  Dwayne  Grant
A.K.A.  Marvin  Gardens…
Justice  was just an  illusion
l  made this  life
So  he  escaped  into
an  illusion  of  his  own  making
And  l  deserve this  life
Dwayne  Grant－－
living  out  his  dreams…
in  the  Twilight Zone
Nobody's  gonna  take  it from  me