春秋风月字幕站
http://gdyfdjg.blog.163.com/
^_^=== 春秋风月 原创翻译 ===^_^
Hmm…Ben…
Mmm?
What do you  think
you're  doing?
Mmm…
this  is  a  dream
lt's－－it's  a－－
a  beautiful  dream
[Laughs]  lt doesn't
feel  like  a  dream
Oh    no    but－－but  it  is
l'm  not  really doing  this
Mmm
Or this…
or this…
No    l'm  not doing  anything
l'm  sound  asleep
just  like you
Oh
You're  not sound  asleep
and  this  is  not a  dream
Well    let's  pretend  that  it  is
Ben    we  agreed.  No  more  sex
until  we  get  married
Right.  Why did  we  agree
to that again?
－Hmm?
－Mmm
Mmm!
lt'll  make
the  wedding  night special
lt'll  be  like  starting  over
Well    let's  start
over  right  now
Hi.  My  name's  Ben.
What's your  name?
－Oh…Ben…
－What?
We're  not doing  this
Didn't you  give
Father  Brendan  your  word?
Yeah.  l－－l  had
my fingers  crossed
Oh.  l  sometimes  wonder  how
committed  you  are to  all  this
－What－-to  all  what?
－To  our  getting  married!
l'm－－l'm  committed
l－－l  proposed…didn't  l?  Hmm?
Yes    you  did.
And  very sweetly    too
Maybe you  could  throw  me  a  bone
once  in  a  while    hmm?
Yeah
OK.  OK
OK.  No  sex for  six  months.  OK
This  is  a  test    right?
Yeah    OK
Don't worry    Samantha.
l'll  pass  with  flying  colors
Yeah    if  l  don't explode first
－Oh    you  won't explode.
-Yeah?
Mmm
Oh.  Hey.  Hi.
Oh.  How  are you?
Hey    uh－－
Oh    hi.  Excuse  me
Excuse  me
Oh    hey－－hey there
Hi－－hi  there.
Ho－－ho there
－l    uh    l  work  here.
－OK
l'm  the  senior  photo  editor
so  if you  have  any  pictures…
you'd  like  me to  look  at
l'd  be  glad  to    uh    to  look
[Girls  laugh]
Have you  seen
the  women  out there?
Nines    tens.
l  think  l  even  saw  a  twelve
You  and  Samantha
still  not  having  sex?
ls  it that obvious?
l  feel  your  pain    chief
That was  one  nasty virus
Good  thing  you  backed  up
your  hard  drive
For you
What's this?
The  best sex
you're  not  having
And  it's  absolutely guilt-free
A  virtual  sex  program?
Are you  serious?
l  don't  need  this.
l  love  my fiancёe
And  you  two  make
a  very cute  couple…
but this  has  nothing
to  do  with  Samantha
“Sensuous  Cindy”
is the  greatest  program…
Fantadyne's  ever  cooked  up
Fantadyne?
The－-the  game  simulation  people?
Samantha  works for them
l  bet she  didn't work
on  this  sucker
How  did  you  get ahold  of  it?
Easy.  A friend
snuck  me  a  beta  copy
－Really?
-Yeah
Have－－have you  tried…this?
Hey    l  don't  kiss  and  tell
Now    what  is  it    six  more  months
until  the  wedding  night?
Well…
lt's your  decision    chief
l  like  it
Oh….wha…
What?
Ow!
Mmm!
Hi    Ben
l've  been  waiting  for you
Sexual  fantasies…
every one  of  us  has them
Harmless  enough
most of the time
On  the  eve  of  his  marriage…
Benjamin  Baker  has  decided
to  indulge  himself
He's  about to  get
very    very  lucky
Or  is  he?
You're traveling
to  another  dimension…
a  dimension  not only
of sight and  sound…
but of  mind
A journey
into  a  wondrous  land…
whose  boundaries  are  only
that of the  imagination
You're  entering…
Oh    you  taste  great!
So  do you
How－－how  is this
uh    happening?
l－－l  mean    how－－
how  does  it    uh    work?
Well    l  could
draw you  a  diagram…
but that  might  ruin
the  mystery
So    what did  you
have  in  mind…
something  naughty…
or  something  nice?
Well    l－－l－－l  don't－－
l－－um…
Look  at these  curtains!
Amazing!
They feel  just  like  silk!
Did  you  come to  play
with  the  curtains…
or to  play with  me?
Uh…
Ohh!
Why don't you  just  lay  back
and  relax  and  let  me  drive?
Uh…
OK…
Ohhh…Cindy…
l  don't  know
if  l  can  do this
This  all  feels too  real
Gee    Ben
l'm  just a  computer  program
Yeah    some  program
You  know    l－－
l'm  engaged  to  be  married
You  are?  That's  so  sweet
Yeah
You're  not  married  yet
are you?
Uh…no.  l  am  not
Then  consider this  practice
Hey    mister…
there's  a  speed  limit
in  this town
Oh
Just  kidding
[Music  playing]
l  could  stay  like this forever
Most guys  are just
wham－bam-thank-you－ma'am
Well    you  know  guys
You're  different
You're  sweet…
considerate
l  mean
don't get  me  wrong
You  were  a  real  tiger
when  it counted
Well    you  were
pretty terrific  yourself
You're  so  sweet
l  could  really
get  used  to this
Wow…
Ohh!  Ha  ha!  lt's you!
What's the  occasion?
Oh    no  occasion
We're  not  having  sex
Benjamin
That's fine  with  me
And  reverse  psychology's
not gonna  work
What are you  talkin'  about?
No.  Six  months  is  nothing
lt's  a  drop  in  the  bucket
and    besides    like you  said…
it－－it'll  make for－－
for  one  hell  of a  wedding  night
－l  love you.
－Do you?
Well    these flowers
weren't cheap
－Oh    be  serious!
－l'm  being  serious
l  mean    about  loving  you
not about the…flowers
You're the  only  man
l'll  ever  love
-Yeah?
－Mmm…
Ohh…
Hello?
Yeah    he's  right  here
－lt's for you.
－Oh
Hello?
－Ben?
-Yes
lt's  me.  Cindy
Cindy.  Cindy who?
Sensuous  Cindy    silly
l  had  such  a  great
time today with  you…
and  l－－l  can't stop
thinkin'  about you
Uh－－it－－Cindy?
Who－－who  is this  really?
l  told  you.  lt's  me.  Cindy
Cindy from  this  morning?
Just  hearin' the  sound
of your  voice  again…
gives  me  butterflies
Well    no－－
But－butterflies?
You're－-you're
a  computer  program
Who  is  it?
Oh    it's    uh    uh－－
it's    uh    somebody…
uh    from  work.
Nobody    uh    y-you  know
Uh    th-this  can  wait
until  morning
We'll－－we'll  discuss  it then
Will  you  promise to  come  see  me?
First thing?
Uh    yeah    sure.  Fine
Can't wait for you  to  hold  me
in  your  arms  again.  lt was  so－－
ls  everything  all  right?
What?  Oh    uh    great.  Yeah
Uh    so－something  came  up
Uh    no－－nothing  r－really
lt's－－it's    uh    something
but  it's  nothing
Every－－everything's
under    uh    control
Must've  been  a  glitch
of some  sort
Whatcha  doin'    Ben?
Aah!
Didn't you  make  a  little  promise
to  me  last  night?
l'm  confused.  ls－－is－－
is－－is this  part of the  program?
Look    all  l  know  is  l've  never
felt  like this  before
Uh    l－－l－－l  don't  know
what you're talking  about
l'm  talking
about chemistry    silly
You  know
that  mysterious  attraction…
between  two  people
who  belong  together?
Pheromones
and  all  that good  stuff?
No    no.  You－-you  have to  be
human  to－-to  have  pheromones
Well    l  was  human  enough
for you  last  night
Yeah.  Um…
w－well    why－－why don't  l…
come  visit you
uh    a－after  work?
And  afterwards  will  you
hold  me for  a  while?
Well    y-yeah.
Uh    holding    uh    touching…
w－w－whatever you  want
[Telephone  rings]
Hello
Hi    Sam
No    l  had  to    uh    work  late
l  had  a  photo  layout
l  had  to finish
Yeah.  No    l'm  outta  here
as  soon  as  we  hang  up
OK.  l  love you    too.  Bye
[Sighs]
Ben?
l've  been  waiting  so  long
Where  are you?
Ben?
[Elevator  cables  screech]
Hey    there    mister
Aren't you
forgetting  something?
Cindy    please.
Start the  elevator
Not  until  we  get a  few
things  straightened  out
Boy    when  you  sweat
you  really sweat
Yeah    well    l  have  a  thing  about
being…trapped  in  small  spaces
So    now    Cindy
l'm  approaching  meltdown  here…
and  it's  not gonna  be  pretty
Well    how  do you
think  l  feel?
l  mean    l  can't eat
l  can't sleep－－
OK    you  never  eat.
You  never  sleep
l  keep  dreaming  about you
Look    you  just said
you  can't sleep!
Ben    l  want to  be  with  you.
l  want  us to  be together
－We  can't  be together!
－Why?
Because you're  a  com－－
You're…
Ben    l  know you  like  me
Yes    yes!  Yes!
Yes    like you!  l  like you!
But  l－－l  love  Samantha!
l'm  OK  with  that
B－but  l'm  not!
OK?  lt was－－
it was  sex    Cindy
That's  all!
l'm  sorry
l  meant  nothing  to you
and  it was－－
it was just a  fling
a  one－night stand?
Well    yeah－－uh…
l  don't－－l  don't want
to  hurt you…
but    yes
you  meant  nothing  to  me
lt was just a  fling
a  one－night stand
l'm  so  disappointed  in  you
Cindy?  Cindy?
Don't  leave  me.  Cindy?
Cindy?
OK…OK    OK
OK.  The  walls－-the  walls
are  starting  to  close  in
OK.  OK.  OK.  OK
Help!  Help!  Help!
OK    OK    OK    l  made  a  mistake.
A  big  mistake
OK    OK    OK    OK
l－－l  should  have
come to  see you
l  should  have  come to  see you
Cindy…please    please
please    please
l－－l'll  do  anything  you  want
Anything  you  want
Forgive  me…please.
l－－l－－l－－l－－
l  didn't  know
what  l  was  saying
l  just want to  be
with  you    Ben
ls that such  a  bad  thing?
No    no    no.
No.  No    no    no    no
Ben?  l'm  waiting
Where  are you?
l－－l'll  be there
in  a  minute
l－－l  have－－l  have
to  use the  men's  room
Ben?
Oh    Ben?
Where  are you?
Ben!
This  isn't funny anymore
l  know you're  out there
What    are you  trying
to  kill  me?
Why couldn't  l  take
the  elevator?
－lt  isn't safe.  Nowhere's  safe.
－lt's  25  stories!
Ben?
Who's that?
Hey    about  how  much  longer?
Don't  rush  me
l  can't  believe  l'm  doin' this
This  is  a  crime    a  real  crime
You  want to talk  about a  crime?
How  about attempted  kidnapping?
The  elevator  got stuck.
lt  happens
l'm  tellin' you
she  wasn't gonna  let  me  out
Would  you  stop talkin'
about  her  like  she's  real?
-You're  weirdin'  me  out.
－Let  me tell  you  something…
you  know  she's  not  real
l  know  she's  not  real…
but Cindy sees things
a  little  differently
She's  a  series
of ones  and  zeros
Ones  and  zeros  wrapped  in
the  cutest    hottest  little  body
Would  you  stop  it?
l  feel  guilty enough
as  it  is
But  not as  guilty as  l'd  feel
if  Sam  ever finds  out
Sam's  a  software  developer
She'd  probably think
Cindy was  pretty damn  cool
Don't you  get  it?
We  made  a  vow－－
no  sex  until  our  wedding
That  means  not with  each  other
not with  others    and  not with…
some  sex－happy computer  program
Your  loss.  Your  loss
l  push  this  key…
and  that's  it
Cindy vanishes
from  your  life forever
What do you  say    chief?
Terminate  her
Now
Hi.  l'm  home
ln  the  office
Hi
－Tough  day?
-Yeah
Uh    l  won't  bore you
with  the  details
Poor  baby.
l  know  how you  feel
l'm  having  trouble
with  my  hard  drive
l  can't access  any of  my files
You  want  me to  check  it out?
Who's the  computer  expert  here?
Well    a  fresh  set of eyes
l'll  open  the  wine
Yeah…
let's  see
“Terminate  her”?
Did  l  actually  hear you  say
No!  You  can't  be  here.
We  got  rid  of you
You  tried    but  l  was  hiding…
in  the  computer
in  the  office  next door
Having  any  luck?
Uh－－oh    look…
no    the－-the  damn  thing
it    uh    froze  up  on  me
Why don't we    uh
pop  some  popcorn?
－We'll  watch  a  movie.
－Wine  and  popcorn?
Yeah    let's  stick  a  bag
in  the  microwave
l'll－－l'll  see  what's  on
Sometimes you  can  be  so  cute
Why are you  trying
to  hurt  me    Ben?
l  love you
l'll－－l'll  get  it
Yeah?
Maybe  it's time  Samantha  and  l
had  a  little talk
No    no    no
don't－－don't do that
l'll－－l'll－－
l'll  come to the  office
Don't do  anything
on  my account
No    l  want to  come  see you
We'll  talk
And  once
we're  done talking…
l'm  a  tiger    remember?
Grrrr
-You  are  so  cute.
-Yeah－－
－Will  you  stay the  night?
－Uh    uh    stay the  night?
Yeah.  Uh    sure.
Anything  you  want
OK    but  hurry
No－－l'm  already out the  door
Ben?
l  got some－－
the  office  called
There's  a  fire
l  have to  put out
l  gotta  go
Hi
What took you  so  long?
Oh.  What can  l  say?
Traffic  was  horrendous
l  was  gonna  stop
for flowers    but－－
Oh
Uh    well    l  hope
uh    you  like them
They're  beautiful
What did  you  do to  me?
Uh    well    that's－－
oh    it's－－it's  a  virus
l－－l  stopped  by
uh    Garrett's
He－－he  wrote  it for  me
But why?
l'm  sorry    Cindy
but  being  with  you…
made  me  realize  how  much
l  really  love  Samantha
That  is  so  romantic
You  are  so  sweet
Yeah    l  guess    but－－oh…
Cindy?
Hello?
Ben    are you  OK?
Yeah    l'm  OK
Did  you  get the fire  put out?
Yeah.  Yeah    it  looks that way
l  know  it's  late…
but could  you  stop  by the  store
on  your  way  home?
Sure
l  e－mailed  a  list
of what we  need
The  computer's  working  fine
by the  way
Uh    great.
So    l'll  see you  soon?
No  need  to  hurry
No  problem.  Sam?
What?
l  love you
Me    too.  Bye
Bye
Sorry  l'm  late.
l  was  dealing  with  my fiancё
He's  been  acting
a  little  strange  lately
lf  l  didn't  know  better
l'd  swear  he  was  cheating  on  me
Hmph.  Men…
You  can't trust them
Benjamin  Baker
narrowly escaped  his fantasy…
while  his fiancёe
explores  her  own  sensual  nature
A  glimpse  into the future
of  modern  romance…
for  better  or for  worse…
courtesy of
The  Twilight Zone