-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-
- =http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-
Sync:nooho9
Hung
Season 02 Episode 10
* Need a new love? *
* Hey,i'm ready *
* Want my time? *
* And i'm willing,yeah *
* 'Cause i'm the one *
* Who's gonna show *
* When there's nobody *
* I'll be your man *
* Yeah,i'm the one *
* Who's gonna show *
* When there's nobody *
* I'll be your man *
* All right. *
there were 100 things
i wanted to say to her.
and if i chose the right
one,would she stay with me?
You're freezing. Come on.
Here.
There.
- what?
- nothing.
Nothing?
You're beautiful.
No no no,i should go.
Go where?
I have to go.
Do you want to go?
No.
Hey,when will i see you again?
I don't know.
This was really great.
hello?
hey,mindy. Is this mindy?
this is she.
hi,it's ronnie.ronnie haxon.
mindy,how are you?
where are you? Are you okay?
I
- I don't think so,no.
I could use a ride.
mindy,do you think maybe you could,um,
I don't know,just pick me up?
damon?
What are you doing here?
Can i come inside for a second?
- your apartment's awesome.
- thanks.
- are you okay?
- i'm sorry.
You want to call your dad and see if
he can come and get you? because i-
i came here to ask you something.
Can you,like,make me a better poet?
You know,like,be my mentor?
Wh
- why do you want me to be Your mentor?
Because you're kind of awesome.
Damon,earlier tonight I
hit a woman with a belt.
Okay? I took off my belt
and i hit someone with it.
Over and over! I hit
my boss with a belt.
Well,maybe she deserved it.
No one deserves to be hit with a belt.
You invited me to your poetry thing,
And you helped me when i was tripping out
on pot scones,And i thought i was a fetus.
So you hit one lady over
the head with a belt.
So what?!
You changed my life.
Do you remember the
first time that we met?
You told me that i was funny.
I always thought that i was
funny,But no one ever said it before.
It's like we're in michigan
And everyone else here is the same.
Except you.
* heaven isn't too far away *
* Closer to it every day... *
- well,ron,that's the
thing about marriage.
And about women
- whim and fancy.
chicken and mole.
Man,on your big night
- ouch.
That's rough.
All right,i'm gonna get some
beef jerky. You want something?
- no thanks.
- come on.
Rice krispie treat,twix bar,nothing?
- maybe a twix bar.
- all right.
I didn't invite him to come with me.
He just
- he invited himself.
Oh sure.
I'm sorry she left you stranded.
It's an awful thing to do.
To leave like that?
Just walk out?
I'll be okay.
But in a way
I wish i could do the same thing.
Walk the fuck out.
My marriage is dead,ron.
I'm all alone all the
time,even when i'm not.
so am i.
- oh,ron.
- min,mindy!
I don't want to be stuck. I
don't want to be alone anymore.
- min.
- oh,ron.
I just
- i've always felt that there's something between you and me.
- oh,min
- this just feels so easy and so right. doesn't it?
- mindy.
- Oh,ron.
Ron,i wouldn't have
left you on that stage.
I wouldn't have left you
standing at that podium.
I would not have left
you alone on that stage.
- mindy,he's
- he's paying. He's signing his credit card.
hurry! Hurry hurry.
- oh,come on. - he's
exit- he's exiting.
- oh,hurry.
- he's coming!
- twix bar.
- thanks.
- Don't mention it.
no,i don't think you
understand me clearly.
Where am i even calling? Is this india?
Can i speak to your manager,please?
Listen,i know your
name is not john smith.
It's abdul or sharif or malik.
And you're in some call center in india.
So stop pretending your name
is john and you're in michigan
and get me your manager.
- my name actually is john.
- here,that's $1,000. i gotta get to work.
1,000? You're short.
1,000 is all i have,okay? You
wanna see my bank statement?
I need 500 more. This
is not a suggestion,ray.
It's not
pay-what-you-can.
Why don't you keep
that as a parting gift?
Oh,i'm sorry
- are you going somewhere?
Look,i-
i-
I need to-
Take a break.
A break from what?
from this business.
why,did your dick break?
I need to make some changes in my life.
Oh,okay.
Go ahead and quit. Go back to your tent.
Go back to being a nobody
with your nobody friend tanya.
- leave tanya out of it.
- fuck tanya.
She owes me a lot more than money.
I've got liz booked this afternoon.
Are you gonna see her or not?
What is going on,ray?
What is this about?
It's none of your business.
Is this about jessica?
what,you think you're gonna
get back together with her?
She left you for a reason,ray.
Maybe there's a reason
she wants me back.
Why? You think you've changed
and she's gonna come back to you?
I don't need this.
And i don't need you.
And i am not a nobody. I'm a father.
i'm a coach. I'm a teacher.
And i used to be a pretty good husband.
And if i get another shot at it,
I'm not gonna screw it up this time.
koontz!
Turn that off,will ya?
Hey,how are you?
How's things? How are the,um...
how's the,uh...
I'm okay,ray. I'm keeping busy.
Good. Yeah,busy's good.
so,still interested in
making me an offer on the...
You wanna sell me your house?
Yeah.
Well,i don't know,ray. I'm not sure.
Well,you said you were-
A couple months ago.
thought i'd come to you first.
I'd better check with my wife.
Frances!
Please,frances.
- don't- don't be
frightened. - go away!
You're gonna have to run me over.
If you don't move,i'm
gonna call the police.
Frances,please,i'm
just here to apologize.
I don't care why you're
here. i'm going to church!
all right,frances,please, Just
give me 30 seconds to apologize.
- may i approach your window,please?
- no!
- frances,i'm asking permission.
I'm not here to scare you or intimidate you
Or make you feel like you're being blackmailed.
I don't care why you're here.
I was wrong,all right? I'm guilty.
I'm going to pay back every penny.
When you go to church, Frances,
i hope that you will pray for me.
But for right
now,please,just for a moment,
May i approach your window
just for a moment,please?
Look,i know. I know i've been a bully.
I have given you every
reason not to like me,
But i'm not here to talk about me.
I'm here to talk about you and mike.
whenever i think of mike,i think of you!
i'm sorry.
when you're my age And you meet someone
And it turns out only to be a mirage-
Mike is not a mirage.
He's a nice man who
- he likes you so much.
- he would never do anything to hurt you.
- you don't understand.
I know i was paying for him.
Someday he'll look at
me and he'll remember.
I mean,what kind of woman...
Is willing to pay for sex?
What basis is that for a relationship?
Frances,you just have to believe
This man,he loves
you. Just believe that.
Frances,you and him,it's
whatever you want it to be.
Jess?
After the awards,
Mindy tried to jerk me off.
She tried,i stopped her.
I
- i took her hand
And i pulled it out of my pants.
- what?
- i told her. I said,"mindy, I need you to stop."
Mindy... Gave you a handjob.
That's not the point.
The point is You went to see another
dermatologist; mindy touched me;
They cancel each other out.
We're even steven,right?
No.
I need a break,ron.
Me and the kids,my mom,
We need to get away for a little while.
You know, I shouldn't have
told you about the handjob.
It's not about the handjob,ron.
Is that it?
Is that what happens?
I give you everything
i have, And you leave?
I can't live with you anymore.
Jess,
I forgive you.
If that's what you need,i
will sleep on the couch,
I'll sleep in the garage.
- i just need you to think about it.
- i've thought about it a lot.
I've thought about it a lot.
the players got that look.
The playoffs-
It's what the season's been about.
Now it's here.
They didn't make it by themselves,mike.
Our guys got there because you and me,
Well,we care a little bit
more than the rest of them.
We got hunter,round one.
That's a tough team. What do you think?
Ray,i'm sitting here because
this is still my desk.
And right now it's-
The best place for me to go.
Okay.
The third baseman's the
only real bat they've got.
We pitch around him,we'll be fine.
What else you got for me?
Mike,i fucked up. I had
no idea what was going on.
But i do know...
You were happy.
You shouldn't let that slip away.
- thanks for coming,jess.
- what are you doing,ray?
Ah,you were right.
I grew up here
- so what?
- what?!
- i'm selling the house.
Ray,you love this house.
I know,but i'm gonna get another house-
A bigger one,a better one.
It might not be by the lake,but...
Ray,i have to tell you something.
I have to tell you something too.
Last night in the lake,in the tent-
i don't want that to stop.
and i don't want you to go away.
I don't want you to forget about it
Or pretend it never happened.
I don't know what i'm doing,
But i do know i was happiest
with you, so I'm asking
What do i do?
Tell me what to do to get you back.
- just say it and i'll do it.
- it's not about that.
I was with you for 20 years.
I
- i love you.
I know you,but-
I can't be with you right now.
I can't just go from man to man.
I have to be on my
own for a little while.
Say okay,ray.
Say good luck.
Say you're proud of me.
did lenore talk to you?
I have to go.
Mom?
Wow,new office.
It's big.
You got "the seventh seal" framed.
What do you care? It
went right over your head.
Well,mom,i was 10. you took me to
see "the seventh seal" when i was 10.
Some parents never take their children
anywhere. What do you want,tanya?
Um,mom,i'm sorry,i
need to ask you a favor.
Just will you hear me
out before you say no?
I need to get the necklace back-
The gift?
And i need to get the
money back from marvin too.
He- he- he offered to
pay. Do you remember?
You want to be reimbursed for my dinner?
Mom,i know. I'm sorry.
Look,you were right. I can't afford it.
But,uh,please,
I need the money.
* there's a palace a
- falling *
* there's a smoke in the sky *
* there's a boy running down
into the lowlands tonight *
* and he's catching a train to
where he's heard you have been *
* he's a fool now among us *
* the dreamer within
dreaming of you... *
* and you know it's a lion's heart *
* that will tumble and tear apart *
* when he's coming
down the hills for you *
* well,he'll walk in the city forever *
* oh,walk in a time to be gone *
* well,there's no real
goodbye if you mean it *
* so i guess i'm forever alone *
* and you know it's a lion's heart *
* that will tumble and tear apart. *
Howard,it's,
a little low.
It's cash,ray.
My house is worth twice this.
Nobody can get a loan these
days,ray. Everything's crashing.
We save on broker fees.
I'll write you a check.
What do you say?
I'll get back to you.
- you can't sell the house,dad.
- i'll get another one.
- yeah,but we like this house.
- you'll have your own rooms.
Why can't you just finish fixing
this one,like you promised?
- we're like orphans.
- you're not orphans,guys.
Orphans don't have parents.
You have two great parents.
- then we're homeless.
- homeless orphans. This sucks.
You're not homeless. I have a home
and i'll have another home soon.
Yeah,but right now we're living in a hotel
And we left all of our stuff at ronnie's.
He's probably like in my room
right now, touching all my stuff.
- sniffing it.
- Guys,knock it off,will you?
Your mother needs her space right now,
And you need to support that.
She needs space from that weirdo
lenore. I mean, Why is she always around?
She's not around right now.
Right now it's just
the three of us,right?
And we've got hamburgers and hot dogs.
okay? Who's hungry?
Dad,did you invite tanya?
- hi.
- hey.
We're having a barbecue.
yeah,great-
It smells great.
Can i talk to you for a second?
Take over,will you? I'll be right back.
So i
- i got the money,ray.
I got it all back and
i'm giving it to frances.
that's not good enough.
no,i know. I know.
i trusted you.
look,i fucked up,okay? I fucked up.
I don't know,i just-
I didn't do any of it to hurt
you or mike or frances Or anyone.
I just got off track.
I don't- i don't-
i don't even know what happened.
Look,i just
- i need you to forgive me,okay?
That is so fucked up.
Come here. C'mon.
What,are you gonna drown me in the lake?
I'd understand if you did.
Or if you wanted to.
i don't.
where are we going?
This is my favorite place in the world.
So,um,so that's it?
You're gonna be with
lenore now for good?
I don't know.
I told her i quit.
- you did?
- yeah.
How did that go over?
You know,it's lenore. How do you think?
I- i think i'm still
in love with my ex-wife.
But i got no money,
She's best friends with lenore-
how am i supposed to get her back?
maybe i could help.
you wanna help me get my wife back?
i could try. I know a lot about women.
Yeah okay,tanya.
Come on,ray,we've made women happy,
All right,with happiness consultants.
Until we forgot the happiness part.
You think?
We could do it again,if you wanted.
Can i stay for the barbecue?
Okay.
i remember the day we moved in.
i was six years old.
i thought it was the
greatest house i'd ever seen
and i was the luckiest kid in detroit.
it was time to get lucky again.
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-
- =http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-
Sync:nooho9
Hung
Season 02 Episode 10
* There were moments of
dreams i was offered to save *
* I lived less like a workhorse *
* More like a slave *
* I thought that one quick moment *
* That was noble
or brave would be worth *
* The most of my life *
* So i pointed my fingers *
* And shouted a few quotes i knew *
* As if something that's written *
* Should be taken as true *
* But every path i had
taken and conclusion i drew *
* Would put truth
back under the knife *
* And now the only piece of advice *
* That continues to help... *
* When *
* My time comes *
* Oh-hhh. *