1080p english subtitles (salaam Bombay 1988)
prepared by moviesbyrizzo
Hey, Moti, get ready to leave!
Krishna! the boss is on his way.
Get to work! Its not as if you have a father
who's going to do it for you instead.
I need you to run to town and do an errand for me.
Bring back three tins of  "Ganesh paan masala".
Make damn sure it's "Ganesh" brand.
Don't try to trick me by getting me some other.
A ticket to a big city please.
Get your money out.
Which city is this ticket to?
Bombay. You might even come back
from there a movie star!
Where are you all going?
I'm looking for a gal to be my queen
Salaams (greetings) to all the jerks in Bombay
Keep moving!
Move, move along!
Move along faster now! Move!
Keep moving! keep moving!
-Give me back my paan masala!
- I don't know what you're  talking about!
Are you gonna give it back or what?
Om, peace, peace, Om
Hurry, let's get going! There's a policeman coming this way.
Give me back my paan masala!
Hey Tea-boy!
Bring me some Tea!
Yes, yes. Thats it. Now, more to the left.
Don't you understand? I said  Left!
-Baba, I've brought tea.
-Where's Chillum?
I don't know.
Go look for him. Send him here.
Chillum!
Salim, how about the  money
you owe me he tea you had yesterday?
Hey stupid, watch that
sack doesn't falll.
Hey, Salim!
-At least let me have my tea.
-Pay me for the tea.
Take off! Imagine wanting to be paid
for the tea!
Where is 109?
Calm yourself! Come on inside.
Here's your money.
Have it!
Where do you come from?
Do you not understand Hindi?
Don't worry. You'll soon pick up on it and
come to understand everything around here.
She does look good don't you think?
She's new here.
What are all of you doing here? There's got to be
some work you could instead be doing around the house!
Now please leave the room!
All of you! Out!
Here, have a bit of tea.
Well, there goes that glass of tea!
And for that matter, the glass too.
There's a glass missing.
lt broke, Chacha.
Don't look like you don't know what
I'm going to do about it.
As I've previously told you, if a glass gets broken, it comes out of your pay.
Chacha, how much pay have l
altogether now saved up with you?
Here, see for yourself
You've been wasting your life being on the streets.
You should be in school learning to read!
You've saved 5 rupees a day that you've earned.
That's a total of 150 rupees.
Less 10 rupees for the tea thats
been had by your pals around here.
Minus 2 rupees for the broken glass today.
So, its 150 rupees minus the twelve
as I've just explained .
How long then should it take
for me to save up 500 rupees?
Saving up now for your
wedding in the future are you?
That sum will take a long
time to save, run along now!
Tea-boy, this tea is really
watered down!
What do you expect me to do about it?
Water's plentiful around after all.
See, the man runs away...
steals something and then runs away.
Look, Ma.
Look, he's on time.
Place the tea here.
Sit down
Have a seat on the chair..
Take your shirt off.
Manju, pass me the towel.
Come on now! Lets have that shirt off..
Why so shy?
I've seen more than that in my time.
Listen Ma! Its my song!
[indian song playing]
Hi, my goddess
My queen, the gal of my dreams.
l knew it. You'd never let me down.
You know what Chungal said?
There's a new girl in 109.
Looks quite sexy he says..
Sexy, huh. So what?
You'll soon see. Like Mandakini, she'll be a
changed gal after she's been through some knocks around there.
[sings lines from indian movie song]
Know what this Bumpkin
said to the new girl in 109?
"Here, have some.
have a drink of some tea"
I dont want to play with
you guys anymore.
l'll take you with me.
l'll show you how to keep the girls happy.
What'd he say?
Oh never mind. Just be quiet!
Have you got any money?
l'm feeling lucky today.
No
Saving it up are you? I bet you're rich enough.
Can't you even lend me a little bit of money?
Who me? I'm not rich. I have to
save 500 rupees for something.
Chacha deducted 2 rupees
from my pay recently.
The new girl broke a
glass of tea I offered her.
Which new girl?
So, you've lost your mind
to this new girl, have you
No, my friend.
How old is she? 15?
13?
14?
-16?
-Yes she's 16
Sweet Sixteen, catchy phrase!
Now lets have some of that money.
Give me the money! Let's see how
much you've got on you.
You already owe me some money. Give me that back.
Oh come on,, for this fiver,
l'd be hapy to even show you around the Taj Mahal.
Don't tell anyone about
this,or I'll finish you off
State Bank, Chillum Branch.
The bank's empty, but not for long.
You, you act as manager.
Keep your money here.
It'd be safer here than entrusting it to that crook
Chacha.This here's a Full-time safe!
Thank's, boss.
[sings song line
from Indian movie]
Rafique Bhai said you had work.
Clean the place. You'll get 3 rupees each.
Who is she?
-Sweet Sixteen.
-What a stupid name!
Shut up, runt!
Why are you hollering?
We've paid, just like you.
We'll do as we please.
England? Which land?
America.
-Coke, coke?
-No coke.
Where are your mom,
and your dad?
New York.
Theres only one way to
go, - flying Air lndia.
-How much?
-250.
-Too much.
-Too much? No, man!
-Not 250.
-Okay. For you...
special price.
-150.
-Why not?
-Give some to your brother, okay?
-Thank you.
Salaam, Hashim Bhai.
A man who doesn't smoke hash
is like a man without balls.
lsn't that right?
Go easy on that
your first time.
l ripped off a white boy.
So l said, "Let's celebrate."
Thought l'd show Bumpkin here
the real thing.
Not Baba's trash.
Did I give you a  real scare?
Why did you do that?
l want to go back. Come on.
We've come this far,
and yet you want to go back?
Give me your hand.
Hey, Chillum, the sky's spinning.
So let it spin. Let's sit down.
This is the granddaddy of all poisons.
Sometimes my heart tells me...
l should swallow rat poison...
and sleep for the last time.
All the end.
Why don't you quit being an addict?
You wouldn't understand.
Once it gets you, it won't let go
Not until you die
Not until you're dead
I'm remembering that  foreigner!
You were as green when you first got here.
Do you remember that day?
When did you come to Bombay?
lt's ancient history, kid. l forgot.
How could you forget?
l was half your size
when l ran away from home.
When l was that high,
l had seen all of lndia three times.
By train, without paying the fare
Up, down...
left, right....
And then?
Forget it. Why spoil a good high?
So, what are your thoughts about?
Would you go back to
the cold air of the village?
Yes. Just as soon as l
have 500 rupees saved.
What's with this obsession with
wanting to save up 500 rupees?
You know, my brother lied
to my mother about me.
He said l stole his money.
He beat me and did
so whenever he felt like it.
When Father died, he became head of the family
l got upset.
He was a mechanic.
One day he came home with a client's bike.
l set it on fire.
Ma said l couldn't stay home anymore.
You bastard!
What happened next?
Ma took me to the circus...
and left me there. She said:
"Don't come back until you have earned
500 rupees to give your brother."
l said, "Fine.
"ln a month and 17 days,
l'll save 500 and come back home."
You stupid ass! You'll get burnt someday.
Forget them all!
Mothers, fathers, brothers, sisters, friends...
lovers, Sweet Sixteen.... Useless bloody lot.
Me, too?
Aren't l your friend?
Chillum has no friends.
Mind your own business, or else....
Or else? The Chiller Room?
What's this Chiller Room?
Want to see it?
No problem.
l'll hand you over to a cop.
He'll show you in to the Chiller Room.
You'd never do that to me.
You've shown me paradise.
How many times must l tell you?
When l'm working, get lost!
-Scratching the door like an alley cat!
-No, l wasn't.
Now, what's wrong with this fuse?
Ma, Chaipau doesn't play with me.
Nobody does.
He gave Sweet Sixteen the baby chicken.
He didn't give it to me.
No one plays with me.
My heart, my sweet baby.
No one plays with you?
l'll play with you.
Want to hear a story?
Once upon a time, there lived a dog...
and a butterfly.
She'd fly here, she'd fly there.
The bad dog wanted to eat her up.
-And the butterfly?
-She'd fly here and there.
She flew away!
The lights are back on.
We had such fun in the dark.
We saw a butterfly and a dog.
Manju, scram.
Remember the last time the lights went out?
Do you remember
my dear?
You shouldn't be sleeping out here
Hey, Bumpkin. One tea here.
l'll pay.
Prince, they're getting your virgin ready.
Where were you?
Can't come when you're sent for?
Think you're getting smart are you?
Your days are numbered.
Got your money.
Know Padmini in 103?
No. Why?
She died of an overdose.
Really? l didn't know.
You should know.
l see you sell on this street, you're dead.
Scum, you know the rules, don't you?
Me? Sell Baba's drugs on Baba's street?
l don't do local business.
l only sell to foreigners
or to fools who say, as they die:
"Thank you, Baba."
Back off. This is my last warning.
Okay, Boss.
Bastard!
And you? Bitch!
What's going on here?
They set fire to the house.
Bouncer caught them.
This bastard brought her matches.
We paid a fortune for your virginity...
and you burn the house down?
You set the fire?
-She said what?
-She says she wants to die.
So die, you bitch!
Do you want the Police involved?
l'll cut you up into little pieces.
-Baba's here now.
-She's got some nerve.
lf l catch you here again...
l'll wring your neck. Get out!
Want something to drink?
Some tea? Some water?
Don't worry.
Baba's here. lt'll be all right.
Nobody will dare say a word.
Your tactics won't work
here at number109.
Looking for more trouble? Calmly, now.
Want a job? Tame her for me.
Baba doesn't do that work anymore.
Think it over.
She's worth 10,000.
Once she's deflowered,
it'll be 1000 for you. Well?
"Respected Mother, greetings.
"l'm well. Hope you are, too.
"l didn't run away.
"l went back to the circus,
but they had all left.
"l work in Chacha's tea shop.
l think of home."
Go on.
"l want to come home".
"As soon as l have the 500, l'll be back".
"They call me Chaipau here, not Krishna".
"Don't worry about me".
"When l go to sleep, l miss you".
That line will cost extra. 50 paisa more.
Then drop it.
"Your obedient son...." What's your name?
Krishna.
Mother's address?
Bijapur village. Near the riverbank.
Near Bholabhai's shop.
Ask for Krishna's mother, Sundari.
-That's an address?
-Yes.
Your "yes" won't get it there.
There are many Bijapurs all over lndia.
Which one do you mean?
lt's near Bangalore.
lt'll have to do. "Bijapur, near Bangalore."
Don't know where these
suckers all come from
Waste of a stamp!
The crow flies, the bird flies,
the parrot flies, the house flies.
You lost that round.
Manju, do something for me.
Give this to Sweet Sixteen.
-You gave it to her?
-Yes.
This journalist wants to talk to you.
Tell her...
Baba's current woman
used to work the streets here.
l rescued her from the gutter.
This is my child.
Say hello.
He says the woman he lives with
was a prostitute.
And he rescued her and brought her here.
And that's his daughter.
My actions speak louder than words.
And tell her...
she's beautiful stuff.
You think I'll tell her that?
What did he say?
He said, "Would you like to have some tea?"
Order some tea.
Three teas, up here!
-The camera for sale?
-No.
Want a two-in-one?
Another white sucker!
Chillum, prince of my kingdom!
What's the hurry? We'll put on a little show.
Stand over here.
Okay, jump!
Good! Bravo!
Well done.
Please.
Hang on. Where are you going?
Look, wait! Listen....
Still here? This your father's house?
The bird's flown.
Shut your mouth!
Go on, laugh! You'll be crying soon.
What did l do?
You no longer work for Baba.
Firing me just for laughing?
l'm tired of your mug.
The same mug has sold
your drugs for years.
-Our accounts are clear.
- No they're not!
What about the 150 the tourist paid?
That was a slip.
People do make mistakes. l'll give you back the 150.
The dealings between
you and I are at an end!
Take off. You're now retired.
What will Baba do? Start a new company?
Hook another bumpkin on drugs?
Listen, hero. Bullshit the others, not me.
-You going?
-l'm going, with pleasure.
Now you know what Baba is.
Baba, play with me.
Came with the child?
l couldn't leave her at home.
Sit here. Don't touch anything.
Chaipau...
this is Manju.
See how they dance.
How nicely they dance.
Here, look.
lsn't it nice?
l'm in the big room.
Will you come and see me?
Will you come?
Come soon!
When will you come?
Chillum!
l'll finish him off!
The cops will come!
l'll kill that pimp!
Are you mad?
Who told Baba about the tourist?
lt wasn't me.
Who squealed?
Not me. l told only Chungal.
lf you'd told me not to,
I wouldn't have said anything
Got any money?
-No, pal. l swear it!
Come, get some sleep rest
l can't sleep!
l can't sleep without a fix.
Everyone it seems  looks
very happy tonight.
Baba, look.
Go sleep outside.
l want to sleep here.
-No. Outside.
-Can't l sleep here?
l told you, go outside,
or you'll get a slap.
What would have been so wrong about
letting Manju sleep here tonight?
You took her with you?
l couldn't leave her with
you in your state of mind.
Aren't you ashamed
to say such a thing to me?
Go on...
... answer me.
Her training started already?
You pimp. Get out of my life!
l'll finish you off!
How dare you touch me!
What did l say? Just don't take her with you.
ls this place any better for her?
What a louse you are!
You promised me the world.
"When she's born,
we'll start a new life." New life!
Bloody liar!
Everyone thinks l'm a two-bit pimp.
What can l say now?
Spit out your anger, my angel.
What's happened has happened.
Bury your anger.
Tell me....
Where did you go, my jewel?
To Ravi's.
Doesn't matter.
A new nightie?
Think you're a whore's
who's  too fancy for me?
Just like any "John"
l told you to get lost!
Chillum's very sick.
We need money for medicine.
Take what you need.
l took out 20.
Fine.
Chillum said the souls
of Bombay's dead children...
wander under the bridge at night.
You believe everything Chillum says?
This drug racket isn't my scene.
So don't tell Chillum.
l won't.
Please come this way.
Now, be pleasant.
Don't think of other things.
Ready...
one, two, three.
Thank you.
Who said you could take her out?
Gungu Bai, you want her tamed, right?
You know Baba's style.
lf you don't trust me....
Never mind trust! All I can say
is she'd better still be a virgin!
l don't cheat clients. A virgin is what
they want, and a virgin is what I give them
Do a good job with those chickens.
You'll be paid 10 rupees each.
Here's the knife.
l can do it.
lt's very easy.
Chaipau...
help me!
Ask the boss for an advance.
Ask him for a little. Please.
No.
You got paid?
Yes. Where were you?
Looking for money.
Had a smoke?
No, pal. No smoke.
l was waiting for you. Got any money?
lt's money to go home.
Listen fella, you are not coming?
We've been slaving all day.
l missed my tea rounds.
Chacha will beat me. And you!
Lecturing me for 2 lousy rupees.
-Let me have it, please
-No.
l'll go home with you.
Let me have it now.
-Forgive me!
-Don't touch me.
-One more chance.
-You stink!
Bloody pimp!
Lives off women!
Chacha, a tea, please.
He's been smoking too much.
Stop it! What's come over you?
l need it badly. l need some dope.
Chaipau, get me some!
lt feels tight inside.
Ask your mother for money.
She's not home.
l want to die. l want to die.
l don't want to die. Chaipau, save me.
Don't worry, l'll do something.
l'll save money. We'll go back to the village.
lt's lovely there.
We'll leave this Bombay, forever.
Stand straight!
Didn't l tell you to make it tighter?
But how will the poor girl breathe?
You won't stop breathing, will you?
Do as you're told.
The first client is vital.
Take it off.
You did your job.
It's now over. Well done!
l'll send you your money.
Don't bother coming over here again.
Keep the door open.
What a beauty you are.
So lovely.
So innocent.
Like a rose in the gutter.
l'll take you away from here.
As soon as l get money...
l'll buy off your "madam".
Do you understand?
l'll rescue you.
Be patient.
Tell me...
will you wait for me?
Will you?
And where were you?
Am l running a charity?
Where were you?
Working. l told a pal to do my rounds.
You told a pal of yours?
Like you've ever been on time!
Broke glasses, made trouble in 109...
lost me business. l've warned you before...
if you dont work out
right, you're out!
Seen many like you
come though here
Here's 300 minus 50...
for all the trouble you've caused.
Don't come back tomorrow.
You no longer work here.
Can't ever collect trash these days.
They're guarding that, too.
l told you! Stop collecting trash.
Coolie work is best.
Shut up! You're like a broken record.
Chaipau! Why such a long face?
Chacha sacked me.
Hey, fellows, want to do a job?
We know your kind of job.
Cash. Hard cash!
No guts, no glory.
Count me in.
Need a boy to fetch milk?
Yes, that's right.
Little girl, what's your name?
-You go to school?
-Yes.
And who are you?
Brothers.
Sit down. l'll bring you kids
something to eat.
Like a sweet treat?
Nothing, sir!
How did you get in? Who are you? Thieves!
Chungal, leave him to me.
l've got to pee.
Run, Bumpkin!
l'm Coalpiece of Grant Road. l'll save you.
l've studied to fifth grade.
l can even speak English.
Hello! Shut up! As you like!
Salaam to the King of Bombay,
salute, my buddy
celebrate big-city life,
eat, drink and be merry
Get it?
l'm the queen of butterflies, here l come
l flee! l fly!
So what if the train's in! l'm not budging.
Be it whiskey or be it palm wine
Drinking is a must
Keep on drinking till you go bust
Fantastic! Bravo!
What poetry! Let's hear another.
My perfume lingers in your beard
My flower lingers in your crotch
How do you feel?
lf one had to live,
then life should be like this.
Not missing your mother?
l am! l'm going home tomorrow.
Baba, wake up!
What is it?
Chillum's very sick.
You woke me for that?
He's shaking like a leaf. He's ice-cold.
All that junkie needs is a fix.
What happened?
He overdosed.
The name of God is truth.
What are you up to?
You lousy thief!
Where's my money?
Give me back my money.
My money to go home.
Chillum took your money. l saw him.
Jerk! Accuse me of
being a thief?
l want to go home.
Hey, there, wash the
glasses properly.
Thats just what l'm doing?
Don't pester me.
Mommy, he hit me.
Pass the food.
No tips for us?
Be grateful for what you get.
We're not beggars, sir.
Just 20 rupees for so much work?
Shut up and eat. Here, Manju.
Eat all you can. Now's your chance.
This bill looks torn.
Guess it'll do.
My stomach's bursting!
You ate enough for 20 meals.
Didn't you do the same?
No. ls that a stomach
or
a large edifice you have?
Hey, Salim. You shouldn't have hit that kid.
We would've had it.
With rich kids, you can never win.
The rich don't scare me.
Stop!
What are you up to?
We're going home, sir.
We've just finished duty at a wedding.
What's this?
King of samosa thieves!
l didn't steal them, sir.
What's in there?
My money to go home.
lt's true, sir.
Sure it's true! Come on.
l'll take you home.
lt'll be all right.
One day...
in our lndia, things will be all right.
Come down!
Brothers!
Sing with one voice.
Yes, sir!
You are my father, you are my mother
You are my friend, you are everything to me
We're the flowers that never bloom
We're the dust that lies beneath your feet
Always look upon us
with mercy in your eyes
You are my friend, you are everything to me
Long live lndia!
What's your name?
Krishna.
Here for stealing butter like Lord Krishna!
So, what are you in for?
-What's it to you?
-Don't act smart. Answer.
-l did nothing.
-Liar.
Don't call me a liar.
They're off to another court hearing.
Show me your card.
What's on it?
Your court date is in six months.
So take it easy, relax. Be cool.
My name is Murtaza.
l saw you destroy Lalua Chor.
They're always picking on me.
l'm not even new.
Been here five years.
Five years!
Some boys have been here longer.
l didn't do anything. They can't keep me.
They can. See that buddy over there?
He was caught pissing on the street.
They got him.
He's been inside for three years.
l didn't do anything.
Even if l did, l've forgotten.
Five years, and they all forget us.
See that boy?
They pick on him all day.
He spends his time washing his shirt!
His screw is loose.
You know what I mean by a loose "screw"?
Krishna, teach me your kick.
Show me how you do it.
Like this?
Krishna, is this right?
Manju Golub!
Manju.
How are you?
Are you all right?
Why don't you  respond?
How can l tell you
how lost l feel without you?
Your friends ask,
"Where's Manju?"
What a nice dress that is!
Want to play?
Don't worry, my dear
We'll take you home soon.
Don't worry.
Don't be scared.
We'll come back and take you home.
Long live Lord Ganesh
ln your presence,
all obstacles can be overcome
Krishna, have l got it right?
Get lost!
Come here, you retard!
Hiding like a mouse.
Leave him alone.
Think you're in charge?
Enough of your tough act.
Now watch me!
When can l take her home?
Have a seat.
Children don't always know
what's best for them.
We have children whose parents beat them.
Yet they cling to their parents.
l've never hit her.
What on earth are you on about?
Just an example.
Look at Manju. Why doesn't she speak?
She wants to go home.
She doesn't like it here.
She was fine. She used to talk a lot.
The past is irrelevant.
We're dealing with the present here.
You see, women like you....
Well, let's forget about that.
Your file's here. Let me look.
"Due to the fact
that the mother is a prostitute...
"the state has decided...
"for the child's welfare, she must be kept...
"in state custody until she comes of age."
Of course, you have the right to appeal.
But why would you?
Why not let her be adopted
by a good family?
She will have a life.
lt'll be easier on you, too. Won't it?
She's my daughter.
She's all l have in the world.
How can the State be her mother?
Sixer!
Bad luck!
He can't play cricket.
He's better doing toothpaste ads on TV!
Go brush your teeth instead!
Quiet! Let me listen.
Silence! Silence!
Every night, l dream that l escape
from the Chiller Room.
lf anyone tries to stop me, l kick them.
Anyone gets in my way,
l just kick them.
Right! Dream on!
Krishna, want to try?
Get lost, fool!
l swear it. l'm not joking.
That way.
lt's seems so far.
Let's try our luck.
No luck!
Look over there.
Hurry! Come on.
-Just wat are you up to?
-lt's mine.
Who are you?
Chillum.
Where are the others?
On trash rounds.
You work for Baba?
-Yes.
-Sell his drugs?
-Do you smoke the stuff too?
- Mind your own business.
l'm going home.
Will you come with me?
This way, please.
Just look at her! Stand up, dear.
Turn around, dear.
lsn't she a pure bud?
l've kept her safely, especially for you.
Beautiful!
Come, my dear.
Where are you going?
Are you leaving home?
-Without Manju there is no home.
-But l'm here.
You said this wasn't a good place for Manju.
l'll bring her back.
Promise. Baba's promise.
l know what trust to put into your promises.
Go to that gal "Sweet Sixteen".
That was work. Nothing else.
Must l refuse work?
Drop it.
lf you say drop it, l'll drop it.
Now l'm yours, full-time.
Tired of work? lt happens, l understand.
Let's go out. Where shall we go?
Where will you live?
You won't survive out there in
this merciless city of Bombay.
Out of my way!
What haven't l done for you?
You're leaving with a valid reason.
Turning holy, whore?
Think you can now perhaps
just  wash away your sins?
Think you could now even
become "Mother lndia"?
Look, l don't want trouble.
Get out of my way.
Or else what? Will you kill me?
Finish me off, my angel.
Kill me! Go on!
Finish me off, kill me!
1080p english subtitles
(salaam Bombay 1988)
by moviesbyrizzo