Camera? Yes, I'll be the camera today.
Ah, Fantia! Fantia's article!
Ah, it's public!
Ah, well...
I'll do Fantia first.
Wait a minute, I'll tweet it too.
Fantia...
Ah, is it another computer?
I'm uploading Fantia.
Um...
Is this still unreleased?
Hm? I'm uploading it.
Eh? It's not being released?
Ah, it's not being released.
Wait a minute.
I'll do this...
There we go.
I think the data is probably already being released.
The data.
The article isn't being released, but the product is already out.
Look at the article, it's already been released.
There we go.
I'll do the X too.
X.
I'm not doing the free part today.
Well, the free part...
I'm not doing it, so...
Well...
I'll talk a little bit about it live first, and then...
Um...
I'll do a lot of things.
That's what I'm thinking.
First...
I'll do a tweet...
X? Post?
There we go.
It's starting.
Sakura.
Um...
First, live...
Live...
Live chat?
There we go.
I tweeted.
I'm feeling good.
Speaking of feeling good, today...
Um...
What was it?
Ah, but I'll talk about it during the pillow talk.
What should I do?
What happened today...
I'll start the video in about 15 minutes.
At first, 10 minutes...
About 10 minutes.
I'll talk for about 10 minutes from now on.
My voice is hoarse.
I've been sleeping all this time because I'm not feeling well.
Um...
Well...
X...
I wrote something for X.
The video I made today...
I was planning to do it on the 24th.
But on the 24th, there was a huge wave of people getting sick.
And then, I realized that live streaming was a bit difficult.
So I recorded the rest of the fan club and Nico Nico.
I recorded it.
Yeah.
So I went to the hospital.
I went to a different hospital.
I consulted with the doctor and changed my medicine.
And that medicine was a bit...
I still had one day left today, so it's a bit...
I tried it, but I was really sleepy.
I was sleeping all the time.
I...
In my dream, I ate chicken nuggets.
When I woke up, my mouth was like,
I was munching on my food.
I couldn't tell the dream from the reality.
I was dreaming of chicken nuggets.
Yeah, chicken nuggets.
I was dreaming of eating chicken nuggets.
I was munching on my food while I was awake.
And that's it.
And today's video...
I got a video from a video editor.
And I just wanted to make sure.
I really...
I was wondering if the video editor was okay.
I always thank the video editor, but I think it's because of the coronavirus.
I don't know if it's because of the coronavirus.
I don't know if I'm making a mistake at work.
I don't know if I should put it on the video.
Yeah, there's something like that.
So I'm going to watch it all again.
I'm going to watch the full video.
I'm going to cut this part for a few minutes.
I can see my chin here.
I'm going to do that.
Yeah, I'm going to do that.
I'll do it around the evening.
And I just got a video from the video editor.
I'm going to do that.
I've already cut it in advance.
I've already cut the angle change.
I think it's a little short.
I usually do it for about two hours.
And the rental plan is 1 hour and 30 minutes.
It's long, so it's about 1 hour and 50 minutes.
This video is about an hour and a half.
It's about an hour and 20 minutes.
It's about that long.
But the content is...
I'm really cutting all the angles.
I think the tempo is good.
I think the tempo is getting better.
I've been recording for about three hours.
I think I can do it.
I did it.
I think everyone's break is over.
Everyone's break is over.
I think I can do it because it's a video.
Shoulder angle.
I think I can see my neck a little.
I think I can do it because it's a video.
I'll try to look at it from below.
I hope you'll take a look.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll take a break.
I dropped my earring.
I'm worried.
I'm worried if I'll fall asleep.
The medicine I got from the hospital is different from the usual medicine.
I got a new medicine.
I'm really sleepy.
If I have a job at night,
I drink it three hours before.
Or after the broadcast, I eat yogurt or rice balls.
I can't drink it without eating.
If you drink it without eating, it will have twice the effect.
I'm afraid of side effects, so I have half of it.
I had a half of a cup of it.
If the broadcast starts at 23 o'clock, I'll check the video in the evening.
I checked the video and finished it.
What time is it?
18 o'clock?
I ate a little and drank it at 18 o'clock.
It was really bad.
It's really bad.
It's a big deal.
So...
I'm still sleepy.
I'll put the details in the summary section.
Miko-san.
I want to talk about pillow talk.
I want to talk about the impression of the past.
And what it will be like in the future.
I want to talk about my current situation.
I want to talk about how I can continue for a long time.
I don't talk about negative things.
You don't understand.
If you hear my voice, you'll be in the way of the management comments.
I talked about it when I was smiling.
I hope you'll be immersed in this video.
I'm going to be immersed in this video.
That's right.
Good, good.
What will happen next?
I'll be back on the show.
I'm not going to be on the show.
I'll be back on the show in a few days.
It's embarrassing.
This is the third time.
The fourth time.
I checked the data and the face.
I gave it to the video editor.
I checked the data from the video editor.
The video editor came to me three times.
I did an audio documentary.
This is the fourth time.
I don't want to talk about my own situation.
I'm full.
I know this is coming.
I'll say this line after this.
I'll tell you a story.
I'll start.
I'll change the page.
Wait a minute.
I'll start.
The site URL is...
I'll show you the URL on the bottom right.
There's a hip angle.
Yes.
I'm nervous.
I took a break.
I edited the video.
But I had a lot of fun.
I had a lot of fun.
I'm about to...
I'm about to end the broadcast.
It's been an hour.
It's been an hour and 20 minutes.
It's hard to be in the archive.
I can't see the archive.
It's about an hour and a half in real time.
I'll see you again in an hour and a half.
I'm going to say, please go.
Wait a minute.
It's the worst.
Please go.
I'm Kanan.
I'm Miko today.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm a little out of it.
I'm Miko today.
Last year, there were some bad things.
I'll set it up.
Last year, I was unlucky.
I was a little out of it.
I'll set you up like a drug lord.
I hope everything goes well this year.
I'm going to do a lot of bad things.
I'm nervous.
I'm not used to it.
I'm not used to this feeling.
I'm nervous.
I hope you feel good.
I'll do my best to get rid of the drugs.
I'm going to do a lot of bad things.
First of all, I'll say hello.
I'll start with a greeting.
My face is a little short.
Happy New Year.
I look forward to working with you this year.
Thank you for coming to the temple today.
I'll do my best.
Please enjoy it.
First of all, I'll lick your ears.
I'll take all the bad things in your ears.
How do you feel?
I feel a lot better.
I feel like my ears are being cleaned.
I'm going to lick your ears.
My body is getting hot.
I'll make you feel good.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to lick your ears.
I'll make your ears and chin feel good.
Come closer.
I'll do it gently at first.
I'll make you feel good.
I only have you and me here now.
You don't have to hold your voice.
It feels good to be rubbed against the back of your head.
It feels good here, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It's okay.
I'll make you feel better.
I'll make your ears and chin feel good.
I'll lick your ears.
I'm thirsty.
I'll make you feel good.
It feels good.
I'll make your ears and chin feel good.
I'll take all the bad things and go to bed.
Tickle tickle tickle.
The other side too.
It hurts.
Can't you take it anymore?
Kiss me.
If you can't take it anymore,
ask me for more.
Ask me.
I can't take it anymore,
so please make my day feel good.
Say it properly.
Kiss me.
I can't take it anymore.
Then, I'll give you a drink.
Wait.
You look so lonely.
Do you want to kiss me a little more?
I have a lot of bad things in my mouth.
I can't take it anymore.
Then, I'll make your day feel good.
It's hot.
I'll change the angle.
I'll give you a kiss.
Then, I'll give you a kiss in this angle.
Kiss me.
I'll give you a kiss.
I can't give you a kiss yet.
I'm going to sleep.
Oh no, I'm getting a little wet.
What? Does it hurt?
You don't want me to move?
I wonder if you want to see it.
Kiss.
I'm going to put a lot of banana blotches on you.
I'll make you a bed.
I'm going to kiss you.
I'll kiss you.
It hurts.
I can't get it all in.
It's delicious.
I'll give you a little more.
I'm sleepy.
The smell of the banana blotches spread all over my mouth.
I'm getting really wet.
It hurts.
Your butt?
I want to see more of your butt.
I can't take it anymore.
Do you want to use my mouth?
I'll take it out.
Wait a minute.
Before I use my butt.
I'll use my butt.
I'll put a little bit of wet on you.
I'm going to kiss you.
I'm getting wet.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I'll put it in your mouth.
I'm getting wet.
I can't take it anymore.
I'll count down for you.
I'm getting wet.
Did you get wet?
I'll show you what's inside my mouth.
Wait a minute.
I'll wipe it.
I'm getting wet.
Look at my butt.
My butt is wriggling.
I'm getting wet.
I'll put it in your mouth.
There's a lot of water.
Did you get wet?
But I'm going to drink about half of it.
There's a lot of water.
So, are we going to feel good this time?
I'm going to feel good, too.
I'm getting wet.
I'll wipe it.
This time,
I'm going to feel good, too.
I've never done it before.
I'll do it.
I'm going to do it with Miko's clothes.
I feel like I'm going to wear it.
Here.
About this much.
I'll put this in.
It's not a syringe.
I'll put two fingers in.
Two fingers.
I think it's a little thick.
Compared to this syringe,
I can't put it in.
I think it's a little thick.
Your syringe is thick.
It's thick.
I think it'll feel good.
I'm starting to dream.
Let's start dreaming together.
What should I do?
But before that,
I'm a little wet right now.
I'm already...
I'll let it go a little bit more.
I have to loosen it up a lot.
It's quite...
I think it's that.
Then, at first...
Hmm...
What should I do?
Since it's a special day, I'll take my time and relax.
Take my time.
Look at my breasts.
My breasts are really...
They're all wrinkled.
They're really wrinkled.
It's a bit difficult, but...
Then, today...
I'll use this egg.
Egg.
This is...
What kind of thing is this?
Long-term brushing stimulation.
It's called a long-term.
What does it feel like?
I'll open it up.
Wow!
It's like a mojatto ball.
This is bad.
This is the root of the bad thing.
It's not good.
Since I'm a shrine maiden, I can't lose to this.
What? Is it Japanese?
I can't lose to this.
So...
I'll use it.
I wonder how it feels.
Then, this...
Last time, before that...
When I used this, it was a bit...
It felt good, but it felt like it lasted longer.
It felt like that.
This time, look, this is a special lotion.
It's really sticky.
It feels good.
This...
Rub, rub.
I'll use this.
I'll put it here.
It feels good already.
It already feels good.
Rub, rub, rub.
A lie detector.
Huh?
Then, I'll flip this over.
And do this.
Huh? This...
I can do it somehow, right?
It's in the frame.
But I can do it somehow.
So, today, I'll do it specially.
I'll take it off.
The bandage.
Hide the H-line.
Wait.
I took it off.
Then, now...
I'll do it without the bandage.
Without the bandage.
I'll hide it with this H-line.
It feels good.
Then, slowly, slowly...
I'll do it slowly.
Ah...
It's so slippery.
I'll rub it all over.
Today...
I want to do it while rubbing my boobs.
But my boobs are hard.
It's hard, right?
My boobs are hard.
It's out.
Just now, the panties...
Not panties, the swimsuits...
I took them off.
But, after all...
I thought it would be better to see it.
So, like this...
I'll do it while showing it.
Like this.
My mouth is probably...
You're excited, too, right?
Then...
With this...
Like this...
Then, lend me your ears.
I'll do it from here.
Ah... It feels good.
I'll rub it all over.
Can I touch your nipples?
This is really... How should I say it?
It's really relaxing.
Look at the screen.
I'll take the nipples off.
It feels good.
I'll rub it all over.
This is bad.
I don't want to put it in.
I'll put my fingers in.
Wait a minute.
I don't want to put my fingers in.
This feels good.
It's hot.
I'll take two fingers and loosen it.
A lot.
I'll put it on.
I'll put my fingers in.
This is bad.
It feels good.
I don't want to put my fingers in.
What should I do?
This is bad.
This feels good.
Looking at this one finger,
I'm getting nervous again.
Miko-san is getting excited with this kind of heat.
This is bad.
This feels good.
A lot.
This is bad.
I'll do it.
I'll do it lightly.
This is really sticky.
Wait a minute.
I'll put something on.
I want to use this too.
I'll be in the frame.
I'll use a massage device.
Massage device.
I want to use the massage device next.
Wait a minute.
I want to relax.
I can't lick your ears.
I can't lick your ears at this height.
This time,
I'll use a massage device.
Massage device.
I'll do it.
I'm happy.
Wait a minute.
This is bad.
I'll do it.
I don't want to do it anymore.
I'll sleep with this.
This...
I'll do it while I'm in the frame.
Then,
I'll put you in the frame.
Here we go.
Punch.
I'm embarrassed.
Here we go.
Then,
I'll put you in the frame.
My heart is pounding.
I'll do it.
I'm not good at punching.
I'll put you in the frame again.
This is bad.
I'll sleep with this.
I'll do it again.
I'm still in the frame.
Wait a minute.
I'll do it again.
This is really hard.
This is bad.
I feel like I'm in the frame.
My face is shaking.
More.
I'm in the frame.
I feel good.
Help me.
This is bad.
I'm out.
I was shaking.
I'm in the frame.
Wait a minute.
I feel good.
I'm in the frame.
Wait a minute.
I'll do it again.
I'm in the frame.
I did it.
I feel good.
Wait a minute.
I'm satisfied.
It's harder than usual.
There are times like that.
I feel good.
Camera.
I'm in the frame.
My hair is sweaty.
My hands are sweaty.
I'm in the frame.
This is a heart.
It's a little slanted.
Slanted.
Then,
in a different angle,
I'll do the eyes.
I always do it in this angle.
I can see your face.
I'm scared.
I'll do it from the bottom.
I'll take a break.
I'm in the frame.
This angle.
I'm scared.
I'm from the bottom.
I'll try it.
I don't think it's in.
I'll take it off.
I forgot to turn off the air conditioner.
I'm taking a break.
I'll be quiet.
I'm in the frame.
I can see a lot of places.
It's really slanted.
Maybe it's because of the sweat.
This hair is inside out.
It's a beautiful hand roll.
I'm worried.
I think I'm tired from behind.
I'm tired from behind.
I took something off.
Can I take this off?
It's torn.
I couldn't stand the pressure.
I'll do a female shampoo at the end.
I'll do a female shampoo.
I'll lick your ears a lot.
I'll give you a lot.
I'll squeeze your hair until the end.
I've squeezed it out of the chin.
Lastly, I'll finish with a lip tape kiss.
Finally, I'll finish with a lip tape kiss.
I'll do it again.
I'm not going to be able to do it.
This is the only part.
I can only show you.
I'll do it again.
It's delicious.
I love you.
Thanks to you,
I'm alive.
I'll be with you forever.
I love you.
It's delicious.
I'll give you a lot.
I love you.
Breathe.
Okay...
Kiss...
Hugyoo...
Wait, I'm curious about this.
I'm curious.
I love you, I love you, I love you.
I feel refreshed today.
If I feel refreshed even a little,
I'm happy.
I hope you'll be happy.
Then I'll count down.
I'll start with 10 seconds.
Open your mouth wide.
It's refreshing.
I'm going to eat this.
10 seconds.
Open your mouth.
2.
1.
Open your mouth wide.
2.
1.
Even if I become zero, I'll kiss you forever.
I'm sweating.
I feel refreshed with this outfit.
I can see my face.
Today...
Wait, I can't see.
I'll edit this.
I can see my chin.
I'm glad I called you.
I'm a little...
Well, I don't know.
I'm a little different from usual.
How was it?
I'm glad I felt a little better.
I'm a little...
I'm a little hard to breathe.
It's hard to breathe.
It's hard to breathe in life, but it's not.
It's a little...
Yeah, it's a little...
It's hard to breathe.
But I spent a lot of time today.
I spent a lot of time today.
It felt good.
I don't know.
I think it would have been bad if I did a live stream.
I think I could have done a live stream.
I think it was a little weird.
I'm glad we felt good together while taking a break today.
I'm glad.
Then, let's...
I look like an anime character.
This is...
I'm a little...
My face is...
I'm wearing this.
I can see a lot.
It's big.
My head is going crazy.
I'm back.
It's February 1, 2024.
It's 33 minutes.
I watched the whole thing.
Everyone's reaction was funny.
I've been watching it a little bit.
I'm worried if it's going to stop.
It's like I'm back.
I'm like a pruneriff.
A place where it feels like a pruneriff.
Again,
No, this is...
a break
I did it, so I edited it a bit.
Yeah, that's how I saw it.
Was it embarrassing?
The underwear was in it.
Yeah, underwear, underwear, underwear, underwear.
I thought I took off my swimsuit, but I'm going to talk about what happened.
I thought I took off my underwear and swimsuit, but I was wearing it.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Let's talk about the pillow.
What should I do? Pillow talk video...
Is this it?
I didn't turn on the air conditioner.
I didn't turn on the air conditioner because I turned it on earlier.
Let's talk about it.
How was it? First of all,
I was a little irregular this time, but I was a little like a recording.
Yes, it was like a simultaneous viewing.
Oh, I should have blown my butt.
I'm a little scared to do that kind of live broadcast.
I can't cut the abs scene, so I didn't cut it.
Yeah, it was rare.
Was it good to see the angle from below?
Really?
Oh, my butt was a little bit of a bite.
Yeah, I was eating my bare swimsuit and eating it.
And I don't do much, but after I ate it, I put my back on it.
I'll show you a little bit of my thighs.
Yeah, yeah, that's kind of like an accident.
I wonder if it's okay.
I felt a lot of things.
Really? That's great.
Of course, I think the live broadcast is the best.
Well, I'm really in good shape to record.
I'm trying to make it a means of helping when I'm not feeling well.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, really.
I didn't know Miko was there.
The last part of Miko's hair was like a shaggy character.
Nagachichi is like a shaggy character.
I thought so, too.
The flow was smooth, but one thing.
Everyone, well, everyone.
Well, looking at you.
Yeah, what I thought when I saw you.
I feel like it's going to be a little hard without a break.
Yeah, so if I'm going to record it in the future,
Well, it's almost an hour and a half, isn't it?
It's almost an hour and a half, so I thought it would be okay to take a break for a while.
Yeah, well, I don't know if I'll make it live or record it.
I think it's okay for me to do both.
The reason I couldn't do the live broadcast was because I was having a hard time breathing.
I was really depressed.
I'm having a mental illness right now.
I'm taking some medicine.
I'm taking new medicine right now.
I'm having a hard time breathing.
Yeah, it's basically a live broadcast.
Of course, of course, of course.
I'll try to make it live this month.
This month? Oh, this month.
Yeah, it's hard to breathe.
Yeah, I have sexual desire.
Well, I don't have it, but I have sexual desire.
It's hard to breathe.
Especially on live broadcasts, I'm really serious in a weird place.
Well, how do I say this?
There may be men, but I'm a shitty girl from the beginning.
I'm a
I'm a slut, but I'm a slut, but I'm a slut.
That's a little pressure.
Yeah, well, everyone's looking forward to it.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
You said you liked me.
So I want to feel good and I want to feel good.
I feel like I'm going to die.
I don't know if it's going to be hard to breathe.
Maybe there's someone who's worried about my ED.
I'm starting to feel like that.
Well, I had you put together for about an hour and 20 minutes this time.
Actually, it's already been a long time.
Two and a half hours or something.
I was taking a break from a very long break.
I was editing the video while I was resting.
So, I thought it would be better to record it this time.
I couldn't do it live, but I probably couldn't.
I can't do it, but I have to finish the live in three hours.
I was a little like, wow.
But I was happy.
When I saw the comments, I was like,
It was a little hard to breathe.
When we talked,
But that's what I'm proud of.
I'm proud of what I've said.
I was so happy to hear that you said,
I'm so happy.
I'm crying.
What do you mean?
I'm wearing glasses right now.
I'm being careful.
I was a little happy.
I was proud.
It took me a while.
I'm being chased by the time of the hotel.
Is there a time for a hotel?
I'm glad I could go.
I want to make you feel better.
I want to be myself.
I want to cherish this time more and more.
I'm not feeling well.
But I'm taking my medicine.
Can I talk about the hospital I went to today?
I'm so serious.
I really talked about it at the hospital.
The hospital I went to today was a female nurse.
The nurse was a woman.
The doctor was a woman.
Everyone was a woman.
I chose that place.
I don't like men.
The hospital I went to for the first time.
I went to a big hospital.
I didn't feel well.
Is it a woman?
I don't think it's a woman.
There was a man.
I'm looking forward to men coming to the hospital.
I'm glad the woman is a woman.
It's good to go to the hospital.
I thought it would be easier to talk to a woman.
I went to the hospital.
I was diagnosed with this disease at the previous hospital.
I was taking this medicine.
The nurse was listening to me.
The nurse was talking to me.
I was a little nervous.
I was aware of the symptoms of the disease in the fall of 2022.
I was nervous.
I gave the story I just told to the nurse.
I told her to tell me the story.
I told her to think about the medicine.
I waited in the waiting room.
I went to the hospital in the morning.
The nurse was in my room.
The nurse was very lively.
She had perfect makeup.
She wrote a job.
What kind of job is it?
I was surprised.
I had to say something.
I was a little surprised.
I was surprised.
Youtube finds it otro.
I don't understand
the truth.
I've been asked a lot of questions.
I've been asked to tell me the channel name.
I was told that it was hard and I would be on your side.
I was told to tell me the channel name.
I was embarrassed.
But I became a good person.
I'm worried that the medicine will change.
I'm sleepy and worried.
I want to get better.
I've been feeling down lately.
I'm affected by various things.
I was influenced by fan clubs and Niconico.
I'm working in a business.
I was influenced by my job.
I'm not good at being myself.
I'm not good at working.
I'm not good at anything.
But the doctor was kind.
Everyone is kind.
I'll be treated.
This is not a sad tear.
This is a happy tear.
Everyone is kind.
I really like it.
Everyone is cute.
I was scared in the comments.
I can't go to the video.
I don't like it at all.
What if I say, I don't like it.
The comments are funny.
When I was doing a push-up, I laughed.
I laughed at the past.
I laughed.
I thought it was cute.
I thought I should trust everyone.
I'm always negative.
I want to accept that I'm bad.
Why am I so bad?
Everyone thinks so.
I want to lower myself.
I think this is a kind of self-defeating act.
I'm going to push it.
I want to do it properly.
Everyone likes me more than that.
I want to believe that.
Thank you.
I'm not sure what to do next February.
I was a cat last year.
Is there a picture?
Can I show you a picture?
Wait a minute.
I drink water.
I was a cat.
I'm climbing a slope.
Which one?
This is May.
I'm climbing a slope.
This is March.
This is around here.
Wait a minute.
This is January.
Is there a picture?
What?
No?
It's gone.
There is no cat picture.
I'm a cute cat.
This?
This is it.
There is a picture.
There are 10 pictures on the thumbnail.
What does that mean?
Why is there a picture?
There is a picture.
This is it.
This is the picture from last year.
This is not it.
This is February.
I think so.
I think it's February.
It's a new year's fortune.
Tiger pattern?
A leopard pattern cosplay.
I think I'm wearing a high-resolution costume.
This is last year.
Last year?
What should I do this year?
What should I do?
Long hair until March.
April is a change of mood.
I cut my hair last April.
Is that right?
Long hair.
It's a cat day.
I think I'll cut it into a new year's fortune.
I think it's the end of the month.
It's a little late.
It's a good time.
But it's not until the 29th.
I feel good because there's a wave until the 29th.
I'm thinking of not being late.
Let's do it again.
I'll do it live this time.
Let's shave my head this time.
I'll show you.
I'll shave it.
There's a Valentine's Day.
It's true.
There's a Valentine's Day on February 14th.
What?
I can eat as much as I want.
It's Valentine's Day.
I don't know what the Valentine's costume is.
Chocolate pastry.
Last year, I did it at the Nico Nico store.
It's a mess.
I've done it before.
Valentine's Day?
When I was in high school,
There was a culture of exchanging handmade chocolates with high school girls.
So I always made it.
When I was in high school,
I made chocolate brownies and cookies.
I took it to school and exchanged it with my friends.
I did that.
I don't want to hear it.
It's too much.
It's not good.
It's a choco.
I gave it to Nico.
I think I gave it to him.
Chocolate conversation.
And...
I put it in the archive of the first Nico Nico channel.
Was it YouTube?
Unchoco.
Unchoco?
It's a Nico Nico channel.
I think I uploaded the chocolate I made in 2019.
I mixed marshmallows, chocolate and biscuits.
It's like a crispy kit-cut.
How should I say it?
I heard it was delicious.
I made it, but it's not digested.
I want to see something that's not digested.
No, really.
I'm really going to watch it later.
You can watch the archive for 500 yen on the Nico Nico channel.
It's really a good deal.
If you're in a fan club,
5000 yen is...
You're watching me, right?
So, 500 yen plus.
I'm glad you're in the Nico Nico channel.
You can watch a lot of things.
I'm streaming four times a month.
It's a good deal.
Yeah.
I'm talking about the fan club.
I'm talking about the future fan club.
I'm really unstable.
I'm a genius.
Everyone hates me.
I hate myself.
I'm a social incompatible person.
I can't work.
I'm a mentally unstable woman.
I'm not going to start a fan club.
At first,
I was thinking of making it 10,000 yen.
If I'm going to complain,
I'll make it 10,000 yen.
I don't have to do it for 5000 yen.
I'm not serious.
I didn't make this plan.
I made the 5000 yen plan.
I want a lot of people to see it.
I want as many people as possible to see my sexy side.
But if you show me your beauty for free,
It lowers your value.
I want as many people as possible to see it.
I set it up.
I can't forget it.
If I make it 10,000 yen, it's twice as much.
I can't see it.
I can't upload a short video.
I'll upload a short video when I'm feeling better.
Please wait a moment.
I'm really not good at it.
When I'm mentally unstable,
Even if I have a narrow view,
I can only see the negative opinions.
I'm sorry.
I'm trying to calm down.
I've been receiving the first year's bonus points.
The first one was from the beginning of last month.
I think it will start to arrive in February.
Please wait a moment.
I want to show you the video.
I'm showing you my belly.
I've been filming for a year.
I'm not in a soundproof room.
I'm in a bad shape.
I'm filming with a stomach that can be seen.
I want to show you.
The manager is taking care of me.
It's taking a while.
Please wait a moment.
I'll make my neck longer and become a giraffe.
Make it longer.
Drink water.
I'm looking forward to it.
Is it the lotus flower?
The lotus flower plan has been going on for a year.
I think the person who planned it yesterday had a check.
Check and check holder.
I don't have a video.
How was it?
I'm a genius.
I've been removing bad things.
I'm doing legal procedures.
I'm tired of it.
I think it's hard.
The one of the Kaizu era.
The one of the nipples.
The one of the nipples festival in autumn 2022.
I'm finally settled.
I've finally been able to identify it.
I can't do it now.
I've been receiving a lot of things from my partner.
I'm sorry.
I can't afford this amount.
I'll pay you every month.
I've been wearing it.
I think so.
I think everyone is the same.
I don't think there's anyone.
Everyone, don't do anything bad.
If you do something bad, everyone will be unhappy.
It's hard for the person who did something bad.
It's a little hard for the person who did something bad.
It's hard.
It's really hard.
That's right.
But I'll keep protecting the content that's important to everyone.
From now on.
I'll protect it.
I'll do my best.
I don't want to be punished.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you for thinking that way.
You're a good person.
There are many underaged people.
It's not just one or two.
My parents and my father said,
I'm sorry.
My child.
That's right.
My heart hurts.
A demon that distorts the young's
You can't see the young's picture.
You can't.
Because I'm a pervert.
This is on the Internet.
The information I have now is.
That person is a Yahoo!
I'm talking to a Yahoo!
I said it because I'm a pervert.
I don't say anything else.
Yes.
Of course.
Which prefecture are you from?
How old are you?
I don't need personal information.
I got a document from Kanan when I was a minor.
What should I do?
I was surprised when I heard that from the listener.
That's right.
Well.
I thought it was about my age.
I wrote it down.
I don't think it's my age.
I thought it was my age.
I really can't do it.
It's natural, but.
Especially to me.
Kanan.
I can't write that I got this document.
I said that I would forgive you, but don't write it in the future.
Don't write it in the future.
I said that.
I'm done talking about that.
I think the fan club will continue to be the same.
When I'm not on live, I take a video and I do a little risk.
I don't think it's a basic thing.
I'd like to do that, so please take care of me.
I was watching the live stream and I thought I wanted to make my boobs really sticky.
I thought I could make my boobs sticky next time.
I thought I couldn't forget it.
My boobs are sticky.
This is still unknown, but if I do live streaming for 2 hours and a half, I'll do it.
I'm doing live streaming including angle changes.
If I need a break for 2 hours and a half, I'll record a part of it.
I'll record the last angle like today.
I'll record the angle that's hard to do on live.
I'll record a part of it and record the angle.
If it's better for me to do it, I'll try it.
I'd like to try a lot of things.
By the way, I was drinking black tea.
I was watching your comments and drinking black tea.
I bought a good black tea, so I put it in and drank it.
I was watching you for an hour and a half.
I was watching your comments.
It's fashionable, isn't it?
I was drinking white tea.
I don't know the difference between white tea and black tea, but I drank white tea.
I was watching your comments.
I was doing it elegantly.
In a sense, it's hell.
It's not hell.
I like to see everyone looking at me.
I think it's a natural tendency.
I'm a natural.
I'm happy that I'm feeling good about myself.
I'm happy.
I really like the fan club and the fan club.
I thought it would be better to stop the fan club and the fan club.
I'm not a professional because I'm not satisfied with my physical condition.
I'm not a professional.
You can see it, right?
I've never been surprised by the way you make fun of me.
I'm not good at it, but I'm not a professional.
I'm too confident in myself.
So I quit.
How many parts are there now?
I'll show you the picture.
I'll overwrite this picture.
It's part 19.
I'm still in a bad mood even if it's part 19.
It's a little painful.
I can't move well.
I had a cramping ceremony.
I thought it was painful.
I thought it might hurt.
But when I said I was tired, I thought I was going to cool down.
I don't know if I'm a high school girl.
I don't know why I'm the first time I've ever dated my boyfriend.
I don't want to be hated, so I have to put up with it.
I don't want to be hated.
I made a comment without thinking.
I feel like I'm back.
I thought the video was back in the fan club.
I thought it was amazing.
I thought I was going to take a break.
I cut it once.
I thought I'd take a break for about 10 minutes.
I cut it once and edited it.
I'm free for 10 minutes, so I can't edit it well.
I can't edit it well.
I think that's just for the video.
I didn't edit it.
I edited it.
I edited it so much that it was a little bit of a mess.
I think it's a little bit of a mess.
But I think there's a lot of flexibility.
A woman's body is a little bit of a romance.
Two fingers are fine.
If it's really wet, I think it's important to make a sound.
Suddenly, I suddenly felt like I was going to go.
I stopped it for a moment because it hurt.
I should have done it slowly.
I'm going to do it.
But it wasn't fun.
I'll do it again.
I'll do it again in the future.
I wanted to do it with Miko.
I'm looking forward to what kind of video I'll make next.
What kind of video will I make next?
What should I do?
I've been thinking about doing a video like Calvin Klein for a long time.
I'm thinking about doing a house-style video.
I'm still doing cosplay.
I'm not doing cosplay.
I'm doing a video like Calvin Klein.
I'm thinking about doing a video like a video call.
I'm thinking about various things.
That video was also popular.
I've been talking about it for a long time.
I'm thinking about it.
I was shooting a video today.
I was shooting a video.
The camera angle was small.
I can't talk for a long time.
I'm thinking about doing a video like a video call.
I want to do various things.
But I really don't want to be negative.
Do you all like me?
I'm thinking about it.
I like everyone.
I really want to cherish that feeling.
I want to do it.
I'm thinking about the price of the video.
It seemed that the pressure was increasing.
Of course, the best feeling is always good.
I'll be happy, though.
The feeling mental pressure has become a burden for me.
From such a pure video, I watched the video with bare eyes.
But until then, I think I can make you feel good.
I can enjoy my first love.
I'm going to jump in.
I want to hear your voice, I want to support you, so I'm in a fan club.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I'm not laughing.
I'm happy.
Thank you.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm calm.
Thank you very much.
I'm not good at myself.
I'm thinking about 0 or 100.
I'm going to stop thinking about anything.
I'm worried about everyone.
I'm drinking tea.
I'll do it again next time.
I'm going to do a tea time.
Thank you.
I'm going to throw away everything I don't need.
I'm going to talk about something good at the end.
I'm going to talk about something good.
Everyone will make me cry.
Everyone will be moved by me and make me cry.
I'm calm.
I'm going to talk about something sexy.
I bought something new.
Wait a minute.
What was it?
I bought it on Amazon.
I want to try it next time.
My voice is a mess.
What was it?
Amazon.
I think I bought something.
Did you get it?
I think this is really good.
It's a one-point concentration of a woman who bullies her.
It's called a one-point concentration.
It says it's a salt-blowing vibe.
I've never blown salt.
I've seen a lot of women blowing salt in AVs.
I want to try it.
I looked it up and it said it's easy to blow salt if you drink a lot of water and bully the clitoris.
I want to wear this.
What's this?
I believe in it.
What's a C-spot?
It says C-spot stimulation, but it's not a G.
There's a C-spot.
If you blow salt, you'll be banned.
If you blow salt, you'll be banned?
I think it's a pee.
If you blow salt, you'll be banned.
Is it bad?
If it's salt, it's bad.
Is it a salt-blowing thing?
On the contrary, I don't blow salt.
Is it a good thing?
Is it a ban?
Is this a short video?
Is that so?
That's probably true.
I don't think it's a good thing to pee.
I'm glad.
Is it saved by its weight?
If it's just sound.
Sound is like a fart.
I don't know if I've ever blown salt.
I'm probably a bad person.
I can't make a sound.
I think I'll do it.
I'm too excited.
I'll finish in 30 minutes.
I'm always early.
I'm tired.
I'm not in a bad mood.
I've been on a diet lately.
I don't know why.
I'm on a diet.
But I'm doing that.
When I'm peeing.
I heard that it's good to stop peeing.
I'm going to do a map training in the future.
I don't have any reason to do it now.
I don't think I can use this for fan-cut.
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do a map training.
I heard that it's good to stop peeing.
It says it's good for the joints.
I'm not in a good mood.
I'm not in a good mood when I'm peeing.
I'm going to do a map training.
There's a ball in the map.
I don't think I can use that.
I thought it was going to hurt.
I'm going to do it.
How do you get that information?
It's the Internet.
It's on the Internet.
It's on Twitter.
It's the Internet that makes me feel good when I do it.
And...
I saw a column about pee.
A girl's column.
What was it?
There's a column.
I used to use a lotion that I could lick.
There was a column on the website where I bought the lotion.
I think.
There is.
There's something like that.
I've never bought anything else.
It's like a perfume that invites lipid.
It's so stupid to sell it.
When I go out, everyone says,
I think I'm going to be attacked.
Inviting lipid.
There is.
There's a lot of liquid in the perfume.
It's in the perfume.
It's a perfume for a boyfriend.
I'm not a boyfriend.
I'm a pervert.
It's a world of porn and eroticism.
I'm not a pervert.
I'm a pervert.
I have a boyfriend.
I have a boyfriend who I want him to look at.
I don't think so.
I'm going to meet you alone.
Before I meet you alone, I'm going to take a train or a taxi.
I'm going to take a taxi.
I'm going to get excited.
I don't think so.
I'm going to meet you alone.
When I meet you alone, I'm going to take a taxi.
I don't know.
I'm going to a beautiful place where I can see the night view.
I'm going to a hotel after this.
I'm going to a restaurant.
When I get back to the restaurant, the waitress there is also a pervert.
I'm a pervert except for my boyfriend.
I'm sorry.
It's too dangerous.
It's dangerous.
Is it okay to do that?
I have a bad mood.
I'm under the influence of drugs.
If I change my perfume, I'll be in trouble.
I'll change my perfume before the limited broadcast.
I'll change my perfume.
I wonder if that's going to happen.
I hope it works for me.
I want to spend my precious time with everyone.
Can I buy it?
I'll report it to you.
I'm going to go outside.
I can't do it because I'm in danger of getting a serious delivery.
I'm in the house.
I smell good.
I'm a delivery man.
I have a bad mood.
I'm influenced by you.
I'm always in the back of my head.
Everyone in my house is a male.
I'm influenced by you.
I wonder if I'll be a pervert.
I'm worried.
If I show up in your house,
Everyone is a male.
I don't like touching you with perfume.
I don't like perfume.
I smell bad.
I'm worried about my weight.
I'm sure I have foreign blood in my body.
I was told that my face was small.
I'm worried about my weight.
I wash my body with soap.
I wash it with a double.
I don't use perfume.
I'll try perfume.
30 minutes.
I'll sleep.
Thank you for the pillow talk.
It was a video, so it felt good.
I cried in the pillow talk.
I feel refreshed.
I feel refreshed in many ways.
Thank you.
I'll sleep.
I'm uploading a fan letter.
Thank you in February.
I'm looking forward to the first broadcast of Niconico in February.
I have to take medicine for a week.
I'm sleepy.
I'm worried.
I'll drink a lot of medicine for a week.
I'll do my best.
I'll live calmly.
I'll do ASMR.
Good night.
Thank you.
Thank you always.
I'll do my best.
All I can do is...
I have to take care of myself.
I have to believe in everyone.
I have to love myself.
There is a famous song that I forgot.
I'll live calmly.
Thank you.
Please watch this video a lot.
I cut the video, so you can see it easily.
The butt.
The part that feels good.
The last angle.
Please watch various parts.
Good night.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for supporting me.
I'm sorry I'm recording today.
I'll record the last part next time.
I'll do my best to be in good shape this month.
I'll do it in three weeks.
Thank you.
Good night.
I love you.
Thank you.
Good night.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to the channel.
Please watch other videos, too.