BlLLY CONNOLLY: I'm at the start
of an incredible adventure.
I'm going 10,000 miles from
the Atlantic Ocean to the Pacific Ocean,
and I'm doing it the hard way,
above the Arctic Circle
by a legendary route, the Northwest Passage,
the mythical sea route
across the top of Canada,
linking two oceans.
Whoa!
How unbelievable is this?
lt's like being on another planet.
I'm going to places I've never seen before,
meet people I've never met before
and do things I've never done before.
lt's an absolute sensation.
I'm going on the most extraordinary journey
of my life,
one that some of the world's
greatest sailors and adventurers
have tried to make and failed,
and one that's going to take me
to the very edge of the world.
Why don't you come with me?
We'll have a laugh.
Piece of cake.
l'm on the threshold
of an extraordinary adventure
right across the top of Canada
between the two oceans.
For centuries, people have dreamed of
the Northwest Passage as a trade route,
but it was always iced up.
Now, with the changing climate,
the melting ice should clear
for just enough time for me to go
and have a wee look.
My journey starts on the Atlantic coast
of Canada in Nova Scotia,
and then it's north through Newfoundland,
down to Baffin Island above the Arctic Circle,
and then through
the Northwest Passage itself,
before heading south through the Yukon
to British Columbia,
and my final destination, Vancouver Island,
on the Pacific coast.
You and me, we're gonna do it together,
and it's gonna be fun.
In 10 weeks, I'm going to travel by road,
by boat and by aeroplane,
right round the top of the world.
It's gonna be an epic journey.
By God, it's parky out today.
It will be cold and wet, snowy and blowy,
and everything else you can imagine.
l am bloody freezing.
I'll be meeting all sorts of amazing people
along the way.
Oh, wow!
The joy of the unexpected
brings a light to my eye.
(EXPLODlNG)
Oh!
(LAUGHlNG)
Job done. Helicopter!
The world's a fantastic place,
and I'm heading for some of the most
remarkable and remote landscapes anywhere.
I'm getting very excited
just thinking about it.
Well, l'm off the coast of Nova Scotia,
and l've no idea where l'm going.
l don't know where l'm going
or where l've been.
This journey could be longer than 10 weeks.
Just like countless explorers and pioneers
before me
who braved the North Atlantic
to reach America,
there's no better way to start an adventure
than to arrive by boat.
For the first leg of my journey,
I'm going to explore Canada's Atlantic coast,
and I'm starting here at Halifax, Nova Scotia.
Today it's a busy seaport, but this was once
the gateway for hordes of Europeans
who'd come here to make a new life in
what was for them the edge of the world.
This is a very famous place, Pier 21,
where millions of immigrants landed,
almost two million,
people from Europe coming here to settle
in Canada for one reason or another.
lt's sort of Canada's Ellis lsland.
These days it's where cruise ships dock
and tourists are welcomed ashore,
and it's a much happier place
than it used to be.
Look at this!
l didn't realise it was moving
when l came out the door.
l love ships.
l worked in a shipyard, you know.
l love the whole line.
l find great beauty in that.
l used to be a welder.
(BAGPlPES PLAYlNG)
God's music!
lsn't that the best?
This is kind of welcoming
and happy, jolly music.
But there's also really sad music
associated with this,
and, actually, more in lreland
than in Scotland.
There was music...
They called it an American wake.
When you were leaving to come here,
they would have your wake,
while you were still alive, playing music,
'cause they knew they were never
going to see you again,
so coming here was like dying.
So a lot of that music is kind of sad.
But l love this.
Oyez!
l extend a most warm and sincere welcome!
We wish you good luck
and may God be with you all!
-You did that rather well.
-Thank you very much.
That's wonderful, isn't it?
With its town crier and museum,
Pier 21 is now a sideshow of a previous era
for the tourists who flit through here
off cruise ships.
When l see these things,
l don't think of tourism,
although it's a huge and great industry here.
l think of all those immigrants
and how odd they must have felt
stepping off here in this strange country,
although they were given a lovely welcome.
It must have been hellishly daunting
to leave behind everything and everyone
from their homeland, knowing they would
probably never return.
I know many of them
had Irish and Scottish blood, just like me.
l'm going to see how many Billy Connollys
came here.
lt's just a silly idea.
l was just wondering, can you tell me
how many William Connollys came here?
Sure.
There's 30 of them, came in.
Thirty Billy Connollys?
You don't deserve that.
(LAUGHlNG)
What do you think you did
to deserve 30 of them arriving?
Look! Twenty-third of November.
My birthday's the 24th of November.
This is too weird for me.
l don't even know the guy
and l'm going all kind of tingly and quivery.
If there were 30 Billy Connollys
that passed through here,
there must be millions of Canadians
who can trace their roots back
through this gateway to Europe.
I'm going to meet some of the descendants
of those early settlers.
What's left, I wonder, of the old world
their forefathers brought with them?
But I've one stop to make
before I leave Halifax,
and it makes me smile.
After Pier 21, the first place the tourists
are taken is here, the Titanic graveyard.
-Doesn't it make you smile?
-lt does.
You're on a cruise
and they come and show you...
First thing they want to show you
is the sinking. Yes.
And it's usually right after breakfast.
BlLLY: That's something wonderful,
just after breakfast.
BLAlR BEED: lt is.
Just when you thought it was safe
to go back in the water.
Exactly.
I have a great fondness for graveyards
and the stories they tell.
The Titanic one is particularly fascinating.
Blair Beed shows me round the graves
of 120 victims of that awful disaster.
Now, these wee identical stones,
what's the story there?
-How come some of them are different sizes?
-White Star Line only gave one size stone.
lf you wanted a bigger stone,
your family paid for a bigger stone.
-So it was an extra expense.
-Oh, really?
So, for instance, here's Mr Elliott,
the family paid extra for this.
He was a crew member, and they were mad
that the newspaper of the day
said crew members survived,
women and children died.
So as you read the verse at the bottom
that they put on,
you can almost hear
the glorious trumpets sounding
-about how he stood at his post.
-Oh, right.
''And showed once more to all the world
how Englishmen should die.''
And trumpets go.
(MlMlCKlNG TRUMPET FANFARE)
The Titanic has a magical quality
that just goes on and on forever.
lt's like there's nothing dead about it.
Just it's so alive.
BEED: And it keeps coming back.
l was at a shipyard museum in Belfast,
and they gave me the T-shirt.
And it says, ''Titanic, built in Belfast.''
And on the back it says,
''She was okay when she left here''.
That's a great T-shirt.
l don't know what we could put for Halifax.
''We've got the dead.''
l mean, that just wouldn't sell.
Or maybe it would.
There's one particular grave here
that attracts so much attention
the grass has been totally worn away
by hordes of adoring girls.
Now, you probably saw the movie where
Leonardo DiCaprio played Jack Dawson,
the great lover who drowned
towards the end of the movie.
Well, they think he's in there.
The grave just says ''J. Dawson''.
But it's a guy called Joseph Dawson.
But nobody seems to be bothered too much
about that.
So in death he became sexy in Hollywood.
Good on him, l say.
I'm leaving Halifax behind me for the next leg
of my epic journey to the edge of the world.
I'm heading for the coast
for a spot of cod fishing.
As I hit the road, the scale of this trip
is just beginning to dawn on me.
l'm taking 10 weeks to cross Canada,
and it's a big journey,
and it gives you an extraordinary feeling
of how enormous this country is.
Nova Scotia is just the first square
on the Monopoly board,
and I've got the whole nation to cross.
But I'm excited by the adventure of it all.
I've come to Lunenburg.
For over 200 years, this was North America's
fishing capital and cod was king.
Fishing was a way of life for generations
of people who came over from Europe.
But years of overfishing have meant the cod
has pretty much gone,
and Lunenburg now survives on tourism.
Welcome to Lunenburg.
Haven't been here 24 hours,
and l've got the Nova Scotia hat.
Tourist till l die.
What? You got doughnuts?
-Yeah, we eat doughnuts.
-Just in case you get hungry.
I'm going out fishing with Bobby and Ralph.
They've worked these waters all their lives.
I'm hoping to catch some cod for my lunch.
But it's now in such short supply,
there's no guarantee I'll get any.
There is no cod fishing here any more.
l think we're a lot to blame for it,
ourselves, you know.
We destroyed a lot of fish back in the years.
Commercial cod fishing is now banned.
But it's okay if we try to catch the odd one
by hook and line.
l've never seen a hook
that's circular like that.
And the way the fishing is right now,
if you get one on, you don't want to lose it.
'Cause it's a long time
before another one comes by.
Exactly right.
l'll see if l can get the bait first.
l'm gonna try and catch a fishy.
Ah, here we are.
-You can't talk a fish into existence.
-No, you can't.
They say... What is it?
''A fool on one end and a fish on the other.''
Well, you got a fishing line, so...
lt's good fun when they're biting,
but it's not much fun when they're not.
Not so long ago, fish would have
been leaping into the boat
just to have a wee nosey, but not any more.
I don't really mind, though.
It's just a delight to be at sea
in this cocoon of fog,
fishing with these two lovely guys.
Did you spit on your bait?
-No, l said a wee prayer.
-Did you?
lt wasn't a big enough one, l don't believe.
-Quite a tail, look.
-BlLLY: You caught a bit of tail.
RALPH: Not quite a codfish, but it is a fish.
The thieving bastard.
l'm glad we're not doing this for a living,
aren't you?
Fishing is a hard life, and dangerous.
Bobby wasn't going to tell me
till I squeezed it out of him,
but he nearly lost his life in '93
when his boat was completely iced up
and started to capsize.
They figure it was 35 below, the wind chill.
They estimate it was about 70 tons of ice
on the frozen...
Seventy tons of ice clinging to your boat?
Yeah, froze to the side of the boat.
-And that's what threw it off balance?
-Yeah.
She just made that last heave under
and started to load herself full of water.
There was no recovering it then,
just kept sinking.
How did that feel?
(LAUGHlNG)
lt wasn't the best of feelings.
Bobby was rescued, but it ended in tragedy
for some of his friends.
There was five fellows we lost that time.
And them fellows, l don't know
what really happened to 'em.
We picked up three of the bodies
and two of them didn't even get off the boat.
-Really?
-Yeah.
It's a terrifying story,
and I so admire how Bobby has dealt with it,
and has kept his love of the sea.
lt's good to be out here.
l can't imagine being on a fishing boat
at 35 below, 150 miles off shore,
with ice all clinging to your boat
and wondering if you're going to get home.
l can't imagine anything harder than that.
-We're not very good fishermen.
-No, we're pretty crap, aren't we?
We wouldn't make much money.
-We tell a good tale, though.
-Oh, yeah.
Oh!
At long last, our fortunes change,
but it's not cod.
l've got some mackerel.
Whoa!
(WHOOPlNG)
RALPH: Holy mackerel,
them are the big ones!
lt's mackerel-o-rama.
lt's funny, we get nothing for ages,
and now we can't put the hooks
back in quick enough.
We did catch one cod, by the way,
but he was such a wee tiddler,
we threw him back.
RALPH: That's one of our codfish,
but he will grow, hopefully.
It's so sad that as the cod fishing has gone,
guys like Bobby and Ralph have
become a dying breed of men.
A way of life that brought
so many people here, just wiped out.
The old fishing livelihood may be gone,
but next, I'm heading north
to where some surprising old country
customs are very much alive and kicking.
So where do you think you might be?
Oban? lnverness?
Aberdeenshire? Mallaig?
We're in New Brunswick.
Since 1 753, people have been coming here
from Scotland,
since the Highland Clearances, really.
And they tend to cling to the culture
of what they see as the culture.
Personally, l have mixed feelings about it.
You have a big head?
That's not bad.
-Oh, my God.
-Oh, that's fabulous.
Can l have a picture with you
and that hat on?
No. How dare you? Leave me alone.
(LAUGHlNG)
I think it's a New World thing,
a need for something old.
And they seem to assume
that old means good.
When l was a wee boy,
not only didn't we wear kilts,
we frowned on people who did.
We used to shout, ''Kilty, kilty, cold bum!''
And to this day,
l am wary of people who wear kilts.
But then there are bits of Scottish culture
I just love,
and it's hard for me not to get carried away
by it all.
This is the real thing.
lt's poetry. lt's wordless poetry.
The band of Scots that landed here
has clung on to its Highland traditions
and kept them remarkably intact.
This sport shows you how boring life was
in Highland villages.
The people would say,
''Let's throw trees this afternoon.
''l know what we'll do.
We'll throw a tree up in the air.''
His underwear's a bit on the long side.
Y-fronts don't cut it.
Calvin Klein means nothing here.
Here we go. Here we go.
Oh, yes! Perfect! Perfect! Excellent!
I think culture should be constantly
on the move, forever changing.
But people here seem to relish being
more Scottish than the Scots themselves.
-Hello, Sean, how do you do?
-Mr Connolly, good to meet you.
-Nice to see you, yeah.
-You as well.
l've seen people here who've never been
in Scotland who are wearing all the stuff
and a very Scottish air about it.
How do you feel about that?
When we get here,
we get amongst these people,
and we wear the kilt and we hear bagpipes,
something...
All the worries of life go away.
lt just makes us feel good.
l can understand that.
Most of these people here aren't
really working to be Scottish.
-They're just out enjoying being Scottish.
-They're just enjoying themselves.
l've got nothing against that whatsoever.
l don't know if this is the direction
l would have gone in, if l was an immigrant.
In one way I find it refreshing, in another way
I find it kind of very mysterious.
I find myself being swung towards
their way of thinking.
But then again, I was always easily led.
l think you can tell.
Direct from Scotland, we have a visitor,
Mr Billy Connolly.
And when the massed bands strike up,
something stirs in me.
No matter how much l try not to like this,
l love it.
l go all wobbly inside. l can't help it.
When the drums and pipes go, it's just...
l'm putty in their hands.
You can't refuse an occasion
to make Scottish cool.
And it really is pretty nifty.
As I hit the road,
with the music still ringing in my ears,
I think I can see why all this Scottishness
is so strong over here.
l think it's the size of the place,
and the amount of wilderness
that makes them so keen on their culture.
Anything that you can grab
that makes you feel at home
must bring you great solace.
I've driven through Nova Scotia
to Cape Breton Island,
where I'm heading towards a town
called Cheticamp,
where I'm going to meet a different group of
settlers that have made their colourful mark.
Before this was ever Nova Scotia,
it was called New France.
And hereabouts,
the people still speak French.
They call themselves Acadians, descendants
of 17th-century French colonists.
There's a distinctly odd feel to this place,
and I like it.
What l'm looking forward to,
there's a scarecrow maker.
l've never met a scarecrow maker before.
l never thought there were such things.
l thought farmers just hammered them
together from brushes and old clothes.
This should be a bit interesting.
Oh, God, it's quite scary!
Look at that line at the back.
That is so weird.
Oh, l like this.
There's a funky, weird edge to this
that l'm beginning to like.
Stone the crows.
lt's... l can't explain it to you.
l think it's because they're absolute life-size
with real clothes on.
There's a definite Village of the Damned
feel about it.
l think it's this thing. l think it's this pose.
lt's like some kind of satanic rite.
Oh, God, Margaret Thatcher's here,
of all people.
lt gets more bizarre by the yard.
l love these things.
The other visitors, they're just like me.
People are, you know...
The average expression is...
What the fudd is this?
lsn't it odd? l mean,
l don't know if you can feel it up the lens.
lt's like getting into a graveyard and finding
all the people standing, l'm telling you.
I was wondering what kind of oddball
was behind all this,
when Chester shows up,
and he's a true delight.
-How are you?
-How do you do? Billy Connolly.
-Are you Chester Delaney?
-Pleased to meet you.
What a delight. How nice to meet you.
l was just talking about your stuff.
l was... They call me the artist.
(LAUGHlNG)
-How dare they?
-Yeah, yeah.
-So this is your stuff. That's extraordinary.
-This is all my scarecrows.
-And l have 90.
-Ninety?
Ninety scarecrows, yes.
And l dress them all new every year.
l've been doing that since the last 13 years.
-There's something wrong with you.
-No, they tell me l'm all right.
-l dress them all new every year.
-Nobody's ever told me that.
lt's a big job.
lt is very unusual.
l try to put, see, a little note
on each one of them.
Like, even that guy that l call Wayne.
Like, he died two years ago.
But he was a miner.
He worked hard all his life.
So that's why l put ''Wayne Collins''
on the scarecrow.
-Yeah, so now that's a memorial to him.
-Yes, that's what it is.
''l'm a working man, l am.
And l'll go down underground. l'm Wayne.''
''Shift work took me out the door
till Sydney Steel was no more.''
Oh, l found Pamela. She's changed.
The witch. l'm not sure about that at all.
Don't know if my wife will approve that.
-Now, l have a little surprise for you.
-Oh, yeah?
-Would you come here with me?
-Aye.
Oh, my God!
Oh, l've joined the merry throng.
When I was a child,
my ambition was to be a tramp.
And l've actually... l've almost reached it.
(SlNGlNG lN FRENCH)
What a smashing man
playing absolutely smashing music.
There's no mistake he plays well.
You know, his art is good. His life is good.
He's a true, nice man.
What a jolly day!
You crazy people.
You are. You're French.
That's what's wrong with you.
BlLLY: I like this bit of the world. It's happy.
There's a continental happiness
that really appeals to me.
Even the landscape lifts your spirit.
Just north of Cheticamp is
the scenic Cabot Trail,
named after the early explorer John Cabot.
It winds around the rocky splendour
of Cape Breton's western shore
and it's taking me up to the northernmost tip
of Nova Scotia.
And there's only one way to do it justice.
The Cabot Trail is one
of the top five motorcycle rides in the world.
I can understand why. It's spectacular.
What a stunning place.
My God, it's beautiful.
lt's a lovely feeling rolling along
in the open air,
especially when you get
to the top of these hills
and you go over the top and it dips.
You see it dipping and winding like that.
It's an extraordinary rush.
It's a feeling of freedom.
It's a lovely feeling. You're free as a bird.
The only thing to look out for
around here is moose.
I mean, look at it, the big daft article.
It has no idea it's one of Canada's
biggest killers on the roads.
Nice, eh?
Don't say l never take you anywhere.
Look at that. Pleasant Bay.
Strange little name,
but it kind of sums it up, really.
This is at the very end of Nova Scotia,
Cape Breton,
New Brunswick,
all that Acadian stuff we showed you.
This is up towards the end of it.
We're now going to Newfoundland. That way.
Now I've never been to Newfoundland before,
but I've met many Newfies in my travels
and I can't wait to meet some more.
I'm on a journey to the edge of the world.
I'm leaving Nova Scotia and I'm flying north
to the island of Newfoundland
and St John's.
It was here on this rocky shoreline that
some of the earliest European explorers
from the 15th century set foot
in the New World.
This is Cape Spear, not Cape Fear, mind you.
Cape Spear.
And the main reason l'm here
is that this is the most easterly point
of North America.
The nicest thing about it is you can see that
this is how the explorers first saw it
coming this way.
John Cabot, 1 497.
You must remember that
Christopher Columbus was 1 492.
He said the fish were so bountiful,
you don't even need a net, he says.
You just throw a basket over the side
with a weight in it.
And you can pull fish in.
And that brought thousands of people.
Thousands to get the cod.
For over 500 years,
fishing has been the lifeblood here.
Generations of mainly
English and Irish immigrants
give St John's a lively feel
that I instantly liked.
I've headed down to the harbour
for a look-see.
See, l've always liked docks since
l was a wee boy in Glasgow.
They have a peculiar smell.
The smell of ropes,
tar, wood, sawdust.
ln Scotland you would get the smell
of whisky and wood together
and it's a thing that appealed to me as a boy.
lt always smelled of foreign places
and leaving and going on a voyage
and being a man
and growing up and all that kind of thing.
The harbour here is
a shadow of what it used to be
before the cod got fished into oblivion.
MAN: They're usually bigger than that, eh?
These days it's mainly crabs
and shelly creatures,
and I wonder if their days are numbered, too.
Look at this poor bugger.
This is what it's all about.
Picking him out of the ocean.
Minding his own business.
Winking at the girls that were passing by.
(MAKES WHOOSHlNG SOUND)
St John's.
But nowhere does hospitality
like Newfoundland.
An old seafaring tradition of welcoming
outsiders to become honorary Newfies
has become a tourist ritual
called ''Screeching in. ''
Thank you very much.
l'm the one who wants to be a Newfie.
# Oh, well, l had a hat when l came in
And l hung it on the rack
# And l'll have a hat when l go out
Or l'll break somebody's back
# l'm a decent man, l am, l am
And l don't want to shout
# But l had a hat when l came in
BOTH: # And l'll have a hat when l go out! #
(SPEAKlNG lN THlCK
NEWFOUNDLAND ACCENT)
l understand now you're a CFA wants to get
Screeched in and become
a right proper Newfoundlander, right?
-Yes.
-ls you a Screecher?
(SPEAKlNG GlBBERlSH)
You came out of the gate good, my son,
you just gotta get down the fairway
a little bit better.
So you say, '''Deed l is, me old cock.''
'Deed l is, me old cock.
-''Long may your big jib draw.''
-Long may your big jib draw.
-There you go, my son, good for you!
-'Deed l is, me old cock.
Long may your big jib draw.
-Got a little buddy for you to meet.
-Oh, yes.
I'm supposed to kiss a cod,
but there aren't any,
so this trout will have to do.
Some sweet.
Okay, now, now...
l never got you to sign any waiver forms
or anything like that,
so for heaven's sakes,
don't get any of that on your skin, okay?
The infamous local tipple is Jamaican rum
called Screech.
If you have any sense about you,
you'll avoid Screech.
Up to the lips, over the gunnels,
look out gullet,
here she comes! Plunge her back!
(COUGHS)
(BOTH WHOOPlNG)
I made do with pop.
By all the powers vested in me,
l dub thee a Screecher.
Rise up and find thy newfound heritage.
Welcome to Newfoundland, my son.
-Thank you.
-Pleasure to have you over this way.
Long may your big jib draw.
There you go, you got it, my son.
You're quick.
-There you go.
-Oh! l'm a Screecher.
l'm very proud now to be a Newfie.
Even if my name is spelled wrong
on the certificate.
It rains more here, it snows more here,
they get more fog, and they give most
to charity of all the major places.
And now wait till l tell you this wee factoid.
They have more sex than anybody else.
Now, how can they possibly know that?
But there's one fact there's no doubt about.
Newfies are some of the most
generous people on Earth.
And one event sums this up.
What happened in a little town called Gander
when the world came to town
in the wake of the 9/1 1 disaster.
Welcome to Gander,
in the middle of Newfoundland.
On that infamous day, everything in the air
was ordered to hit the deck.
Thirty-nine jets landed here.
All at the same time.
6,500 people were dumped on this place.
The population is only 10,000.
People were here for six days,
but they opened their arms,
put the people up in their houses, fed them,
looked after them.
And it's a legend in the world of hospitality.
I've come to have a wee taste
of that legendary hospitality
as the town celebrates its 50th birthday
with a party.
Welcome to Gander, Newfoundland, sir.
Mayor Elliott.
-Mayor!
-l'm the mayor here. How are you doing?
They told me l might bump into you.
Well, it's a pleasure to have you here.
lt's a pleasure for me to be in a town
that's younger than me.
Well, me, too!
For a community of 10,000 to have 6,500,
7,000 people drop in...
Well, we just had extra people for dinner,
that's all.
-l love that.
-Yeah, it was no big deal.
l love the attitude, it's extraordinary.
(HONKlNG)
Oh, there's real Mounties, l see a Mountie.
This was the uniform to kill them all.
Hospitality seems to be deeply ingrained
in the DNA of Newfies.
I'm off now to meet a local fisherman
and hunter, Dave Brake.
He's put on a spread of lunch at his home
and wouldn't take no for an answer.
l got trout in there that is fit for a king.
In fact, the king is not getting them.
You can have them.
The king ain't getting them.
We've got a lovely caribou soup,
caribou that l shot myself.
And, of course, my wife's got some
home-made baked buns
and strawberry tarts and lemon cake.
We're gonna have a good little scoff here,
now, boys.
Now, what did l tell you?
That's exactly what l was...
This is astonishing.
l like this. This is a good lunch.
DAVE: Okay, here we go.
BlLLY: That was lovely.
And now a real treat for me.
Dave's taking me fishing in the River Gander,
which is famous for its salmon.
Let's see if I can catch something here.
DAVE: Great conditions for fishing,
if there's any here.
BlLLY: Absolutely.
DAVE: Perfect, as far as l'm concerned.
Wilderness is brilliant.
There's just something really primal about it.
Just the view and the wind and the trees.
lt's a lovely thing.
DAVE: You gotta be positive.
-Absolutely.
-You gotta believe every cast he's coming.
BlLLY: Every single one.
BlLLY: Here it comes, down to the bedrock.
DAVE: There you go.
BlLLY: The salmon just aren't biting.
But it doesn't really matter.
I'm an angler, not a fishmonger.
This is all about relaxation.
People say to me, ''You must get some ideas
when you're fishing.''
Never had an idea in my life
when l'm fishing.
Fishing's for the opposite reason.
I get a lot of nothing when I'm fishing
and it's delightful.
Shuts out the whole world.
Gander is quite a legendary river.
Just not today.
Just a lovely day.
But fishless.
He's not going to let me forget it, guys.
He's not going to let me forget the fishless...
Don't be silly.
-You caught me.
-Sorry.
lt's the only bloody thing
you've caught all day.
Early retirement.
Let's stop this nonsense.
Well, l haven't laughed this hard
in a long time, l must say.
-lt's fun, isn't it?
-Yeah, boy, it is fun.
BlLLY: l may never fish again.
(DAVE LAUGHlNG)
BlLLY: l'm broken-hearted.
Nice little bit of equipment there.
lt's going to take us right to the north
of Newfoundland.
l may be gone for quite some time.
The next part of my journey takes me
even further north to St Anthony.
Flying is nice. Landing is twice as nice.
And it's distinctly cold.
We're an hour north in Newfoundland
of where we were.
We're right up at the very north end of
Newfoundland in a place called St Anthony's.
When I was a wee boy,
I learned that Saint Anthony
was the patron saint
of things that you'd lost.
I feel like a lost soul in a cold place.
They're fond of saying here
that if you don't like the weather,
just wait five minutes and it'll change.
Well, I think the clock has
stopped at fog and drizzle.
We're gonna show you how pretty it is
here up in the north.
And it really is sensationally beautiful.
Look at me, l can hardly see.
lt's hellish.
But in a kind of...nice way.
You feel it's doing your skin a world of good.
And l've had several good-hair days so far
in this drizzle.
The very first Europeans that made
a flying visit here 1,000 years ago
were the Vikings.
Today, out-of-work fishermen make a living
dressed up as Vikings.
They have made a heritage encounter
where none existed before.
I'm looking for the tribe's chieftain.
Nobody here. l guess they must
have buggered off to Greenland.
(MAN LAUGHlNG)
l can hear them in here,
there's raucous laughter.
(KNOCKlNG)
Hello!
(MAN SHOUTlNG)
l am Chieftain Bjorn the Beautiful.
-BlLLY: Bjorn the Beautiful?
-Bjorn the Beautiful.
BlLLY: (LAUGHlNG) That's all right.
That's a good name, isn't it, eh?
BlLLY: lt's amazingly cosy and nice in here,
isn't it?
BJORN: Yeah.
BJORN: Now, a lot of people compare it
to the black houses in Scotland.
They probably copied us, the Vikings.
-They probably copied the Scots.
-Ah, no, no, no.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
l think the Scots were lucky to actually
have the Norsemen.
They talk a good game, the Vikings.
BJORN: What do you mean,
''talk a good game''?
(BJORN LAUGHlNG)
BlLLY: l would love to live in a house
that was covered in flowers like that.
Like being an old hippy from way back.
They found this among the ruins.
-That's why we're posing for pictures.
-Well-preserved as it was.
Absolutely, it was preserved exactly like that.
-Remarkable.
-lt was wrapped in rushes and moss.
BlLLY: Dressing up as Vikings
might seem an odd job,
but at least Bjorn and his tribe
can carry on living here,
while other out-of-work fishermen
have had to leave Newfoundland
to find work.
Tourism for here has been the lifeblood.
-Yeah.
-Because, after the fishery died, that was it.
BlLLY: Yes.
BJORN: So, tourism has kept
a degree of people here.
Not like it was, but a degree.
Newfoundlanders have a bit of a habit,
where, if you can't make it here,
-you go somewhere else.
-Yes.
-And...
-Well, that's how they got here
-in the first place, isn't it?
-Yeah.
BlLLY: People like to be Vikings. People like
the picturesque side of that kind of stuff.
And now the whole economy...
lt seems to me, half the signs here
are to Norseland
and Viking ships on the signs and all that.
And the guys were here for about five years.
It really is a blip on the screen.
l think it's brilliant. Roll on.
Keep up the bed and breakfast
and the Viking image.
lt's better than anything l can think of.
-All right, thank you. Take care.
-See you later, Bjorn. Stay beautiful.
I'm off to get up close and personal
with an iceberg.
Pilot.
You're lucky people.
lceberg Alley, here we come.
Now, I've sat up front with pilots before,
but it's a first for me to be allowed to
have a go at actually flying the plane.
It's something I've always wanted to do.
And, oh, my heart sings a wee song.
I've spotted a handsome-looking iceberg
trapped in a bay,
so it's time to get back on the water.
-Okay, welcome aboard.
-Thanks very much.
Thank you very much.
This guy, he's a local man.
His name's Freeman,
and he's taking us round to the bay
where the iceberg is.
lt's like a big piece of jewellery
floating along.
l think they're wonderful things.
You'll like it, or l'll know the reason why.
lt's a sensational colour.
Even l, just spotting it peeping round
the corner there, got a wee thrill.
lsn't it a sensation?
lt's come from the glacier in Greenland.
That's the same place that produced
the icebergs that sunk the Titanic.
The native Inuit, who live in Arctic Canada,
believe that icebergs contain the spirits
of their ancestors
who come back to see them every spring.
I love that.
l just saw a face.
That's the nose on the left there.
The upper lip, see it?
And then up, and there's hair at the back.
See, that's the way they get you.
l'd love to tow it up the Clyde or up
the Thames or the Tyne or the Mersey
and let all those kids see it.
For some peculiar reason,
it looks edible as well.
lt looks like a big cake.
lt's a meringue, that's what it is. You want it?
We'll tow it back for you.
This is just a taster of the frozen north
that's ahead of me.
I'm almost at the end of this part
of my journey.
From here,
I'll be travelling beyond the Arctic Circle,
but before that, there's something
I'd love to catch sight of.
I'm going to the Quirpon Lighthouse,
which is only about half an hour away.
But it's the most northerly bit
of Newfoundland.
And it's famous for whale-spotting.
As soon as you say,
''lt's famous for whale-spotting,''
you get the feeling that
all the whales go, ''Right...''
and dive.
Some people are good
at spotting them spouting.
l would have been a lousy whaler.
l don't see it till half the tail is
flapping over my boat.
# Oh, for the life of the rolling seas #
Whoa!
Suddenly the full Newfoundland breakfast
isn't such a good idea.
More scrambled eggs for me, please.
Nurse, the screens. Nurse!
Oh, nurse!
No more black pudding for me!
Apparently there's a whale up ahead.
Oh, l saw it blowing there.
l'm going to shout ''There she blows,''
the next time it happens.
lt's always nice, isn't it,
to see a whale? lt's always such a privilege.
MAN: Tail's coming, there it is. Look.
BlLLY: Oh! l saw it there.
That was just amazing.
Now, this is what I call
getting away from it all.
I'm going to spend my last night in the most
remote lighthouse in Newfoundland.
l ordered a white stretch limo with colour TV.
Didn't show up.
l've been booked into some weird places
in my time.
This takes the biscuit.
WOMAN: Hello!
-BlLLY: Hello!
-Welcome to the island.
Thank you very, very much indeed.
l never entered a hotel quite like that
in my life.
Okay.
Do people usually look as amazed as l do?
WOMAN: l don't know.
We're at the very northern tip
of Newfoundland.
From here, we're going north and west.
And it just seems like
the most extraordinary journey.
We've hardly started yet.
When you think of everything
we've done together,
we've seen fantastic scenery
in this immense country.
There was Pier 21,
fishing at sea with Bobby and Ralph,
the stirring massed bands
at the Highland Games,
the delightful Chester
and his bizarre scarecrows,
having a laugh with Dave
on the River Gander.
Welcome to Newfoundland, my son.
Ordinary folk, generous, warm people
just getting on with their lives,
but clinging on nostalgically to a world
that seems to be slipping away from them.
What will I find as I head for a land
where the going gets really tough?
How are the people up there coping
as the world changes around them?
From here, we're going that way.
Into the wilderness, up to Baffin Island.
If you're stuck for where Baffin Island is,
get yourself a map.
It's slightly left
and a wee bit below Greenland.
The people look different, sound different,
behave different.
That is extraordinary.
You won't believe it.
lt's an absolute sensation.
Why don't you come with me?
We'll have a laugh.
Excuse me, do you have any idea
where l can post a postcard here?
See you later.