This tree is a gateway
between two worlds.
This ground has been disturbed.
The soil is loose. Bring the shovel.
The skull is gone.
Taken.
That's why he returns from the grave.
To take heads
until his own is restored to him.
lchabod?
Split up. Glenn. Theodore.
- Don't pick your teeth, it's a bad habit.
- l am a bad habit.
- There's nothing for it.
- Oh, isn't there?
- Let's get ready for bed.
- Yes.
Beth, run!
Be quiet.
- Wait, he's not after you.
- I'II get him.
We cannot win this.
RemarkabIe. A wound Iike this
shouId have kiIIed him, -
- but it needs no stitch,
and there's hardIy a Ioss of bIood.
- You must be stiII. The fever is on you.
- Katrina ...
Nostradamus, Mediamus,
miIk of mercy, in media nos Iaudamas.
Katrina, I tried to stop Brom ...
Drink this down,
it wiII make you sIeep.
The Horseman was not set to kiII Brom
or me. Had Brom not attacked him ...
Later. Rest now.
The Horseman doesn't kiII at random.
His victims are chosen by
that very person who took his skuII.
Someone who knew where to dig,
of fIesh and bIood, as I've aIways said.
- These are ravings.
- Drink.
Ichabod ...
- You were dreaming.
- Yes. Of things I had forgotten ...
... and wouId not Iike to remember.
- TeII me what you dreamt.
- My mother was an innocent.
A chiId of nature.
Condemned.
Murdered ... by my father.
- Murdered by ..?
- Murdered to save her souI.
By a BibIe-bIack tyrant,
behind a mask of righteousness.
I was seven when I Iost my faith.
- What do you beIieve in?
- Sense and reason.
Cause and consequence.
But here my rationaI mind has been
so controverted by the spirit worId.
You'II take nothing from SIeepy HoIIow
that was worth the coming here?
No, not nothing.
A kiss from a IoveIy young woman,
before she saw me or knew my name.
Yes, without sense or reason.
Forgive me. I speak of kisses,
and you've Iost your brave man Brom.
I have shed my tears for Brom, -
- and yet my heart is not broken.
Do you think me wicked?
No. But perhaps
there is a bit of witch in you.
- Why do you say that?
- Because you've bewitched me.
You sIept Iike the dead.
You're too kind to me. I don't Iook
to be served by the Iady of the house.
Nor wouId you be,
but that the servant girI has vanished.
- Sarah?
- Run away, Iike so many others.
Theyre aII Ieaving in fear.
Where is Katrina?
She watched over you tiII dawn.
Now it is her turn to sIeep.
I'm fit for another day, I think.
Fit enough to face a mortaI adversary.
Dr. Lancaster.
Reverend Steenwyck.
Notary Hardenbrook
and Magistrate PhiIipse ...
... who tried to cut and run,
and Iost his head.
Four frightened men arguing together
on the very night PhiIipse was kiIIed.
There is conspiracy here.
The doctor, the reverend,
the notary and the magistrate.
What is the secret that unites them?
Magistrate PhiIipse knew
there were five bodies to four graves.
He knew the widow was pregnant and
wouId not teII me the father's name.
What does this point to?
We must proceed
by process of eIimination.
I'II Iist everyone in town, starting with
its chief citizen, BaItus Van TasseI.
- I feeI we're getting very cIose.
- Yes ...
I suppose BaItus is the chief citizen,
now that oId Van Garrett is dead.
The Van Garretts ...
I'd aImost forgotten them.
Come with me,
to Notary Hardenbrook's.
- Have you thought of something?
- Yes ... I have.
HopeIess.
My father's satcheI.
Why is it here?
- Leave me aIone.
- Notary Hardenbrook ...
Show me the Iast wiII and testament
of oId man Van Garrett.
- The wiII Ieaves everything to his son.
- Who died with him.
- The estate passes to the next of kin.
- NaturaIIy. AII IegaI and above board.
- Sir?.
- I'm a dead man. No ...
Van Garrett's seaI, broken.
He made a new wiII just before he died,
naming ... Widow Winship?
And here, Iook.
A marriage certificate.
He secretIy married the widow and Ieft
everything to her and her unborn chiId.
It stood between Van Garrett's fortune
and the one who'd have got everything.
It's true, but we four
were drawn in against our wiII.
- Your wiII?
- He means ...
Of course, the four town eIders.
Now I see what parts you had to pIay.
Steenwyck knew the secret.
He performed the marriage. Lancaster
attended the pregnant woman.
PhiIipse gave protection of the Iaw.
Hardenbrook conceaIed documents -
- entrusted by Van Garrett
to his faithfuI servant.
- The conspirators drawn into the pIot.
- We knew not it was a murdering pIot.
But I have not finished, sir.
First, the Van Garretts sIain by
a horseman raised from the grave.
Up pops a widow with a cIaim
on the fortune. Off with her head.
But murder begets murder.
It was the servant ...
... Jonathan Masbath. The night father
and son quarreIIed over the new wiII.
Masbath was summoned upstairs
to bear witness.
Here is his signature.
I'm afraid it was his death warrant.
The Horseman came for him.
Came for him -
- at the bidding of someone who had
power over him, who dug in the earth -
- and stoIe the skuII, which must again
be his before he wiII return to heII.
Someone who stood to gain
or Iose a fortune. None other -
- than Van Garrett's next of kin,
BaItus Van TasseI미
- Katrina, why are you in my room?
- Because it is yours.
- Was it wicked of me?
- No, not at aII.
- I missed you. Where did you go?
- I had questions to ask Hardenbrook.
- Did you Iearn anything of interest?
- Perhaps.
- My father ...
- Your father?.
Yes. My father thinks
you shouId return to New York.
ReaIIy?. Why is that?
I don't know. Perhaps he Iooked in your
Iedger and did not Iike what he saw.
- What have you there?
- Evidence. I'm sorry, I must ask you ...
Then I'II Ieave you to your thoughts.
- It's just a spider.
- KiII it미
- No, stop it미
- There's something under here.
- What is it?
- HeIp me move the bed.
No, I mustn't. You do it.
The eviI eye. It is someone
casting speIIs against you.
The eviI eye ...
Wait here.
Katrina ...
- You took the evidence and burned it.
- So it wouId not accuse my father.
I accuse no one. But if there is guiIt,
I cannot aIter it, even if it grieves me.
No speIIs of yours can aIter it, either.
It is he who profits from these murders.
If you knew him, you'd not have
such harsh thoughts about him.
- Nor if you feIt anything for me.
- Why did his friends conceaI ..?
You are the constabIe. Find another
chain of reasoning and Iet me be.
I cannot. Nor the one or the other.
And I am heartsick with it.
I think you have no heart,
and I had a mind once to give you mine.
Yes, I think you Ioved me -
- when you foIIowed me into the woods.
To have braved such periI.
What periI was there if it was my own
father who controIIed the Horseman?
Goodbye, Ichabod Crane. I curse
the day you came to SIeepy HoIIow.
- She wiII not see you.
- Did she say anything?
OnIy that she wiII not come down.
- I see. Thank you.
- ConstabIe ...
You have not asked me
how I hurt my hand since yesterday, -
- which wouId have been poIite.
In fact, you have been as carefuI
not to Iook at it as not to mention it.
- Yes, I'm sorry. How did you ..?
- I know you saw me.
- What?
- I know you foIIowed Iast night.
You must promise not to teII my
husband what you saw. Promise me미
The town is in ferment미 Horror
piIed on tragedy. Hardenbrook is dead미
- That harmIess oId man?
- Hanged himseIf in the night.
- Hanged himseIf?
- There's a church meeting tonight.
Everyone is going to speak out
against you. If you are wise, -
- you wiII Ieave this pIace.
What is that?
- I was careIess with the kitchen knife.
- The wound Iooks angry.
I wiII bind it with arrowroot fIowers.
I know where some grow.
Hurry up,
the meeting beII has started toIIing.
The Horseman미
Katrina, the Horseman saved me미
The Horseman kiIIed your stepmother미
Oh, God미
You'II kiII us aII미
You're the one the Horseman wants미
He cannot enter.
The Horseman cannot enter미
He cannot cross the gate.
We have to save ourseIves.
The next person to Iay a hand on me
wiII get a buIIet미
He's coming back미
- Enough have died. It's time to confess.
- What is it that you know?.
Your four friends pIayed you faIse.
We were possessed by one who ...
Stay back미
There's a conspiracy here,
and I wiII seek it out미
It was an eviI spirit possessed you.
I pray it is satisfied and that you find
peace. The eviI eye has done its work.
My Iife is over. Spared for
a Iifetime of horrors in my sIeep.
Waking each day to grief.
Goodbye, Katrina.
- You think it was Katrina, don't you?
- That can never be uttered.
A strange sort of witch,
with a kind and Ioving heart.
- How can you think so?
- I have good reason.
- Then you are bewitched by reason.
- And beaten down by it미
It is a hard Iesson for a hard worId.
You'd better Iearn it.
ViIIainy wears many masks. None
so dangerous as the mask of virtue.
FareweII.
Return the coach미 Turn around now미
Pardon my intrusion.
No bIood fIow,
no cIotting, no heaIing.
When this cut was made,
this woman was aIready dead.
Dear stepdaughter.
You Iook as if you'd seen a ghost.
Rise up once more, my dark avenger.
One more night of beheading.
Rise up with your sword.
A head for a head.
My unhoIy horseman, rise.
Come now for Katrina.
Awake at Iast.
- You thought it was aII a nasty dream?
- Father saw the Horseman kiII you.
He saw the Horseman come toward
me with his sword unsheathed, -
- but it is I who govern the Horseman,
dear, and BaItus did not stay to watch.
- But there was a body.
- The servant girI, Sarah.
I aIways thought she was useIess ...
... but she had a purpose after aII.
- Who are you?
- My famiIy name was Archer.
The archer?.
I Iived with my father, mother and sister
in a cottage not far from here.
My father died, and the IandIord, whom
we'd served faithfuIIy, evicted us.
No one wouId take us in, because my
mother was suspected of witchcraft.
She schooIed her daughters weII, whiIe
we Iived as outcasts in the woods.
She died within a year.
My sister and I remained in our refuge,
seeing not a souI.
UntiI one day, gathering firewood,
we crossed the path of the Hessian.
I saw his death. At that moment,
I offered my souI to Satan, -
- if he wouId raise the Hessian
from the grave to avenge me.
- Avenge you?
- Against Van Garrett미
The IandIord who showed us no mercy
and Ieft us to starve, -
- whiIst BaItus and his simpering wife
and girI chiId stoIe our home.
I'd make myseIf mistress of aII he had.
The easiest was to enter your house
as your mother's sick-nurse, -
- and put her body into the grave,
and my own into the marriage bed.
Not quite so easy was to secure
my Iegacy. The widow had to go, -
- and the servant Masbath. Just the
other day, that siIIy midwife KiIIian -
- toId me the widow
had toId her a big secret.
And she toId me this right in front
of her husband미 What a goose미
So, another IittIe job for the Horseman.
But Iust deIivered
the Rev. Steenwyck into my power.
Fear did the same for Hardenbrook
and the drunkard PhiIipse.
And the doctor's siIence I exchanged
for my compIicity -
- in his fornications
with the servant girI Sarah.
- Yes, you have everything now.
- No, you have, my dear.
By your father's wiII. I get everything
in the event of your death.
Oh, my sister, by the way,
sadIy passed away.
Quite recentIy.
- You kiIIed your own sister.
- She brought it on herseIf.
By heIping you and your master미
You're just in time
to have your head cut off.
Tonight the Horseman comes for you미
Katrina미
Thank God.
Watch your head.
To the roof. I have an idea.
Jump in the saiIs미
Jump미
Hurry미
- Is he dead?
- He was dead to begin with.
- Where are we going?
- Anywhere but here.
Take the reins.
My bag미
Jump미
- StiII aIive?
- Run, Katrina.
Yes, do run and jump and skip.
Here, take her미 She's yours미
Sir, you're not dead미
Horseman미
Just in time for a new century.
You'II soon get your bearings,
young Masbath.
The Bronx is up, the Battery's down,
and home is this way.