Even hunters help animals who lost
their way...
I will remain behind with them
if you decide to leave.
Bastard!
Don't you miss your mother?
...She would be proud of me.
Let's go together, as far as we can.
Why aren't we leaving? Yuan's
troops are coming!
Let's go.
Order them to carry the palanquin...
Quickly...
This palanquin is holding us back.
General...
Are we waiting for Yuan's
troops to join us?
- They ask you to give up the palanquin.
- Who said so?
Get out.
Order them to carry my palanquin at once!
Stop!
The enemy will catch us if we
allow her to ride on that palanquin.
Let us attack them first then.
Let's go.
It's foolish to chase those
who are chasing us.
I make the decisions here,
You just do as you're told.
Let's go.
Cavalry have less of an
advantage in the forest.
Keep pace a meter behind me.
If we lose track you will be
alone against the enemy.
Are you afraid?
Stay here until you hear something.
You can rush out then.
I will go down instead of you, General.
Watch the hill.
If we allow them to pass, the
Princess will be lost to us.
On my signal, everyone rush them.
Do exactly as i say, understand?
Dansaeng.
Yes.
Is that you?
We'll take care of things here.
Go and protect the Princess.
Look, Byuljang is coming.
This is very important.
Please make sure it is delivered.
Trust my husband.
Now, go.
They are coming!
Go, hurry!
Be careful!
Move, Princess!
The Princess is over there.
Stand back!
Stop it! Don't move!
Take away your filthy hands, you slave!
You could have killed me! I'm a Princess!
Stop screaming!
Don't assume you're better than
all of us because you're a Princess.
Leave me alone.
Take this.
Byuljang...
How are you feeling?
Where are my troops?
Help me up.
What happened to the enemy?
Daejung wiped out them with
the Joojin troops, sir.
What about the Princess?
She is safe, sir.
We will resume the journey
We are leaving.
It is quite late...
and you must rest a bit more, sir.
it's better leaving early in the morning, sir.
I said get up!
If you wish to leave, go by yourself, sir.
We will get some rest and then leave
You have been the agitator all along.
Up to now I've let you have your way...
but I tolerate it no longer.
- Leave him alone!
- Dochoong, Seat down...
General, please remove your sword.
How dare you!
Byuljang, arrest these men at once.
Now!
Look here...
Why don't we make Captain Daejung
as our leader from now on?
That's the only way we'll
reach the castle, right?
Dochoong!
General...
Pass your authority to Daejung.
You think we've come this far alone?
With everything swirling around us
someone has had to make the tough decisions.
Did you know that?
I made these decisions on
behalf of the group.
Anyone who tries to stop me will have their
throat slashed under the name of the king
General, you are still recovering...
Did you know the one I want
to kill the most...
...is you.
Why doesn't anyone stop the General?
General, come back!
You may lead these poor people,
but that doesn't change our situation.
Do you think all of
this happened because of him?
I am not bright enough to know the future.
We should have held onto the General.
The only thing I desire most
is for us all to go home.
We must leave!
Your highness, did you have a nightmare?
The fortress is not too far away,
we must leave now.
But your highness, everyone is asleep.
Don't worry too much
He couldn't have gone too far.
Even if he wanted to come back,
his pride will never let him do so.
This is Princess BuYong,
I am being chased by Yuan's soldiers.
I am headed towards the clay fortress.
Send the soldiers there immediately.
Wehae!
We will go around the forest.
We cannot sir.
If we don't go after them now,
we will lose them in the woods.
Their destination lies at the
end of the woods.
I vowed to return with the Princess.
We are all prepared to die in
the heat of the battle.
The Mongolian are not afraid of death!
Not afraid of death!
Be careful, you carry a child.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Daejung!
How are the wounds?
The poison in his body is almost neutraliZed.
- Why aren't you helping the general up?
- It is not necessary! I can get up by myself!
General, get up...
Do not call me a General anymore.
Regardless of what you say,
you are still a general.
You've led this group well.
Please come with us.
Come with me.
A well!
Where are all the boats?
Where are Ming's troops?
We came all this way because
of that bitch's words! Now what?
It's not the Princess's fault...
Then whose fault is it?
Was it yours?
Stop it! How could any
of us know this would happen?
Yuan's troops will be here soon.
Decide whether we leave or stay.
Let's leave this place.
Close the gates!
Go get a bar!
Hurry!
Call a man who can speak Korean.
Listen! For years, Korea has been
the vassal of the great Won Empire.
If you hand over the Princess,
we will let you all live.
Daejung, we are out matched.
The Princess is...
none of our concern anymore.
What they want is me.
You have kept your promise,
you have escorted me here.
There is no need for anymore
sacrifices for me.
If you refuse to hand her over,
we will destroy you all!
Daejung, you must decide.
Help us.
Huh? The gates are opening.
So the great fighter is still alive.
He ruined everything!
Those who wish to leave may do so.
Honey, honey!
Pitch the tents. We will prepare for battle.
Father!
Why the hell did you do that?
Daejung, I found the bamboos you wanted.
Hey! Get away, get away!
You still look pale.
It's alright, I wanna help you.
Water! Come get some!
We have water here!
We have water!
I'm so happy!
They are going to strike quickly.
First, they will attack the gate.
Then they'll surround us and climb in.
We have no defenses here.
General, please lead us.
I don't want to become a fool again.
Everyone knows why Koreans are
outstanding in defense of castles.
It is because they had excellent leaders.
General!
I will fight by myself.
I was the one who made us head to Korea.
I made us save the Princess...
I started this all.
Whether we go home or not,
fight for your name...
This is the time for all of us to unite.
It is none of your business.
This is my war.
Distribute liquor to the soldiers and
let them sleep until the sun is fully up.
We have to capture the Princess
and return to the base as soon as possible.
For the past three months,
we haven't had a single day's peace.
We need to attack them quickly!
What if Ming's troops come...
Only two people know were are here.
Us, and them.
How many of us will survive?
stay with me.
Wow! Thank you brother.
It is relatively safe at the coast and sides
of the castle. We need to protect the front.
Monk, take care of the Princess
and the elderly people.
The Interpreter and I will
take care the front gate.
You and Dochoong in the east
- Yeosol and HA-Il will protect in the west....
- Dochoong and I will cover the east
what about me, sir?
Dansaeng has something for you to do.
Don't come out, never! You hear?
Stay there.
You'll be in big trouble
if you make one move.
Don't come out...
Pull!
Whoa, you've made a ton of
spears haven't you.
Huh? They start to move...
Dochoong, don't shoot your arrows
without my signal!
Wait until they come closer!
Shoot!
Yuan's troops are coming!
Sit down!
Cut the ropes!
Attack!!
Don't retreat! Keep your place!!
Use your shields!
Break the fortress gate! Go!
Daejung, Hurry up!
General, the messenger has arrived!
Stop the attack.
We received orders to withdraw? Shit!
What the hell? We're about to win!
Kill them all!
Saori... Saori!
Look over there..,
A white flag at Yuan's side.
It is to mourn the death
of someone in high position.
If they attack again...
We don't have a chance at
holding them back.
General! Why did you
order us to withdraw?
Dig deep wells in the middle of the hill.
We were almost at victory!
Cookoo has passed away...
Right after we left headquarters.
We will hold a memorial ceremony first.
Then we will resume our attack.
Why did you leave your post?
Because of you, so
many people died!
Stop your god damn chanting!
Please stop crying.
We've beaten the enemy.
You family has been loyal
to the Ming empire...
for that the Emperor will reward you greatly.
Reward?!
You dragged us to die here!
First my husband, now my daughter!
How dare you speak like
that to the Princess!
You go! Then, we're all safe!
Because of you, we're all
going to die like dogs!
Byuljang!
What the hell are they doing?
The water channel is blocked
Everything will be over by tomorrow
Cookoo started a losing war.
The dreams of the great Ghengis Khan
have faded away forever.
Don't say that. Your words hold
great influence over the fighting sprit.
Let us return to the prairies.
You mean we should just leave like this?
No...the Princess will be with us.
The children are waiting for you.
Why are they looking for me?
I have no business with them, right?
You have nothing to be ashamed of.
You told me
that I was irresponsible, didn't you?
You were right.
I'm just a coward...a coward.
In this situation, it is more difficult
for one not to fight than to fight.
If you disagree to useless cruelty,
keep your conviction.
Don't you think that is also courage?
At one time,
I was a student of Confucianism,
dreaming of the righteous world.
But for a countryman like me,
I was not even given the chance to
apply for a position of a government official.
That is why I joined this journey.
No one else wanted to go.
I had to create an opportunity.
I always end up on the short end...why?
Pray for a hundred days to Buddha.
He will help you.
Does it really work?
Y should go to the children.
She is giving birth!
We need hot water...
What shall we do?
We don't even have drinking water.
What the hell you guys all doing here?
Get out, get out!
Isn't that Dansaeng?
Where is he going?
That son of bitch...
He is out of mind!
Dansaeng!
Call everyone over.
I'll go and get him.
What can we do?
Shit! Be careful!
There are thieves!
General, two men
stole water from our well.
What about Dansaeng?
Where is he?
Uh? He was right behind me!
Where is he? Uh, over there!
Dansaeng!
Dansaeng get up!
Give me that.
Dochoong
Throw the fire.
- Dansaeng!
- Hurry!
- Run! Run!
- Almost...
- Climb up!
Get the rope!
Climb up! Climb up!
Dansaeng!
Hurry up!
Wait!
What the hell he's doing?!
Dansaeng, come back!
Come on. Hurry up!
Get this one first!
Hurry up!
Pretty clever...
Do you want to try?
Dansaeng. That's alright...
Give me your hand.
No!!!
Dansaeng
Shit...Stop crying.
Let him cry.
How dare you come here, huh?
You want to kill us all?
Dochoong!
Give me back my eye!
Give it to me!
You told us you would give us a boat,
didn't you?
What good is the Princess of the Ming Empire
when she can't even get us a small boat!!
Your words brought us here.
where is the damned boat?!
Why did you hit me? Why??
Why the hell did you hit me?
Then, hit me! Hit me more!
Don't blame the Princess,
Everything was my decision.
The general will take responsibility?
How can you take responsibility
for a situation like this?
We just have to send the Princess out
alone - why can't we do that!?
Why?!
Why don't you just sent her out?!
That's enough...
Let me go, you son of a bitch!
Someone has to tell the
Princess about this!
Shut up!
Daejung! Don't stop them...
It's better them to say what's on their minds.
General, what are they talking about?
You are all cowards.
Then let's just cut the Princess's head off.
You keep out of this.
If we hang her head outside the fortress
wall, they might turn back.
If you all wish, I'll do that.
Interpreter, what's Yeesol saying?
I order you to tell me!
That you should be sent to the enemy.
Shut your mouth!
You want me to tell her
what he really said?
Do you understand how much
your words hurt her?
I only came all the way here for her.
Never wish for something
you can never get.
Don't forget you are a slave.
Have you ever heard of the slave,
Manjuk?
He said, 'People are all the equal.'
Are Kings of different blood
than any of us?
After saying those words, he was beheaded.
Whoever aims at my neck
will have their arm cut off first.
My sword carries no mercy.
Do you want a match?
Too many have died already, too many...
Now you want us to kill each other?
That is the last time you interfere.
I don't need your help any longer.
It's a boy!
Your highness. Please.
Bless this child
for luck and health.
What are you doing here?
Do you want him to freeze?
- She only cares for herself.
- She doesn't deserve to hold the child...
Hurry and take the child inside,
Before he catches cold.
Your highness...
Please forgive me.
Bring me a horse.
I am leaving this fortress.
Stop this, your highness.
You are what we are fighting for.
Don't you see that everybody wants
me to leave as soon as possible?
As the Princess of the Great Ming Empire,
I will end this war with my own hands.
Your highness,
please don't go...Please.
Do you want me to take
my own life right here?
No one may step forward.
I will go by myself.
General...
Get out of my way.
The Koreans won't give up,
your highness.
Please trust me!
How dare you block me?
Let us wait...
they are coming towards us.
You can't go.
Will you watch guard
outside the fortress?
Kill him!
Wait.
Let him pick up his sword.
What happened to the others?
What about Yeesol?
Just stay where you are.
Daejung, Daejung
You can't move sir, not now.
Stay still.
The royal castle was too suffocating...
I thought that if I left
there I would be free.
This is all my fault.
I'm so scared.
I don't think I can bear it any longer.
Neither can I.
I'm nothing but a cowward.
I was always afraid...
...that people would notice that.
I do not deserve being called General.
Everyone come here!
Is he dead?
Wait, he's moving...
I'm not sure how long he's got.
General,
what is the meaning of this?
When they open the gate doors
to rescue him, we'll rush them.
If they decide not to come for him,
we keep their best warrior.
Is anyone going to save him?
- I'll go down to get him.
- General...
if we open the door now
we'll all die.
It's a trap.
So you're saying we stand
back and do nothing?
That's the only way.
It is better for him to die
quickly by our own hand.
Should I throw the torch?
The moonlight is bright enough.
Daejung... Daejung
Don't shoot.
You like him too, don't you?
Daejung.
Do you still consider me General?
I want to lead the battle tomorrow.
Up till now,
we have gone through so much.
It is a miracle
that we've made it this far.
I remember
an old Chinese proverb -
'If we attempt to live, we die,
if we attempt to die, we live.'
Let us trust each other and unite.
Even if we all die...
Tomorrow they will break
through the gate and enter.
When they come in
we will use these bombs.
Be careful.
Come here...
Everyone, stand up.
Tomorrow,
we will protect you, your highness.
Do you wish to become
a general in the Yuan Empire?
I am a free man...kill me.
They never took your
existence seriously.
In order to rebuild the Yuan Empire,
we need courageous warriors like you.
~ the morning mountain home,
white bird sings a song ~
~ I want to hear the song,
wish to go back home ~
Sir, you resemble my father
who had passed away.
The Koreans and the Hans look
very much alike. We're like brothers.
We're like brothers.
This has gone on too long...
everyone will die.
Before sunset comes
we return to the prairie.
No, no, wait a minute.
Fire, fire, fire! They're using fire first!
Don't move.
Everyone run for cover!
General...
we've failed.
Daejung....
Let us have an honorable death.
That is my wish.
Jaosinwe! Jaosinwe!
We must go out and fight together!
Dochoong!
Dochoong...
Protect the Princess
Leave this fortress with her!
So many warriors have died
because of you!
Yesol...
My son...
It's too dangerous
You cannot cross the sea with that boat.
I must go.
Only those who have a long journey
will see the long roads to go home