Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 19.02.24 13:58:39
太初有道， In the beginning, the Word already existed.
道与　神魂在， The Word was with God...
道就是  神.(1:1) and the Word was God.
这道太初与　神魂在。(1:2) From the very beginning,  the Word was with God.
万物是藉着他造的； Through him God made all things.
凡被造的，没有一样不是藉着他造的。(1:3) Not one thing in all creation  was made without him.
生命在他里头， The Word was the source of life...
这生命就是?的光。(1:4) and this life brought light to people.
光照在黑暗里， The light shines in the darkness...
黑暗?不接受光。(1:5) and the darkness has never put it out.
有一个?，是从　神那里差来的， God sent his messenger...
名叫约翰。(1:6) a man named John...
这?来，为要作见证，就是为光作见证， who came to tell people about the light...
叫众?因他可以信。(1:7) so that all should hear the message  and believe.
他不是那光，乃是要为光作见证。(1:8) He himself was not the light.  He came to tell about the light.
那光是真光， This was the real light...
照亮一?生在世上的?。(1:9) the light that comes into the world  and shines on all people.
他在世界， The Word was in the world...
世界也是藉着他造的， and though God made the world  through him...
世界?不?识他。(1:10) yet the world did not recognize him.
他到自己的地方来， He came to his own country...
自己的?倒不接待他。(1:11) but his own people did not receive him.
凡接待他的，就是信他名的?， Some, however, did receive him  and believed in him...
他就赐他们?柄，作　神的儿女。(1:12) so he gave them the right  to become God's children.
这等?不是从血?生的，不是从?欲生的， They did not become God's children  by natural means...
也不是从?意生的， that is, by being born  as the children of a human father.
乃是从　神生的。 God himself...
乃是从　神生的。(1:13) was their father.
道成了?身， The Word became a human being...
住在我们中间，充充满满地有恩典，有真理。 and full of grace and truth, lived among us.
我们也见过他的?光， We saw his glory...
正是父独生子的?光。(1:14) the glory which he received  as the Father's only Son.
约翰为他作见证，喊着说： John spoke about him.
“这就是我曾说： This is the one  I was talking about when I said:
‘那在我以后来的， "He comes after me...
反成了在我以?的， "but he is greater than I am...
因他本来在我以?。’”(1:15) "because he existed before I was born!"
从他丰满的恩典里，我们都领受了，  Out of the fullness of his grace,  he has blessed us all...
而?恩上加恩。(1:16) giving us one blessing after another.
律法本是藉着摩西传的， God gave the Law through Moses...
恩典和真理 but grace and truth...
都是批耶稣基督来的。(1:17) came through Jesus Christ.
从来没有?看见　神， No one has ever seen God.
只有在父怀里的独生子 The only Son, who is the same as God...
只有在父怀里的独生子 and is at the Father's side...
将他表明出来。(1:18) he has made him known.
(约翰所作的见证记在下面：)漠太?从耶路?冷差祭司和利未?到约翰那里， The Jewish authorities in Jerusalem  sent some priests and Levites to John.
问他说：“你是谁？” (1:19) Who are you?
他就明说，并不隐瞒；明说：  John did not refuse to answer,  but spoke out openly and clearly.
“我不是基督。”(1:20) 他们又问他说：“这样，你是谁呢？ -I am not the Messiah.  -Who are you then?
是以利亚吗？”他说：“我不是。” -Are you Elijah?  -No, I'm not.
“是那先知吗？”他回答说：“不是。”(1:21) -Are you the Prophet?  -No.
于是他们说：“你到底是谁？ Then tell us who you are.
叫我们好回覆差我们来的?。 We have to take an answer back  to those who sent us.
你自己说，你是谁？” (1:22) What do you say about yourself?
他说： John answered  by quoting the prophet, Isaiah.
“我就是那在旷野有?声喊着说： "I am the voice of someone  shouting in the desert:
‘囊直主的道路’，正?先知以?亚所说的。”(1:23)  "'Make a straight path  for the Lord to travel!"'
那些?是法利??差来的（注：或作“那差来的是法利??”）。　 (1:24) 他们就问他说： The messengers, who had been sent  by the Pharisees, then asked John:
“你既不是基督，不是以利亚，也不是那先知， If you are not the Messiah,  nor Elijah, nor the Prophet...
为什么施洗呢？” (1:25) why do you baptize?
约翰回答说：“我是用水施洗， I baptize with water.
但有一位站在你们中间，是你们不?识的，(1:26) But among you  stands the one you do not know.
就是那在我以后来的， He is coming after me.
我给他解鞋带也不配。”  But I am not good enough...
我给他解鞋带也不配。” (1:27) even to untie his sandals.
这是在约旦河外伯大尼（注：有古卷作“伯大巴喇”）， All this happened in Bethany,  on the east side of the Jordan River...
约翰施洗的地方作的见证。 (1:28) where John was baptizing.
次?，约翰看见耶稣来到他那里， The next day,  John saw Jesus coming to him.
就说：“看哪，　神的羔羊， There is the Lamb of God...
除?（注：或作“背负”）世?罪孽的。 (1:29) who takes away the sin of the world.
这就是我曾说 This is the one I was talking about  when I said:
‘有一位在我以后来， "A man is coming after me...
反成了在我以?的，因他本来在我以?。’(1:30) "but he is greater than I am,  because he existed before I was born."
我先?不?识他， I did not know who he would be.
?今我来用水施洗， But I came baptizing with water...
为要叫他显明给以色列?。” (1:31) in order to make him known  to the people of Israel.
约翰又作见证说： And John gave this testimony:
“我曾看见圣灵仿佛鸽子从天降下，住在他的身上。 (1:32) I saw the Spirit come down,  like a dove from heaven, and stay on him.
我先?不?识他，只是那 I still did not know that he was the one.  But God...
差我来用水施洗的，对我说： who sent me to baptize with water,  had said to me:
‘你看见圣灵降下来，住在谁的身上， "You will see the Spirit come down  and stay on a man.
谁就是用圣灵施洗的。’ (1:33) "He is the one  who baptizes with the Holy Spirit. "
我看见了，就证明 I have seen it, and I tell you...
这是　神的儿子。” (1:34) that he is the Son of God.
再次?，约翰魂两个门徒站在那里。 (1:35) The next day, John was standing there  again with two of his disciples...
他见耶稣行走， when he saw Jesus walking by.
就说：“看哪，这是　神的羔羊!” (1:36) There is the Lamb of God.
两个门徒听见他的话， The two disciples heard him say this...
就跟从了耶稣。(1:37) and went with Jesus.
耶稣转过身来，看见他们跟着， Jesus turned, saw them following him.
就问他们说：“你们要什么？ What are you looking for?
”他们说：“拉比（“拉比”翻出来就是“夫子”），在哪里住？”  Where do you live, Rabbi?
”他们说：“拉比（“拉比”翻出来就是“夫子”），在哪里住？” (1:38) This word means "teacher. "
耶稣说：“你们来看。” Come and see.
他们就?看他在哪里住，这一天便与他魂住。那时约有申正了。 It was then about 4.:00 in the afternoon...
他们就?看他在哪里住，这一天便与他魂住。那时约有申正了。 so they went with him  and saw where he lived...
他们就?看他在哪里住，这一天便与他魂住。那时约有申正了。(1:39) and spent the rest of that day with him.
听见约翰的话，跟从耶稣的那两个?， One of them was Andrew...
一个是西门彼得的兄弟安得烈。(1:40) Simon Peter's brother.
他先找着自己的哥哥西门， At once, he found his brother Simon.
对他说：“我们遇见弥?亚了 We have found the Messiah.
（“弥?亚”翻出来就是“基督”）！” (1:41) This word means "Christ. "
Come.
于是领他?见耶稣。 Then he took Simon to Jesus.
耶稣看着他说： Jesus looked at him.
“你是约翰的儿子西门（注：“约翰”马太16章17节称“约拿”）， Your name is Simon, son of John...
你要称为矶法 but you will be called Cephas.
（“矶法”翻出来就是“彼得”）。” (1:42) This is the same as Peter,  and means "a rock. "
又次?，耶稣想要往加利利?， The next day,  Jesus decided to go to Galilee.
遇见腓力， He found Philip...
就对他说： and said to him.:
“来，跟从我吧!” (1:43) Come with me.
这腓力是伯?大?，和安得烈、彼得魂城。 (1:44) Philip was from Bethsaida,  the town where Andrew and Peter lived.
腓力找着拿但业， Philip found Nathanael.
对他说：“摩西在律法上所写的 We have found the one whom  Moses wrote about in the Book of the Law...
和众先知所记的那一位，我们遇见了， and whom the prophets also wrote about.
就是约瑟的儿子拿?勒?耶稣。” (1:45) He is Jesus, son of Joseph, from Nazareth.
拿但业对他说：“拿?勒还能出什么好的吗？”腓力说：“你来看！” (1:46) -Can anything good come from Nazareth?  -Come and see.
耶稣看见拿但业来，就指着他说： When Jesus saw Nathanael coming to him,  he said about him:
“看哪，这是个真以色列?， "Here is a real Israelite. "
他心里是没有诡诈的。” (1:47) There is nothing false in him.
拿但业对耶稣说：“你从哪里知道我呢？” How do you know me?
耶稣回答说：“腓力还没有招呼你，你在无花果树底下，我就看见你了。” (1:48) I saw you when you were under the fig tree  before Philip called you.
拿但业说：“拉比， Teacher...
你是　神的儿子， you are the Son of God.
你是以色列的王！” (1:49) You are the King of Israel.
耶稣对他说：“因为我说在无花果树底下看见你，你就信吗？ Do you believe just because I told you  I saw you when you were under the fig tree?
你将要看见比这更大的事。” (1:50) You will see much greater things than this.
又说：“我实实在在的告诉你们， I am telling you the truth.
你们将要看见天开了， You will see heaven open...
神的使者上?下来在?子身上。” (1:51) and God's angels going up  and coming down on the Son of Man.
第??，在加利利的迦拿有??的筵席， Two days later, there was a wedding  in the town of Cana in Galilee.
耶稣的母?在那里。 (2:1) Jesus' mother was there...
耶稣和他的门徒也被??赴席。(2:2) and Jesus and his disciples  had also been invited to the wedding.
酒用尽了， When the wine had given out...
耶稣的母?对他说：“他们没有酒了。” (2:3) Jesus' mother said to him,  "They are out of wine. "
耶稣说：“母?（注：原文作“妇?”）， Madam...
我与你有什么相干？ what do you have to do with this?
我的时候还没有到。” (2:4) My time has not yet come.
他母?对用?说：“他告诉你们什么，你们就做什么。”　 (2:5) Do whatever he tells you.
照漠太?洁净的规矩， The Jews have rules about ritual washing...
有六口石缸摆在那里， and for this purpose,  six stone water jars were there...
每口可以盛两?桶水。 (2:6) each one large enough  to hold between 20 and 30 gallons.
耶稣对用?说：“把缸倒满了水。” Fill these jars with water.
他们就倒满了，直到缸口。(2:7) They filled them to the brim.
耶稣又说：“现在可以舀出来，送给管筵席的。” Now draw some water out,  and take it to the man in charge of the feast.
他们就送了?。(2:8) They took him the water,  which now had turned into wine...
管筵席的尝了那水变的酒， and he tasted it.
并不知道是哪里来的， He did not know  where this wine had come from...
只有舀水的用?知道。 but, of course, the servants  who had drawn out the water knew.
管筵席的便叫新郎来，(2:9) So he called the bridegroom.
对他说：“?都是先摆上好酒，等客喝足了， Everyone else serves the best wine first,  and after the guests have drunk a lot...
才摆上次的；你倒把好酒留到?今！” (2:10) he serves the ordinary wine.  But you have kept the best wine until now.
这是耶稣所行的头一件神?，是在加利利的迦拿行的， Jesus performed this first miracle  in Cana in Galilee.
显出他的?耀来，他的门徒就信他了。(2:11) There he revealed his glory,  and his disciples believed in him.
这事以后，耶稣与他的母?、弟兄和门徒 After this, Jesus and his mother, brothers,  and disciples...
都下迦百农?，在那里住了不多几?。 (2:12) went to Capernaum  and stayed there a few days.
漠太?的逾越节近了，耶稣就上耶路?冷?。　(2:13) It was almost time for the Passover Festival,  so Jesus went to Jerusalem.
看见殿里 There, in the Temple...
有卖牛、羊、鸽子的， he found people selling cattle,  sheep and pigeons...
并有兑换银?的?坐在那里。(2:14) and also the moneychangers  sitting at their tables.
耶稣就拿绳子做成鞭子， So he made a whip from cords and  drove all the animals out of the Temple...
把牛羊都赶出殿?， both the sheep and the cattle.
倒出兑换银?之?的银?，推翻他们的桌子。 He overturned the tables  of the moneychangers...
倒出兑换银?之?的银?，推翻他们的桌子。(2:15) and scattered their coins.
又对卖鸽子的说： And he ordered those who sold pigeons:
“把这些东西拿?！ Take them out of here!
不要将我父的殿当作买卖的地方。” (2:16) Stop making my Father's house  a marketplace!
他的门徒就想?经上记着说： His disciples remembered  that the scripture says:
“我为你的殿，心里焦急，?魂火烧。” (2:17) "My devotion to your house, O God,  burns in me like a fire. "
因此漠太?问他说： The Jewish authorities came back at him  with a question:
“你既做这些事，还显什么神?给我们看呢？” (2:18) What miracle can you perform to show us  that you have the right to do this?
耶稣回答说：“你们拆毁这殿，我??内要再建立?来。” (2:19) Tear down this temple,  and in three days I will build it again.
漠太?便说：“这殿是四十六年才造成的，你??内就再建立?来吗？” Are you going to build it again  in three days?
漠太?便说：“这殿是四十六年才造成的，你??内就再建立?来吗？” (2:20) It has taken 46 years to build this temple.
但耶稣这话， But the temple Jesus was speaking about...
是以他的身伐为殿。 (2:21) was his body.
所以到他从死里复活以后， So when he was raised from death...
门徒就想?他说过这话， his disciples remembered  that he had said this...
便信了圣经和耶稣所说的。(2:22) and they believed the scripture,  and what Jesus had said.
当耶稣在耶路?冷过逾越节的时候， While Jesus was in Jerusalem  during the Passover Festival...
有许多?看见他所行的神?，就信了他的名。(2:23)  many believed in him  as they saw the miracles he performed.
耶稣?不将自己交托他们，因为他知道万?； (2:24) But Jesus did not trust himself to them,  because he knew them all.
也用不着谁见证?怎样， There was no need for anyone  to tell him about them...
因他知道?心里所存的。(2:25) because he himself knew  what was in their hearts.
有一个法利??，名叫尼哥德慕， There was a Jewish leader  named Nicodemus...
是漠太?的官。 (3:1) who belonged to the party of the Pharisees.
这?夜里来见耶稣， One night, he went to Jesus.
说：“拉比， Rabbi, we know...
我们知道你是批　神那里来作师傅的， that you are a teacher sent by God.
因为你所行的神?，?没有　神魂在，无?能行。” (3:2) No one could perform the miracles  you are doing, unless God were with him.
耶稣回答说：“我实实在在地告诉你： I am telling you the truth.
??不重生， No one can see the kingdom of God...
就不能见　神的国。” (3:3) without being born again.
尼哥德慕说：“?已经老了，?何能重生呢？ How can a grown man be born again?
?能再进母腹生出来吗？” (3:4) He certainly cannot enter his mother's womb  and be born a second time.
耶稣说：“我实实在在地告诉你： I am telling you the truth.
??不是从水和圣灵生的，就不能进　神的国。(3:5) No one can enter the kingdom of God  without being born of water and the Spirit.
从?身生的，就是?身； A person is born physically  of human parents...
从灵生的，就是灵。 (3:6) but is born spiritually of the Spirit.
我说‘你们必须重生’，你不要以为希?。(3:7) Do not be surprised because I tell you  that you must all be born again.
风随着意思吹， The wind blows wherever it wishes.
你听见风的响声， You hear the sound it makes...
?不晓得从哪里来，往哪里?； but you do not know where it comes from,  or where it is going.
凡从圣灵生的，也是?此。” (3:8) It is like that with everyone  who is born of the Spirit.
尼哥德慕问他说：“怎能有这事呢？” (3:9) How can this be?
耶稣回答说：“你是以色列?的先生， You are a great teacher in Israel...
还不明白这事吗？ (3:10) and you don't know this?
我实实在在地告诉你： I am telling you the truth.
我们所说的，是我们知道的；我们所见证的，是我们见过的； We speak of what we know,  and report what we have seen.
你们?不领受我们的见证。 (3:11) Yet none of you is willing  to accept our message.
我对你们说地上的事，你们尚?不信； You do not believe me when I tell you  about the things of this world.
?说天上的事，?何能信呢？(3:12) How will you ever believe me, then,  when I tell you about the things of heaven?
除了从天降下?旧在天的?子， And no one has ever gone up to heaven...
没有?升过天。 (3:13) except the Son of Man,  who came down from heaven.
摩西在旷野怎样举蛇， As Moses lifted up the bronze snake  on a pole in the desert...
?子也必照样被举?来， (3:14) in the same way,  the Son of Man must be lifted up...
叫一?信他的都得永生（注：或作“叫一?信的?在他里面得永生”）。 (3:15) so that everyone who believes in him  may have eternal life.
神爱世?，甚至将他的独生子赐给他们， For God loved the world so much  that He gave his only Son...
叫一?信他的，不至灭亡，反得永生。 (3:16) so that everyone who believes in him  may not die, but have eternal life.
因为　神差他的儿子降世，不是要定世?的罪（注：或作“诀判世? ”。下魂），乃是要叫世?因他得救。 (3:17) For God did not send his Son into the world  to be its judge, but to be its savior.
信他的?，不被定罪； Those who believe in the Son  are not judged.
不信的?，罪已经定了， But those who do not believe  have already been judged...
因为他不信　神独生子的名。  because they have not believed  in God's only Son.
因为他不信　神独生子的名。 (3:18) This is how the judgment works:
光来到世间， The light has come into the world...
世?因自己的行为是恶的， but people love the darkness  rather than the light...
不爱光倒爱黑暗，定他们的罪就是在此。(3:19) because their deeds are evil.
凡作恶的便恨光，并不来就光， Those who do evil things hate the light  and will not come to the light...
恐怕他的行为受责备； (3:20) because they do not want their evil deed  to be shown up.
但行真理的必来就光， But those who do what is true  come to the light...
要显明他所行的是靠　神而行。” (3:21) in order that the light may show  that what they did was in obedience to God.
这事以后，耶稣和门徒到了漠太地， After this, Jesus and his disciples  went to the province of Judaea...
在那里居住施洗。(3:22) where he spent some time with them,  and baptized.
约翰在靠近?冷的 John also was baptizing in Aenon...
哀嫩也施洗， not far from Salim...
因为那里水多， because there was plenty of water  in that place.
众?都?受洗。 (3:23) People were going to him,  and he was baptizing them.
那时约翰还没有下在监里 。 (3:24) This was before John  had been put in prison.
约翰的门徒和一个漠太?辩论 Some of John's disciples  began arguing with a Jew...
洁净的礼，(3:25) about the matter of ritual washing.
就来见约翰说：“拉比， Teacher...
从?魂你在约旦河外、 you remember the man who was with you  on the east side of Jordan...
你所见证的那位， the one you spoke about?
现在施洗，众?都往他那里?了。” (3:26) He is baptizing now,  and everyone's going to him.
约翰说：“?不是从天上赐的，?就不能得什么。 (3:27) No one can have anything  unless God gives it.
我曾说‘我不是基督，是奉差?在他?面的’，你们自己可以给我作见证。  You yourselves are my witnesses,  that I said:
我曾说‘我不是基督，是奉差?在他?面的’，你们自己可以给我作见证。 (3:28) "I am not the Messiah,  but I have been sent ahead of him."
?新妇的就是新郎， The bridegroom is the one to whom  the bride belongs.
新郎的朋友  but the bridegroom's friend...
站着听见新郎的声音就甚喜乐， who stands by and listens, is glad  when he hears the bridegroom's voice.
故此我这喜乐满足了。(3:29) This is how my own happiness  is made complete.
他必兴旺，我必衰微。(3:30) He must become more important  while I become less important.
从天上来的，是在万有之上； He who comes from above  is greater than all.
从地上来的，是属乎地， He who is from the earth  belongs to the earth...
他所说的也是属乎地。 and speaks about earthly matters...
从天上来的是在万有之上。(3:31) but he who comes from heaven is above all.
他将所见所闻的见证出来， He tells what he has seen and heard...
只是没有?领受他的见证。 (3:32) yet no one accepts his message.
那领受他见证的，  But whoever accepts his message...
就印上印，证明　神是真的。 (3:33) confirms by this that God is truthful.
神所差来的，就说　神的话， The one whom God has sent  speaks God's words...
因为　神赐圣灵给他，是没有限量的。 (3:34) because God gives him  the fullness of his Spirit.
父爱子，已将万有交在他手里。(3:35) The Father loves his Son,  and has put everything in his power.
信子的?有永生； Whoever believes in the Son has eternal life.
不信子的?得不着永生（注：原文作“不得见永生 ”），　 Whoever disobeys the Son  will not have life...
神的震怒常在他身上。” (3:36) but will remain under God's punishment.
主知道法利??听见他收门徒施洗比约翰还多 (4:1) The Pharisees heard that Jesus was winning  and baptizing more disciples than John.
（?实不是耶稣?自施洗，乃是他的门徒施洗。） (4:2) Actually, Jesus himself did not  baptize anyone. Only his disciples did.
So when Jesus heard what was being said...
他就离了漠太，又往加利利?。 (4:3) he left Judea and went back to Galilee.
必须经过?马利亚， (4:4) On his way there,  he had to go through Samaria.
于是到了?马利亚的一座城，名叫叙加， In Samaria,  he came to a town named Sychar...
靠近雅各给他儿子约瑟的那块地。 (4:5) which was not far from the field  that Jacob had given to his son, Joseph.
在那里有雅各井。 Jacob's well was there...
耶稣因走路困乏，就坐在井旁。 and Jesus, tired out by the trip...
所以他坐在井边休息. sat down by the well.
那时约有午正。(4:6) It was about noon.
有一个?马利亚的妇?来打水， A Samaritan woman  came to draw some water.
耶稣对她说：“?你给我水喝。”(4:7) Give me a drink of water.
那时门徒进城买食物?了。(4:8) His disciples had gone into town  to buy food.
?马利亚的妇?对他说：“你既是漠太?， You're a Jew, and I'm a Samaritan.
怎么向我一个?马利亚妇?要水喝呢？” So how can you ask me for a drink?
原来漠太?和?马利亚?没有来往。 (4:9) Jews will not use the same cups and bowls  that Samaritans use.
耶稣回答说：“你?知道　神的恩赐 If you only knew what God gives...
和对你说‘给我水喝’的是谁，你必早?他，  and who it is that is asking you for a drink,  you would ask him...
他也必早给了你活水。”(4:10) and he would give you life-giving water.
妇?说：“先生，没有打水的?具，井又深， Sir, you don't have a bucket,  and the well is deep.
你从哪里得活水呢？ (4:11) Where would you get that life-giving water?
我们的祖宗雅各将这井留给我们， It was our ancestor Jacob  who gave us this well.
他自己和儿子并牲畜也都喝这井里的水， He and his children and his flocks  all drank from it.
难道你比他还大吗？” (4:12) You don't claim to be greater than Jacob,  do you?
耶稣回答说：“凡喝这水的，还要再渴； (4:13) Those who drink this water  will get thirsty again...
??喝我所赐的水，就永远不渴。 but those who drink the water  that I give them will never be thirsty again.
我所赐的水要在他里头成为?源， The water that I will give them  will become, in them, a spring...
直涌到永生。” (4:14) which will provide them with  life-giving water, and give them eternal life.
妇?说：“先生，?把这水赐给我，叫我不渴， Sir, give me that water.  Then I will never be thirsty again...
也不用来这么远打水。” (4:15) nor will I have to come here to draw water.
耶稣说：“你?叫你丈夫也到这里来。” (4:16) Go and call your husband, and come back.
妇?说：“我没有丈夫。” I don't have a husband.
耶稣说：“你说没有丈夫，是不错的。(4:17) You're right when you say  you don't have a husband.
你已经有五个丈夫， You've been married to five men...
你现在有的，并不是你的丈夫， and the man you live with now  is not really your husband.
你这话是真的。” (4:18) You've told me the truth.
妇?说：“先生，我看出你是先知。(4:19) I see you are a prophet, sir.
我们的祖宗在这山上礼拜， My Samaritan ancestors worshipped God  on this mountain...
你们倒说，应当礼拜的地方是在耶路?冷。” (4:20) but you Jews say that Jerusalem is the place  where we should worship God.
耶稣说：“妇?，你当信我。 Believe me, woman...
时候将到，你们拜父也不在这山上， a time will come when people won't worship  the Father either on this mountain...
也不在耶路?冷。 (4:21) or in Jerusalem.
你们所拜的，你们不知道； You Samaritans do not really know  whom you worship.
我们所拜的，我们知道， But we Jews know whom we worship...
因为救恩是从漠太?出来的。 (4:22) because it is from the Jews  that salvation comes.
时候将到， But the time is coming...
?今就是了。 and is already here...
那真正拜父的，要用心灵和诚实拜他， when, by the power of God's Spirit...
那真正拜父的，要用心灵和诚实拜他， people will worship the Father  as he really is...
因为父要这样的?拜他。(4:23) offering him the true worship that he wants.
神是个灵（注：或无“个”字）， God is Spirit.
所以拜他的，必须用心灵和诚实拜他。” And only by the power of his Spirit...
所以拜他的，必须用心灵和诚实拜他。” (4:24) can people worship him as he really is.
妇?说：“我知道弥?亚（就是那称为基督的）要来， I know that the Messiah will come.
他来了，必将一?的事都告诉我们。” (4:25) And when he comes,  he will tell us everything.
耶稣说：“这和你说话的就是他。”  I am he.
耶稣说：“这和你说话的就是他。” (4:26) I, who am talking with you.
当下门徒回来， At that moment, Jesus' disciples returned...
就希?耶稣和一个妇?说话。 and they were greatly surprised  to find him talking with a woman.
只是没有?说：“你是要什么？” But none of them said to her,  "What do you want?"
或说：“你为什么和她说话？”(4:27)"  Or asked him,  "Why are you talking with her?"
那妇?就留下水罐子，往城里?，对众?说：(4:28) Then the woman left her water jar  and went back to the town.
“你们来看！有一个?将我素来所行的一?事都给我说出来了， Come and see the man who told me  everything I have ever done.
莫阏饩褪腔督吗？” (4:29) Could he be the Messiah?
众?就出城往耶稣那里?。 (4:30) So they left the town, and went to Jesus.
这?间，门徒对耶稣说： In the meantime,  the disciples were begging Jesus:
“拉比，?颈。” (4:31) 耶稣说：“  "Teacher, have something to eat!"  But he answered:
我有食物颈，是你们不知道的。”(4:32) I have food to eat  that you know nothing about.
门徒就彼此对问说： So the disciples  started asking among themselves.:
“莫阌?拿什么给他颈吗？”(4:33) "Could somebody have brought him food?"
耶稣说：“我的食物就是遵行差我来者的旨意， My food is to obey the will  of the one who sent me...
做成他的工。(4:34) and to finish the work he gave me to do.
你们?不说‘到收割的时候还有四个月’吗？ You have a saying,  "Four more months, and then the harvest."
我告诉你们：举目向田观看， But I tell you, take a good look at the fields.
庄稼已经熟了（注：原文作“发白”），可以收割了。 (4:35) The crops are now ripe  and ready to be harvested.
收割的?得工价，积蓄五谷到永生， The one who reaps the harvest is being paid  and gathers the crops for eternal life.
叫?种的和收割的一魂快乐。(4:36) So the one who plants  and the one who reaps will be glad together.
俗语说‘那??种，这?收割’，这话可见是真的。　(4:37) For the saying is true.  Someone plants, someone else reaps.
我差你们?收你们所没有劳苦的，”  I have sent you to reap a harvest  in a field where you did not work.
别?劳苦， Others worked there...
你们享受他们所劳苦的。(4:38) and you profit from their work.
那城里有好些?马利亚?信了耶稣， Many of the Samaritans in that town  believed in Jesus...
因为那妇?作见证说：“他将我素来所行的一?事都给我说出来了。” (4:39) because the woman had said,  "He told me everything I have ever done. "
于是?马利亚?来见耶稣， So when the Samaritans came to him...
?他在他们那里住下， they begged him to stay with them...
他便在那里住了两天。(4:40) and Jesus stayed there two days.
因耶稣的话，信的?就更多了。(4:41) 便对妇?说： Many more believed because of  his message, and they told the woman.:
“现在我们信，不是因为你的话， "We believe now,  not because of what you said...
是我们?自听见了， "but because we ourselves have heard him...
知道这真是救世主。”(4:42) "and we know  that he really is the Savior of the world. "
过了那两天， After spending two days there...
耶稣离了那地方，往加利利?。(4:43) Jesus left, and went to Galilee.
因为耶稣自己作过见证说： For he himself had said:
“先知在本地是没有?尊敬的。” (4:44) "Prophets are not respected  in their own country. "
到了加利利， When he arrived in Galilee,  the people there welcomed him...
加利利?既?看见他在耶路?冷过节所行的一?事，就接待他，因为他们也是上?过节。 because they had gone  to the Passover Festival in Jerusalem...
加利利?既?看见他在耶路?冷过节所行的一?事，就接待他，因为他们也是上?过节。 (4:45) and had seen everything that he had done  during the festival.
耶稣又到了加利利的迦拿， Then Jesus went back to Cana in Galilee...
就是他从?变水为酒的地方。 where he had turned the water into wine.
有一个大臣，他的儿子在迦百农患病。 (4:46) A government official was there,  whose son was sick in Capernaum.
他听见耶稣从漠太到了加利利， When he heard that Jesus had come  from Judea to Galilee...
就来见他， he went to him...
?他下?医治他的儿子， and asked him to go to Capernaum...
因为他儿子快要死了。(4:47) and heal his son, who was about to die.
耶稣就对他说：“?不看见神??事，你们总是不信。” (4:48) None of you will ever believe  unless you see miracles and wonders.
那大臣说：“先生，?你趁着我的孩子还没有死  Sir, come with me...
就下?。”(4:49) before my child dies.
耶稣对他说：“回?吧！ Go.
你的儿子活了。” Your son will live.
那?信耶稣所说的话，就回?了。(4:50) The man believed Jesus' words and went.
正下?的时候，他的??迎见他， On his way home,  his servants met him with the news.
说他的儿子活了。 (4:51) Your boy is going to live!
他就问什么时候见好的。 He asked them what time it was  when his son got better.
他们说：“昨?未时?就退了。” (4:52) It was 1 :00 yesterday afternoon  when the fever left him!
他便知道这正是耶稣对他说 Then the father remembered that it was  at that very hour when Jesus had told him:
“你儿子活了”的时候； Your son will live.
他自己和?家就都信了。 (4:53) So he and all his family believed.
这是耶稣在加利利行的第二件神?， This was the second miracle...
是他从漠太回?以后行的。 (4:54) that Jesus performed  after coming from Judea to Galilee.
这事以后，到了漠太?的一个节?，耶稣就上耶路?冷?。(5:1) After this, Jesus went to Jerusalem  for a religious festival.
在耶路?冷，靠近羊门有一个池子，希伯来话叫作毕士大， Near the Sheep Gate in Jerusalem,  there is a pool with five porches.
旁边有五个廊子。(5:2) In Hebrew, it is called Bethzatha.
里面躺着 A large crowd of sick people  were lying on the porches...
瞎眼的、?腿的、血?枯干的许多病?。（注：有古卷在此有“等候水动， (5:3) 因为有天使按时下池子搅动那水，水动之后，谁先下?，无论害什么病就?愈了。”） (5:4) the blind, the lame, and the paralyzed.
在那里有一个?，病了?十八年。(5:5) A man was there  who had been sick for 38 years.
耶稣看见他躺着， Jesus saw him lying there...
知道他病了许久， and he knew that the man had been sick  for such a long time.
就问他说：“你要?愈吗？” (5:6) Do you want to get well?
病?回答说：“先生，水动的时候，没有?把我放在池子里； Sir, I don't have anyone here to put me  in the pool when the water is stirred up.
我正?的时候，就有别?比我先下?。”(5:7) While I'm trying to get in,  someone else gets there first.
耶稣对他说：“?来， Get up.
拿你的?子走吧！” (5:8) Pick up your mat and walk.
那?立刻?愈， Immediately, the man got well.
就拿??子来 He picked up his mat...
走了。(5:9) and started walking.
那天是安息?， The day this happened was a Sabbath...
所以漠太?对那医好的?说： so the Jewish authorities  told the man who had been healed:
“今天是安息?，你拿?子是不可的！”(5:10) This is a Sabbath, and it is against our law  for you to carry your mat.
他?回答说：“那使我?愈的对我说：‘拿你的?子走吧!’”(5:11) The man who made me well  told me to pick up my mat and walk.
他们问他说：“对你说‘拿?子走’的是什么?？” (5:12) Who is the man who told you to do this?
那医好的?不知道是谁， But the man who had been healed  did not know who Jesus was...
因为那里的?多，耶稣已经躲开了。 (5:13) for there was a crowd in that place,  and Jesus had slipped away.
后来耶稣在殿里遇见他， Afterwards, Jesus found him in the Temple.
对他说：“你已经?愈了， You're well now...
不要再犯罪， so stop sinning...
恐怕你遭遇的更加利害。” (5:14) or something worse may happen to you.
那?就? Then the man left...
告诉漠太?，使他?愈的是耶稣。 (5:15) and told the Jewish authorities  that it was Jesus who had healed him.
所以漠太?逼?耶稣， So they began to persecute Jesus...
因为他在安息?做了这事。 (5:16) because he had done this healing  on a Sabbath.
耶稣就对他们说： Jesus answered them.:
“我父做事直到?今， My Father is always working.
我也做事。” (5:17) And I, too, must work.
所以漠太?越发想要杀他， This saying made the Jewish authorities  all the more determined to kill him.
因他不但犯了安息?， Not only had he broken the Sabbath law...
并?称　神为他的父， but he had said  that God was his own Father...
将自己和　神当作?等。(5:18) and, in this way,  had made himself equal with God.
耶稣对他们说： So Jesus answered them:
“我实实在在地告诉你们： I tell you the truth!
子?着自己不能做什么， The Son can do nothing on his own!
惟有看见父所做的，子才能做；父所做的事，子也照样做。 (5:19) He does only what he sees his Father doing!  What the Father does, the Son also does.
父爱子， For the Father loves the Son...
将自己所做的一?事指给他看， and shows him all that he himself is doing.
还要将比这更大的事指给他看，叫你们希?。 (5:20) He will show him even greater things  to do than this, and you will all be amazed!
父怎样叫死??来，使他们活着， Just as the Father raises the dead  and gives them life...
子也照样随自己的意思使?活着。(5:21) in the same way,  the Son gives life to those he wants to.
父不诀判什么?， Nor does the Father himself judge anyone.
乃将诀判的事?交与子， (5:22) He has given his Son  the full right to judge...
叫?都尊敬子?魂尊敬父一样。 so that all will honor the Son  in the same way as they honor the Father.
不尊敬子的，就是不尊敬差子来的父。(5:23) Whoever does not honor the Son  does not honor the Father who sent him.
我实实在在地告诉你们： I am telling you the truth!
那听我话、又信差我来者的， Those who hear my words  and believe in him who sent me...
就有永生， have eternal life.
不至于定罪，是已经出死?生了。(5:24) They will not be judged,  but have already passed from death to life.
我实实在在地告诉你们： I am telling you the truth.
时候将到， The time is coming.
现在就是了， The time has already come...
死?要听见　神儿子的声音， when the dead will hear  the voice of the Son of God.
听见的?就要活了。 (5:25) And those who hear it will come to life.
因为父怎样在自己有生命，就赐给他儿子也照样在自己有生命， (5:26) Just as the Father is, himself,  the source of life...
就赐给他儿子也照样在自己有生命， (5:26) in the same way, he has made his Son  to be the source of life.
并?因为他是?子，就赐给他行诀判的?柄。 And he has given the Son the right to judge,  because he is...
并?因为他是?子，就赐给他行诀判的?柄。(5:27) the Son of Man!
你们不要把这事看作希?。 Do not be surprised at this.
时候要到，凡在坟墓里的，都要听见他的声音，就出来。 (5:28) The time is coming when all the dead will  hear his voice and come out of their graves.
行善的，复活得生；作恶的，复活定罪。 (5:29) Those who have done good  will rise and live.
作恶的， And those who have done evil..
复活定罪。 (5:29) will rise and be condemned.
我?着自己不能做什么， I can do nothing on my own authority!
我怎么听见，就怎么诀判。我的诀判也是公?的， I judge only as God tells me,  so my judgment is right...
因为我不?自己的意思，只?那差我来者的意思。 (5:30) because I am not trying to do what I want,  but only what he who sent me wants!
我?为自己作见证， If I testify on my own behalf...
我的见证就不真；(5:31) what I say is not to be accepted  as real proof.
另有一位给我作见证， But there is someone else  who testifies on my behalf.
我也知道他给我作的见证是真的。(5:32) And I know that  what he says about me is true.
你们曾差?到约翰那里， John is the one  to whom you sent your messengers.
他为真理作过见证。 (5:33) ?实我所受的见证不是从?来的； And he spoke on behalf of the truth.  It is not that I must have a human witness...
?而我说这些话，为要叫你们得救。(5:34) I say this only in order that  you may be saved!
约翰是点着的明灯， John was like a lamp, burning and shining...
你们?愿暂时喜欢他的光。(5:35) and you were willing, for a while,  to enjoy his light.
但我有比约翰更大的见证， But I have a witness on my behalf...
但我有比约翰更大的见证， which is even greater than the witness  that John gave.
因为父交给我要我成就的事，就是我所做的事， What I do...
因为父交给我要我成就的事，就是我所做的事， that is, the deeds my Father gave me to do...
这便见证我是父所差来的。 (5:36) these speak on my behalf  and show that the Father has sent me.
差我来的父也为我作过见证。 And the Father who sent me  also testifies on my behalf.
你们从来没有听见他的声音，也没有看见他的形像。(5:37) You have never heard his voice  or seen his face...
你们并没有他的道存在心里， and you do not keep his message  in your hearts...
因为他所差来的，你们不信。 (5:38) for you do not believe  in the one whom he sent.
你们查考圣经（注：或作“应当查考圣经”）， You study the Scriptures,  because you think that in them...
因你们以为内中有永生；给我作见证的就是这经。(5:39) you will find eternal life!  And these very scriptures speak about me!
?而你们不肯到我这里来得生命。 (5:40) Yet you are not willing to come to me  in order to have life.
我不受从?来的?耀，(5:41) I am not looking for human praise.
但我知道， But I know what kind of people you are.
你们心里没有　神的爱。 (5:42) And I know that you have no love for God  in your hearts.
我奉我父的名来，你们并不接待我； I have come with my Father's authority,  but you have not received me.
?有别?奉自己的名来，你们倒要接待他。 (5:43) When, however, someone comes  with his own authority, you will receive him.
你们互相受?耀， You like to receive praise  from one another...
?不?从独一之　神来的?耀， but you do not try to win praise  from the one who alone is God!
怎能信我呢？(5:44) How, then, can you believe me?
不要想我在父面?要告你们， Do not think, however, that I am the one  who will accuse you to my Father.
有一位告你们的，就是你们所仰赖的摩西。(5:45) Moses, in whom you have put your hope,  is the very one who will accuse you.
你们?果信摩西，也必信我， If you had really believed Moses,  you would've believed me...
因为他书上有指着我写的话。(5:46) because he wrote about me.
你们?不信他的书，怎能信我的话呢？”(5:47) But since you do not believe what he wrote,  how can you believe what I say?
这事以后，耶稣渡过加利利海， After this, Jesus went across Lake Galilee...
就是提比哩亚海。(6:1) or Lake Tiberias, as it is also called.
有许多?因为看见他在病?身上所行的神?， A large crowd followed him...
就跟随他。(6:2) because they had seen his miracles  of healing the sick.
耶稣上了山，和门徒一魂坐在那里。(6:3) Jesus went up a hill  and sat down with his disciples.
那时漠太?的逾越节近了。 (6:4) The time for the Passover Festival was near.
耶稣举目看见许多?来， Jesus looked around and saw  that a large crowd was coming to him.
就对腓力说：“我们从哪里买饼叫这些?颈呢？” (6:5) Where can we buy enough food  to feed all these people?
他说这话是要试验腓力， He said this to test Philip.
他自己原知道要怎样行。 (6:6) Actually, he already knew what he would do.
腓力回答说：“就是二十两银子的饼，叫他们各?颈一点，也是不够的。” For everyone to have even a little...
腓力回答说：“就是二十两银子的饼，叫他们各?颈一点，也是不够的。” (6:7) it would take more than 200 silver coins  to buy enough bread.
有一个门徒，就是西门彼得的兄弟安得烈，对耶稣说：(6:8) Another one of his disciples, Andrew,  who was Simon Peter's brother, said:
“在这里有一个孩童，带着五个大麦饼、两条话， There is a boy here who has  five loaves of barley bread and two fish.
只是分给这许多? ，还算什么呢？” (6:9) But they will certainly not be enough  for all these people.
耶稣说：“你们叫众?坐下。” Make the people sit down.
原来那地方的草多， There was a lot of grass there...
众?就坐下， so all the people sat down.
数目约有五?。(6:10) There were about 5,000 men.
耶稣拿?饼来， Jesus took the bread...
祝谢了， gave thanks to God...
就分给那坐着的?， and distributed it  to the people who were sitting there.
分话也是这样， He did the same with the fish...
都随着他们所要的。(6:11) and they all had as much as they wanted.
他们颈饱了， When they were all full,  he said to his disciples.:
耶稣对门徒说：“把剩下的零碎收拾?来， Gather the pieces left over.
免得有糟蹋的。” (6:12) Let us not waste a bit.
他们便将那五个大麦饼的零碎，就是众?颈了剩下的， So they gathered them all  and filled 12 baskets...
收拾?来，装满了十二个篮子。 (6:13) with the pieces left over from the five  barley loaves which the people had eaten.
众?看见耶稣所行的神?， Seeing this miracle that Jesus  had performed, the people there said:
就说： "Surely this is the Prophet...
“这真是那要到世间来的先知。”(6:14) "who was to come into the wold!"
耶稣既知道众?要来 Jesus knew that they were about  to come and seize him...
?逼他作王， in order to make him king by force.
就独自又退到山上?了。(6:15) So he went off again to the hills by himself.
到了晚上，他的门徒下海边?，(6:16) When evening came,  Jesus' disciples went down to the lake...
上了船， got into a boat...
要过海往迦百农?。 and went back across the lake  towards Capernaum.
天已经黑了，耶稣还没有来到他们那里。(6:17) Night came on,  and Jesus still had not come to them.
忽?狂风大作，海就翻腾?来。 (6:18) By then a strong wind was blowing  and stirring up the water.
门徒摇橹约行了十里多路， The disciples had rowed  about three or four miles...
看见耶稣 when they saw Jesus...
在海面上走， walking on the water...
渐渐近了船， coming near the boat...
他们就害怕。 (6:19) and they were terrified.
耶稣对他们说：“是我， 不要怕！” Don't be afraid.
耶稣对他们说：“是我， 不要怕！”(6:20) It is I.
门徒就喜欢接他上船， Then they willingly took him into the boat...
船立时到了 and immediately the boat reached land...
他们所要?的地方。(6:21) at the place they were heading for.
第二?，站在海那边的众?， Next day, the crowd which had stayed  on the other side of the lake...
知道那里没有别的船，只有一只小船； realized that there had been  only one boat there.
又知道耶稣没有魂他的门徒上船， They knew that Jesus had not gone in it  with his disciples...
乃是门徒自己?的。 (6:22) but that they had left without him.
?而，有几只小船从提比哩亚来， Other boats, which were from Tiberias,  came to shore near the place...
靠近主祝谢后分饼给?颈的地方。(6:23) where the crowd had eaten  the bread after the Lord had given thanks.
众?见耶稣和门徒都不在那里， When the crowd saw  that Jesus was not there, nor his disciples...
就上了船，往迦百农?找耶稣。(6:24) they got into those boats  and went to Capernaum, looking for him.
既在海那边找着了，就对他说： When the people found Jesus on  the other side of the lake, they said to him:
“拉比，是几时到这里来的？” (6:25) "Teacher, when did you get here?"
耶稣回答说：“我实实在在地告诉你们： I am telling you the truth.
你们找我，并不是因见了神?，乃是因颈饼得饱。  You are looking for me because  you ate the bread and had all you wanted...
你们找我，并不是因见了神?，乃是因颈饼得饱。 (6:26) not because you understood my miracles.
不要为那必坏的食物劳力， Do not work for food that spoils.
要为那存到永生的食物劳力， Instead, work for the food  that lasts for eternal life.
就是?子要赐给你们的， This is the food  the Son of Man will give you...
因为?子是父　神所印证的。” (6:27) because God, the Father,  has put his mark of approval on him.
众?问他说：“我们当行什么，才算做　神的工呢？” (6:28) What can we do in order to do  what God wants us to do?
耶稣回答说：“信　神所差来的，这就是做　神的工。”(6:29) What God wants you to do  is to believe in the one he sent.
他们又说：“你行什么神?，叫我们看见就信你？ What miracle will you perform  so that we may see it and believe you?
你到底做什么事呢？ (6:30) What will you do?
我们的祖宗在旷野颈过吗哪，?经上写着说： Our ancestors ate manna in the desert,  just as the scripture says:
‘他从天上赐下粮来给他们颈。’(6:31) "He gave them bread from heaven to eat."
耶稣说：“我实实在在地告诉你们： I am telling you the truth.
那从天上来的粮，不是摩西赐给你们的， What Moses gave you  was not the bread from heaven.
乃是我父将天上来的真粮赐给你们。 (6:32) It is my Father who gives you  the real bread from heaven.
因为　神的粮，就是那从天上降下来 For the bread that God gives  is he who comes down from heaven...
赐生命给世界的。” (6:33) and gives life to the world.
他们说：“主啊，常将这粮赐给我们。”(6:34) Sir, give us this bread.  Give us this bread always.
耶稣说：“我就是生命的粮， I am the bread of life!
到我这里来的，必定不饿； Those who come to me  will never be hungry.
信我的，永远不渴。(6:35) Those who believe in me  will never be thirsty.
只是我对你们说过，你们已经看见我，还是不信。 (6:36) Now I told you that you have seen me,  but will not believe.
凡父所赐给我的?，必到我这里来； Everyone whom my Father gives me  will come to me.
到我这里来的，我总不丢?他。 (6:37) I will never turn away  anyone who comes to me...
因为我从天上降下来，不是要按自己的意思行， because I have come down from heaven  to do not my own will..
乃是要按那差我来者的意思行。 (6:38) but the will of him who sent me.
差我来者的意思 And it is the will of him who sent me...
差我来者的意思就是： And it is the will of him who sent me...
他所赐给我的，叫我一个也不失落， that I should not lose any  of all those he has given me...
在末??叫他复活。(6:39) but that I should raise them all to life  on the last day!
因为我父的意思 For what my Father wants...
是叫一?见子而信的?得永生， is that all who see the Son  and believe in him should have eternal life.
并?在末?我要叫他复活。” (6:40) And I will raise them to life on the last day.
漠太?因为耶稣说“我是从天上降下来的粮”， The people started grumbling about him,  because he said.:
就私下议论他，说： (6:41) "I am the bread  that came down from heaven. "
“这不是约瑟的儿子耶稣吗？ This man...
“这不是约瑟的儿子耶稣吗？ is Jesus, son of Joseph, isn't he?
他的父母我们?不?得吗？ We know his father and mother!
他?今怎么说‘我是从天上降下来的’呢？” (6:42) How, then, does he now say  he came down from heaven?
耶稣回答说：“你们不要大家议论。 (6:43) Stop grumbling among yourselves!
?不是差我来的父吸引?，就没有能到我这里来的； People cannot come to me unless  the Father who sent me draws them to me!
到我这里来的，在末?我要叫他复活。 (6:44) And I will raise them to life on the last day.
在先知书上写着说： The prophets wrote:
‘他们都要蒙　神的教训。 "Everyone will be taught by God."
’凡听见父之教训又学习的，就到我这里来。 (6:45). Anyone who hears the Father  and learns from him comes to me.
这不是说有?看见过父， This does not mean  that anyone has seen the Father.
惟独从　神来的，他看见过父。 (6:46) He who is from God  is the only one who has seen the Father.
我实实在在地告诉你们： I am telling you the truth.
信的? He who believes...
有永生。 (6:47) has eternal life.
我就是生命的粮。 (6:48) I am the bread of life!
你们的祖宗在旷野颈过吗哪，还是死了。 (6:49) Your ancestors ate manna in the desert,  but they died.
这是从天上降下来的粮， But the bread that comes down from heaven  is of such a kind...
叫?颈了就不死。(6:50) that whoever eats it will not die.
我是从天上降下来生命的粮； I am the living bread  that came down from heaven!
??颈这粮，就必永远活着。 If you eat this bread, you will live forever!
我所要赐的粮，就是我的?， The bread that I will give you is my flesh...
为世?之生命所赐的。” (6:51) which I give so that the world may live!
因此，漠太?彼此争论说： This started an angry argument  among them.
“这个?怎能把他的?给我们颈呢？” (6:52) How can this man give us his flesh to eat?
耶稣说：“我实实在在地告诉你们： I am telling you the truth.
你们?不颈?子的?，不喝?子的血， If you do not eat the flesh of the Son of Man  and drink his blood...
就没有生命在你们里面。 (6:53) you will not have life in yourselves!
颈我?喝我血的?就有永生， Those who eat my flesh and drink my blood  have eternal life...
在末?我要叫他复活。 (6:54) and I will raise them to life on the last day.
我的?真是可颈的，我的血真是可喝的。 (6:55) For my flesh is the real food,  my blood is the real drink!
颈我?、喝我血的?常在我里面， Those who eat my flesh and drink my blood  live in me...
我也常在他里面。(6:56) and I live in them.
永活的父怎样差我来， The living Father sent me...
我又因父活着； and because of him I live also.
照样，颈我?的?也要因我活着。 (6:57) In the same way, whoever eats me  will live because of me.
这就是从天上降下来的粮。颈这粮的?，就永远活着，不像你们的祖宗颈过吗哪还是死了。”  This, then, is the bread  that came down from heaven.
这就是从天上降下来的粮。颈这粮的?，就永远活着，不像你们的祖宗颈过吗哪还是死了。”  It is not like the bread  that your ancestors ate, but then later died.
这就是从天上降下来的粮。颈这粮的?，就永远活着，不像你们的祖宗颈过吗哪还是死了。”  Those who eat this bread...
这就是从天上降下来的粮。颈这粮的?，就永远活着，不像你们的祖宗颈过吗哪还是死了。” (6:58) will live forever.
这些话是耶稣在迦百农会堂里教训?说的。 (6:59) Jesus said this as he taught  in the synagogue in Capernaum.
他的门徒中有好些?听见了，  Many of his followers heard this and said:
就说：“这话甚难，谁能听呢？”(6:60) "This teaching is too hard.  Who can listen to it?"
耶稣心里知道门徒为这话议论，就对他们说： Without being told, Jesus knew  that they were grumbling about this.
“这话是叫你们聪?吗（注：“聪?”原文作“跌倒”）？ (6:61) Does this make you want to give up?
倘或 Suppose, then...
你们看见?子升到他原来所在之处，怎么样呢？ (6:62) that you should see the Son of Man go back  up to the place where he was before?
叫?活着的乃是灵， What gives life is God's Spirit.
?伐是无益的。 Human power is of no use at all.
我对你们所说的话就是灵，就是生命。 (6:63) The words I have spoken to you  bring God's life-giving Spirit.
只是你们中间 Yet some of you...
有不信的?。 do not believe.
”耶稣从?头就知道谁不信他， Jesus knew from the very beginning  who were the ones that would not believe...
谁要卖他。 (6:64) and which one would betray him.
耶稣又说：“所以我对你们说过， This is the very reason I told you...
?不是蒙我父的恩赐，  that no people can come to me...
没有?能到我这里来。”(6:65) unless the Father makes it possible  for them to do so.
从此，他门徒中多有 Because of this, many of Jesus' followers...
退?的，不再和他魂行。(6:66) turned back  and would not go with him anymore.
耶稣就对那十二个门徒说： And you...
“你们也要?吗？” (6:67) would you also like to leave?
西门彼得回答说：“主啊，你有永生之道， Lord, to whom would we go?
我们还归从谁呢？ (6:68) You have the words that give eternal life.
我们已经信了， And now we believe and know...
又知道你是 that you are the Holy One...
神的圣者。”(6:69) who has come from God.
耶稣说：“我不是拣选了你们十二个门徒吗？ I chose the 12 of you, didn't I?
但你们中间有一个是魔鬼。” (6:70) Yet one of you is a devil.
耶稣这话是指着加略?西门的儿子漠大说的； He was talking about Judas,  the son of Simon Iscariot.
他本是十二个门徒里的一个， For Judas, even though he was  one of the 12 disciples...
后来要卖耶稣的。(6:71) was going to betray him.
这事以后，耶稣在加利利游行， After this, Jesus traveled in Galilee.
不愿在漠太游行， He did not want to travel in Judea...
因为漠太?想要杀他。(7:1) because the Jewish authorities there  were wanting to kill him.
当时，漠太?的住棚节近了， (7:2) The time for the Festival of Shelters  was near...
耶稣的弟兄就对他说： so Jesus' brothers said to him:
“你离开这里上漠太?吧！ "Leave this place and go to Judea...
叫你的门徒也看见你所行的事。 (7:3) "so that your followers will see  the things that you are doing. "
?要显扬名声，没有在暗处行事的， People don't hide what they're doing  if they want to be well known.
你?果行这些事，就当将自己显明给世?看。” (7:4) Since you are doing these things,  let the whole world know about you.
因为连他的弟兄说这话，是因为不信他。 (7:5) Not even his brothers believed in him.
耶稣就对他们说:“我的时候还没有到， The right time for me has not yet come.
你们的时候常是方便的。(7:6) Any time is right for you.
世?不能恨你们，?是恨我， The world cannot hate you,  but it hates me...
因为我指证他们所做的事是恶的。 (7:7) because I keep telling it  that its ways are bad.
你们上?过节吧！ You go on to the festival
我现在不上?过这节， I am not going to this festival...
因为我的时候还没有满。”(7:8) because the right time has not come for me.
耶稣说了这话，?旧住在加利利。 (7:9) He said this, and then stayed on in Galilee.
但他弟兄上?以后，他也上?过节， After his brothers had gone to the festival,  Jesus also went.
不是明?，似乎是暗?的。 (7:10) However, he did not go openly, but secretly.
正在节?，漠太?寻找耶稣 The Jewish authorities were looking for him  at the Festival.
说：“他在哪里？”(7:11) "Where is he?" they asked.
众?为他纷纷议论， There was much whispering about him  in the crowd.
有的说：“他是好?。”有的说：“不?， "He is a good man, " some people said.  "No, " others said...
他是迷惑众?的。”(7:12) "he fools the people. "
只是没有?明明地讲论他， But no one talked about him openly...
因为怕漠太?。 (7:13) because they were afraid  of the Jewish authorities.
到了节?， The Festival was nearly half over...
耶稣上殿里?教训?。 (7:14) when Jesus went to the Temple  and began teaching.
漠太?就希?说： The Jewish authorities  were greatly surprised.
“这个?没有学过，怎么明白书呢？” How does this man know so much...
“这个?没有学过，怎么明白书呢？”(7:15) when he has never been to school?
耶稣说：“我的教训不是我自己的，乃是那差我来者的。 (7:16) What I teach is not my own teaching,  but it comes from God, who sent me.
??立志遵着他的旨意行， Those willing to do  what God wants will know...
就必晓得这教训或是出于　神，或是我?着自己说的。(7:17) whether what I teach comes from God,  or whether I speak on my own authority.
??着自己说，是?自己的?耀； Those who speak on their own authority  are trying to gain glory for themselves.
惟有?那差他来者的?耀， But he who wants glory  for the one who sent him is honest...
这?是真的，在他心里没有不义。 (7:18) and there is nothing false in him.
摩西?不是传律法给你们吗？ Moses gave you the Law, didn't he?
你们?没有一个?守律法。 But not one of you obeys the Law.
为什么想要杀我呢？” (7:19) Why are you trying to kill me?
众?回答说：“你是被鬼附着了！谁想要杀你？” (7:20) You have a demon in you.  Who is trying to kill you?
耶稣说：“我做了一件事，你们都以为希?。(7:21) I performed one miracle,  and you were all surprised.
摩西传割礼给你们 Moses ordered you  to circumcise your sons...
（?实不是从摩西?的，乃是从祖先?的）， although it was not Moses  but your ancestors who started it.
因此你们也在安息?给?行割礼。 (7:22) And so, you circumcise a boy  on the Sabbath.
??在安息?受割礼，免得违背摩西的律法， If a boy is circumcised on the Sabbath  so that Moses' Law is not broken...
我在安息?叫一个???好了，你们就向我生?吗？ why are you angry with me...
我在安息?叫一个???好了，你们就向我生?吗？　 (7:23) because I made a man completely well  on the Sabbath?
不可按外貌断定是悖 Stop judging by external standards...
总要按公?断定是恪！(7:24) and judge by true standards.
耶路?冷?中有的说：  Some of the people of Jerusalem said:
“这不是他们想要杀的?吗？(7:25) "Isn't this the man  the authorities are trying to kill?
你看他还明明地讲道，他们也不向他说什么， "Look, he is talking in public,  and they say nothing against him.
难道官长真知道这是基督吗？ (7:26) "Can it be that they really know  that he is the Messiah?
?而我们知道这个?从哪里来；只是基督来的时候，没有?知道他从哪里来。”  "But when the Messiah comes,  no one will know where he is from.
?而我们知道这个?从哪里来；只是基督来的时候，没有?知道他从哪里来。” (7:27) "And we all know  where this man comes from. "
那时，耶稣在殿里教训?，大声说： As Jesus taught in the Temple,  he said in a loud voice:
“你们也知道我， Do you really know me...
也知道我从哪里来； and know where I am from?
我来并不是批于自己， I have not come on my own authority.
但那差我来的是真的。 He who sent me, however, is truthful.
你们不?识他， (7:28) 我??识他， You do not know him, but I know him...
因为我是从他来的，他也是差了我来。” (7:29) because I come from him, and he sent me.
他们就想要捉拿耶稣， Then they tried to seize him...
只是没有?下手，因为他的时候还没有到。(7:30) but no one laid a hand on him,  because his hour had not yet come.
但众?中间有好些信他的，说： But many in the crowd believed in him.
“基督来的时候，他所行的神??能比这?所行的更多吗？” (7:31) When the Messiah comes, will he perform  more miracles than this man has?
法利??听见众?为耶稣这样纷纷议论， The Pharisees heard the crowd  whispering these things about Jesus...
祭司长和法利??就打发差役?捉拿他。 (7:32) so they and the chief priests  sent some guards to arrest him.
于是耶稣说：“我还有不多的时候和你们魂在， I shall be with you a little while longer...
以后就回到差我来的那里?。 (7:33) and then I shall go away  to him who sent me.
你们要找我，?找不着； You will look for me,  but you will not find me...
我所在的地方，你们不能到。” (7:34) because you cannot go where I will be.
漠太?就彼此对问说： The Jewish authorities  said among themselves:
“这?要往哪里?，叫我们找不着呢？ "Where is he about to go  so that we shall not find him?"
难道他要往散住希腊中的漠太?那里?教训希腊?吗？ (7:35) Will he go to the Greek cities,  where our people live and teach the Greeks?
他说‘你们要找我， He says that we will look for him...
?找不着； but will not find him...
我所在的地方，你们不能到’， and that we cannot go where he will be.
这话是什么意思呢？” (7:36) What does he mean?
节?的末?，就是最大之?， On the last and most important day  of the festival...
耶稣站着高声说： Jesus stood up and said in a loud voice.:
“??渴了，可以到我这里来喝！ (7:37) 信我的?， Whoever is thirsty should come to me,  and whoever believes in me should drink.
就?经上所说： As the scripture says:
‘从他腹中要流出活水的江河来。’” (7:38) "Streams of life-giving water  will pour out from his side."
耶稣这话 Jesus said this about the Spirit...
是指着信他之?要受圣灵说的。 which those who believed in him  were going to receive.
那时还没有赐下圣灵来， At that time,  the Spirit had not yet been given...
因为耶稣尚未得着?耀。 (7:39) because Jesus had not been raised to glory.
众?听见这话，有的说： Some of the people in the crowd  heard him say this.
“这真是那先知。” (7:40) 有的说：“这是基督。” This man is really the Prophet!
但也有的说：“基督?是从加利利出来的吗？(7:41) The Messiah will not come from Galilee!
经上?不是说‘基督是大卫的后裔， The scripture says that the Messiah  will be a descendant of King David...
从大卫本乡伯利恒出来的’吗？” (7:42) and will be born in Bethlehem,  the town where David lived.
于是众?因着耶稣?了纷争。 (7:43) So there was a division in the crowd  because of Jesus.
?中有?要捉拿他， Some wanted to seize him...
只是无?下手。 (7:44) but no one laid a hand on him.
差役回到祭司长和法利??那里， When the guards went back...
他们对差役说：“ the chief priests and Pharisees asked them:
你们为什么没有带他来呢？” (7:45) Why did you not bring him?
差役回答说：“从来没有像他这样说话的。” (7:46) Nobody has ever talked the way  this man does.
法利??说：“你们也受了迷惑吗？ (7:47) Did he fool you, too?
官长或是法利???有信他的呢？ (7:48) Have you ever known one of the authorities  or one Pharisee to believe in him?
但这些不明白律法的百姓 This crowd does not know  the Law of Moses.
是被咒诅的。” (7:49) So they are under God's curse.
内中有尼哥德慕，就是从??见耶稣的，对他们说：　(7:50) One of the Pharisees there was Nicodemus,  the man who had gone to see Jesus before.
“不先听本?的口供，不知道他所做的事， According to our Law, we cannot  condemn people before hearing them...
难道我们的律法还定他的罪吗？” (7:51) and finding out what they have done.
他们回答说：“你也是出于加利利吗？ Are you also from Galilee?
你??查考， Study the scriptures...
就可知道加利利没有出过先知。” (7:52) and you will learn  that no prophet ever comes from Galilee.
于是各?都回家?了， Then everyone went home...
耶稣?往橄榄山?。 (8:1) but Jesus went to the Mount of Olives.
?早又回到殿里， Early the next morning,  he went back to the Temple.
众百姓都到他那里?，他就坐下教训他们。(8:2) All the people gathered round him,  and he sat down and began to teach them.
文士和法利?? The teachers of the Law and the Pharisees...
带着一个行淫时被拿的妇?来， brought in a woman  who had been caught committing adultery...
叫她站在当中。 (8:3) and they made her stand before them all.
就对耶稣说：“夫子， Teacher...
这妇?是正行淫之时被拿的。(8:4) this woman was caught in the very act  of committing adultery!
摩西在律法上吩咐我们， In our Law, Moses commanded...
把这样的妇?用石头打死。 that such a woman must be stoned to death.
你说该把她怎么样呢？” (8:5) Now, what do you say?
他们说这话，乃试探耶稣，要得着告他的把柄。 They said this to trap Jesus,  so that they could accuse him.
耶稣?弯着腰用指头在地上画字。 (8:6) But he bent over  and wrote on the ground with his finger.
他们还是不住地问他， As they stood there asking him questions...
耶稣就直?腰来， he straightened up.
对他们说：“你们中间谁是没有罪的， Whichever one of you  has committed no sin...
谁就可以先拿石头打她。”(8:7) may throw the first stone at her.
于是又弯着腰用指头在地上画字。 (8:8) Then he bent over again  and wrote on the ground.
他们听见这话， When they heard this,  they all left, one by one...
就从老到少一个一个地都出?了， the older ones first.
只剩下耶稣一?，还有那妇???站在当中。(8:9) Jesus was left alone  with the woman still standing there.
耶稣就直?腰来，对她说：“妇?，那些?在哪里呢？没有?定你的罪吗？” (8:10) He straightened up.
“妇?，那些?在哪里呢？ Where are they?
没有?定你的罪吗？” (8:10) Is there no one left to condemn you?
她说：“主啊，没有。” No one, sir.
耶稣说： Well, then...
“我也不定你的罪， I do not condemn you either.
?吧！ Go...
从此不要再犯罪了。” (8:11) but do not sin again.
耶稣又对众?说： Jesus spoke to the Pharisees again.
“我是世界的光。 I am the light of the world.
跟从我的，就不在黑暗里走，必要得着生命的光。”(8:12) Who follows me will have the light of life  and will never walk in darkness.
法利??对他说：“你是为自己作见证， Now you are testifying on your own behalf!
你的见证不真。” (8:13) -What you say proves nothing!  -No.
耶稣说：“我虽?为自己作见证，我的见证还是真的。 Even though I do testify on my own behalf,  what I say is true...
因我知道我从哪里来，往哪里?； because I know where I came from  and where I am going.
你们?不知道我从哪里来，往哪里?。(8:14) You do not know where I came from  or where I'm going.
你们是以外貌（注：原文作“??身”）判断?， You make judgments in a purely human way.
我?不判断?(8:15) I pass judgment on no one.
就是判断?，我的判断也是真的， But if I were to do so,  my judgment would be true...
因为不是我独自在这里， because I am not alone in this.
还有差我来的父与我魂在。 (8:16) The Father who sent me is with me.
你们的律法上也记着说： It is written in your Law...
‘两个?的见证 that when two witnesses agree...
是真的。’ (8:17) what they say is true.
我是为自己作见证， I testify on my own behalf...
还有差我来的父也是为我作见证。” (8:18) and the Father who sent me  also testifies on my behalf.
他们就问他说：“你的父在哪里？” Where is your "Father"?
耶稣回答说：“你们不?识我，也不?识我的父； You know neither me nor my Father.
?是?识我，也就?识我的父。” (8:19) If you knew me,  you would know my Father also.
这些话是耶稣在殿里的 Jesus said all this  as he taught in the Temple...
库房教训?时所说的， in the room  where the offering boxes were placed.
也没有?拿他， And no one arrested him...
因为他的时候还没有到。 (8:20) because his hour had not come.
耶稣又对他们说：“我要?了，你们要找我， I will go away, and you will look for me...
并?你们要死在罪中； but you will die in your sins.
我所?的地方，你们不能到。” (8:21) You cannot go where I am going.
漠太?说：“他说‘我所?的地方，你们不能到’， He says that we cannot go  where he is going.
难道他要自尽吗？” (8:22) Does this mean that he will kill himself?
耶稣对他们说：“你们是从下头来的， You belong to this world here below...
我是从上头来的； but I come from above.
你们是属这世界的，我不是属这世界的。 (8:23) You are from this world,  but I am not from this world.
所以我对你们说，你们要死在罪中； That is why I told you  that you will die in your sins.
你们?不信我是基督， And you will die in your sins...
必要死在罪中。”(8:24) if you do not believe that "I Am Who I Am."
他们就问他说：“你是谁？” Who are you?
耶稣对他们说：“就是我从?初所告诉你们的。 (8:25) What I have told you  from the very beginning.
我有许多事讲论你们， I have much to say about you...
判断你们； much to condemn you for.
但那差我来的是真的， The one who sent me, however, is truthful...
我在他那里所听见的，我就传给世?。” (8:26) and I tell the world only  what I have heard from him.
他们不明白耶稣是指着父说的。 (8:27) They did not understand that Jesus  was talking to them about the Father.
所以耶稣说：“你们举??子以后， When you lift up the Son of Man,  you will know...
必知道我是基督， that "I Am Who I Am."
并?知道我没有一件事是?着自己做的。 Then you will know  that I do nothing on my own authority...
我说这些话，乃是照着父所教训我的。(8:28) but I say only  what the Father has instructed me to say.
那差我来的，是与我魂在； And he who sent me is with me.
他没有?下我独自在这里， He has not left me alone...
因为我常做他所喜悦的事。” (8:29) because I always do what pleases him.
耶稣说这话的时候，就有许多?信他。 (8:30) Many who heard Jesus say these things  believed in him.
耶稣对信他的漠太?说：“你们?常常遵守我的道，就真是我的门徒。 (8:31) If you obey my teaching,  you are really my disciples.
你们必晓得真理，真理必叫你们得以自批。” (8:32) You will know the truth,  and the truth will set you free.
他们回答说：“我们是亚伯拉罕的后裔，从来没有作过谁的奴?， We are the descendants of Abraham,  and we have never been anybody's slaves.
你怎么说‘你们必得以自批’呢？” (8:33) What do you mean, then,  by saying, "You will be free"?
耶稣回答说：“我实实在在地告诉你们： I am telling you the truth.
所有犯罪的，就是罪的奴?。 (8:34) Everyone who sins is a slave of sin.
奴?不能永远住在家里， A slave does not belong  to a family permanently...
儿子是永远住在家ā！(8:35) but a son belongs there forever.
所以天父的儿子?叫你们自批，你们就真自批了。 (8:36) If the Son sets you free,  then you will be really free.
我知道你们是亚伯拉罕的子孙， I know you are Abraham's descendants.
你们?想要杀我，因为你们心里?不下我的道。 (8:37) Yet you are trying to kill me  because you will not accept my teaching.
我所说的，是在我父那里看见的； I talk about what my Father has shown me...
你们所行的，是在你们的父那里听见的。” (8:38) but you do what your father has told you!
他们说：“我们的父就是亚伯拉罕。” Our father is Abraham.
耶稣说：“你们?是亚伯拉罕的儿子，就必行亚伯拉罕所行的事。 (8:39) If you really were Abraham's children,  you would do the same things that he did!
我将在　神那里所听见的真理告诉了你们， All I have ever done  is to tell you the truth I heard from God...
现在你们?想要杀我！ yet you are trying to kill me.
这不是亚伯拉罕所行的事， (8:40) Abraham did nothing like this.
你们是行你们父所行的事。” You are doing what your father did.
他们说：“我们不是从淫乱生的，我们只有一位父，就是　神。” God Himself is the only Father we have...
他们说：“我们不是从淫乱生的，我们只有一位父，就是　神。” (8:41) and we are his true children.
耶稣说：“倘?　神是你们的父， If God really were your father...
你们就必爱我， you would love me  because I came from God...
因为我本是出于神，也是从　神而来， and now I am here.
并不是批着自己来， I did not come on my own authority...
乃是他差我来。 (8:42) but He sent me!
你们为什么不明白我的话呢？ Why do you not understand what I say?
无闶且蚰忝遣荒芴我的道。(8:43) It is because you cannot bear to listen  to my message.
你们是出于你们的父魔鬼， You are the children of your father,  the Devil...
你们父的私欲，你们?要行。 and you want to follow  your father's desires!
他从?初是杀?的， From the very beginning,  he was a murderer...
不守真理， and has never been on the side of truth...
因他心里没有真理； because there is no truth in him!
他说谎是出于自己， When he tells a lie,  he is only doing what is natural to him...
因他本来是说谎的，也是说谎之?的父。 (8:44) because he is a liar and the father of all lies!
我将真理告诉你们， But I tell the truth...
你们就因此不信我。 (8:45) and that is why you do not believe me.
你们中间谁能指证我有罪呢？ Which one of you can prove  that I am guilty of sin?
我既?将真理告诉你们，为什么不信我呢？(8:46) If I tell the truth,  then why do you not believe me?
出于　神的，必听　神的话； He who comes from God  listens to God's words.
你们不听， You, however, are not from God...
因为你们不是出于　神。” (8:47) and that is why you will not listen.
漠太?回答说：“我们说你是?马利亚?， Were we not right in saying  that you are a Samaritan...
并?是鬼附着的，这话?不正对吗？” (8:48) and have a demon in you?
耶稣说：“我不是鬼附着的， I have no demon.
我尊敬我的父，你们倒?慢我。(8:49) I honor my Father, but you dishonor me.
我不?自己的?耀，  I am not seeking honor for myself.
有一位为我??耀、定是愕摹(8:50) But there is one who is seeking it,  and who judges in my favor.
我实实在在地告诉你们： I am telling you the truth!
??遵守我的道，就永远不见死。” (8:51) Whoever obeys my teaching will never die!
漠太?对他说：“现在我们知道你是鬼附着的。 Now we know for sure  that you have a demon.
亚伯拉罕死了，众先知也死了， Abraham died, and the prophets died...
你还说‘??遵守我的道，就永远不尝死味’。(8:52) yet you say that whoever obeys  your teaching will never die.
难道你比我们的祖宗亚伯拉罕还大吗？他死了， Our father Abraham died.
难道你比我们的祖宗亚伯拉罕还大吗？他死了， You do not claim  to be greater than Abraham, do you?
众先知也死了！ And the prophets also died.
你将自己当作什么?呢？” (8:53) Who do you think you are?
耶稣回答说：“我??耀自己，我的?耀就算不得什么； If I were to honor myself,  that honor would be worth nothing.
?耀我的乃是我的父，就是你们所说是你们的　神。 (8:54) The one who honors me is my Father,  the very one you say is your God!
你们未曾?识他，我??识他。 You have never known him, but I know him.
我?说不?识他，我就是说谎的，像你们一样； If I were to say I do not know him...
但我?识他，也遵守他的道。(8:55) I would be a liar like you,  but I do know him, and I obey his Word.
你们的祖宗亚伯拉罕 Your father Abraham rejoiced...
欢欢喜喜地仰望我的?子， that he was to see the time of my coming.
既看见了，就快乐。” (8:56) He saw it and was glad.
漠太?说：“你还没有五十岁，?见过亚伯拉罕呢？” (8:57) You are not even 50 years old,  and you have seen Abraham?
耶稣说：“我实实在在地告诉你们： I am telling you the truth.
还没有亚伯拉罕 Before Abraham was born...
就有了我。” (8:58) "I am."
于是他们拿石头要打他， Stone him!
于是他们拿石头要打他， Then they picked up stones  to throw at him...
耶稣?躲藏，从殿里出?了。 (8:59) but Jesus hid himself and left the Temple.
耶稣过?的时候，看见一个?生来是瞎眼的。(9:1) As Jesus was walking along,  he saw a man who had been born blind.
门徒问耶稣说：“拉比， Teacher...
这?生来是瞎眼的，是谁犯了罪？ whose sin caused him to be born blind?
是这?呢？是他父母呢？” (9:2) Was it his own, or his parents' sin?
耶稣回答说：“也不是这?犯了罪，也不是他父母犯了罪， His blindness has nothing to do  with his sins or his parents' sins.
是要在他身上显出　神的作为来。 (9:3) He is blind so that God's power  might be seen at work in him.
趁着白?， As long as it is day...
我们必须做那差我来者的工； we must keep on doing the work  of him who sent me.
黑夜将到， Night is coming...
就没有?能做工了。 (9:4) when no one can work.
我在世上的时候， While I am in the world...
是世上的光。” (9:5) I am the light for the world.
耶稣说了这话，就吐唾沫在地上， After he said this,  Jesus spat on the ground...
用唾沫和泥 and made some mud with the spittle.
抹在瞎子的眼睛上，(9:6) He rubbed the mud on the man's eyes.
对他说：“你往西罗亚池子里?洗。” Go and wash your face  in the pool of Siloam.
（“西罗亚”翻出来，就是“ 奉差?”） This name means "Sent. "
他?一洗， So the man went, washed his face...
回头就看见了。(9:7) and came back seeing.
他的邻舍和那素常见他是讨饭的，就说： His neighbors, then, and the people who  had seen him begging before this asked:
“这不是那从?坐着讨饭的?吗？” (9:8) "Isn't this the man  who used to sit and beg?"
有?说：“是他。”又有?说：“不是，?是像他。” -He is the one.  -No, he isn't. He just looks like him.
他自己说：“是我。” (9:9) I am the man.
他们对他说：“你的眼睛是怎么开的呢？” (9:10) How is it that you can now see?
他回答说：“有一个?名叫耶稣，他和泥抹我的眼睛， The man called Jesus made some mud,  rubbed it on my eyes...
对我说‘你往西罗亚池子?洗’； and told me to go to Siloam  and wash my face.
我?一洗， So I went, and as soon as I washed...
就看见了。” (9:11) I could see.
他们说：“那个?在哪里？”他说：“我不知道。” (9:12) -Where is he?  -I don't know.
他们把从?瞎眼的?带到法利??那里。 (9:13) Then they took to the Pharisees  the man who had been blind.
耶稣和泥开他眼睛的?子是安息?。 (9:14) The day that Jesus made the mud and  cured him of his blindness was a Sabbath.
法利??也问他是怎么得看见的。 The Pharisees then asked the man again  how he had received his sight.
瞎子对他们说：“他把泥抹在我的眼睛上， He put some mud on my eyes...
我?一洗，就看见了。” (9:15) I washed my face, and now I can see.
法利??中有的说：“这个?不是从　神来的，因为他不守安息?。” The man who did this cannot be from God,  for he does not obey the Sabbath law.
又有?说：“一个罪?怎能行这样的神?呢？” How could a man who is a sinner  perform such miracles as these?
他们就?了纷争。 (9:16) And there was division among them.
他们又对瞎子说：“他既?开了你的眼睛， You say he cured you of your blindness.
你说他是怎样的?呢？” What do you say about him?
他说：“是个先知。” (9:17) He is a prophet!
漠太?不信他从?是瞎眼，后来能看见的， The Jewish authorities, however,  were not willing to believe...
等到叫了他的父母来， (9:18) that he had been blind and could now see  until they called his parents.
问他们说：“这是你们的儿子吗？ Is this your son?
你们说他生来是瞎眼的， You say that he was born blind.
?今怎么能看见了呢？” (9:19) How is it, then, that he can now see?
他父母回答说：“他是我们的儿子，生来就瞎眼，这是我们知道的。 (9:20) We know that he is our son,  and we know that he was born blind.
至于他?今怎么能看见，我们?不知道； But we don't know how it is  that he is now able to see...
是谁开了他的眼睛，我们也不知道。 nor do we know who cured him  of his blindness.
他已经成了?，你们问他吧！他自己必能说。” Ask him.
他已经成了?，你们问他吧！他自己必能说。” (9:21) He is old enough,  and he can answer for himself.
他父母说这话，是怕漠太?， His parents said this because  they were afraid of the Jewish authorities...
因为漠太?已经商议定了，?有 who had already agreed  that anyone who said he believed...
?耶稣是基督的，要把他赶出会堂。 (9:22) that Jesus was the Messiah  would be expelled from the synagogue.
因此他父母说：“他已经成了?，你们问他吧！” (9:23) That is why his parents said,  "He is old enough. Ask him. "
所以法利??第二次叫了那从?瞎眼的?来， A second time, they called back  the man who had been born blind.
对他说：“你该将?耀归给　神， Promise before God  that you will tell the truth.
我们知道这?是个罪?。” (9:24) We know that this man who cured you  is a sinner.
他说：“他是个罪?不是，我不知道； I do not know if he is a sinner or not.
有一件事我知道： One thing I do know.
从?我是眼瞎的， I was blind...
?今能看见了！” (9:25) and now I see.
他们就问他说：“他向你做什么？ What did he do to you?
是怎么开了你的眼睛呢？” (9:26) How did he cure you of your blindness?
他回答说：“我方才告诉你们，你们不听， I have already told you,  and you would not listen.
为什么又要听呢？莫隳忝且惨作他的门徒吗？” (9:27) Why do you want to hear it again? Maybe  you, too, would like to be his disciples?
他们就骂他说： They insulted him and said:
“你是他的门徒，我们是摩西的门徒！(9:28) You are that fellow's disciple,  but we are Moses' disciples!
神对摩西说话，是我们知道的； We know that God spoke to Moses!
只是这个?，我们不知道他从哪里来。” (9:29) As for that fellow, however,  we do not even know where he comes from.
那?回答说：“他开了我的眼睛，你们竟不知道他从哪里来，这真是?怪！ What a strange thing that is.
那?回答说：“他开了我的眼睛，你们竟不知道他从哪里来，这真是?怪！(9:30) You do not know where he comes from,  but he cured me of my blindness.
我们知道　神不听罪?， We know  that God does not listen to sinners.
惟有敬奉　神、遵行他旨意的，　神才听他。(9:31) He does listen to people who respect him  and do what he wants them to do.
从创世以来， Since the beginning of the world...
未曾听见有?把生来是瞎子的眼睛开了。 (9:32) nobody has heard of anyone  giving sight to a person born blind.
这??不是从　神来的，什么也不能做。” (9:33) Unless this man came from God,  he would not be able to do a thing!
他们回答说：“你??生在罪孽中， You were born and brought up in sin...
还要教训我们吗？” and you are trying to teach us?
于是把他赶出?了。(9:34) And they expelled him from the synagogue.
耶稣听说他们把他赶出?，后来遇见他，就说： When Jesus heard what had happened,  he found the man.
“你信　神的儿子吗？” (9:35) Do you believe in the Son of Man?
他回答说：“主啊，谁是　神的儿子，叫我信他呢？”(9:36) Tell me who he is, sir,  so that I can believe in him.
耶稣说：“你已经看见他， You have already seen him...
现在和你说话的就是他。” (9:37) and he is the one  who is talking with you now.
他说：“主啊，我信！” I believe, Lord.
就拜耶稣。 (9:38) And he knelt down before Jesus.
耶稣说：“我为诀判到这世上来， I came to this world to judge...
叫不能看见的，可以看见； so that the blind should see...
能看见的，反瞎了眼。” (9:39) and those who see should become blind.
魂他在那里的法利??听见这话，就说： Some Pharisees who were there with him  heard him say this and asked him.:
“难道我们也瞎了眼吗？” (9:40) Surely you don't mean  that we are blind, too?
耶稣对他们说：“你们?瞎了眼，就没有罪了； If you were blind,  then you would not be guilty.
但?今你们说：‘我们能看见，’ But since you claim that you can see...
所以你们的罪还在。 (9:41) this means that you are still guilty.
我实实在在地告诉你们： I am telling you the truth!
?进羊?，不从门进?， The man who does not enter the sheep pen  by the gate...
倒从别处爬进?，那?就是贼，就是?盗。 (10:1) but climbs in some other way  is a thief and a robber!
从门进?的，才是羊的灵?。 (10:2) The man who goes in through the gate  is the shepherd of the sheep.
看门的就给他开门， The gatekeeper opens the gate for him.
羊也听他的声音。他按著名叫自己的羊， The sheep hear his voice  as he calls his own sheep by name...
把羊领出来。(10:3) 既放出自己的羊来， and he leads them out.  When he has brought them out...
就在?头走，羊也跟着他，因为?得他的声音。 (10:4) he goes ahead of them, and the sheep  follow him because they know his voice.
羊不跟着生?， They will not follow someone else.
因为不?得他的声音， Instead they will run away  from such a person...
必要逃跑。” (10:5) because they do not know his voice.
耶稣将这比喻告诉他们，但他们不明白所说的是什么意思。 (10:6) Jesus told them this parable,  but they did not understand what he meant.
所以耶稣又对他们说： So Jesus said again.:
“我实实在在地告诉你们：我就是羊的门。 (10:7) I am telling you the truth.  I am the gate for the sheep.
凡在我以先来的，都是贼，是?盗， All others who came before me  are thieves and robbers...
羊?不听他们。 (10:8) but the sheep did not listen to them.
我就是门，凡从我进来的， I am the gate.
必?得救， Those who come in by me will be saved.
并?出?得草颈。 (10:9) They will come in and go out  and find pasture.
盗贼来，无阋偷?、杀害、毁坏； The thief comes only in order  to steal, kill, and destroy.
我来了，是要叫羊（注：或作“?”）得生命， I have come in order  that you might have life.
并?得的更丰盛。(10:10) Life in all its fullness.
我是好灵?，好灵?为羊舍命。 (10:11) I am the good shepherd,  who is willing to die for the sheep.
?是雇工，不是灵?，羊也不是他自己的， When the hired man, who is not a shepherd  and does not own the sheep...
他看见狼来， sees a wolf coming...
就?下羊逃走； he leaves the sheep and runs away.
狼抓住羊，赶散了羊?。 (10:12) So the wolf snatches the sheep  and scatters them.
雇工逃走，因他是雇工， The hired man runs away  because he is only a hired man...
并不顾念羊。 (10:13) and does not care about the sheep.
我是好灵?，我?识我的羊，我的羊也?识我。 (10:14) I am the good shepherd.
正?父?识我，我也?识父一样， As the Father knows me,  and I know the Father...
正?父?识我，我也?识父一样， in the same way I know my sheep,  and they know me.
并?我为羊舍命。(10:15) And I am willing to die for them.
我另外有羊， There are other sheep which belong to me...
不是这?里的； that are not in this sheep pen.
我必须领他们来， I must bring them, too.
他们也要听我的声音， They will listen to my voice...
并?要合成一?，归一个灵?了。 (10:16). and they will become one flock  with one shepherd.
我父爱我， The Father loves me...
因我将命舍?，好再?回来。 (10:17) because I am willing to give up my life  in order that I may receive it back again.
没有?夺我的命?， No one takes my life away from me.
是我自己舍的。 I give it up of my own free will.
我有?柄舍了， I have the right to give it up...
也有?柄?回来， and I have the right to take it back.
这是我从我父所受的命令。” (10:18) This is what my Father  has commanded me to do.
漠太?为这些话又?了纷争。 (10:19) Again there was division among the people  because of these words.
内中有好些?说：“他是被鬼附着，而?疯了， -He has a demon!  -He is crazy!
为什么听他呢？” (10:20) 又有?说：“这不是鬼附之?所说的话， -Why do you listen to him?  -A man with a demon cannot talk like this!
鬼?能叫瞎子的眼睛开了呢？”(10:21) How could a demon give sight  to blind people?
在耶路?冷有囊殿节，是冬天的时候。 It was winter...
在耶路?冷有囊殿节，是冬天的时候。 (10:22) and the Festival of the Dedication of the  Temple was being celebrated in Jerusalem.
耶稣在殿里所罗门的廊下行走。 (10:23) Jesus was walking in Solomon's Porch  in the Temple...
漠太?围着他说： when the people gathered round him.
“你叫我们漠疑不定到几时呢？ How long are you going  to keep us in suspense?
你?是基督，就明明地告诉我们。” (10:24) Tell us the plain truth. Are you the Messiah?
耶稣回答说：“我已经告诉你们，你们不信。 I have already told you,  but you would not believe me.
我奉我父之名所行的事可以为我作见证； (10:25) The deeds I do by my Father's authority  speak on my behalf.
只是你们不信， But you will not believe...
因为你们不是我的羊。 (10:26) for you are not my sheep.
我的羊听我的声音， My sheep listen to my voice.
我也?识他们，他们也跟着我； (10:27) I know them, and they follow me.
我又赐给他们永生，他们永不灭亡， I give them eternal life,  and they shall never die.
谁也不能从我手里把他们夺?。(10:28) No one can snatch them away from me.
我父把羊赐给我，他比万有都大， What my Father has given me  is greater than everything...
谁也不能从我父手里把他们夺?。 (10:29) and no one can snatch them away  from the Father's care.
我与父原为一。” (10:30) The Father and I are one.
漠太?又拿?石头来要打他。  Blasphemy! Stone him!
漠太?又拿?石头来要打他。 (10:31) Then the people again picked up stones  to throw at him.
耶稣对他们说：“我从父 I have done many good deeds  in your presence...
显出许多善事给你们看， which the Father gave me to do.
你们是为哪一件拿石头打我呢？” (10:32) For which one of these  do you want to stone me?
漠太?回答说：“我们不是为善事拿石头打你， We do not want to stone you  because of any good deeds...
是为你说僭妄的话； but because of your blasphemy!
又为你是个?，反将自己当作　神。” (10:33) You are only a man,  but you are trying to make yourself God!
耶稣说：“你们的律法上?不是写着 It is written in your own Law...
‘我曾说你们是神’吗？ (10:34) that God said, "You are gods."
经上的话是不能废的。 We know that what the scripture says  is true forever...
?那些承受　神道的?， and God called those people gods...
尚?称为神；(10:35) the people to whom his message was given.
父所分别为圣，又差到世间来的， As for me, the Father chose me  and sent me into the world.
他自称是　神的儿子，你们还向他说‘你说僭妄的话’吗？  How, then, can you say that I blaspheme...
他自称是　神的儿子，你们还向他说‘你说僭妄的话’吗？ (10:36) because I said that I am the Son of God?
我?不行我父的事，你们就不必信我； (10:37) Do not believe me, then, if I am not doing  the things my Father wants me to do.
我?行了，你们纵?不信我， But if I do them,  even though you do not believe me...
也当信这些事， you should at least believe my deeds...
叫你们又知道又明白： in order that you may know,  once and for all...
父在我里面， that the Father is in me...
我也在父里面。” (10:38) and that I am in the Father.
他们又要拿他，他?逃出他们的手走了。  Blasphemy!
他们又要拿他，他?逃出他们的手走了。 (10:39) Once more, they tried to seize Jesus,  but he slipped out of their hands.
耶稣又往约旦河外?， Jesus then went back again  across the Jordan River...
到了约翰?初施洗的地方， to the place  where John had been baptizing...
就住在那里。(10:40) and he stayed there.
有许多?来到他那里， Many people came to him.
他们说：“约翰一件神?没有行过， "John performed no miracls, " they said...
但约翰指着这?所说的一?话都是真的。” (10:41) "but everything he said  about this man was true. "
在那里信耶稣的?就多了。 (10:42) And many people there believed in him.
有一个患病的?，名叫拉?路，住在伯大尼， A man named Lazarus,  who lived in Bethany, became sick.
就是马利亚和她姐姐马大的村庄。(11:1) Bethany was the town  where Mary and her sister Martha lived.
这马利亚就是那用香膏抹主， This Mary was the one  who poured the perfume on the Lord's feet...
又用头发擦他脚的， and wiped them with her hair.
患病的拉?路是她的兄弟。 (11:2) It was her brother, Lazarus, who was sick.
她姊妹两个就打发??见耶稣说： The sisters sent Jesus a message.:
“主啊，你所爱的?病了。” (11:3) "Lord, your dear friend is sick. "
耶稣听见就说： When Jesus heard it, he said.:
“这病不至于死， "The final result of this sickness  will not be the death of Lazarus.
乃是为　神的?耀， "This has happened in order  to bring glory to God...
叫　神的儿子因此得?耀。” (11:4) "and it will be the means  by which the Son of God will receive glory. "
耶稣素来爱马大和她妹子并拉?路，(11:5) Jesus loved Martha, and her sister,  and Lazarus.
听见拉?路病了， Yet when he received the news  that Lazarus was sick...
就在所居之地?住了两天。 (11:6) he stayed where he was for two more days.
?后对门徒说：“我们再往漠太?吧！” (11:7) Then he said to his disciples,  "Let us go back to Judea. "
门徒说：“拉比，漠太?近来要拿石头打你， Teacher, just a short time ago,  the people there wanted to stone you...
你还往那里?吗？” (11:8) and are you planning to go back?
耶稣回答说：“白?不是有十二小时吗？ A day has 1 2 hours, doesn't it?
?在白?走路，就不至跌倒， So those who walk in broad daylight  do not stumble...
因为看见这世上的光；(11:9) for they see the light of this world.
?在黑夜走路，就必跌倒， But if they walk  during the night, they stumble...
因为他没有光。” (11:10) because they have no light.
耶稣说了这话，随后对他们说：“我们的朋友拉?路睡了， Our friend Lazarus has fallen asleep...
我?叫醒他！” (11:11) but I will go and wake him up.
门徒说：“主啊，他?睡了，就必好了。” (11:12) If he is asleep, Lord, he will get well.
耶稣这话是指着他死说的， Jesus meant that Lazarus had died...
他们?以为是说照常睡了。 (11:13) but they thought he meant natural sleep.
耶稣就明明地告诉他们说： So Jesus told them plainly.:
“拉?路死了。 (11:14) Lazarus is dead.
我没有在那里就欢喜，这是为你们的缘故， But for your sake...
我没有在那里就欢喜，这是为你们的缘故， I am glad that I was not with him...
好叫你们相信。 so that you will believe.
?今我们可以往他那里?吧！” (11:15) Let us go to him.
多马，又称为低土马，就对那魂作门徒的说： Thomas, called the Twin,  said to his fellow disciples.:
“我们也?和他魂死吧。” (11:16) Let us all go along with the Teacher,  so that we may die with him!
耶稣到了，就知道拉?路在坟墓里已经四天了。　 (11:17) When Jesus arrived, he found that Lazarus  had been buried four days before.
伯大尼离耶路?冷不远，约有六里路。 (11:18) Bethany was less than two miles  from Jerusalem...
有好些漠太?来看马大和马利亚， and many Judeans had come  to see Martha and Mary...
要为她们的兄弟安慰她们。 (11:19) to comfort them about their brother's death.
马大听见耶稣来了，就出?迎接他； When Martha heard that Jesus was coming,  she went out to meet him...
马利亚???坐在家里。 (11:20) but Mary stayed in the house.
马大对耶稣说：“主啊，你?早在这里， If you had been here, Lord...
我兄弟必不死！ (11:21) my brother would not have died.
就是现在，我也知道， But I know that even now...
你无论向　神?什么，　神也必赐给你。”  (11:22) God will give you whatever you ask him for.
耶稣说：“你兄弟必?复活。” (11:23) Your brother will rise to life.
马大说：“我知道在末?复活的时候，他必复活；” (11:24) I know that he will rise to life  on the last day.
耶稣对她说：“复活在我，生命也在我！ I am the resurrection and the life.
信我的?，虽?死了， Those who believe in me will live...
也必复活。(11:25) even though they die.
凡活着信我的? And those who live and believe in me...
必永远不死。 will never die.
你信这话吗？” (11:26) Do you believe this?
马大说：“主啊，是的， Yes, Lord.
我信你是基督， I do believe that you are the Messiah...
是　神的儿子，就是那要临到世界的。” (11:27) the Son of God,  who is to come into the world.
马大说了这话， After Martha said this...
就回?暗暗地叫她妹子马利亚说： she went back  and called her sister Mary privately.
“夫子来了， The Teacher is here...
叫你。” (11:28) and is asking for you.
马利亚听见了，就急忙?来，到耶稣那里?。 (11:29) When Mary heard this,  she got up and hurried out to meet him.
那时，耶稣还没有进村子， Jesus had not yet arrived in the village...
?在马大迎接他的地方。 (11:30) but was still in the place  where Martha had met him.
那些魂马利亚在家里安慰她的漠太?， The people who were in the house  with Mary, comforting her...
见她急忙?来出?，就跟着她， followed her  when they saw her get up and hurry out.
以为她要往坟墓那里?哭。 (11:31) They thought that she was going  to the grave to weep there.
马利亚到了耶稣那里，看见他，就俯伏在他脚?，说： Mary arrived where Jesus was, and  as soon as she saw him, she fell at his feet.
“主啊， Lord...
你?早在这里， if you had been here...
我兄弟必不死。”  (11:32) my brother would not have died.
耶稣看见她哭， Jesus saw her weeping...
并看见与她魂来的漠太?也哭， and he saw how the people with her  were weeping also.
就心里悲叹，又甚忧愁， (11:33) His heart was touched,  and he was deeply moved.
便说：“你们把他安放在哪里？” Where have you buried him?
他们回答说：“?主来看。” (11:34) Come and see, Lord.
耶稣哭了。(11:35) Jesus wept.
漠太?就说：“你看他爱这?是何等恳?。” (11:36) "See how much he loved him, "  the people said.
?中有?说： But some of them said:
“他既?开了瞎子的眼睛， "He gave sight to the blind man, didn't he?
?不能叫这?不死吗？” (11:37) "Could he not have kept Lazarus  from dying?"
耶稣又心里悲叹，来到坟墓?； Deeply moved once more,  Jesus went to the tomb...
那坟墓是个洞，有一块石头挡着。 (11:38) which was a cave  with a stone placed at the entrance.
耶稣说：“你们把石头挪开！” Take the stone away.
那死?的姐姐马大对他说：“主啊，他现在必是臭了，因为他死了已经四天了。” (11:39) There will be a bad smell, Lord.  He has been buried four days.
耶稣说：“我不是对你说过，你?信，就必看见　神的?耀吗？” (11:40) Didn't I tell you that you would see  God's glory if you believed?
他们就把石头挪开。 They took the stone away.
耶稣举目望天说： Jesus looked up.
“父啊，我感谢你，因为你已经听我； (11:41) I thank you, Father, that you listen to me.
我也知道你常听我。 I know that you always listen to me...
但我说这话，是为周围站着的众?， but I say this for the sake  of the people here...
叫他们信是你差了我来。” (11:42) so that they will believe that you sent me.
说了这话，就大声呼叫说： After he had said this,  he called out in a loud voice:
“拉?路 Lazarus...
出来！” (11:43) come out!
那死?就出来了， He came out...
手脚裹着布， his hands and feet  wrapped in grave clothes...
脸上包着手巾。 and with a cloth round his face.
耶稣对他们说：“解开，叫他走！” (11:44) Untie him, and let him go.
那些来看马利亚的漠太?，见了耶稣所做的事， Many of the people who had come  to visit Mary saw what Jesus did...
就多有信他的。 (11:45) and they believed in him.
但?中也有?见法利??的，将耶稣所做的事告诉他们。  (11:46) But some of them returned to the Pharisees  and told them what Jesus had done.
祭司长和法利??聚集公会，说： So the Pharisees and the chief priests  met with the Council and said.:
“这?行好些神?，我们怎么办呢？ "What shall we do?"
“这?行好些神?，我们怎么办呢？ (11:47) Look at all the miracles  this man is performing!
?这样批着他，??都要信他， If we let him go on in this way,  everyone will believe in him...
罗马?也要来夺我们的地土和我们的百姓。” (11:48) and the Roman authorities will take action  and destroy our temple and our nation!
内中有一个?，名叫该亚法，本年作大祭司， One of them, named Caiaphas,  who was High Priest that year, said.:
对他们说：“你们不知道什么。  What fools you are!
对他们说：“你们不知道什么。 (11:49) Don't you realize...
独不想一个?替百姓死，免得通国灭亡， that it is better for you  to have let one man die for the people...
就是你们的益处。”  (11:50) instead of having  the whole nation destroyed?
他这话不是出于自己， Actually, he did not say this  of his own accord.
是因他本年作大祭司， Rather, as he was High Priest that year...
所以预言耶稣将要替这一国死。 (11:51) he was prophesying that Jesus  was going to die for the Jewish people...
也不但替这一国死， and not only for them,  but also to bring together into one body...
并要将　神四散的子民都聚集归一。 (11:52) all the scattered people of God.
从那??他们就商议要杀耶稣。 (11:53). From that day on, the Jewish authorities  made plans to kill Jesus.
所以耶稣不再显?行在漠太?中间，就离开那里往靠近旷野的地方?。 So Jesus did not travel openly in Judea, but  left, and went to a place near the desert...
到了一座城，名叫以法莲，就在那里和门徒魂住。 (11:54) to a town named Ephraim,  where he stayed with his disciples.
漠太?的逾越节近了， The time for the Passover Festival  was near...
有许多?从乡下上耶路?冷?， and many people went up from the country  to Jerusalem...
要在节?洁净自己。 (11:55) to perform the ritual of purification  before the festival.
他们就寻找耶稣， They were looking for Jesus...
站在殿里彼此说： and as they gathered in the Temple,  they asked one another.:
“你们的意思?何？他不来过节吗？”  (11:56) "What do you think? Surely, he will not  come to the Festival, will he?"
那时，祭司长和法利??早已吩咐说： The chief priests and the Pharisees  had given orders...
“?有?知道耶稣在哪里，就要报明， that if anyone knew where Jesus was,  he must report it...
好?拿他。” (11:57) so that they could arrest him.
逾越节?六?， Six days before the Passover...
耶稣来到伯大尼， Jesus went to Bethany,  the home of Lazarus...
就是他叫拉?路从死里复活之处。 (12:1) the man he had raised from death.
有?在那里给耶稣预备筵席，马大伺候， They prepared a dinner for him there,  which Martha helped serve.
拉?路也在那魂耶稣坐席的?中。 (12:2) Lazarus was one of those  who were sitting at the table with Jesus.
马利亚就拿着一斤极贵的 Then Mary took a whole pint  of a very expensive perfume...
真哪哒香膏 made of pure nard...
抹耶稣的脚， poured it on Jesus' feet...
又用自己头发?擦， and wiped them with her hair.
屋里就满了膏的香?。 (12:3) The sweet smell of the perfume  filled the whole house.
有一个门徒， One of Jesus' disciples, Judas Iscariot...
就是那将要卖耶稣的加略?漠大， (12:4) the one who was going to betray him, said.:
说：“这香膏为什么不卖 Why wasn't this perfume sold...
?十两银子 for 300 silver coins...
k济??呢？” and the money...
k济??呢？” (12:5) given to the poor?
他说这话，并不是挂念??， He said this not because  he cared about the poor...
乃因他是个贼， but because he was a thief.
又带着?囊，常??中所存的。 (12:6) He carried the money bag  and would help himself from it.
耶稣说：“批她吧！ Leave her alone.
她是为我安葬之?存留的。 (12:7) Let her keep what she has  for the day of my burial.
因为常有??和你们魂在， You will always have poor people with you...
只是你们不常有我。” (12:8) but you will not always have me.
有许多漠太?知道耶稣在那里， A large number of people  heard that Jesus was in Bethany...
就来了，不但是为耶稣的缘故，也是要看 so they went there, not only  because of Jesus, but also to see Lazarus...
他从死里所复活的拉?路。 (12:9) whom Jesus had raised from death.
但祭司长商议连拉?路也要杀了， (12:10) So the chief priests made plans  to kill Lazarus, too...
因有好些漠太?为拉?路的缘故，回?信了耶稣。(12:11) because, on his account, many Jews  were rejecting them and believing in Jesus.
第二天，有许多上来过节的?， The next day, the large crowd  that had come to the Passover Festival...
听见耶稣将到耶路?冷，  (12:12) heard that Jesus was coming to Jerusalem.
就拿着棕树枝，出?迎接他，喊着说： So they took branches of palm trees  and went out to meet him, shouting.:
“和散那！奉主名来的 "Praise God! God bless him  who comes in the name of the Lord!
以色列王是应当称颂的！” (12:13) "God bless the King of Israel!"
耶稣得了一个驴驹，就?上，?经上所记的说： (12:14) Jesus found a donkey and rode on it,  just as the scripture says.:
“锡安的民哪（注：“民”原文作“女子”），不要惧怕！ "Do not be afraid, city of Zion!
你的王?着驴驹来了。” (12:15) "Here comes your King,  riding on a young donkey. "
这些事门徒?先不明白， His disciples did not understand this  at the time...
等到耶稣得了?耀以后， but when Jesus had been raised to glory...
才想?这话是指着他写的， they remembered  that the scripture said this about him...
并?众?果?向他这样行了。 (12:16) and that they had done this for him.
当耶稣呼唤拉?路， The people who had been with Jesus...
叫他从死复活出坟墓的时候， when he called Lazarus out of the grave  and raised him from death...
魂耶稣在那里的众?就作见证。 (12:17) had reported what had happened.
众?因听见耶稣行了这神?，就?迎接他。 That was why the crowd met him...
众?因听见耶稣行了这神?，就?迎接他。 (12:18) because they heard  he had performed this miracle.
法利??彼此说： The Pharisees then said to one another.:
“看哪，你们是徒劳无益， You see, we are not succeeding at all!
世?都随从他?了。” (12:19) Look, the whole world is following him!
那时，上来过节礼拜的?中， Some Greeks were among those...
有几个希腊?。  (12:20) who had gone to Jerusalem  to worship during the festival.
他们来见加利利伯?大的 They went to Philip...
腓力，?他说： he was from Bethsaida in Galilee, and said.:
“先生，我们愿意见耶稣。” (12:21) "Sir, we want to see Jesus. "
腓力?告诉安得烈， Philip went and told Andrew...
安得烈魂腓力?告诉耶稣。 (12:22) and the two of them went and told Jesus.
耶稣说：“?子得?耀的时候到了。  (12:23) The hour has now come for the Son of Man  to receive great glory.
我实实在在地告诉你们： I am telling you the truth.
一粒麦子不落在地里死了， A grain of wheat remains  no more than a single grain...
?旧是一粒； unless it is dropped into the ground  and dies.
?是死了， If it does die...
就结出许多子粒来。 (12:24) then it produces many grains.
爱惜自己生命的，就失丧生命； Those who love their own life will lose it.
在这世上恨恶自己生命的，就要保守生命到永生。 (12:25) Those who hate their own life in this world  will keep it for life eternal.
?有?服事我，就当跟从我； Whoever wants to serve me  must follow me...
我在哪里，服事我的?也要在那里； so that my servant  will be with me where I am.
?有?服事我，我父必尊重他。 (12:26) And my Father will honor anyone  who serves me.
我现在心里忧愁，我说什么才好呢？ Now my heart is troubled. What shall I say?
父啊， Shall I say, "Father, do not let this hour  come upon me"?
救我脱离这时候， But that is why I came...
但我原是为这时候来的。  (12:27) so that I might go through  this hour of suffering.
父啊， Father...
愿你?耀你的名。” bring glory to Your name.
当时就有声音从天上来说： Then a voice spoke from heaven.:
“我已经?耀了我的名，还要再?耀。” (12:28) "I have brought glory to it,  and I will do so again. "
站在旁边的众?听见，就说：“打雷了。” The crowd standing there heard the voice,  and some of them said it was thunder...
还有?说：“有天使对他说话。” (12:29) while others said, "An angel spoke to him. "
耶稣说：“这声音不是为我，是为你们来的。  (12:30) It was not for my sake that this voice spoke,  but for yours.
现在这世界受诀判， Now is the time for this world to be judged.
这世界的王要被赶出?。  (12:31) Now the ruler of this world  will be overthrown.
我?从地上被举?来， When I am lifted up from the earth...
就要吸引万?来归我。” (12:32) I will draw everyone to me.
耶稣这话原是指着自己将要怎样死说的。 (12:33) In saying this, he indicated  the kind of death he was going to suffer.
众?回答说：“我们听见律法上有话说‘基督是永存的’， Our Law tells us  that the Messiah will live forever.
你怎么说‘?子必须被举?来’呢？ How then can you say  that the Son of Man must be lifted up?
这?子是谁呢？” (12:34) Who is this Son of Man?
耶稣对他们说：“光在你们中间还有不多的时候， The light will be among you a little longer.
应当趁着有光行走， Continue on your way  while you have the light...
免得黑暗临到你们； so that the darkness  will not come upon you!
那在黑暗里行走的，不知道往何处?。 (12:35) For the one who walks in the dark  does not know where he is going.
你们应当趁着有光，信从这光， Believe in the light, then, while you have it...
使你们成为光明之子。” so that you will be the people of the light!
耶稣说了这话，就离开他们，隐藏了。 (12:36) After Jesus said this,  he went off and hid himself from them.
他虽?在他们面?行了许多神?， Even though he had performed  all these miracles in their presence...
他们还是不信他。 (12:37) they did not believe in him...
这是要应验先知以?亚的话，说： so that what the prophet Isaiah had said  might come true:
“主啊，我们所传的有谁信呢？ "Lord, who believed the message we told?
主的膀臂向谁显露呢？” (12:38) "To whom did the Lord reveal his power?"
他们所以不能信，因为以?亚又说：  (12:39) And so, they were not able to believe,  because Isaiah also said.:
“主叫他们瞎了眼、硬了心， "God has blinded their eyes  and closed their minds...
免得他们眼睛看见，心里明白， "so that their eyes would not see,  and their minds would not understand...
回转过来，我就医治他们。” "and they would not turn to me, " says God...
回转过来，我就医治他们。” (12:40) "for me to heal them. "
以?亚因为看见他的?耀，就指着他说这话。(12:41) Isaiah said this because  he saw Jesus' glory and spoke about him.
虽??此，官长中?有好些信他的， Even then, many of the Jewish authorities  believed in Jesus...
只因法利??的缘故，就不承?， but because of the Pharisees,  they did not talk about it openly...
恐怕被赶出会堂。 (12:42) so as not to be expelled  from the synagogue.
这是因他们爱?的?耀过于爱　神的?耀。(12:43) They loved human approval  rather than the approval of God.
耶稣大声说： Jesus said in a loud voice:
“信我的，不是信我， Whoever believes in me  believes not only in me...
乃是信那差我来的。 (12:44) but also in him who sent me.
?看见我，就是看见那差我来的。 (12:45) Whoever sees me  sees also him who sent me.
我到世上来，乃是光， I have come into the world as light...
叫凡信我的，不住在黑暗里。 (12:46) so that everyone who believes in me  should not remain in the darkness.
?有?听见我的话不遵守， If people hear my message  and do not obey it...
我不诀判他。 I will not judge them.
我来本不是要诀判世界，乃是要拯救世界。　(12:47) I came not to judge the world,  but to save it.
?绝我、不领受我话的?， Those who reject me  and do not accept my message...
有诀判他的， have one who will judge them.
就是我所讲的道，在末?要诀判他。 (12:48) The words I have spoken  will be their judge on the last day.
因为我没有?着自己讲， This is true because I have not spoken  on my own authority.
惟有差我来的父， But the Father who sent me...
已经给我命令，叫我说什么，讲什么。 (12:49) has commanded me  what I must say and speak.
我也知道他的命令就是永生。 And I know that his command  brings eternal life.
故此，我所讲的话正是照着父对我所说的。” (12:50) What I say, then,  is what the Father has told me to say.
逾越节以?， It was now the day  before the Passover Festival.
耶稣知道自己离世 Jesus knew that the hour had come  for him to leave this world...
归父的时候到了， and go to the Father.
他既?爱世间属自己的?， He had always loved those in the world  who were his own...
就爱他们到底。 (13:1) and he loved them to the very end.
颈晚饭的时候， Jesus and his disciples were at supper.
魔鬼已将卖耶稣的意思 The Devil had already put into the heart  of Judas, the son of Simon Iscariot...
放在西门的儿子加略?漠大心里。(13:2) the thought of betraying Jesus.
耶稣知道父已将万有交在他手里， Jesus knew that  the Father had given him complete power.
?知道自己是从　神出来的，又要归到　神那里?，(13:3) He knew that he had come from God  and was going to God.
就离席站?来脱了衣服， So he rose from the table,  took off his outer garment...
拿一条手巾束腰， (13:4) and tied a towel round his waist.
随后把水倒在盆里， Then he poured some water  into a washbasin...
就洗门徒的脚， and began to wash the disciples' feet...
并用自己所束的手巾擦干。 (13:5) and dry them  with the towel round his waist.
挨到西门彼得， He came to Simon Peter.
彼得对他说：“主啊，你洗我的脚吗？” (13:6) Are you going to wash my feet, Lord?
耶稣回答说：“我所做的，你?今不知道， You do not understand now  what I am doing...
后来必明白。 ”(13:7) but you will understand later.
彼得说：“你永不可洗我的脚！” Never, at any time, will you wash my feet.
耶稣说：“我?不洗你， If I do not wash your feet...
你就与我无分了。” (13:8) you will no longer be my disciple.
西门彼得说：“主啊， Lord...
不但我的脚， do not wash only my feet, then.
连手和头也要洗！。” (13:9) Wash my hands and head, too.
耶稣说：“凡洗过澡的?， Those who have taken a bath  are completely clean...
只要把脚一洗， and do not need to wash themselves...
?身就干净了； except for their feet.
你们是干净的， All of you are clean.
?而不都是干净的。” (13:10) All, except one.
耶稣原知道要卖他的是谁，  Jesus already knew  who was going to betray him.
所以说：“你们不都是干净的。”(13:11) That is why he said,  "All of you, except one, are clean. "
耶稣洗完了他们的脚， After Jesus had washed their feet...
就穿上衣服，又坐下，对他们说： he put his outer garment back on  and returned to his place at the table.
“我向你们所做的，你们明白吗？  (13:12) Do you understand  what I have just done to you?
你们称呼我夫子，称呼我主， You call me Teacher and Lord...
你们说的不错，我本来是。 (13:13) and it is right that you should do so,  because that is what I am.
我是你们的主，你们的夫子，尚?洗你们的脚， I, your Lord and Teacher,  have just washed your feet.
你们也当彼此洗脚。(13:14) You, then, should wash one another's feet.
我给你们作了榜样， I have set an example for you...
叫你们照着我向你们所做的?做。 (13:15) so that you will do  just what I have done for you.
我实实在在地告诉你们： I am telling you the truth.
??不能大于主?， No slaves are greater than their master...
差?也不能大于差他的?。 (13:16) and no messengers are greater  than the one who sent them.
你们既知道这事， Now that you know this truth...
?是?行就有福了。 (13:17) how happy you will be  if you put it into practice.
我这话不是指着你们众?说的， I am not talking about all of you.
我知道我所拣选的是谁。 I know those I have chosen.
现在要应验经上的话，说： But the scripture must come true that says:
‘魂我颈饭的?，用脚踢我。’(13:18) "The man who shared my food  turned against me."
?今事?还没有成就，我要先告诉你们， I tell you this now before it happens...
叫你们到事?成就的时候，可以信我是基督。  (13:19) so that when it does happen,  you will believe that "I Am Who I Am."
我实实在在地告诉你们： I am telling you the truth.
有?接待我所差?的，就是接待我； Whoever receives anyone I send  receives me also...
接待我，就是接待那差?我的。” (13:20) and whoever receives me  receives him who sent me.
耶稣说了这话， After Jesus had said this...
心里忧愁，就明说： he was deeply troubled  and declared openly:
“我实实在在地告诉你们： I am telling you the truth.
你们中间有一个?要卖我了。” (13:21) One of you is going to betray me.
门徒彼此对看，猜不透所说的是谁。 (13:22) The disciples looked at one another,  completely puzzled about whom he meant.
有一个门徒，是耶稣所爱的， One of the disciples,  the one whom Jesus loved...
侧身挨近耶稣的怀里。(13:22) was sitting next to Jesus.
西门彼得点头对他说： Simon Peter motioned to him.
“你告诉我们，主是指着谁说的。” (13:24) Ask him whom he is talking about.
那门徒便就势靠着耶稣的胸膛， So that disciple  moved closer to Jesus' side.
问他说：“主啊，是谁呢？” (13:25) Who is it, Lord?
耶稣回答说：“我蘸一点饼给谁， I will dip some bread in the sauce  and give it to him.
就是谁。” He is the man.
耶稣就蘸了一点饼， So he took a piece of bread, dipped it...
递给加略?西门的儿子漠大。 (13:26) and gave it to Judas,  the son of Simon Iscariot.
他颈了以后，?但就?了他的心。 As soon as Judas took the bread,  Satan entered into him.
耶稣便对他说：“你所做的，快做吧！” (13:27) Hurry, and do what you must.
魂席的?，没有一个知道是为什么对他说这话。 (13:28) None of the others at the table understood  why Jesus said this to him.
有?因漠大带着?囊， Since Judas was  in charge of the money bag...
以为耶稣是对他说： some of the disciples thought  that Jesus had told him...
“你?买我们过节所应用的东西”， to go and buy  what they needed for the festival...
或是叫他拿什么k济??。 (13:29) or to give something to the poor.
漠大受了那点饼，立刻就出?。 Judas accepted the bread  and went out at once.
那时候是夜间了。 (13:30) It was night.
他既出?，耶稣就说： After Judas had left, Jesus said.:
“?今?子得了?耀， Now the Son of Man's glory is revealed.
神在?子身上也得了?耀。 (13:31) Now God's glory is revealed through him.
神要因自己 And if God's glory is revealed through him...
?耀?子， then God will reveal the glory  of the Son of Man in himself.
并?要快快地?耀他。 (13:32) And he will do so at once.
小子们， My children...
我还有不多的时候与你们魂在， I shall not be with you very much longer.
后来你们要找我，但我所?的地方你们不能到。这话我曾对漠太?说过，?今也照样对你们说。 You will look for me, but I tell you now  what I told the Jewish authorities:
后来你们要找我，但我所?的地方你们不能到。这话我曾对漠太?说过，?今也照样对你们说。 (13:33) You cannot go where I am going.
我赐给你们一条新命令，乃是叫你们 And now I give you a new commandment:
彼此相爱； Love one another.
我怎样爱你们，你们也要怎样相爱。 (13:34) As I have loved you,  so you must love one another.
你们?有彼此相爱的心， If you have love for one another...
众?因此就?出你们是我的门徒了。” (13:35) then everyone will know  that you are my disciples.
西门彼得问耶稣说：“主往哪里?？” Where are you going, Lord?
耶稣回答说：“我所?的地方，你现在不能跟我?， You cannot follow me now  where I am going...
后来?要跟我?。” (13:36) but later you will follow me.
彼得说：“主啊，我为什么现在不能跟你?？我愿意为你舍命。” (13:37) Lord, why can't I follow you now?  I am ready to die for you.
耶稣说：“你愿意为我舍命吗？ Are you really ready to die for me?
我实实在在地告诉你： I am telling you the truth.
鸡叫以先，你要?次不?我。 (13:38) Before the rooster crows, you will say  three times that you do not know me.
你们心里不要忧愁， Do not be worried and upset.
你们信　神， Believe in God...
也当信我。(14:1) and believe, also, in me.
在我父的家里有许多住处；?是没有，我就早已告诉你们了；我?原是为你们预备地方?。  There are many rooms  in my Father's house...
在我父的家里有许多住处；?是没有，我就早已告诉你们了；我?原是为你们预备地方?。  and I am going to prepare a place for you.
在我父的家里有许多住处；?是没有，我就早已告诉你们了；我?原是为你们预备地方?。 (14:2) I would not tell you this if it were not so.
我??为你们预备了地方，就必再来接你们到我那里?； And after I go and prepare a place for you,  I will come back and take you to myself...
我在哪里，叫你们也在那里。 (14:3) so that you will be where I am.
我往哪里?，你们知道；那条路，你们也知道（注：有古卷作“我往哪里?，你们知道那条路”）。” (14:4) You know the way that leads  to the place where I am going.
多马对他说：“主啊，我们不知道你往哪里?， Lord, we do not know  where you are going...
怎么知道那条路呢？ ”(14:5) so how can we know the way to get there?
耶稣说：“我就是道路、 I am the way...
真理、生命； the truth, and the life.
?不藉着我，没有?能到父那里?。 (14:6) No one goes to the Father except by me.
你们??识我，也就?识我的父。 Now that you have known me,  you will know my Father also.
从今以后，你们?识他，并?已经看见他。” (14:7) And from now on,  you do know him, and you have seen him.
腓力对他说：“?主 Lord...
将父显给我们看， show us the Father.
我们就知足了。” (14:8) That is all we need.
耶稣对他说：“腓力，我与你们魂在这样长久， For a long time, I have been with you all.
你还不?识我吗？ Yet you do not know me, Philip?
?看见了我，就是看见了父， Whoever has seen me has seen the Father.
你怎么说‘将父显给我们看’呢？ (14:9) Why, then, do you say,  "Show us the Father"?
我在父里面，父在我里面，你不信吗？ Do you not believe, Philip, that I am  in the Father and the Father is in me?
我对你们所说的话，不是?着自己说的， The words I have spoken to you  do not come from me.
乃是住在我里面的父做他自己的事。 (14:10) The Father, who remains in me,  does his own work.
你们当信我，我在父里面，父在我里面； Believe me when I say that I am in the Father  and the Father is in me.
即或不信，也当因我所做的事信我。  (14:11) If not, believe because of the things I do.
我实实在在地告诉你们： I am telling you the truth.
我所做的事，信我的?也要做；并?要做比这更大的事， Those who believe in me will do what I do.  Yes, they will do even greater things...
因为我往父那里?。 (14:12) because I am going to the Father.
你们奉我的名无论?什么，我必成就， And I will do whatever you ask for  in my name...
叫父因儿子得?耀。 (14:13) so that the Father's glory  will be shown through the Son.
只要你们奉我的名所?... If you ask me for anything in my name...
你们?奉我的名?什么，我必成就。(14:14) I will do it.
你们?爱我，就必遵守我的命令。 (14:15) If you love me,  you will obey my commandments.
我要?父，父就另外赐给你们一位保惠师（注：或作“训慰师”。下魂）， I will ask the Father,  and he will give you another Helper...
叫他永远与你们魂在， (14:16) who will stay with you forever.
就是真理的圣灵， He is the Spirit  who reveals the truth about God.
乃世?不能接受的，因为不见他，也不?识他； The world cannot receive him,  because it cannot see him or know him.
你们??识他，因他常与你们魂在，也要在你们里面。 (14:17) But you know him,  because he remains with you and is in you.
我不?下你们为孤儿，我必到你们这里来。 (14:18) When I go, you will not be left all alone.  I will come back to you.
还有不多的时候，世?不再看见我； In a little while,  the world will see me no more...
你们?看见我， but you will see me.
因为我活着，你们也要活着。 (14:19) And because I live, you also will live.
到那? When that day comes...
你们就知道我在父里面，你们在我里面，我也在你们里面。 (14:20) you will know that I am in my Father,  and that you are in me, just as I am in you.
有了我的命令又遵守的，这?就是爱我的； Those who accept my commandments  and obey them are the ones who love me.
爱我的必蒙我父爱他，  My Father will love those who love me.
我也要爱他，并?要向他显现。” (14:21) I, too, will love them  and reveal myself to them.
漠大（不是加略?漠大）问耶稣说： Judas, not Judas Iscariot, said.:
“主啊，为什么要向我们显现，不向世?显现呢？” (14:22) Lord, how can it be that you will  reveal yourself to us and not to the world?
耶稣回答说：“??爱我，就必遵守我的道， Those who love me will obey my teaching.
我父也必爱他，并?我们要到他那里?，与他魂住。 (14:23) My Father will love them, and my Father  and I will come to them and live with them.
不爱我的?就不遵守我的道， Those who do not love me  do not obey my teaching.
你们所听见的道不是我的，乃是差我来之父的道。 (14:24) The teaching you have heard is not mine,  but comes from the Father who sent me.
我还与你们魂住的时候，已将这些话对你们说了。(14:25) I have told you this while I am still with you.
但保惠师，就是父因我的名所要差来的圣灵， The Helper, the Holy Spirit,  whom the Father will send in my name...
他要将一?的事指教你们，并?要叫你们想?我对你们所说的一?话。 (14:26) will teach you everything and  make you remember all that I have told you.
我留下?安给你们， Peace is what I leave with you.
我将我的?安赐给你们。 It is my own peace that I give you.
我所赐的，不像世?所赐的； I do not give it as the world does.
你们心里不要忧愁，也不要胆?。 (14:27)  Do not be worried and upset.  Do not be afraid.
你们听见我对你们说了，我?还要到你们这里来。 You heard me say to you,  "I am leaving, but I will come back to you."
你们?爱我，因我到父那里?，就必喜乐， If you loved me, you would be glad  that I am going to the Father...
因为父是比我大的。(14:28) for he is greater than I.
现在事?还没有成就，我预先告诉你们， I have told you this now  before it all happens...
叫你们到事?成就的时候，就可以信。 (14:29) so that when it does happen,  you will believe.
以后我不再和你们多说话， I cannot talk with you much longer...
因为这世界的王将到， because the ruler of this world is coming.
他在我里面是毫无所有；(14:30) 但要叫世?知道 He has no power over me,  but the world must know...
我爱父，并?父怎样吩咐我，我就怎样行。 that I love the Father, and that is why  I do everything as he commands me.
?来，我们走吧。 (14:31) Come, let us go from this place.
我是真?萄树，我父是栽培的?。(15:1) I am the real vine,  and my Father is the gardener.
凡属我不结果子的枝子，他就剪?； He breaks off every branch in me  that does not bear fruit...
凡结果子的，他就囊理干净， and he prunes every branch  that does bear fruit...
使枝子结果子更多。(15:2) so that it will be clean and bear more fruit.
现在你们因我讲给你们的道，已经干净了。(15:3) You have been made clean already  by the teaching I have given you.
你们要常在我里面， Remain united to me...
我也常在你们里面。 and I will remain united to you.
枝子?不常在?萄树上， A branch cannot bear fruit by itself.
自己就不能结果子； It can do so only if it remains on the vine.
你们?不常在我里面，也是这样。 (15:4) In the same way, you cannot bear fruit  unless you remain in me.
我是?萄树，你们是枝子； I am the vine, and you are the branches.
常在我里面的，我也常在他里面，这?就多结果子。 Those who remain in me, and I in them,  will bear much fruit...
因为离了我，你们就不能做什么。 (15:5) for you can do nothing without me.
??不常在我里面，就像枝子丢在外面枯干， Those who do not remain in me  are thrown out like a branch and dry up.
?拾?来 Such branches are gathered up  and thrown into the fire...
?在火里烧了。 (15:6) where they are burned.
你们?常在我里面，我的话也常在你们里面；凡你们所愿意的，??就给你们成就。(15:7) If you remain in me  and my words remain in you...
你们多结果子， then you will ask for anything you wish,  and you shall have it.
我父就因此得?耀， My Father's glory is shown  by your bearing much fruit...
你们也就是我的门徒了。(15:8) and in this way, you become my disciples.
我爱你们，正?父爱我一样， I love you, just as the Father loves me.
你们要常在我的爱里。 (15:9) Remain in my love.
你们?遵守我的命令，就常在我的爱里； If you obey my commands,  you will remain in my love...
正?我遵守了我父的命令，常在他的爱里。 (15:10) just as I have obeyed my Father's  commands, and remain in his love.
这些事我已经对你们说了，是要叫我的喜乐存在你们心里， I have told you this  so that my joy may be in you...
并叫你们的喜乐可以满足。 (15:11) and that your joy may be complete.
你们要彼此相爱，像我爱你们一样，这就是我的命令。　 (15:12) My commandment is this.:  Love one another, just as I love you.
?为朋友舍命，?的爱心没有比这个大的。 (15:13) The greatest love you can have  for your friends is to give your life for them.
你们?遵行我所吩咐的，就是我的朋友了。 (15:14) And you are my friends  if you do what I command you.
以后我不再称你们为??， I do not call you servants any longer...
因??不知道主?所做的事； because servants do not know  what their master is doing.
我乃称你们为朋友，因我从我父所听见的，已经都告诉你们了。(15:15) Instead, I call you friends, because I have  told you everything I heard from my Father.
不是你们拣选了我， You did not choose me.
是我拣选了你们； I chose you...
并?分派你们?结果子， and appointed you  to go and bear much fruit...
叫你们的果子常存， the kind of fruit that endures.
使你们 And so...
奉我的名，无论向父?什么，他就赐给你们。 (15:16) the Father will give you  whatever you ask of him in my name.
我这样吩咐你们，是要叫你们 This, then, is what I command you:
彼此相爱。(15:17) Love one another.
世??恨你们， If the world hates you...
你们知道（注：或作“该知道”）恨你们以先，已经恨我了。 (15:18) just remember that it has hated me first.
你们?属世界，世界必爱属自己的； If you belonged to the world,  then the world would love you as its own.
只因你们不属世界，乃是我从世界中拣选了你们， But I chose you from this world,  and you do not belong to it.
所以世界就恨你们。 (15:19) That is why the world hates you.
你们要记念我从?对你们所说的话：‘??不能大于主?。’ Remember what I told you.  "Slaves are not greater than their master. "
他们?逼?了我，也要逼?你们； If people persecuted me,  they will persecute you, too.
?遵守了我的话，也要遵守你们的话。  (15:20) If they obeyed my teaching,  they will obey yours, too.
但他们因我的名要向你们行这一?的事， But they will do all this to you  because you are mine...
因为他们不?识那差我来的。 (15:21) for they do not know the One who sent me.
我?没有来教训他们，他们就没有罪； They would not have been guilty of sin  if I had not come and spoken to them.
但?今他们的罪无可推诿了。  (15:22) As it is, they no longer have  any excuse for their sin.
恨我的，也恨我的父。 (15:23) Whoever hates me hates my Father also.
我?没有在他们中间行过别?未曾行的事， They would not have been guilty of sin...
他们就没有罪； if I had not done among them  the things that no one else ever did.
但?今连我与我的父， As it is, they have seen what I did...
他们也看见也恨恶了。 (15:24) and they hate both me and my Father.
这要应验 This, however, was bound to happen...
他们律法上所写的话， so that what is written in their Law  may come true.:
说：‘他们无故地恨我。’(15:25) "They hated me for no reason at all. "
但我要从父那里差保惠师来， The Helper will come...
就是从父出来真理的圣灵， the Spirit who reveals the truth about God  and who comes from the Father.
他来了，就要为我作见证。 (15:26) I will send him to you from the Father,  and he will speak about me.
你们也要作见证， And you, too, will speak about me...
因为你们从?头就与我魂在。 (15:27) because you have been with me  from the very beginning.
我已将这些事告诉你们，使你们不至于跌倒。 (16:1) I have told you this  so that you will not give up your faith.
?要把你们赶出会堂， You will be expelled from the synagogues...
并?时候将到， and the time will come  when those who kill you...
凡杀你们的，就以为是事奉神。 (16:2) will think that by doing this  they are serving God.
他们这样行， People will do these things to you...
是因未曾?识父，也未曾?识我。 (16:3) because they have not known  either the Father or me.
我将这事告诉你们， But I have told you this...
是叫你们到了时候， so that when the time comes  for them to do these things...
可以想?我对你们说过了。 you will remember what I told you.
我?先没有将这事告诉你们，因为我与你们魂在。(16:4) I did not tell you these things  at the beginning, for I was with you.
现今我往差我来的父那里?， But now I am going to him who sent me...
你们中间并没有?问我：‘你往哪里?？’(16:5) yet none of you asks me where I am going.
只因我将这事告诉你们，你们就满心忧愁。 (16:6) And now that I have told you,  your hearts are full of sadness.
?而我将真?告诉你们， But I am telling you the truth.
我?是与你们有益的。 It is better for you that I go away.
我?不?，保惠师就不到你们这里来； Because if I do not go,  the Helper will not come to you.
我??，就差他来。 (16:7) But if I do go away,  then I will send him to you.
他既来了，就要叫世? And when he comes,  he will prove to the people of the world...
为罪、为义、 that they are wrong about sin,  and about what is right...
为诀判，自己责备自己。 (16:8) and about God's judgment.
为罪，是因他们不信我； (16:9) They are wrong about sin  because they do not believe in me.
为义， They are wrong about what is right...
是因我往父那里?，你们就不再见我； (16:10) because I am going to the Father  and you will not see me anymore.
为诀判， And they are wrong about judgment...
是因这世界的王 because the ruler of this world...
受了诀判。” (16:11) has already been judged.
我还有好些事要告诉你们， I have much more to tell you...
但你们现在担当不了（注：或作“不能领会”）。 (16:12) but now, it would be too much  for you to bear.
只等真理的圣灵来了， When, however, the Spirit comes,  who reveals the truth about God...
他要引导你们明白（注：原文作“进?”）一?的真理， he will lead you into all the truth.
因为他不是?自己说的， He will not speak on his own authority,  but he will speak of what he hears...
乃是把他所听见的都说出来，并要把将来的事告诉你们。  (16:13) and will tell you of things to come.
他要?耀我，因为他要将受于我的告诉你们。 (16:14) He will give me glory, because he will  take what I say and tell it to you.
凡父所有的，都是我的， All that my Father has is mine.
所以我说，他要将受于我的告诉你们。 (16:15) That is why I said that the Spirit will take  what I give him and tell it to you.
等不多时，你们就不得见我； In a little while,  you will not see me anymore.
再等不多时，你们还要见我。” (16:16) And then, a little while later,  you will see me.
有几个门徒就彼此说： Some of his disciples asked  among themselves, "What does this mean?
“他对我们说‘等不多时，你们就不得见我； "He tells us that in a little while,  we will not see him...
再等不多时，你们还要见我’； "and then a little while later,  we will see him.
又说‘因我往父那里?’，这是什么意思呢？” (16:17) "and he also says, 'It is because  I am going to the Father. '
门徒彼此说：“他说‘等不多时’到底是什么意思呢？ "What does this 'a little while' mean?
我们不明白他所说的话。” (16:18) "We don't know what he is talking about. "
耶稣看出他们要问他，就说： Jesus knew  that they wanted to question him.
“我说‘等不多时，你们就不得见我； I said, "In a little while,  you will not see me...
再等不多时，你们还要见我’， "and then, a little while later,  you will see me."
你们为这话彼此相问吗？ (16:19)  Is this what you are asking about  among yourselves?
我实实在在地告诉你们： I am telling you the truth.
你们将要痛哭、哀号，世?倒要喜乐； You will cry and weep,  but the world will be glad.
你们将要忧愁，?而你们的忧愁要变为喜乐。 (16:20) You will be sad,  but your sadness will turn into gladness.
妇?生产的时候就忧愁，因为她的时候到了； When a woman is about to give birth, she is  sad because her hour of suffering has come.
既生了孩子，就不再记念那苦楚， But when the baby is born,  she forgets her suffering...
因为欢喜世上生了一个?。 (16:21) because she is happy  that a baby has been born into the world.
你们现在也是忧愁， That is how it is with you.  Now you are sad...
但我要再见你们，你们的心就喜乐了； but I will see you again, and your hearts  will be filled with gladness...
这喜乐也没有?能夺?。(16:22)  the kind of gladness  that no one can take away from you.
到那?，你们什么也就不问我了。 When that day comes,  you will not ask me for anything.
我实实在在地告诉你们： I am telling you the truth.
你们?向父?什么，他必因我的名赐给你们。 (16:23) The Father will give you  whatever you ask of him in my name.
向来你们没有奉我的名?什么， Until now, you have not asked for anything  in my name.
?今你们?就必得着， Ask, and you will receive...
叫你们的喜乐可以满足。  (16:24) so that your happiness may be complete.
这些事，我是用比喻对你们说的； I have used figures of speech  to tell you these things.
时候将到，我不再用比喻对你们说， But the time will come  when I will not do so...
乃要将父明明地告诉你们。 (16:25) but will speak to you plainly  about the Father.
到那?，你们要奉我的名??； When that day comes,  you will ask him in my name.
我并不对你们说，我要为你们?父。 (16:26) And I do not say  that I will ask him on your behalf...
父自己爱你们， for the Father himself loves you.
因为你们已经爱我，又信我是从父出来的。 (16:27) He loves you because you love me  and have believed that I came from God.
我从父出来，到了世界； I did come from the Father,  and I came into the world...
我又离开世界，往父那里?。” (16:28) and now I am leaving the world  and going to the Father.
门徒说： Then his disciples said to him...
“?今你是明说，并不用比喻了。 (16:29) "Now you are speaking plainly  without using figures of speech.
现在我们晓得你凡事都知道， "We know now that you know everything.
也不用?问你， "You do not need to have someone  ask you questions.
因此我们信你是从　神出来的。”(16:30) "This makes us believe  that you came from God. "
耶稣说：“现在你们信吗？ (16:31) 看哪，时候将到，?是已经到了， Do you believe now?  The time is coming, it is already here...
你们要分散，各归自己的地方?， when all of you will be scattered,  each of you to your own home...
留下我独自一?； and I will be left all alone.
?实我不是独自一?，因为有父与我魂在。  (16:32) But I am not really alone,  because the Father is with me.
我将这些事告诉你们，是要叫你们在我里面有?安。 I have told you this so that  you will have peace by being united to me.
在世上你们有苦难，但你们可以放心， The world will make you suffer.  But be brave.
我已经痉了世界。” (16:33) I have defeated the world.
耶稣说了这话，就举目望天说： After Jesus finished saying this,  he looked up to heaven and said.:
“父啊， Father...
时候到了， the hour has come.
愿你?耀你的儿子， Give glory to your Son...
使儿子也?耀你；(17:1) so that the Son may give glory to you.
正?你曾赐给他?柄，管理凡有血?的， For you gave him authority over all people...
叫他将永生赐给你所赐给他的?。 (17:2) so that he might give eternal life  to all those you gave him.
?识你独一的真　神，并??识你所差来的耶稣基督， And eternal life means to know you,  the only true God...
这就是永生。 (17:3) and to know Jesus Christ, whom you sent.
我在地上已经?耀你， I have shown your glory on Earth.
你所托付我的事，我已成?了。 (17:4) I have finished the work you gave me to do.
父啊， Father...
现在?你使我魂你享?耀， give me glory in your presence now...
就是未有世界以先，我魂你所有的?耀。 (17:5) the same glory I had with you  before the world was made.
你从世上赐给我的?， I have made you known  to those you gave me out of the world.
我已将你的名显明与他们。 They belonged to you,  and you gave them to me.
他们本是你的，你将他们赐给我，他们也遵守了你的道。 (17:6) They have obeyed your word...
?今他们知道，凡你所赐给我的，都是从你那里来的； (17:7) and now they know that everything  you gave me comes from you.
因为你所赐给我的道，我已经赐给他们。他们也领受了， I gave them the message that you gave me,  and they received it.
又?实知道，我是从你出来的， They know that it is true  that I came from you...
并?信你差了我来。 (17:8) and they believe that you sent me.
我为他们??， I pray for them.
不为世???，?为你所赐给我的???， I do not pray for the world,  but for those you gave me...
因他们本是你的。 (17:9) for they belong to you.
凡是我的都是你的， All I have is yours...
你的也是我的， and all you have is mine.
并?我因他们得了?耀。(17:10)  And my glory is shown through them.
从今以后，我不在世上， And now I am coming to you.
他们?在世上；我往你那里?。 I am no longer in the world,  but they are in the world.
圣父啊，?你因你所赐给我的名保守他们， Holy Father, keep them safe  by the power of your name...
圣父啊，?你因你所赐给我的名保守他们， the name you gave me...
叫他们合而为一， so that they may be one...
像我们一样。 (17:11) just as you and I are one.
我与他们魂在的时候， While I was with them, I kept them safe  by the power of your name...
因你所赐给我的名保守了他们， the name you gave me.
我也护卫了他们； I protected them,  and not one of them was lost...
?中除了那灭亡之子，没有一个灭亡的，好叫经上的话得应验。 (17:12) except the man who was bound to be lost,  so that the Scripture might come true.
现在我往你那里?，我还在世上说这话， And now, I am coming to you,  and I say these things in the world...
是叫他们心里充满我的喜乐。(17:13) so that they may have my joy in their hearts  in all its fullness.
我已将你的道赐给他们。世界又恨他们， I gave them your message,  and the world hated them...
因为他们不属世界，正?我不属世界一样。 (17:14) because they do not belong to the world,  just as I do not belong to the world.
我不?你叫他们离开世界， I do not ask you  to take them out of the world...
只?你保守他们脱离那恶者（注：或作“ 脱离罪恶”）。 (17:15) but I do ask you to keep them safe  from the Evil One.
他们不属世界，正?我不属世界一样。 (17:16) Just as I do not belong to the world,  they do not belong to the world.
?你用真理使他们成圣， Dedicate them to yourself  by means of the truth.
你的道就是真理。  (17:17) Your Word is truth.
你怎样差我到世上，我也照样差他们到世上。 (17:18) I sent them into the world,  just as you sent me into the world.
我为他们的缘故，自己分别为圣， And for their sake,  I dedicate myself to you...
叫他们也因真理成圣。  (17:19) in order that they, too,  may be truly dedicated to you.
我不但为这些???，也为那些因他们的话信我的???， (17:20) I pray not only for them, but also for those  who believe in me because of their message.
使他们都合而为一。 I pray that they may all be one.
正?你父在我里面，我在你里面，使他们也在我们里面， Father...
正?你父在我里面，我在你里面，使他们也在我们里面， may they be in us,  just as you are in me and I am in you.
叫世?可以信你差了我来。(17:21) May they be one, so that the world  will believe that you sent me.
你所赐给我的?耀，我已赐给他们， I gave them the same glory you gave me...
使他们合而为一，像我们合而为一。  (17:22) so that they may be one,  just as you and I are one...
我在他们里面，你在我里面， I in them, and you in me...
使他们完完??地合而为一， so that they may be completely one...
叫世?知道你差了我来， in order that the world may know  that you sent me...
也知道你爱他们?魂爱我一样。 (17:23) and that you love them as you love me.
父啊，我在哪里， Father, you have given them to me...
愿你所赐给我的?也魂我在那里， and I want them to be with me where I am...
叫他们看见你所赐给我的?耀。 so that they may see my glory,  the glory you gave me...
因为创立世界以?，你已经爱我了。(17:24) for you loved me  before the world was made.
公义的父啊， Righteous Father...
世?未曾?识你，我??识你， the world does not know you,  but I know you...
这些?也知道你差了我来。(17:25) and these know that you sent me.
我已将你的名指示他们，还要指示他们， I made you known to them,  and I will continue to do so...
使你所爱我的爱在他们里面，  in order that the love you have for me  may be in them...
我也在他们里面。”(17:26) and so that I also may be in them.
耶稣说了这话， After Jesus had said this prayer...
就魂门徒出?，过了汲沦溪， he left with his disciples  and went across Kidron Brook.
在那里有一个园子， There was a garden in that place...
他和门徒进?了。 (18:1) and Jesus and his disciples went in.
卖耶稣的漠大也知道那地方， Judas, the traitor, knew where it was...
因为耶稣和门徒屡次上那里?聚集。(18:2) because many times  Jesus had met there with his disciples.
漠大领了一队兵 So Judas went to the garden,  taking with him a group of Roman soldiers...
和祭司长并法利??的差役， and some temple guards  sent by the chief priests and the Pharisees.
拿着灯笼、火把、兵?，就来到园里。 (18:3) They were armed,  and carried lanterns and torches.
耶稣知道将要临到自己的一?事， Jesus knew everything  that was going to happen to him...
就出来对他们说： so he stepped forward and asked them.:
“你们找谁？” (18:4) 他们回答说：“找拿?勒?耶稣。 -Who is it you are looking for?  -Jesus of Nazareth.
”耶稣说：“我就是！”卖他的漠大也魂他们站在那里。  Judas, the traitor,  was standing there with them...
”耶稣说：“我就是！”卖他的漠大也魂他们站在那里。  when Jesus said to them.:
”耶稣说：“我就是！”卖他的漠大也魂他们站在那里。 (18:5) I am he.
耶稣一说“我就是”，他们就退后倒在地上。 (18:6) They moved back and fell to the ground.
他又问他们说： Again Jesus asked them.:
“你们找谁？” Who is it you are looking for?
他们说：“找拿?勒?耶稣。” (18:7) Jesus of Nazareth.
耶稣说：“我已经告诉你们，我就是。 I have already told you that I am he.
你们?找我， If, then, you are looking for me...
就?这些??吧！” (18:8) let these others go.
这要应验耶稣从?的话，说： He said this so that  what he had said might come true.:
“你所赐给我的?，我没有失落一个。” (18:9) "Father, I have not lost  even one of those you gave me. "
西门彼得带着一把刀，就拔出来， Simon Peter, who had a sword, drew it  and struck the High Priest's slave...
将大祭司的??砍了一刀，削掉他的右耳， cutting off his right ear.
那??名叫马勒古。(18:10) The name of the slave was Malchus.
耶稣就对彼得说：“收刀??吧！ Put your sword back in its place!
我父所给我的那杯，我?可不喝呢？” (18:11) Do you think that I will not drink the cup  of suffering which my Father has given me?
那队兵和?夫长并漠太?的差役 Then the Roman soldiers,  with their commanding officer...
就拿住耶稣， and the Jewish guards arrested Jesus...
把他捆绑了，(18:12) tied him up...
先带到亚那面?， and took him first to Annas.
因为亚那是本年作大祭司该亚法的岳父。(18:13) He was the father-in-law of Caiaphas,  who was High Priest that year.
这该亚法就是从?向漠太?发议论 It was Caiaphas who had advised  the Jewish authorities...
说“一个?替百姓死是有益的”那位。 (18:14) that it was better  that one man should die for all the people.
西门彼得跟着耶稣，还有一个门徒跟着。 Simon Peter and another disciple  followed Jesus.
那门徒是大祭司所?识的， That other disciple was well known  to the High Priest...
他就魂耶稣进了大祭司的院子， (18:15) so he went with Jesus into the courtyard  of the High Priest's house...
彼得?站在门外。 while Peter stayed outside by the gate.
大祭司所?识的那个门徒出来，和看门的使女说了一声， Then the other disciple went back out,  spoke to the girl at the gate...
就领彼得进?。 (18:16) and brought Peter inside.
那看门的使女对彼得说：“你不也是这?的门徒吗？” Aren't you also one of the disciples  of that man?
他说：“我不是。” (18:17) No, I am not.
??和差役因为天冷，就生了炭火， It was cold, so the servants and guards  had built a charcoal fire...
站在那里烤火， and were standing around it,  warming themselves.
彼得也魂他们站着烤火。 (18:18) So Peter went over and stood with them,  warming himself.
大祭司就以耶稣的门徒和他的教训盘问他。  (18:19) The High Priest questioned Jesus  about his disciples and about his teaching.
耶稣回答说： Jesus answered.:
“我从来是明明地对世?说话。 I have always spoken publicly to everyone.
我常在会堂和殿里， All my teaching was done...
就是漠太?聚集的地方教训?， in the synagogues and in the Temple,  where all the people come together.
我在暗地里并没有说什么。  (19:20) I have never said anything in secret.
你为什么问我呢？ Why, then, do you question me?
可以问那听见的?，我对他们说的是什么； Question the people who heard me.  Ask them what I told them.
我所说的，他们都知道。” (19:21) They know what I said.
耶稣说了这话，旁边站着的一个差役用手掌打他，说：“你这样回答大祭司吗？”(19:22) How dare you talk like that  to the High Priest?
耶稣说：“我?说得不是， If I have said anything wrong...
你可以指证那不是； tell everyone here what it was.
我?说得是， But if I am right in what I have said...
你为什么打我呢？” (19:23) why do you hit me?
亚那就把耶稣解到大祭司该亚法那里，?是捆着解?的。 (19:24) Then Annas sent him, still tied up,  to Caiaphas, the High Priest.
西门彼得正站着烤火， Peter was still standing there,  keeping himself warm.
有?对他说： So the others said to him.:
“你不也是他的门徒吗？” "Aren't you also one  of the disciples of that man?"
彼得不承?，说：“我不是！”  No, I am not.
彼得不承?，说：“我不是！” (19:25) But Peter denied it.
有大祭司的一个??， One of the High Priest's slaves...
是彼得削掉耳朵那?的?属，说： a relative of the man  whose ear Peter had cut off, spoke up.
“我不是看见你魂他在园子里吗？” (19:26) 彼得又不承?。 -Didn't I see you with him in the garden?  -No.
立时鸡就叫了。 (18:27) And at once, a rooster crowed.
众?将耶稣从该亚法那里往衙门内解?，那时天还早， Early in the morning...
众?将耶稣从该亚法那里往衙门内解?，那时天还早， Jesus was taken from Caiaphas' house  to the governor's palace.
他们自己?不进衙门， The Jewish authorities  did not go inside the palace...
恐怕?了污秽， for they wanted  to keep themselves ritually clean...
不能颈逾越节的筵席。  (18:28) in order to be able to eat the Passover meal.
彼拉多就出来，到他们那里，说： So Pilate went outside to them and asked.:
“你们告这?是为什么事呢？” (18:29) What do you accuse this man of?
他们回答说：“这??不是作恶的，我们就不把他交给你。” (18:30) We would not have brought him to you  if he had not committed a crime.
彼拉多说：“你们自己带他?，按着你们的律法诀问他吧！” Then you yourselves take him  and try him according to your own law.
漠太?说：“我们没有杀?的?柄。” (18:31) We are not allowed to put anyone to death.
这要应验耶稣所说 This happened in order to make come true  what Jesus had said...
自己将要怎样死的话了。 (18:32) when he indicated  the kind of death he would die.
彼拉多又进了衙门，叫耶稣来，对他说： Pilate went back into the palace  and called Jesus.
“你是漠太?的王吗？”(18:33)  Are you the King of the Jews?
耶稣回答说：“这话是你自己说的， Does this question come from you...
还是别?论我对你说的呢？” (18:34) or have others told you about me?
彼拉多说：“我?是漠太?呢？ Do you think I am a Jew?
你本国的?和祭司长把你交给我， It was your own people and the chief priests  who handed you over to me.
你做了什么事呢？” (18:35) What have you done?
耶稣回答说：“我的国不属这世界。 My kingdom does not belong to this world.
我的国?属这世界， If my kingdom belonged to this world...
我的臣?必要争战，使我不至于被交给漠太?； my followers would fight to keep me from  being handed over to the Jewish authorities.
只是我的国不属这世界。” (18:36) No. My kingdom does not belong here.
彼拉多就对他说：“这样，你是王吗？”耶稣回答说：“你说我是王， -Are you a king, then?  -You say that I am a king.
我为此而生，也为此来到世间， I was born and came into the world  for this one purpose...
特为给真理作见证。 to speak about the truth.
凡属真理的?就听我的话。” (18:37) Whoever belongs to the truth listens to me.
彼拉多说：“真理是什么呢？” And what is truth?
说了这话，又出来到漠太?那里，对他们说： Then Pilate went back outside  to the people and said to them.:
“我查不出他有什么罪来，  (18:38) I cannot find any reason  to condemn him. But....
但你们有个规矩， According to the custom you have...
在逾越节要我给你们释放一个?， I always set free a prisoner for you  during the Passover!
你们要我给你们释放漠太?的王吗？” (18:39) Do you want me to set free for you  "the King of the Jews"?
他们又喊着说：“不要这? No!
他们又喊着说：“不要这?， They answered him with a shout.:
要巴拉巴！” Give us Barabbas!
这巴拉巴是个?盗。  (18:40) Barabbas was a bandit.
当下彼拉多将耶稣鞭打了。 (19:1) Then Pilate took Jesus  and had him whipped.
兵丁用荆棘编作冠冕 The soldiers made a crown  out of thorny branches...
戴在他头上， and put it on his head.
给他穿上紫袍， (19:2) Then they put a purple robe on him  and came to him and said:
又挨近他说：“恭喜漠太?的王啊！” "Long live the King of the Jews!"
他们就用手掌打他。 (19:3) And they went up and slapped him.
彼拉多又出来对众?说： Pilate went back out once more  and said to the crowd.:
“我带他出来见你们， Look, I will bring him out here to you...
叫你们知道我查不出他有什么罪来。” (19:4) to let you see that I cannot find  any reason to condemn him.
耶稣出来，戴着荆棘冠冕，穿着紫袍。彼拉多对他们说：“你们看这个?！” Look, here is the man.
耶稣出来，戴着荆棘冠冕，穿着紫袍。彼拉多对他们说：“你们看这个?！” So Jesus came out...
耶稣出来，戴着荆棘冠冕，穿着紫袍。彼拉多对他们说：“你们看这个?！” (19:5) wearing the crown of thorns  and the purple robe.
祭司长和差役看见他，就喊着说：“钉他十字架！钉他十字架！” Crucify him!
彼拉多说：“你们自己把他钉十字架吧！ You take him, then, and crucify him.
我查不出他有什么罪来。” (19:6) I find no reason to condemn him.
漠太?回答说：“我们有律法，按那律法，他是该死的！ We have a law that says he ought to die...
因他以自己为　神的儿子。” (19:7) because he claimed to be the Son of God!
彼拉多听见这话，越发害怕。 (19:8) When Pilate heard this,  he was even more afraid.
又进衙门，对耶稣说： He went back into the palace  and asked Jesus.:
“你是哪里来的？” Where do you come from?
耶稣?不回答。 (19:9) But Jesus did not answer.
彼拉多说：“你不对我说话吗？ You will not speak to me?
你?不知我有?柄释放你， Remember, I have the authority  to set you free...
也有?柄把你钉十字架吗？” (19:10) and also to have you crucified.
耶稣回答说：“?不是从上头赐给你的， You have authority over me...
你就毫无?柄办我， only because it was given to you by God.
所以把我交给你的那?， So the man who handed me over to you...
罪更重了。” (19:11) is guilty of a worse sin.
从此彼拉多想要释放耶稣，无奈漠太?喊着说： When Pilate heard this,  he tried to find a way to set Jesus free.
“你?释放这个?，就不是凯?的忠臣（注：原文作“朋友”）。 If you set him free,  that means you are not the Emperor's friend.
凡以自己为王的，就是背叛凯?了。” (19:12) Anyone who claims to be a king  is a rebel against the Emperor.
彼拉多听见这话，就带耶稣出来， When Pilate heard these words,  he took Jesus outside...
到了一个地方，名叫?华石处， and sat down on the judge's seat  in the place called "The Stone Pavement. "
希伯来话叫厄巴大，就在那里坐堂。 (19:13) In Hebrew, the name is Gabbatha.
那?是预备逾越节的?子。约有午正， It was then almost noon  of the day before the Passover.
彼拉多对漠太?说： Pilate said to the people.:
“看哪，这是你们的王！” (19:14) Here is your king.
他们喊着说：“除掉他！除掉他！ Kill him!
钉他在十字架上！” Crucify him!
彼拉多说：“我可以把你们的王钉十字架吗？” Do you want me to crucify your king?
祭司长回答说：“除了凯?，我们没有王！” (19:15) The only king we have is the Emperor.
于是，彼拉多将耶稣交给他们?钉十字架。 (19:16) Then Pilate handed Jesus over to them  to be crucified.
他们就把耶稣带了?。耶稣背着自己的十字架出来， So they took charge of Jesus.  He went out, carrying his cross...
到了一个地方，名叫髑髅地， and came to "The Place of the Skull, "  as it is called.
希伯来话叫各各他。(19:17) In Hebrew, it is called Golgotha.
他们就在那里钉他在十字架上， There they crucified him.  And they also crucified two other men...
还有两个?和他一魂钉着，一边一个，耶稣在中间。 (19:18) one on each side, with Jesus between them.
彼拉多又用牌子写了一个名号，安在十字架上， Pilate wrote a notice  and had it put on the cross.:
写的是：“漠太?的王，拿?勒?耶稣。” (19:19) "Jesus of Nazareth, the King of the Jews"  is what he wrote.
有许多漠太?念这名号， Many people read it...
因为耶稣被钉十字架的地方， because the place  where Jesus was crucified...
与城相近， was not far from the city.
并?是用希伯来、罗马、希腊?样文字写的。 (19:20) The notice was written  in Hebrew, Latin, and Greek.
漠太?的祭司长就对彼拉多说： The Chief Priest said to Pilate:
“不要写‘漠太?的王’， "Do not write 'The King of the Jews, '  but rather:
要写‘他自己说我是漠太?的王’。” (19:21) "This man said, 'I am King of the Jews."'
彼拉多说：“我所写的，我已经写上了。” (19:22) What I have written stays written.
兵丁既?将耶稣钉在十字架上，就拿他的衣服 After the soldiers had crucified Jesus,  they took his clothes...
分为四份，每兵一份； and divided them into four parts,  one part for each soldier.
又拿他的里衣， They also took the robe...
这件里衣原来没有缝儿，是上下一?织成的。 (19:23) which was made of one piece  of woven cloth without any seams in it.
他们就彼此说： The soldiers said to one another.:
“我们不要撕开，只要拈阄，看谁得着。” "Let's not tear it,  let's throw dice to see who will get it. "
这要应验经上的话说： This happened in order  to make the scripture come true.:
“他们分了我的外衣，为我的里衣拈阄。” "They divided my clothes among themselves  and gambled for my robe. "
兵丁果?做了这事。 (19:24) And this is what the soldiers did.
站在耶稣十字架旁边的，有他母? Standing close to Jesus' cross  were his mother...
与他母?的姊妹，并革罗罢的?子马利亚和 his mother's sister, Mary,  the wife of Clopas...
抹大拉的马利亚。 (19:25) and Mary Magdalene.
耶稣见母?和他所爱的那门徒 Jesus saw his mother  and the disciple he loved...
站在旁边， standing there.
就对他母?说：“母?（注：原文作“妇?”），看，你的儿子！”(19:26) He is your son.
又对那门徒说： Then he said to the disciple.:
“看，你的母?！” She is your mother.
从此那门徒就接她到自己家里?了。 (19:27) From that time,  the disciple took her to live in his home.
这事以后，耶稣知道各样的事已经成了， Jesus knew that by now  everything had been completed...
为要使经上的话应验，就说： and in order to make  the Scripture come true, he said.:
“我渴了。” (19:28) I am thirsty.
有一个?皿盛满了醋，放在那里， A bowl was there, full of cheap wine...
他们就拿海?蘸满了醋，绑在牛膝草上， so a sponge was soaked in the wine,  put on a stalk of hyssop...
送到他口。 (19:29) and lifted up to his lips.
耶稣尝（注：原文作“受”）了那醋，就说： Jesus drank the wine.
“成了！”， It is finished.
便低下头，将灵魂交付　神了。 (19:30) Then he bowed his head  and gave up his spirit.
漠太?因这?是预备?，又因那安息?是个大?， Then the Jewish authorities asked Pilate...
就?彼拉多叫?打断他们的腿， to allow them to break the legs  of the men who had been crucified...
把他们拿?， and to take the bodies down  from the crosses.
免得尸首当安息? They requested this because it was Friday...
免得尸首当安息? and they did not want the bodies  to stay on the crosses on the Sabbath...
留在十字架上。 (19:31) since the coming Sabbath  was especially holy.
于是兵丁来，把头一个?的腿， So the soldiers went and broke the legs  of the first man...
并与耶稣魂钉第二个?的腿都打断了。 (19:32) and then of the other man  who had been crucified with Jesus.
只是来到耶稣那里，见他已经死了， But when they came to Jesus,  they saw that he was already dead...
就不打断他的腿。 (19:33) so they did not break his legs.
惟有一个兵拿?扎他的肋旁， One of the soldiers, however,  plunged his spear into Jesus' side...
随即有血 And at once blood...
和水流出来。(19:34) and water poured out.
看见这事的那? The one who saw this happen  has spoken of it...
就作见证， so that you may also believe.
他的见证也是真的，并?他知道自己所说的是真的，叫你们也可以信。 (19:35) What he said is true,  and he knows that he speaks the truth.
这些事成了，为要应验经上的话说： This was done  to make the Scripture come true:
“他的骨头一根也不可折断。” (19:36) "Not one of his bones will be broken. "
经上又有一句说： And there is another scripture that says:
“他们要仰望自己所扎的?。” (19:37) "People will look at him,  whom they pierced. "
这些事以后，有亚利马太?约瑟， After this, Joseph,  who was from the town of Arimathea...
是耶稣的门徒，只因怕漠太?，就暗暗地作门徒。他来?彼拉多，要把耶稣的身伐领?。 asked Pilate if he could take Jesus' body.
是耶稣的门徒，只因怕漠太?，就暗暗地作门徒。他来?彼拉多，要把耶稣的身伐领?。 Joseph was a follower of Jesus,  but in secret...
是耶稣的门徒，只因怕漠太?，就暗暗地作门徒。他来?彼拉多，要把耶稣的身伐领?。 because he was afraid  of the Jewish authorities...
彼拉多允准， Pilate told him he could have the body...
他就把耶稣的身伐领?了。 (19:38) so Joseph went and took it away.
又有尼哥德慕，就是先?夜里?见耶稣的， Nicodemus, who at first had gone  to see Jesus at night...
带着没药和沉香约有一百斤?来。 went with Joseph...
带着没药和沉香约有一百斤?来。 taking with him  about 100 pounds of spices...
带着没药和沉香约有一百斤?来。(19:39) a mixture of myrrh and aloe.
他们就照漠太?殡葬的规矩，把耶稣的身伐用细麻布加上香料裹好了。 The two men took Jesus' body  and wrapped it in linen cloths...
他们就照漠太?殡葬的规矩，把耶稣的身伐用细麻布加上香料裹好了。 with the spices...
他们就照漠太?殡葬的规矩，把耶稣的身伐用细麻布加上香料裹好了。 (19:40) according to the Jewish custom  of preparing a body for burial.
在耶稣钉十字架的地方有一个园子， There was a garden in the place  where Jesus had been put to death...
园子里有一座新坟墓，是从来没有葬过?的。  (19:41) and in it there was a new tomb,  where no one had ever been buried.
只因是漠太?的预备?， Since it was the day before the Sabbath...
又因那坟墓近， and because the tomb was close by...
他们就把耶稣安放在那里。(19:42) they placed Jesus' body there.
??的第一??早，天还黑的时候， Early on Sunday morning,  while it was still dark...
抹大拉的马利亚来到坟墓那里， Mary Magdalene went to the tomb...
看见石头从坟墓挪开了， (20:1) and saw that the stone  had been taken away from the entrance.
就跑来见西门彼得和耶稣所爱的那个门徒，对他们说： She went running to Simon Peter  and the other disciple, whom Jesus loved.
“有?把主从坟墓里挪了?，我们不知道放在哪ǎ　 (20:2) They have taken the Lord from the tomb,  and we don't know where they have put him.
彼得和那门徒就出来，往坟墓那里?。 (20:3) Then Peter and the other disciple  went to the tomb.
两个?魂跑， The two of them were running...
那门徒比彼得跑得更快，先到了坟墓， (20:4) but the other disciple ran faster than Peter  and reached the tomb first.
低头往里看，就见细麻布还放在那ǎ He bent over and saw the linen cloths...
只是没有进?。 (20:5) but he did not go in.
西门彼得随后也到了， Behind him came Simon Peter...
进坟墓里?， and he went straight into the tomb.
就看见细麻布还放在那ǎ (20:6) He saw the linen cloths lying there...
又看见耶稣的裹头巾 and the cloth  which had been around Jesus' head.
没有和细麻布放在一处，是另在一处卷着。 (20:7) It was not lying with the linen cloths,  but was rolled up by itself.
先到坟墓的那门徒也进?， Then the other disciple,  who had reached the tomb first also went in.
看见就信了。(20:8) He saw and believed.
因为他们还不明白圣经的意思，就是耶稣必要从死里复活。(20:9) They still did not understand the Scripture  which said he must rise from death.
于是两个门徒回自己的住处?了。 (20:10) Then the disciples went back home.
马利亚?站在坟墓外面哭， Mary stood crying outside the tomb.
哭的时候，低头往坟墓里看，(20:11) While she was still crying,  she bent over and looked in the tomb...
就见两个天使，穿着白衣， and saw two angels there dressed in white...
在安放耶稣身伐的地方坐着， sitting where the body of Jesus had been...
一个在头，一个在脚。 (20:12) one at the head, the other at the feet.
天使对她说：“妇?，你为什么哭？” "Woman, why are you crying?"  they asked her.
她说：“因为有?把我主挪了?，　  They have taken my Lord away...
我不知道放在哪里。”(20:13) and I do not know where they have put him.
说了这话，就转过身来，看见耶稣站在那里， Then she turned around  and saw Jesus standing there...
?不知道是耶稣。 (20:14) but she did not know that it was Jesus.
耶稣问她说：“妇?，为什么哭？ Woman, why are you crying?
你找谁呢？” Who is it that you are looking for?
马利亚以为是看园的，就对他说： She thought he was the gardener,  so she said to him.:
“先生，?是你把他移了?， If you took him away, sir...
?告诉我你把他放在哪里，我便??他。” (20:15) tell me where you have put him,  and I will go and get him.
耶稣说：“马利亚！”  Mary.
马利亚就转过来，用希伯来话对他说： She turned toward him and said in Hebrew.:
“拉波尼 Rabboni!
（拉波尼就是夫子的意思）！”(20:16) This means "Teacher. "
耶稣说：“不要摸我， Do not hold on to me...
因我还没有升上?见我的父。 because I have not yet gone  back up to the Father.
你往我弟兄那里?，告诉他们说：我要升上?见我的父， But go to my brothers and tell them  I am returning to Him who is my Father...
也是你们的父； and their Father...
见我的　神，也是你们的　神。” (20:17) my God and their God.
抹大拉的马利亚就?告诉门徒说：“我已经看见了主！” So Mary Magdalene went and told  the disciples that she had seen the Lord...
她又将主对她说的这话告诉他们。 (20:18) and related to them what he had told her.
那?（就是??的第一?）晚上，门徒所在的地方， It was late that Sunday evening...
因怕漠太?， and the disciples were gathered together  behind locked doors...
门都关了。 because they were afraid  of the Jewish authorities.
耶稣来站在当中， Then Jesus came and stood among them.
对他们说：“愿你们?安！” (20:19) Peace be with you.
说了这话，就把手和肋旁指给他们看。 After saying this,  he showed them his hands and his side.
门徒看见主，就喜乐了。 (20:20) The disciples were filled with joy  at seeing the Lord.
耶稣又对他们说： Jesus said to them again.:
“愿你们?安！ Peace be with you.
父怎样差?了我，我也照样差?你们。”(20:21) As the Father sent me, so I send you.
说了这话，就向他们吹一口?，说： Then he breathed on them.
“你们受圣灵。 (20:22) Receive the Holy Spirit.
你们b免谁的罪，谁的罪就b免了； If you forgive people's sins,  they are forgiven.
你们留下谁的罪， If you do not forgive them...
谁的罪就留下了。” (20:23) they are not forgiven.
那十二个门徒中，有称为低土马的多马， One of the twelve disciples, Thomas,  called the Twin...
耶稣来的时候，他没有和他们魂在。 (20:24) was not with them when Jesus came.
那些门徒就对他说：“我们已经看见主了。” So the other disciples told him,  "We have seen the Lord. "
多马?说：“我憧醇他手上的钉痕， Unless I see the scars of the nails  in his hands...
用指头探?那钉痕，又用手探?他的肋旁， and put my finger on those scars,  and my hand in his side...
我总不信。”(20:25)  I will not believe.
过了八?，门徒又在屋里， A week later,  the disciples were together again indoors...
多马也和他们魂在。 and Thomas was with them.
门都关了。耶稣来站在当中说： The doors were locked,  but Jesus came and stood among them.
“愿你们?安！” (20:26) 就对多马说：“伸过你的指头来，摸（注：“摸”原文作“看”）我的手； Peace be with you.  Put your finger here, and look at my hands.
伸出你的手来，探?我的肋旁。 Then reach out your hand  and put it in my side.
不要疑惑，总要信！” (20:27) Stop your doubting and believe.
多马说：“我的主，我的　神！” (20:28) My Lord, and my God.
耶稣对他说：“你因看见了我才信， Do you believe because you see me?
那没有看见就信的有福了！” (20:29)  How happy are those  who believe without seeing me.
耶稣在门徒面?另外行了许多神?， In his disciples' presence,  Jesus performed many other miracles...
没有记在这书上。　(20:30) which are not written down in this book.
但记这些事， But these have been written...
要叫你们信耶稣是基督， in order that you may believe  that Jesus is the Messiah...
是　神的儿子， the Son of God...
并?叫你们信了他，就可以因他的名得生命。  (20:31) and that through your faith in him,  you may have life.
这些事以后， After this, Jesus appeared once more  to his disciples...
耶稣在提比哩亚海边又向门徒显现。 at Lake Tiberias.
他怎样显现记在下面： (21:1) This is how it happened.:
有西门彼得和称为低土马的多马， Simon Peter, Thomas, called the Twin...
并加利利的迦拿?拿但业，还有西庇太的两个儿子， Nathanael, the one from Cana in Galilee,  the sons of Zebedee...
又有两个门徒，都在一处。 (21:2) and two other disciples of Jesus  were all together.
西门彼得对他们说：“我打话?。” Simon Peter said to the others.:
他们说：“我们也和你魂?。” -I am going fishing.  -We will come with you.
他们说：“我们也和你魂?。” "We will come with you, " they told him.
他们就出?，上了船，那一夜并没有打着什么。(21:3) So they went out in a boat,  but all that night they did not catch a thing.
天将亮的时候，耶稣站在岸上， As the sun was rising,  Jesus stood at the water's edge...
门徒?不知道是耶稣。 (21:4) but the disciples did not know  that it was Jesus.
耶稣就对他们说：“小子！你们有颈的没有？” Young men, haven't you caught anything?
他们回答说：“没有！” (21:5) Not a thing!
耶稣说：“你们把网?在船的右边，就必得着。” Throw your net out on the right side  of the boat, and you will catch some.
他们便?下网?， So they threw the net out...
竟拉不上来了， and could not pull it back in...
因为话甚多。(21:6) because they had caught so many fish.
耶稣所爱的那门徒对彼得说： The disciple whom Jesus loved  said to Peter.:
“是主！” It is the Lord.
那时西门彼得赤着身子，一听见是主， When Peter heard that it was the Lord...
就束上一件外衣， he wrapped his outer garment around him,  for he had taken his clothes off...
跳在海里。 (21:7) and jumped into the water.
?余的门徒离岸不远，约有二百肘（注：古代以肘为尺，一肘约有今时尺半）， The other disciples came to shore  in the boat, pulling the net full of fish.
就在小船上把那网话拉过来。 (21:8) They were not very far from land,  about a hundred yards away.
他们上了岸， When they stepped ashore...
就看见那里有炭火，上面有话，又有饼。 (21:9) they saw a charcoal fire there  with fish on it and some bread.
耶稣对他们说：“把刚才打的话拿几条来。” (21:10) Bring some of the fish you have just caught.
西门彼得就?（注：或作“上船”），把网拉到岸上， Simon Peter went aboard  and dragged the net ashore full of big fish...
那网满了大话，共一百五十?条。 153 in all.
话虽这样多，网?没有?。(21:11) Even though there were so many,  still the net did not tear.
耶稣说：“你们来颈早饭。” Come, and eat.
门徒中没有一个敢问他：“你是谁？”， None of the disciples dared ask him,  "Who are you?"
因为知道是主。 (21:12) Because they knew it was the Lord.
耶稣就来拿饼和话 So Jesus went over, took the bread,  and gave it to them...
给他们。 (21:13) he did the same with the fish.
耶稣从死里复活以后向门徒显现， This, then, was the third time  Jesus appeared to his disciples...
这是第?次。 (21:14) after he was raised from death.
他们颈完了早饭，耶稣对西门彼得说： After they had eaten,  Jesus said to Simon Peter.:
“约翰的儿子西门（注：“约翰”在马太16章17节称“约拿”）， Simon, son of John...
你爱我比这些更深吗？” do you love me more than these others do?
彼得说：“主啊，是的，你知道我爱你。” Yes, Lord, you know that I love you.
耶稣对他说：“你喂养我的小羊。” (21:15) Take care of my lambs.
耶稣第二次又对他说： A second time Jesus said to him.:
“约翰的儿子西门，你爱我吗？” Simon, son of John, do you love me?
彼得说：“主啊，是的，你知道我爱你。” Yes, Lord, you know that I love you.
耶稣说：“你灵养我的羊。” (21:16) Take care of my sheep.
第?次对他说： A third time, Jesus said.:
“约翰的儿子西门， Simon, son of John...
你爱我吗？” do you love me?
彼得因为耶稣第?次对他说：“你爱我吗”，就忧愁， Peter became sad...
彼得因为耶稣第?次对他说：“你爱我吗”，就忧愁， because Jesus asked him the third time.:
彼得因为耶稣第?次对他说：“你爱我吗”，就忧愁， "Do you love me?"
对耶稣说： And so he said to him.:
“主啊， Lord...
你是无所不知的， you know everything.
你知道我爱你。” You know that I love you.
耶稣说：“你喂养我的羊。 (21:17) Take care of my sheep.
我实实在在地告诉你： I am telling you the truth.
你年少的时候， When you were young...
自己束上带子，随意往来； you used to get ready  and go anywhere you wanted to.
但年老的时候，你要伸出手来， But when you are old,  you will stretch out your hands...
别?要把你束上，带你到不愿意?的地方。” (21:18) and someone else will tie you up  and take you where you don't want to go.
耶稣说这话，是指着彼得要怎样死， In saying this, Jesus was indicating  the way in which Peter would die...
?耀　神。 and bring glory to God.
说了这话，就对他说： Then Jesus said to him:
“你跟从我吧！” (21:19) Follow me.
彼得转过来，看见耶稣所爱的那门徒跟着， Peter turned around and saw behind him  that other disciple whom Jesus loved...
就是在晚饭的时候，靠着耶稣胸膛说 the one who had leaned close to Jesus  at the meal and had asked.:
“主啊，卖你的是谁”的那门徒。　 (21:20) 彼得看见他，就问耶稣说： "Lord, who is going to betray you?"  When Peter saw him, he asked.:
“主啊，这?将来?何？” (21:21) Lord, what about this man?
耶稣对他说：“我?要他等到我来的时候，与你何干？ If I want him to live until I come,  what is that to you?
你跟从我吧！” (21:22) Follow me.
于是这话传在弟兄中间，说那门徒不死； So a report spread among the followers  of Jesus that this disciple would not die.
?实耶稣不是说他不死， But Jesus did not say he would not die.
乃是说：“我?要他等到我来的时候，与你何干？” (21:23) He said, "If I want him to live until I come,  what is that to you?"
为这些事作见证，并?记载这些事的 He is the disciple  who spoke of these things...
就是这门徒。 the one who also wrote them down...
我们也知道他的见证是真的。 (21:24) and we know that what he said is true.
耶稣所行的事还有许多； Now, there are many other things  that Jesus did.
?是一一的都写出来，我想， If they were all written down one by one,  I suppose that the whole world...
所写的书，就是世界也?不下了。 (21:25) could not hold the books  that would be written.
“约翰福音” -=结束=-
-------------------------- 本字幕禁止提供做?何商业用途 本字幕根据中文和合本圣经编辑 禁止对字句文意做?何囊改?解 --------------------------
-------------------------- 圣经上说 我向一?听见这书上预言的作见证， ?有?在这预言上加添什么， 神必将写在这书上的灾祸加在他身上；(?示录22:18) --------------------------
--------------------------  这书上的预言，?有?删?什么，　 神必从这书上所写的生命树和圣城删?他的分。(?示录22:19)