Turkish troops advance
into northern Syria,
opening up a complex new front
in the conflict.
Turkey is acting against a Kurdish
militia that has been
fighting Islamic State,
but it regards as
a terrorist group.
Turkey is clearly committed
militarily to this operation,
and has widespread popular support
here.
But if the Turks suffer losses
or a civilian casualties
grow, that could change.
With an emergency debate due
at the United Nations tomorrow,
Turkey's being urged
to show restraint.
Also tonight:
Is your relationship with her over?
No comment.
Ukip leader Henry Bolton's personal
life costs him the support
of the party's ruling body -
now the membership
will decide his fate.
EXPLOSION.
The 12 hour battle to end
an attack on a Kabul hotel,
where foreign nationals
were targeted and killed.
Heavy rain brings flooding and
mudslides to South West England -
elsewhere snow and ice cause
problems on the roads.
And at last something
to cheer about down under,
as England win the one day series
against Australia.
Good evening.
Turkey is being urged to show
restraint tonight, as it continues
an offensive into northern Syria
that its feared will further
destabilise a war-torn region.
Turkish troops crossed the border
with Syria as part of a military
effort to target a Kurdish militia
in the province of Afrin.
The Kurdish group has been backed
by the United States in the fight
against so-called Islamic State.
But Turkey regards it
as a terrorist organisation.
From the border, Mark Lowen
reports on a potential
new front in the Syrian war.
As if Syria needed more of this.
Artillery fire from Turkey,
launching a new ground
and air offensive.
It's called Operation Olive Branch,
though it's anything
but a gesture of peace.
From the air, Turkish
F-16s struck yesterday.
Their target - the Syrian
Kurdish militia, or YPG.
Turkey sees them as terrorists,
linked to the outlawed PKK,
who have long fought an insurgency
in Turkey on behalf
of the Kurdish minority.
And it wants them pushed back
from the border town of Afrin.
Turkey's president has his own
troops fighting for their hero.
And with elections next year,
war rallies his support base.
TRANSLATION: This is
a national struggle,
and in this national struggle,
we will crush anyone
who stands against us.
That's a message that
resonates in border villages,
where grape grower Omer Gazel
and his friends watched the jets.
TRANSLATION: We felt proud
and happy as they took off.
Everyone came out
to bid them farewell.
But the YPG has backing, too.
Both in Syria, where Kurds
rallied today, and beyond.
TRANSLATION: We condemn
the attack on Afrin,
and we tell our brothers
there that they are in our hearts,
and that we are with them.
Because of the bravery
of the YPG heroes, we will win
the battle in Afrin.
The US armed them in the fight
against the Islamic State group,
infuriating Turkey.
France too voiced support
for them today, calling
on Turkey to pull back.
But the Turks are ploughing on.
This unverified footage posted
on pro-government media aiming
to prove Turkey's military might.
In the hills beside the border
we found a further build-up,
as the offensive shows no
sign of ending.
Reinforcements are perched here,
a show of strength, ready to back up
the ground troops and fighter jets
who are ready inside Syria.
Every few minutes, you hear the thud
of an artillery strike.
Turkey has clearly committed
militarily to this operation,
and has widespread popular support
here.
But if the Turks suffer losses
or civilian casualties
grow, that could change.
And the risk is clear.
This border town was hit
by a rocket, said to be
from the YPG, killing one
and injuring more.
Turkey is on dangerous ground,
and a likely long, costly offensive
is only just beginning.
Tonight Turkey is looking
diplomatically isolated. The US,
France, Russia and Iran have spoken
out against the offensive, a
reminder of how Syria has dragged in
summary different powers fighting
their own proxy wars. France has
called on the UN Security Council to
discuss the operation tomorrow. But
it is the US most at odds with
Turkey. One has armed the YPG, the
other fighting to destroy it. Turkey
and the US are vital Nato members,
but this new front in the Syrian war
has thrown this vital relationship
towards breaking point.
Mark Lowen, thank you.
Ukip's National Executive Committee
has backed a vote of no confidence
in the party leader, Henry Bolton,
as he faces further questions
over his personal life.
After a brief relationship
with Jo Marney - whose texts
about Meghan Markle became public -
he says his personal life shouldn't
affect his political career.
Party members will now be asked
to vote on his future.
Here's our political
correspondent Ben Wright..
I'm not making any comment.
Shortly before Ukip's top brass met
to discuss their beleaguered
leader's fate, Henry Bolton
came out fighting.
You could at that point say
the National Executive Committee
of my own party don't have
confidence in me as leader,
I'd better stand down.
I could do but I shan't.
You won't?
No, I won't.
The former soldier has only been
in the job for months,
and it is his fleeting relationship
with 25-year-old Jo Marney that
has got him noticed.
Last week he dropped his
new girlfriend after it emerged
she had sent racist text messages
about Prince Harry's
fiancee, Meghan Markle.
But the two of them were then
spotted out at a London bar.
We're now talking about this
leadership thing being a moral
court, as to the state
of my marriage and my
personal relationships.
What is important to
the nation and to the voters,
and the 17.4 million people
who voted to leave
the European Union, is that this
country gets its independence back
from Brussels and that we can move
forward on that basis
towards being a confident nation.
Henry Bolton became the fourth
Ukip leader in a year,
and promised to bring fresh focus
to the fractious and
floundering party.
But even some of its leading
figures think it could now
be curtains for Ukip.
If we have got a situation
where we are wiped out
in the county council elections,
and then in the general election,
if we are wiped out again
in the district elections too,
then maybe people are going to have
to get round the table and say,
"Is the electorate is trying
to tell us something?
Is that, thank you very
much and good night?"
Earlier this month, the UK
National Executive agreed
to have an emergency meeting today
about their leader's recent antics.
Today's emergency Ukip meeting has
been held in huge secrecy,
and after a lot of digging,
we found out it is being held here,
in the office of the Ukip general
secretary, Paul Oakley,
who's a barrister.
Now this meeting will determine,
possibly, Henry Bolton's fate.
He went in insisting
he was not going to quit.
But it's clear that many
on the Ukip NEC want him to go.
The meeting lasted three hours,
and passed a unanimous vote
of no-confidence in the Ukip leader.
Henry was offered the opportunity
to resign but he has made clear
that he feels he is the right man
to lead the party forward.
And he will now go through
the process of defending himself
to the party via the EGM.
That means the wider Ukip membership
will have to endorse or reject
today's decision at a general
meeting within the next 28 days.
But for now, Henry Bolton soldiers
on without any support
at the top of his party.
Ben Wright, BBC News.
14 foreign nationals working
in the Afghan capital Kabul have
been targeted and killed
in a terrorist attack
on a major hotel.
It took Afghan security forces 12
hours to take control
of the Intercontinental Hotel,
killing the gunmen who stormed it.
Four Afghan citizens
were also killed.
The Taliban says it
carried out the attack.
Zia Shahreyar
reports from Kabul.
The final moments of a fight that
had lasted all night.
Gunfire and explosions,
as Afghan special forces
battle to regain control
of the Intercontinental Hotel.
One soldier throws a grenade.
He moves away, then the explosion.
The room is soon on fire.
Evidence of the struggle
that had taken place.
The Afghan national flag
waving from the roof,
proof that the building
has been retaken.
We are in the area.
You can see the Hotel
Intercontinental on the hill
in Kabul, and as you can see,
it has been burned, part
of the hotel has been burned.
And black smoke blackens
the southern part of the hotel.
More than 150 people,
including some foreigners,
were inside yesterday evening
when gunmen burst
in and opened fire.
Eyewitnesses said they
were after foreigners.
TRANSLATION: The attackers
were knocking on the door of each
room, trying to reach their targets.
They killed ordinary
people and officials.
They were also targeting foreigners.
These images filmed by local TV
showed people escaping by climbing
down the sheets that they had
tied to balconies.
This telecoms engineer fell
from the sixth floor
as he tried to get away.
TRANSLATION: When the sixth floor
caught fire this morning,
my roommates told me to either
burn or escape.
I got a bed sheet and
tied to the balcony.
I tried to come down but I was heavy
and my arms were not strong enough.
I fell down and injured
my shoulder and leg.
This sustained and complex assault
will prompt urgent questions
as to how the gunmen got through.
A 54-year-old man has been arrested,
after the death of an eight-year-old
girl from stab wounds.
Mylee Billingham was rushed
to hospital from a house
at Brownhills in the West Midlands,
but couldn't be saved.
Police are waiting to speak
to the man, who's also in hospital
with a stab wound to the stomach.
Officers say they're not
looking for anyone else.
Thousands of women are demonstrating
in Las Vegas tonight,
in the latest protest to mark
the anniversary of President
Trump's inauguration.
Rallies have already taken place
this weekend in other US
cities and in Europe.
In Las Vegas, women are being urged
to register to vote ahead of this
year's mid term US elections.
Rajini Vaidyanathan reports.
All the way from Paris to London, to
Las Vegas, women have been making
their voices heard. Last year we
were angry. And that's why we turned
out. This year we are organised and
that's why we are turning out.
Empowered, and I'm ready to get
people talking about these issues
and get people excited. A year into
Donald Trump's presidency and the
focus is not just on the man himself
but his policies. Many believe his
immigration plans adversely affect
women. He is pushing to make birth
control less accessible to women.
This is just ridiculous how he is
supposed to be for the people, but
he is against the people. In the
wake of the B2 movement and a
growing conversation around equal
pay, many are here to fight on other
issues. Franey, who came here with
her five-year-old daughter, this is
personal. For 12 years I was the
victim of domestic violence that my
children observed, now I am free,
finally, thank goodness, through no
help of the systems that are
supposed to help us. I hope the
world will listen and we can create
systematic change to help little
girls like Charlie and myself. One
way organisers think that change can
help is by getting more women to
register to vote and even run for
office. They are channelling their
energy on this year's mid-term
congressional elections. The state
of Nevada was picked for this rally
because it is a swing state, a
Senate is -- a Senate seat Democrats
believe they can win back. There may
be thousands of women here, but
don't forget, anyone the election
with a majority of white women
voters. Many of those think he is
doing a great job for women. And so,
like so many issues here in the
United States, even women's rights,
is one where this country is deeply
divided.
A former Premier League
footballer is about to become
president of the West African
nation of Liberia.
George Weah - who played for Chelsea
and Manchester City -
told the BBC he was ready to meet
the expectations of his people.
He will be sworn in tomorrow.
His victory is the latest
extraordinary chapter in Liberia's
emergence from the horrors
of civil war.
From the capital Monrovia, here's
our Africa Editor, Fergal Keane.
A fanfare for the people's man
who rose from the slums to become
an international football star,
and now president of his country.
How are you doing?
George Weah is the face
of a changing nation.
For the first time in over 70 years,
power is being transferred between
democratically elected leaders.
Can you possibly be as successful
a president as a footballer?
Well, you only look at me
as a former footballer,
but I am a human being.
I strive to be excellent,
and I can be successful.
COMMENTATOR: George Weah,
he has one to contend with,
he plays a 1-2, George Weah!
Today he was leading a team of
friends against an army selection.
And still scoring.
It was in Europe, playing for teams
like Chelsea and AC Milan,
that he became a legend.
Fifa Footballer of the Year.
George Weah inherits
a nation still struggling
with the legacy of war.
Nearly two thirds of the population
live below the poverty line.
In Claratown, the slum
where he grew up, they are hoping
he will bring jobs,
health care, housing.
When you come here to the streets
where George Weah grew up,
the scale of problems facing Liberia
is very clear.
For any kind of meaningful change
to take place, peace is essential,
and this is a generation that has
grown up without knowing war,
in a country that was once
a byword for anarchy.
In 14 years of war, a quarter
of a million people were killed.
Child soldiers like Joseph Duo
became symbols of pitiless violence.
Today, he's one of those looking
to George Weah in hope.
Like his nation, Joseph
is scarred by the past
but determined not to repeat it.
Doing homework with his children,
Joseph's life challenges those
who would write off a nation,
even a continent, as failed.
What do you hope George
Weah can do for you?
We hope he will design programmes
and bring investors,
Joseph tells me, so there will be
jobs, and we can have a better
Liberia than before.
Expectations are high.
Can George Weah possibly
meet them, I asked?
Whether or not I am going
to meet the expectations,
because the one thing,
when people love you,
you have to strive for them.
The Liberians love me,
for what I have done before
in my life, and to make
sure that they are OK,
I am going to do it again.
Football teaches that
you can't succeed alone,
and the new president has
the people on-side.
But, more than anything now,
George Weah is going
to need their patience.
Fergal Keane, BBC News, Monrovia.
Extreme weather is affecting
several parts of the UK,
with flooding and mudslides in South
west England and snow and ice
causing problems elsewhere.
The Met Office issued
yellow "be aware" warnings
for many parts today.
Tonight there's concern about ice
as temperatures fall
in North East England.
Phil Bodmer reports.
After the snow came the rain,
and with it, flooding.
The south-west bearing the brunt.
Police say a number
of roads are affected by
flood water and mud slides,
like here in Mudeford, North Devon.
At the Jack Russell
in at swing bridge
near Barnstaple, they were surveying
the damage caused by the flooding.
The kitchen's just as bad.
We've turned everything.
Emergency services helped others.
This flood water rose
in Barnstaple and Kuhn Martin.
In Scotland, two climbers
were airlifted to safety in
the Highlands.
The pair were winched to safety
from 3000 feet after a night
on the mountain in Glencoe.
Glasgow airport closed
for a brief period
this afternoon, so that the runway
could be cleared, after some very
heavy snow.
Well, tonight, much of Britain
remains in winter's icy grip.
Here in Leeds, gritting teams have
been working nonstop to keep
the road network sorted,
with temperatures hovering around
zero degrees.
Northern England also
experienced heavy snow.
This was South Yorkshire.
In Sheffield, drivers
left their cars
at home.
With forecasters predicting milder
conditions ahead, there may
be some better news
for commuters next week.
Phil Bodmer, BBC News.
With all the sport, here's
Lizzie Greenwood Hughes
at the BBC Sport Centre.
Thanks very much.
Good evening.
England's cricketers bounced-back
from their Ashes defeat by winning
the one-day series against Australia
with two games to spare.
Man of the match Jos Butler hit
a brilliant century in Sydney to set
the hosts a target of 303.
And despite losing fast bowler
Liam Plunkett to injury,
England went on to win by 16 runs.
Kyle Edmund says, "You have
to believe", after reaching his
first Grand Slam quarterfinal.
The British number two came
from a set down to make
it to the last eight
of the Australian Open Tennis,
as our correspondent
David Ornstein reports.
Carrying the hopes of a nation is no
easy task, but in the absence of
Andy Murray Britain has a new
flag-bearers. Kyle Edmund's rise has
been steady, his form spectacular.
It did seem that was about to change
when against Andreas Seppi he lost
the opening set and went down a
break of serve in the second. He was
quick to respond. A switch of shoes
coinciding with a change in fortune.
There was no looking back. A decade
Seppi's Junior, Edmund is the higher
ranked and soon the Gulf in quality
became apparent. Both men were
struggling -- hoping to reach a
grand slam semifinal --
quarterfinal. Edmund became the
first British man other than Murray
to make the last eight in Melbourne
since 1995. Hopefully we have more
British the future. For me,
personally, I'm very happy to get
through and I will keep doing my
best. I know people are waking up at
home at silly hours. I'm grateful
for that. He now faces Grigor
Dimitrov. Whatever the outcome,
Britain appears to have a new star
to celebrate.
David Ornstein, BBC News.
There was just one game
in the Premier League today.
Match of the Day 2 and Sportscene
are on BBC One later,
so if you don't want to know
the results, you know what to do.
Southampton are still in the bottom
three after drawing with Tottenham.
Harry Kane scored the Spurs goal,
and now only needs one more
to reach his 100th in the Premier
League.
And Hearts beat their Edinburgh
rivals Hibs to a place in the fifth
round of the Scottish Cup.
Former Malaga manager
Javi Gracia has been named
as Watford's new head coach,
hours after they sacked Marco Silva.
Watford are currently 10th
in the Premier League.
Saracens' hopes of a third
consecutive European
title were kept alive,
thanks to Premiership rivals Wasps,
who beat Ulster in the Champions Cup
today, gifting Saracens
the last quarterfinal place.
They join Scarlets as the only
British teams in the last eight.
And while we have been on the air,
Mark Allen as just won Sanogo's
masters for the first time. He held
off a comeback from Kyren Wilson to
win 10-7 in a tense final at
Alexandra Palace. That is it from
me. There is more on the BBC News
channel, including how Tommy
Fleetwood stormed to the Abu Dhabi
title. Back to you. Thank you.
That's all from me, stay
with us on BBC One ,