five thanks for watching the January
10th edition of CNN 10 my name is Carl
azuz we're explaining news happening
around the world starting with the
evacuations of thousands of people in
Southern California huge parts of this
region have been scorched by wildfires
over the past year and a half and that's
partly responsible for the latest
disaster people there are facing
mudslides heavy rains have been falling
in places like Ventura and Santa Barbara
counties and because the fires burned
away so much vegetation in the area
there are fewer trees and bushes to help
prevent floods so mud tree limbs and
garbage are flowing like rivers sweeping
across busy roads and they've wiped
several homes off their foundations this
area is no stranger to mudslides an
official from the National Weather
Service says they can be caused by a
rainfall rate of a half inch per hour on
Tuesday some parts of Southern
California got more than three times
that in an hour that's led authorities
to give evacuation warnings or orders to
tens of thousands of people one of the
alerts from officials in Santa Barbara
County said simply leave debris flow
areas now go to high ground a resident
named Benjamin Hyatt who sent CNN these
pictures said that two to three feet of
mud surrounded his house in an instant
like a dam breaking officials say at
least five people have been killed in
these storms and last night more rain
was expected worsening fears of flooding
in the u.s. flash floods kill more
people than tornadoes hurricanes or
lightning a flash flood creates a rush
of moving water that can sweep a grown
man off his feet in a car off the road
and even your entire home off its
foundation when the ground becomes so
saturated that water can no longer seep
into the soil it begins to run off
quickly into rivers and streams and this
causes a rise in water in a flash
densely populated areas have an
extremely high risk of flash flooding
with the additional concrete unless
grassy areas for the water to soak into
the soil in they can
see flash flooding very quickly the
mountainous terrain the combination of
gravity plus the easy runoff can lead to
catastrophic flooding when all of that
water is funneled into rivers creeks and
even the valleys remember flash flooding
can happen in the blink of an eye that's
why it's important to stay alert and pay
attention in case a flash flood watch or
warning is issued for your area which of
these scales was named for a Swedish
astronomer who lived in the 1700s
Celsius Fahrenheit Saffir Simpson Coeur
Richter the Celsius temperature scale
was invented by Anders Celsius in 1742
[Music]
while parts of the US East Coast
recently endured record-breaking cold
thanks to the bomb cyclone we told you
about last week
Sydney Australia the nation's most
populated city recently sweltered under
abnormally high temperatures forty seven
point three degrees Celsius which
converts to more than 117 degrees
Fahrenheit it led to warnings about
everything from dehydration and sun
exposure to dangers about potential
fires it's not quite a record in the
Australian City that was set in 1939
when temperatures were about one degree
higher but when they dropped on Monday
to what was called a colder 33 degrees
Celsius or 91 degrees Fahrenheit that
was characterized as a relief so far
today we've discussed fires floods
mudslides and blasts of cold and hot
weather
these things are usually taken into
account when people build new homes or
developers planned communities there's a
tremendous list of options for building
materials wood and steel types of
flooring and climate control levels of
insulation and there are pros and cons
to everything
next we're featuring some materials that
could surround us in homes of the future
our homes of the future may not look
different but how they're built may be
completely new building materials are
getting a makeover
and companies are rethinking how homes
are designed so right now we are
essentially in the penthouse why isn't
this a fancy apartment for bio Mason
innovation means redesigning one of
constructions most popular materials
you're actually trying to then grow the
cement right that's right how do you
actually do that we take bacteria and we
put it in our aggregate and grows around
each grain of aggregate as submit'
components it literally is just using
the same organisms that are already
doing things similar in the end of our
universe exactly building the homes of
the future may mean planning for
catastrophes hurricane sandy devastated
New York in 2012 a few weeks later JDS
development started planning their
newest high-rise when we started
designing this building right after
Hurricane
we're working with 50 or 60 people that
had all just lived as we went around the
room and we said what happened to you
they designed flood proofing measures
below the building and installed a fleet
of generators where the penthouse would
be but most buildings at least in
Manhattan don't do this no nobody does
this the notion that you can't beat you
for that you shouldn't be person safer
in your building then outside it's a
relatively new concept natural gas power
generators means that residents will
have power even if the rest of Manhattan
is in the dark in the future smart tech
won't be limited to inside your home how
our building is changing even if you
can't see it so those are some possible
future materials what about the stuff
that'll go into future homes
specifically the technology that's what
CES is all about the Consumer
Electronics Show
it's an annual trade show where
technological innovations play the
starring role it's been going on for
more than half a century and this year's
event is being held in Las Vegas Nevada
we're almost 4,000 companies are
exhibiting their work for the more than
170,000 people in attendance not all of
the ideas presented here take off but
they do give us an idea of where
manufacturers think technology is headed
the top trends that we're seeing out
here this year number one voice
assistance whether it's Amazon's Alexa
or Google's voice assistant it seems
like every piece of technology here
wants to integrate so that they can just
have you speaking to control their
devices also cities planning for a
future with fewer drivers that doesn't
just mean driverless cars it means that
cities are looking for ways so the
stoplights can know that there's an
accident right there communicate to
yourself driving uber car that there's
an accident there and that they need to
go a different direction so a big
ecosystem for the cars and cities to
function together and plus sports tech
going pro what does that mean exactly
well we've seen a lot of wearables come
and go but now a lot of companies are
looking to get very specific not just
the macro market but a lot of times
micro markets just
for athletes just for the elderly now
every year at CES there's so much about
television some years they lead us
astray 3d televisions remember that well
when was the last time you saw somebody
with 3d glasses
then there were curved televisions but
who needs that when you have a
television that you can roll up like a
yoga mat though I don't think you'll be
taking this one to yoga class LG Display
has this prototype and it is just a
prototype so no price tag right now they
just make screens they're hoping that
one day the actual TV set manufacturers
might integrate this technology so you
can have a TV that can just roll up and
disappear out of the way in your house
but it doesn't ever really disappear
since there's that box right there where
it sits LG thinks that maybe you want to
see your television at different heights
so you can see what music is playing or
the weather at that smaller height then
maybe it goes up but not so tall so you
have a wider format like we're used to
in movie theaters or maybe just going
all the way up and using your television
the way we're all accustomed to using it
now 16 by 9 just to watch TV shows
imagine that cheesesteaks can help
people grow in a number of ways they can
also serve as an entertaining measuring
tool a father in Philadelphia once
noticed that his dinner was about the
same length as his infant son so he
started tracking his baby's growth in
relation to the length of a cheese steak
this has gone on for two years and the
boy has significantly outgrown both the
size of the steaks and having his
picture taken with them after all his
name is Lucas not hoagie and maybe he's
getting tired of being sandwiched
between the camera and mealtime or jokes
about where's the beef maybe he's a
budding vegetarian or maybe he just
thinks this whole idea is cheesy even
though it's clearly not a missed steak
I'm Carl azuz for CNN ten
[Music]