Balance is what human beings chase after
when they are babies learning how to walk.
Although people gradually forget this
after they can walk and run,
balance is always there with us.
Keeping the idea of balance in mind,
one can walk easily even if
he/she is climbing rocky mountain ways;
forgetting about balance, one
can accidentally make such a childish
mistake and fall on a flat road though he/she has grown up.
When people walk in a hurry,
they may think balance is a natural instinct,
but actually it is one goal that we pursue.
Several legends all explain how Go originated.
In the book of Natural History (Bowuzhi in Chinese),
it says the Emperor of Shun invented Go to teach his son wisdom.
In Postscript of Hearsay History (Lushihouji in Chinese),
the hero became the Emperor of Yao,
who made Go as a tool
to teach his son how to be pure and virtuous.
An ancient tomb of the Liao Dynasty in Inner Mongolia
has unearthed the endgame of Go in a game:
the Go board has a 13¡Á13 grid of lines,
and there are several white stones and black stones on the board.
Let's learn something about the Go board.
There are several vertical and horizontal lines
intersected with each other on the board.
One player uses black stones
(the playing pieces) and the other, white.
The players take turns placing the stones
on the vacant intersections of the board.
Hunan Province has also excavated
an ancient tomb of the Tang Dynasty.
There is also a chess board among the funeral objects.
This chess board has a 15¡Á15 grid of lines.
Since its appearance,
the Go board evolved for several times.
In the early time, there was a 11¡Á11 grid of lines,
then 13¡Á13, and also 15¡Á15.
In the end of the Han Dynasty
and the beginning of the Tang Dynasty,
the board gradually changed from a 17¡Á17 style
to the 19¡Á19 grid which now we use.
You may ask such a question:
why do the lines keep increasing
and will the current board continue to change?
Another more direct question is
that from the point of playing the game,
how many lines should there have vertically and horizontally?
Let's see the literal meaning of Go, Weiqi in Chinese.
It means encirclement board game.
The one who has surrounded more territory wins the game.
As we said just now, go can be played at the intersection.
The Go board consists of crisscrossing lines.
According to the distance from the boundary,
the four edges are called Line 1.
The lines adjacent to the edges are called Line 2,
and the upper lines are Line 3 and Line 4.
The points on each line have the relatively same characteristics
due to the same distance to the edge.
We can see that the white stones are on Line 3,
and the blacks are on Line 4 in this picture.
Playing Go is not only about occupying your own land,
but also to grab someone else's territory.
In other words, you can kill your enemy's pieces
and take the place occupied by the other as your own.
For example, if we look at this situation,
the White player has three stones,
but they do not completely surround the Black.
It's surrounded on three sides
The White player only needs to drop stone at point A,
then the black stone is surrounded, and the sunspot is captured.
The star occupied by the black stone is owned by the White player,
and the black stone is killed by the white stones.
So we call it as the white kills the black.
Therefore, Go has a problem with life and death.
When the stones are enclosed in open space,
they must ensure that they could survive,
and at least two independent "point"(mu in Chinese) can be formed.
We can simply understand the "point" as two empty areas.
For example, we look at this graph.
Although the white stones are surrounded by the black ones,
it has two separate "points", which are also called "eyes".
At this time, we said that white survived.
Why do you have to have two "eyes" to survive?
Can't one "eye" still work?
Let's look at such a question to see
what may happen if there is only one point.
The white stones surround the black ones,
and the Black also has a point.
At this moment, the Black cannot survive.
Why? Because the White can throw in (dianyan in Chinese),
that is, place a stone in the empty space surrounded by black stones.
Now, the black stones are pincered both insides and outsides,
both inside and outside are surrounded
At this time, the Black is killed,
and these places are owned by the White.
Since we just talked about that the points
on the same side have the same characteristics.
Let's look at the second, third and fourth lines.
What are the characteristics of these lines?
From the perspective of the game,
the priority is to ensure that the stones
you are playing are not killed by your opponent.
So which line can form a living pattern at the fastest speed?"
So the best way is to rely on natural insurance which is edge.
There is an advantage in playing chess near the edge:
you can create your territory without placing stones.
We use fewer stones to
form a chess piece by using the edge than that in the center,
that is to say, we can use fewer stones to acquire more territories.
Just now we talked about the theory of survival.
Now, we have the fastest living chess pieces on the second, third and fourth lines.
we found that we only use 7 stones
to form a living piece on the third line,
while on the second and fourth lines, we use 8 stones.
Of course, we will use more stones on the fifth and sixth lines.
Thus, from the perspective of the being alive at the fastest speed,
the third line is the best.
So, the third line is a very important line of occupying the edges and corners.
By taking the third line, we can acquire edges and corners,
and by taking the fourth line, we can naturally control the center.
So, the fourth line is very important to control the center.
The 19 lines in each side on the board we use
now have been tested for over one thousand years.
The number of lines has its own rationality.
Where is the rationality?
Mainly reflected in sente (the first one) and
gote (the second one) to play the game
and acquiring territory without any difference.
In fact, according to the current rules of Go, komi should be followed,
that is, a bonus in score given to white
as compensation for going second.
But in ancient China, there was no such thing as komi.
You can play fair by no komi,
that means that going first would not gain advantages.
Even if you go first and occupy five points first,
I go second but can also occupy five points.
Then you have no advantage in going first.
Therefore, we speculate that
from the perspective of territory occupation,
there must be two kinds of counter-forces inside Go
to ensure the fairness of the territory occupation of sente and gote.