Across the world,
tens of thousands of people
have been part of a truly
remarkable scientific project.
It's altering our understanding of
what made you the way you are today.
Scientists think they have
discovered in these people's lives
the secret of a healthy, happy,
long life...
for all of us.
Studying our journeys
from baby to adulthood
is revealing the most important
part of your life,
maybe one you can't even remember.
The nine months
before you were born.
When we think of
what makes us unique,
we don't tend to think of
life before birth,
but we're finding out that life
before birth
is actually shaping
who we are and who we become.
The importance of those crucial
months before birth
has become one of the most
powerful and provocative
new ideas in science.
The whole idea
was extremely controversial.
It blew me away, actually.
It was an incredible idea,
a real paradigm shift.
Understanding what happened to us
in the mysterious world of the womb
holds the promise of living
not just longer lives,
but healthier and happier ones.
This is the story of one man's
struggle to unravel our destiny.
It begins in Britain
over 20 years ago.
Professor David Barker
had spent much of his life
as a practising doctor,
and he thought he'd discovered
a way to predict the future
of each and every one of us.
He began to test this idea
on the people in this room.
They're not part of a scientific
research group or a hi-tech lab.
They are simply people who happen to
be born in Hertfordshire.
Very evocative.
This reminds me of
the way I used to go to school.
I used to walk along a road
past a ford every day,
and then in the summer we would play
in it just like these children do.
He believed from the moment
they were born,
scientific predictions could be made
about these people's lives.
I think their destiny is
in large part already wrought.
Much of their lifetime's well-being
and ability - mental ability,
physical ability and health -
is already determined.
How long they would live.
How healthy they would be.
Whether they would have
a happy and fulfilled old age.
Well, these people are clearly fit.
If you're still able to run
and win cups at 70,
you had a strong constitution.
He believed he could
make these predictions
using only the information
contained in these books -
the birth records of
the county of Hertfordshire.
The books record
the birth weights
and the weights at one
of these men and women,
and in those measurements
lie a description of the life
that lies ahead of them,
in terms of health.
David Barker believed
that in these records
he had found
a simple and powerful link
between a low weight at birth
and heart disease in later life.
The babies who go on to develop
coronary heart disease
were not abnormal in any way.
When they were born,
their arrival was greeted
with the usual enthusiasm.
But they were already marked.
The idea that future health
was linked to birth weight
became known as the Barker theory,
and it sounded too
simple to be true.
That's the first time
I've actually heard that,
that your weight at birth
determines what health risk
you're going to have
later on in life. That's weird.
Really? No.
No, I haven't, no.
I would not think that
that had any relation to a disease
later in your life.
I think it's more to do with
lifestyle factors and things
as you grow old,
so that your weight when
you're a child I can't imagine
would have a big impact on those
kind of factors when you're older.
Critics of the Barker theory
thought there were other
explanations for our health
and well-being in later life.
Conventional wisdom said we
turned out the way we did
because of what we ate as children,
or the lifestyle choices
we made as adults.
From diet to exercise,
we were encouraged to take control
of our own destiny,
and that a long and happy life
would be the result.
But David Barker
believed birth weight
was more important than lifestyle
when it came to future health.
His task was to turn
conventional wisdom on its head.
To silence his critics, David
embarked on a worldwide search.
He has travelled to
the four corners of the globe
to find crucial evidence
to back up his provocative theory.
Because to prove this theory,
he needed to show that
his ideas held true
on every continent
and for each and every one of us.
We're trying to establish
really core truths
which would apply
anywhere in the world,
and no-one is going to think
that findings
that are based on
a southern county in England
represent the globe,
and the only thing you can do to
offset that reasonable criticism
is to go out and do it.
In 1995, one of the key pieces
of evidence for the Barker theory
emerged from one of the most
crowded countries in the world.
By a quirk of fate, the people here
followed every piece of healthy
living advice you can think of.
According to conventional wisdom,
these Indian villagers
had made all the right choices
to lead a long and healthy life.
And yet they were
getting diseases
normally seen
in unhealthy, overweight people.
This was a real puzzle for us.
They are thin, they are eating the
vegetables they grow in their farms.
They walk long distances,
they work in the farms,
and that's the puzzle.
These people are anything
but overweight and obese.
Professor Ranjan Yajnik is a
world-renowned diabetes specialist.
And he's facing
a diabetes epidemic in India.
In the Western world,
type-2 diabetes is seen as
a disease of lifestyle.
It's associated with being
overweight,
a lack of exercise
and an unhealthy diet.
But Ranjan's patients
didn't fit that pattern.
The Western textbooks
I read as a medical student
told me that diabetic patients
were fat and overweight,
but you come to the clinic
in the rural hospital
and these are the people
who fill up our clinics.
They have a lot of diabetes
and heart disease.
The lifestyle of Ranjan's patients
should have given them
a long and healthy old age.
It couldn't explain why
so many of them
were falling victim
to type-2 diabetes.
But for one person, lifestyle
was clearly not the answer.
According to David Barker,
a low weight at birth
could be linked to
later health problems like diabetes.
BABY CRIES
And in India, there was no shortage
of low birth weight children.
Was the key to the disease
already there in these tiny babies?
Ranjan and his colleagues decided
to find out if the Barker theory
might explain what they were seeing.
Well, there was a lot of scepticism
at that stage
because we had learnt
as paediatricians at that time
that low birth weight is associated
with poverty and malnutrition,
whereas diabetes and hypertension
are diseases of affluence,
diseases of lifestyle.
So how were the two going together?
I was trained as
an adult diabetes specialist
and I was even more sceptical
of this idea
because we equated diabetes
with over-nutrition.
So David Barker was describing
the other end of the spectrum.
We do have a large number
of low birth weights
and we are having
a large number of diabetics.
So we are probably in a good
position to test his hypothesis,
so why not try it?
Ranjan and his colleagues
began to follow a group of babies
to see if their birth weight
could be linked to later diabetes.
Babies were measured
when they were born,
then at four years of age,
and again at eight years.
The scientists were looking for
early signs of diabetes -
for instance,
a resistance to insulin.
The first step was to show
that birth weight was related
to insulin resistance.
And we did tests by studying
200 children born in our hospital.
The children from that
original study are now 21.
The scientists have records of their
growth from the day they were born,
as well as a library of
blood samples.
It is these blood samples
that allowed the scientists to find
an early indicator of diabetes.
A low birth weight seemed to be
linked to a resistance to insulin.
So children whom we had found
to be low birth weight,
they are more insulin-resistant
at four years.
They were more insulin-resistant
at eight years,
and they are still insulin-resistant
at 21 years.
With passage of years, their
blood glucose has started rising.
There are other changes
we can observe in the blood
which tell us that their risk of
getting diabetes is now much higher
than their colleagues
who were not low birth weight.
Ranjan was beginning to be converted
to David Barker's
seemingly strange idea
that what happens to you in the womb
affects your destiny.
So David's idea that part of
your destiny
was sealed before you are born
was difficult to understand
for Westerners, but not for me.
As an Indian, I believed that
what happened in your earlier life,
what your parents did,
actually had a bearing on
what happens to you in your life.
This is the theory of karma.
This study was a crucial
piece of evidence
to support David Barker's theory.
But the real power of
the Barker theory
was that it didn't just apply to
very tiny babies.
The predictive power of birth weight
applies to us all.
What was surprising
about these early data
was that there was
a graded relationship
across a whole normal range
of birth weight,
so it was better to be
a seven-pound baby
than a six-pound baby,
and better to be an eight
than a seven and better to be
a nine than an eight-pound baby,
and that is profound.
What this suggested was that
there was an element of destiny
to the future health of
each and every one of us.
Look, look around you.
Clearly there are people
on very unhealthy lifestyles,
who live long lives
and have good constitutions,
and for them healthy lifestyles
may not matter so much.
But there are other people
who are highly vulnerable,
who have poor constitutions,
and for them the lifestyle
is the way forward.
That is what will protect them.
An idea that began in Hertfordshire
was starting to
reveal universal
truths about how our future health
was determined
before we were even born,
and what's true of health
may extend to our personality.
Oh, my goodness, for each of them?
I have two children and from day one
their personalities came out.
I have three children.
My oldest is very outgoing,
my middle child
is very wild and adventurous
and my youngest
is the easy-going, carefree child.
Only a fortune-teller
would attempt to predict
the person we will become
well before we were even born.
Before we could speak.
Before we'd even met our mother
face to face.
Yet many pregnant women
think they can.
I have one child
and she was just a diva
from before she was even born.
While they were in the womb,
they were very different.
This one's definitely
calm like my first,
but strong like my second.
Janet DiPietro is putting this
mother's intuition to the test.
She's a mother of three
and a developmental psychologist.
She wants to discover how much
of our future character is formed
before we've even
experienced the world.
Her work begins by trying to
give what is, in effect,
a personality test
to an unborn baby.
So in adults
and young people and children,
when we want to look at
individual differences,
what we often do is put them in
a new situation to see how they react
because how people react to things
is a big component
of what makes them unique.
To unpick the personality question,
Janet needed a way to test
the reactions of unborn babies.
She started by looking at
the way these tests
were conducted in children.
Some of the 900 babies
that have passed through her lab
are now five years old,
and they're back
to undergo more testing.
Right here.
It's just telling us
about how your body's working, OK?
The experiments put the children
in unusual situations
to see how they react.
Woof. Good.
Asking them to miaow
when they see a dog.
Or getting them to share with
adults, who start to behave
like greedy children.
..Give you one, and then
I'll take two.
One, two.
At five, differences in
personality begin to show
in the way children respond
to these unusual circumstances.
You can see it in their behaviour
and in their heart rates
and stress levels.
But I really like these candies,
so I'm going to take two. One, two.
I like them, too!
You do?
I'm going to give you one,
but I'll take four more.
No! You're taking all of it!
One, two, three, four.
'That little boy was almost
a little bit more intellectual.'
He was adamant when he had
his expectations about sharing...
broken, and so he said "no"
immediately,
'and then he sort of moved on
and he watched what was happening
'with the investigator,
but he was really more adamant.'
What do you think about that?
No.
'Whereas if we look at
the first little boy...'
What do you think about that,
if I take all of them?
..you can see that he
really feels what's going on,
so he'll experience that
very differently in his body, too.
I really like them,
but I think I'll get a stomach ache
if I eat them all.
Some of us react very emotionally
to changes in circumstances.
Our heart rates
and stress levels soar.
While others seem to have no trouble
keeping their body under control.
The characteristics
that distinguish all of us
are how we react to things
and then how we recover
after something happens.
Those are called the core features
of temperament.
We can see them in six-month-olds,
we can see them in five-year-olds,
and in adults
it's a more refined set of traits,
but the core is reactivity
and recovery irregulation.
Janet can even see
these core responses,
how extreme our reaction
to a new situation is
and how quickly we recover,
in the heart rate and stress levels
of six-month-olds.
If they were already there
at six months,
could these core personality traits
start even earlier,
back in the womb?
Janet's experiments allow her
to see how babies react to
a change in circumstances,
even before they're born.
First, she provokes strong emotions
in the pregnant mother
by showing her a video
about childbirth.
As the mother's heart rate
and stress levels change,
Janet watches
to see how the baby responds.
Or she can take a simpler approach,
and surprise the babies directly.
The mum is wearing the spa mask
and the headphones.
She's listening to music,
so she can't hear the stimulus,
but the foetus can.
OK, are you ready?
I'm ready.
All right. Go.
I could see her abdomen jump,
in fact.
You see a very quiet actograph and
then just that discrete little jump.
The foetus is startled at things,
just like babies.
Some babies, to that response,
startle so much that they wake up
and they continue to move.
Some babies
don't really react at all.
And then some babies,
like this one, moved.
Looks like they gave a very specific
response to it,
and then they
went back to their own business.
Even one month before birth,
Janet can begin to see distinctive
responses from the babies.
The core elements of
our future personality.
It feels great to me as a mom
to sort of validate moms everywhere,
that they didn't cause
their child to behave this way,
that their child
was already that way at birth.
But moms have to accept
the good and the bad, right?
So if your child turns out
a pleasant, happy child,
it's not... It's not your doing,
in the same way that
if your child turns out to be
a very difficult, unhappy child,
it's not your doing.
From the moment you're born,
parts of your future health,
happiness and personality
could already be determined.
But there may be a very simple
explanation for this.
It could all be down to the genes
we inherited from our parents.
David Barker needed to show
it was your nine months in the womb
and not just your genes
that made you...you.
Over ten years ago,
he began a collaboration
with Dutch scientists.
It was already clear that
in animals, manipulating
the environment in the womb altered
the health of future generations.
It would be impossible to experiment
on pregnant women in this way,
but sometimes history
creates an experiment for you.
Holland, 1944.
The Nazis were retreating and
leaving devastation in their wake.
All possible food
had been commandeered.
The result, a country-wide famine
which lasted five months.
Well, the Dutch famine occurred
when the Germans
banned all food transport,
and suddenly rations
dropped dramatically.
It was really
an acute period of famine
that struck an entire population.
Biologist Tessa Roseboom
saw an opportunity
to find out if our experience
in the womb
was every bit as important
as our genes.
There was hardly any food available
and we know from the records in
Amsterdam that people ate
two slices of bread, two potatoes
and half a sugarbeet
for the entire day.
So that's around 400 calories,
and we need about 2,000
to 2,500 a day.
Tessa began with the birth records
of one Amsterdam hospital.
After two years of
painstaking research,
she tracked down the people
who had been born in the famine.
We have birth records of
2,414 babies,
who were all born in this hospital
in Amsterdam.
We traced people and we interviewed
lots of people in their homes
and then invited them
to come to the clinic
for measurements,
and then do obviously a lot of
statistics behind the computer.
Tessa found that
whatever genes they carried,
those exposed to the famine in
the womb had more heart disease,
high blood pressure,
raised cholesterol,
diabetes and breast cancer.
And those who were conceived
after the famine...didn't.
We did indeed find
the brothers and sisters
of the people
who were exposed to famine.
They had the same genes from
the parents,
they had the same
post-natal environment, they grew up
in the same family, but the ones
who were exposed to the famine
while in the womb
were actually less healthy.
The later ill-health
was connected to the famine,
to what happened
to these people in the womb.
And the famine even had an effect
when it only lasted for
the first 12 weeks of a pregnancy.
Well, as a biologist,
it seems quite logical
that in the first 12 weeks
in which you lay down your brain,
your heart, your lungs, your
kidneys, all the essential organs,
if the quality of
the building blocks is poor
then the organs aren't as healthy,
or aren't as good as one would have
had with appropriate nutrition.
Because of the way our bodies grow,
the nine months that made you
will also have made your children.
At the time of the Dutch famine,
Tessa's grandmother was pregnant.
The egg that Tessa grew from
was already there,
created inside Tessa's mother's body
when she was an unborn baby
inside Tessa's grandmother.
So the egg that created Tessa
was also permanently altered
by the Dutch famine.
Well, genes can't be changed by
the food we eat,
but we know that food can
actually change whether genes
are switched on or off.
So famine may have affected
the switches on the genes in the egg
and therefore they may have affected
all the cells in the entire body of
the next generation as well.
So of the grandchildren
of women who were pregnant
at the time of the famine.
Tessa's work was powerful support
for the argument
that our life in the womb,
and not just our genes,
makes us more resilient
to future disease.
The picture that's emerging
is that your early development
sets up your constitution
and therefore sets up
how vulnerable you are
to negative things that you may
encounter through your life.
We've hitherto tried to answer that
question by assuming that
there must be genes which explain it,
but those genes have not come forward
and there isn't any particular reason
why they will.
Why would such genes exist?
The theory was that the quality of
nutrition you received in the womb
determined the quality of
your growth before birth.
This development
shapes your birth weight,
your life as a child
and your health to the present day.
But one question remained-
what exactly was happening
inside our bodies
in those crucial nine months
that could shape our destiny?
Back in India,
Professor Ranjan Yaznik was asking
himself the same question.
He had discovered
low birth weight babies
were more likely to end up
as diabetes patients in his clinic.
And the bad health went further.
At 21, some of them
were already showing signs of plaque
forming in their arteries,
an early indicator of heart disease.
Although these patients looked thin,
they were getting diseases normally
seen in overweight and obese people.
There was something
strange going on.
Why were these apparently
thin people's bodies
behaving as if they were fat?
To find out,
Ranjan did another study
to measure the amount of body fat
these low birth weight babies
were carrying.
The babies here
were born at 2.7 kilograms,
but when we measured their body fat
with special techniques,
we realised that they have body fat
which is as high
as that of an English baby,
a baby weighing 3.5 kg.
Almost 800 grams heavier.
They appear very thin,
but they are fat.
We found the same thing
at four years.
They were thin and fat.
At eight years again,
they were thin and fat, and at 21
years they're again thin and fat.
From birth,
it was as if these people's bodies
had the wrong settings.
People with low birth weights
looked thin, but they were actually
carrying the same amount of fat
as someone much heavier than them.
Ranjan thought he, too, might have
this unusual body composition
as he was also
a low birth weight baby.
I was born less than five pounds
and I thought we could investigate
to find out whether I was
at the higher risk of diabetes.
So I did this by actually
studying myself and my friend.
We have both
same body mass index, 22.3,
but John has 9% body fat
and I have 21% body fat.
The same body mass index,
an Indian has more than twice
the amount of fat
that an Englishman has.
This is a perfect example
of a thin/fat Indian.
Ranjan decided to see
if the mother's diet in pregnancy
could be causing these
thin/fat bodies to develop.
He looked at every aspect
of the diet...
and strangely he found
it wasn't all about calories.
To our great surprise,
it was not the mother's calorie
and the protein and the fat intake
which predicted the foetal growth.
It was the...
eating of the micro-nutrient
rich foods.
It was how much green vegetables,
the fruits and the milk
which decided the size of the baby
and how that baby was built.
Ranjan's work showed that it
wasn't the quantity of food
we received in the womb,
but getting the right vitamins
and minerals which was crucial.
Mothers who had low B-12
and high foliate
gave birth to thin/fat babies
which were insulin resistant
as children
and they seemed to be at higher risk
of getting diabetes in future.
These small variations in diet
suggested that even quite ordinary
changes in life before birth
can have noticeable effects
on our future health.
The picture we now have is that
normal human development is fragile.
That very often there is insufficient
resource available to the baby
to perfect every bit of its body.
The body has repair mechanisms
for mending broken bits.
The body has a store
of stem cells of varying quality.
The body has immune defences,
it has defences against oxygen,
and the quality of these systems
determines the quality of health
through life
because health is
essentially about the body's ability
to maintain equilibrium
in the face of challenges.
If our future health was determined
by the quality of our growth
in the womb, David Barker
saw an intriguing possibility -
the chance to intervene and prevent
all these diseases of later life.
It was becoming clear to him that if
you wanted a healthy happy old age,
the nine months you spent
in the womb could be the most
important nine months of your life.
Cheese!
Scientists are discovering
it's not just the food that
reaches us in the womb,
but also the hormones we're exposed
to that could powerfully
affect how our life unfolds.
These monkeys could hold clues
that our behaviour is not all down
to the way we were brought up.
According to Professor Melissa
Hines of Cambridge University,
testosterone levels in the womb
could have changed the way we think.
The reason people have gotten
interested in testosterone levels
in human beings is because there's
thousands of studies in other species
that show that if you manipulate
testosterone experimentally
during development, it influences
the way the brain develops
and as a consequence of that,
the individual's behaviour
across the lifespan
in respect of behaviours
that differ for males and females.
Melissa has found the same effects
of testosterone in the womb
in both monkeys and children.
Female humans,
and other primates, tend
to play with this sort of toy...
Baby.
..while the males, whether
monkey or man, go for another kind.
My favourite is the fire engine.
But the female monkeys, and the
girls, with higher testosterone
levels in the womb
end up acting more like the males
and ditch the dolls for the trucks.
More testosterone exposure
makes your behaviour more male.
So in two recent studies,
we've looked at normal variability.
In the first instance
by measuring maternal
testosterone during pregnancy
and in the second instance by looking
at testosterone and amniotic fluid.
In both cases we find that
the more testosterone the individual
was exposed to pre-natally,
the more male-typical their childhood
behaviour is.
So can you see this shape?
I think...
it might be that one. Yeah.
Other skills could be linked
to testosterone levels in the womb,
from reading emotions
to reading a map,
or spotting hidden triangles
in complex shapes. Well done!
Could the level of testosterone
in the womb be changing our brains,
affecting our abilities?
It's a question another group
of Cambridge scientists are studying
by looking at the brains of
eight-year-olds in an MRI scanner.
So this is the human brain
and this white section that you see
here is called the corpus closum.
It's a fibrotract that
connects the right hemisphere
to the left hemisphere.
One part of this region
of the children's brains varied,
depending on the levels
of testosterone in the womb.
So what we found is that low
testosterone actually meant that
this part of the closum was bigger on
the left side than on the right side.
This is one of the first times
physical differences
in our brain have been directly
linked to testosterone levels
in the womb.
So we can really ask the question,
is foetal testosterone a mechanism
that sort of pushes brains
to being more male or more female?
This work with testosterone
suggests hormones can have
a crucial impact during
the nine months that made you.
And because they affect our brain,
they may affect all aspects
of our personality.
CALL TO PRAYER
By 2011, David Barker
had been working on his theory
for over two decades.
He had evidence that the way
we grew in the womb could have
lasting effects on our health.
But now, he wanted to not
just understand our destiny,
but potentially re-write it.
I'm here because
there are potentially important
medical records
here in the desert of Saudi Arabia.
Records like these
are the key to David's work.
He's always looking
for places where human experience
creates a natural experiment.
David is working
with Saudi scientists
to connect these records
to real people living in the town
of Unizah today.
We have three different types
of records
that we can get a nice idea
of the babies and how they grew up,
what problems they faced,
how this can be linked
to the life in utero and so on.
We have found records in China,
we have found records in India.
There are records
in different European countries.
Some records in America.
Nothing like the records here,
so this is very exciting.
This latest set of records
could reveal a crucial
piece of the puzzle.
They contain the details
of an overlooked companion
that shared our nine months
in the mysterious world of the womb.
We all began life
in a world of water...
..bathed in warm fluid,
surrounded by the muted
sounds of the outside world
and our mother's heartbeat.
Graham Burton of Cambridge
University has been investigating
life in this strange world
his entire career.
This is really where it all began.
There's general agreement
that when life evolved on the
planet, it did so in the seas.
And even today, we recreate this
watery environment within the womb.
The baby develops within a sac of
salty fluid, very similar to the sea.
It's not until the waters break at
the time of delivery that we learn
to take our first breath of air.
Graham knew our mysterious
companion in the womb
would be crucial
to David Barker's work.
So when David first
presented his theory,
I thought this was extremely
interesting, but my first reaction
was of course,
"Well, what about the placenta?"
Because everything that goes
between the mother and the baby
must pass through the placenta.
Your placenta was created during
the same nine months that made you.
It is the link between
a baby, its mother
and the outside world.
Within the placenta there are
these finger-like processes,
rather like the fronds
of the seaweed.
Mother's blood comes in
through the arteries
into this space within the placenta
and passes between
these frond-like processes,
bringing oxygen
and nutrients to the placenta.
Everything that reached us
in the womb
passed through
this extraordinary organ.
Of course, none of us would be
here today without our placentas.
It's really an extension of us.
It shares the same DNA
and in some cultures,
it's almost considered a twin.
To really understand how
we developed in the womb, we need
to unravel the role of our placenta.
It acts as a selective barrier,
designed to both feed
and protect the baby.
And Graham has discovered
key evidence of exactly
how this happens.
So for example,
in placentas where the mother
has smoked during pregnancy,
what we see is a reduction
in the size of the blood vessels
within the placenta
and a thickening
of the barrier separating the
mother's and the baby's blood.
So both of those effects will
impair the transfer of nutrients
from the mother to the baby
and that may account for why the baby
is smaller in women who smoke.
This is just one example
of the many things which can affect
this delicate and responsive organ.
Graham's work shows just how
important the placenta is during
the nine months that made you.
Every placenta is different and in
a way every placenta tells a story,
and if we can read
the clues within the placenta,
then in a way we have a record of
how the placenta and the baby develop
and that may help us in predicting
the future health of the baby.
It's because our placenta
has such a powerful influence
on how our lives unfold
that David Barker
has come to Saudi Arabia.
He has recently begun work
with Dr Saleh Al-Wasel
of King Saud University in Riyadh.
They're in the early stages of
an important new research project.
Hidden in the records
of the Saudi town of Unizah,
Dr Al-Wasel has already
found evidence of how the placenta
may protect the baby
from changes in our mother's diet.
He's discovered the placenta
seems to respond to Ramadan.
Ramadan is a month that
most people here in Saudi Arabia
change their lifestyle.
The frequency of food, the amount of
food and also the quality of food.
If Ramadan occurred during later
pregnancy, Saleh found the placentas
were smaller than usual.
The placenta is not a solid organ.
It's a very plastic organ.
It's very sensitive
to the environment
and responds quickly to changes.
I mean, in Ramadan,
it's just only one month
among nine months of the pregnancy
and you can see changes
in the placenta.
Just for one month,
changes in the size.
You would think a smaller placenta
would mean a smaller baby,
but intriguingly the size
of the babies didn't change.
It seemed the smaller placenta
was capable
of transferring the same amount
of nutrients as a larger one would,
that it was protecting the baby from
any effects of the dietary change.
Here is the baby weight.
2.8, 3.4, 3.2,
3.3, 3.3, 3.4...
These birth records suggest
that even though
the Saudi placenta is always
smaller than a Western one,
it's capable of producing
as large a baby.
Well, it's absolutely clear
looking down this column,
and I've looked
at hundreds of such columns,
that these babies
are of Western size,
but the placentas are much smaller.
The Saudi babies are growing
large and healthy from
these smaller placentas.
It's as if they're working
more efficiently.
To understand why, Saleh is now
working with a hospital in Riyadh.
They are measuring newborn
babies and then analysing
their placentas in the lab.
It's 30 cms.
They hope to discover
why some placentas are better at
transferring nutrients than others.
The interesting thing about this is
that the placenta does not transport
nutrients in the same manner
all day, all stages.
It fluctuates.
So by looking inside the placenta,
we would hope to investigate
how this placenta takes the
nutrients from the mother's side
and delivers it to the baby's side.
Our companion in the womb
is now being given as much respect
by Western science as it has
always had in Saudi culture.
You cannot separate culture
from science
and here, for example,
in Saudi Arabia,
toward the end of the pregnancy,
we look at the placenta as if it
is going to die to bring a live baby
and for this,
we respect this unique organ
and handle it carefully
and bury it in the graveyard.
So I'm very excited that the
placenta is beginning to get the
recognition that it deserves.
David's work has really highlighted
the importance of the intra-uterine
period for adult health and, of
course, the placenta is critical to
that, and it's very rewarding to see
that a number of young investigators
are turning their attention
to the placenta
and I think in the next five,
ten years
we're really going to gain a much
greater insight into its function.
If we can understand
why some placentas seem
to work better than others,
it might be possible to ensure every
baby gets the best start in life,
thanks to a really
efficient placenta.
In the tough environment
of the slums of Mumbai,
David Barker is hoping
his ideas can change lives.
The underlying mechanisms
which affect the quality
of our growth in the womb
are still under investigation,
but David believes we already know
enough to alter the health destiny
of future generations.
It is a new way, it is a feasible way
and it's not even
a very expensive way,
so it's time we got going.
Inspired by David's ideas, his
colleague, Professor Caroline Fall,
is leading a study
with the potential to fix
the diabetes epidemic in India.
At the moment, if you talk
about preventing diabetes,
people are talking about making
middle-aged people lose weight,
and A, that's impossible to do,
and B, it doesn't seem
to work very well anyway.
The idea that you could
build a human being that was
more resistant to this disease
was amazing to me.
Caroline's plan to halt
the diabetes epidemic
doesn't rely on high-tech labs
or fancy science.
It rests mainly on these women
and one kitchen.
These recipes contain all the
crucial building blocks needed to
build a body resistant to disease.
'Folic acid, calcium, iron,
vitamin A.'
The calcium will be important
for bone growth.
The green leafy vegetables
contain small quantities
of essential fatty acids which
are important for brain growth.
All of those nutrients are important
in different tissues of the body.
The foetus, at a very,
very early microscopic stage,
is sensitive to the nutrients
around it and if we miss that,
we feel that we would be missing the
most important stage of development.
Every day, over 1,500 snacks
are made in this kitchen.
There are nutrient-rich recipes and
others that are green vegetable-free
to act as scientific controls.
They are taken to about 50 clinics
in the slums across the city.
In total, over 6,700 women
have participated
and each must begin
eating the supplements
well before they fall pregnant.
It's a logistical nightmare
where the utmost care must be taken
to be scientific.
I'm very glad to have met Meera.
It's been hard work, it's been hard
work setting up a study like this.
To carry it out on the ground
in a population like this
is very difficult.
It's mandatory for a woman
to come to the centre
and have the supplement
in front of the project clerk
because it is very important, you
know, because if they take it home,
somebody else can eat it.
They can throw it out
or the child can eat it.
We are not sure
who the supplement has gone into,
whose stomach, so it's very
important to have women
coming to the centre.
The centre is full of women
eating supplements
from well before pregnancy
until they give birth.
And there are also babies
who must be measured at one,
three, six and 12 months.
Their weight, length
and body fat are recorded,
and they are even testing
their mental development.
It is an ambitious
long-term project.
For seven-and-a-half years.
How many more?
Forever, I think. So nice!
The results of this study
will begin to come in next year.
We're providing better
nutrition into the mother,
but the mother herself
has had a poor early development,
which may affect
the quality of her eggs.
It certainly affects
the size of her uterus
and the quality of the blood supply
to the uterus.
So she is still constraining
the development and growth
of that foetus, even if we are
providing enough building blocks
to develop a better foetus.
We need to follow these children
through and we need to follow
into the next generation
to see the full benefit.
David Barker's ideas have
transformed the way we think
about our time in the womb.
If the work in India is successful,
the study of foetal origins
that began in Hertfordshire
could alter the health of future
generations across the world.
Many people have looked
at genes, but it hasn't been
as promising as we thought
and it's been very difficult
to change lifestyles,
to prevent heart disease,
for instance, but I think
this field of research
that focuses on development during
pregnancy is really very promising.
The benefits of improving
the nutrition of the human embryo
and foetus are not just
reducing the burden of diabetes.
It will reduce the burden
of cardiovascular disease,
osteoporosis,
various brain disorders,
and will prolong lifespan.
Particularly it will prolong
healthy lifespan.
I would like to think
that what we're seeing
here in India
is the beginning of a new dawn
and a new understanding
that will lead us
to take command of our destinies
in terms of our long-term health.
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk