Look! Here they are.
Hey, you!
These two longan seeds were given
by Sister Swallow.
I'll plant one of them right next to the door
when spring comes.
And plant the other one on the other
side of the door.
Then we'll have two longan trees.
Ho ho... l'll plant the seeds with you next spring
Now you keep the seeds safe.
And I'll go and find some radishes, my baby.
I'll go with you. Let me go with you.
It's cold outside. Come and get warm by the fire.
Don't go with me.
No
I'll go with you. Let me go with you.
I'm so lonely without you, Mom.
Ah. I've got an idea. I'll make a snowman for you.
Then you won't feel lonely with her company.
Make a snowman.
Ah
Great! We're making a snowman.
Oh! Great! We're making a snowman.
Taking on my shovel, La la la...
Going with the snowball, La la la...
The wind is whistling, La la la...
The snowflakes are dancing, La la la...
The birds on the trees are singing
The snowman is growing taller and taller.
We finish making the snowman. La la la...
Gone with the Wind song Manshan. La la la...
How beautiful the snowman is. La la la...
She's smiling at me. La la la...
he birds on the trees are singing...
My friends, La la la...
are having a good time.
Look! What a lovely snow child!
But she's missing the most important thing.
Ah, she's missing something.
Oh, I see. She's missing two eyes.
What should be do?
Well...
Look!
Look! She's got eyes!
Mom, how beautiful she is!
Oh, she needs a nose!
Oh, you don't like this nose.
My mom will bring you a nice nose.
I'll give you a new nose in a minute.
Mom! How handsome our snow child is!
Yes. You've got company.
I'll go and look for some radishes.
It's cold outside. Come inside after having fun.
Ah
Don't forget to bring a pretty nose
to the snow child, mom!
Ah
We're good friends now.
Why don't you move closer!
You're so cold, my friend.
Let's move closer to the fire.
Oh, you are not afraid of the chill.
Snowflakes, snowflakes, the pure white
snowflakes.
Floating gently in the sky, floating over the
greatest mountains
Snowflakes, snowflakes, my lovely snowflakes
Round and round, round and round,
playing with me
Come over, come over, little rabbit.
Come over, and join me in the skiing.
Join me in the skiing.
Let our songs be heard, La la la...
Some of my friends how happy.
Round and round, round and round,
the field forest is my family
Mom, Mom!
Ah! My Baby! My Baby!
Mom!
Here's a carrot for you, my baby!
No... The snow child is gone.
What a good children. Look, my baby.
Our snow child has turned into the clear water.
I see the white clouds in the blue sky.
Look over there! The snow child is with us.
La la la...
La la la. It more beautiful is more lovable. La la
la. She's got the purest heart. The purest heart.
Mom, will the snow child come back to us?
Look! Isn't she with us now?