Air and naval
forces of the United States
launched a series of strikes
against terrorist facilities...
Pan Am flight 103 crashed
into the town of Lockerbie.
He has sanctioned
acts of terror
in Africa, Europe
and the Middle East.
This will not stand, this
aggression against, uh, Kuwait.
This relentless
pursuit of terror.
We will make no distinction...
The USS Cole was attacked
while refueling in
the port of Aden.
This was an act of terrorism.
It was a despicable
and cowardly act.
The next samba
we're going to swing for you
is one of the good old
favorites.
...until something stops him.
It was right
in front of my eyes,
and I never saw it coming.
That plane crashed
into the World Trade Center.
Thousands of people running.
We must and we will remain
vigilant at home and abroad.
You're the smartest
and the dumbest fucking person
I've ever known.
I'm not the
one who got it wrong.
I'm the only one
who got it right.
Take 'em.
Take 'em all.
Homeland - 3x10
"Good Night"
Previously on Homeland...
The bomber's the only way
to prove that Brody's innocent.
What the fuck
are you doing, Carrie?
Carrie, turn around now.
This is your last warning.
We got a gunshot wound
to the upper left bicep.
Significant bleeding.
Might have clipped an artery.
Where the fuck is Saul?
He's not what we expected.
But he's what we've got.
The guy's a junkie... sir.
I'm offering you the chance
to be a Marine again.
No more. I...
I'm done.
I have a play.
It involves Brody.
- You told me Javadi was the play.
- He is.
Brody's the next phase.
So, what is it?
What's your big idea?
Darnish Akbari.
Head of Iran's
Revolutionary Guard.
Right.
Javadi's boss.
And the single greatest
impediment to peace.
I want him gone.
Brody can get to him.
Do what Saul's asking.
What you're asking.
All right, what I'm asking.
Look at me, Carrie.
You couldn't send me out for
a pack of cigarettes right now.
We'll get you ready.
You just have to be willing.
The guys get me to the border
where I surrender myself?
Correct, and we chose
Marivan, because
several Al Qaeda commanders
also asked
for political asylum there.
What make you think
I'll ever get close enough
to General Akbari
to take him out?
Javadi's on the ground.
We'll facilitate a meeting
between the two of you.
I will come back from Tehran.
I know you will.
And not just for her.
Brody?
See you on the other side.
Carrie.
We need to talk.
What about?
How's your shoulder?
Brand fucking new.
I want to clear the air
after that clusterfuck
with Franklin at the motel.
I'm not interested.
I'm so tired of
all the bullshit
and people covering their asses,
I can't even tell you.
It was a direct order, Carrie.
I didn't want to risk letting
someone else take the shot.
While you were in surgery,
I took a look
at your medical records.
You what?!
I was worried
about the damage I'd done.
Carrie, you're
15 weeks pregnant.
- So?
- So, I think
you should consider sitting
this part of the operation out.
And why would I do that?
Because it's impossible
for you to be objective
under the circumstances.
The circumstances being,
I'm carrying Brody's child?
Yes.
Well, first of all,
it's not his,
thank you very much.
Second of all,
it's none of your
damn business,
or anyone else's,
so just stay the fuck
out of my way.
_
Medium rare?
Hmm.
Pretty fucking tasty, huh?
Hmm... hmm. Yeah.
The secret is to relax the goat
before you cut his throat.
Which is why Modarres
has lockjaw and sore knees.
- How are they doing?
- Mm.
Good. That move across
Kurdistan was uneventful.
Now...
that's them right there. They're waiting
for nightfall, at which point,
they'll drive him
right up to the border
here, cover him across
to the manned checkpoint
on the Iranian side,
right there.
The risk
of an international incident
is a serious concern
for the President.
We stand 100%
behind what we told him.
The risk of this operation
is worth the reward.
And in the unlikely event
anything goes wrong,
we have it covered.
I'm not even going to
ask what that means.
All he has to do tonight
is walk across the border
and ask for asylum.
That's it.
Is that a Marine thing?
Turn the socks inside out,
get the fresh side.
Well, there is no fresh side.
One side's sweaty,
and the other's just dirty.
Well, maybe it's just
all in my head.
Does it work?
Well, look at me.
I'm a new man.
Comms check.
Kilo-Alpha, this is Zero.
We have visual.
Send signal strength. Over.
Kilo-Alpha.
Signal strength ten.
Kilo-Bravo,
this is Zero. Over.
Bravo. Also strength ten.
Zero, this is Kilo-Alpha.
New Moon, visibility good.
Another day in paradise.
How's the passenger doing?
Not bad.
For a fucking jarhead.
That is all. Alpha out.
Bravo out.
What's he walking into
at the border crossing point?
Hey, Gene, can you bring up
the border photos, please?
Coming up.
Yeah, as of two hours ago,
one barrack hut for eight men,
commanded by a sergeant.
Roadside guard hut manned
in four-hour shifts
by two men with
automatic weapons.
Any updates on the Iranian
border patrol radio traffic?
Hourly comms checks.
Plus, one request
for more ration packs,
two for new radio batteries.
Eight bored
and hungry conscripts
whose radios we're dialed into.
No chance of
underestimating them then?
Fair point.
Let's go over your cover story
one last time.
After the bombing,
Nazir's network left a car
near Langley,
which I took into the woods
on the Canadian border,
where I shaved my head,
and I continued on foot.
There I stole a boat
across the Bay Of Fundy
to Nova Scotia,
where I met a guy
who had ties with Amer El-Maati,
who put me in a shipping
container to Colombia.
Mm-hmm.
Then, mercenaries
working with Hezbollah
took me across to Venezuela,
where they finally put me
into a state oil company plane
to a strip in Iraq,
where I was handed over
to an Al Qaeda cell
who were tasked with getting me
across the border to Iran.
Join Al Qaeda, see the world.
Final checks. Night vision.
Night vision transmissions
coming online.
I'm out of Black Jack.
Any more out there?
Everything okay, sir?
This the last pack?
I got you plenty more.
Don't worry.
Did you write a letter?
What?
Home.
To say good-bye.
Pretty sure you guys
would know if I did.
You could've arranged it
with your, uh, CIA friend,
the blonde.
How you doing?
Good. You?
Feel like I'm in Vegas
betting the mortgage.
Stand by, people.
Show time.
What's going on with Reaper 1?
Sensor bandwidth issues.
It happens.
We're resetting.
All being well, shouldn't
be more than a couple minutes.
"All being well"?
Are we holding the team back
until the drone's back on line?
That drone's mainly for us.
They have satphones
and night vision.
They can move closer to the
border without it for now.
- Shit.
- What?
Road to the border's
as good as blocked.
Foreign gas trucks paying off
local officials with free gas.
Cops, military, you name it,
all on the take.
Where's the border?
Another mile past 'em
on this same road.
Those lights in the distance.
Zero, Kilo-Alpha, over.
Zero send, over.
See what I'm seeing?
Yeah. Wait out.
Guys, get out.
Make it look like car trouble
for anybody passing.
We have a backup plan, right?
Yeah. We're waiting for Langley
to confirm the alternate route.
Now, I need that drone.
Are we gonna have it or not?
Copy that.
What's taking them so long?
I don't know. They had
a technical with the drone.
So how long are we gonna
sit here for?
Shit, man,
you're worse than my kids.
God, those rear echelon
motherfuckers.
Got a problem with the drone.
That's a good start.
Reaper's back.
Good.
Now let's get eyes
on that alternate
route into the border.
Repositioning now.
Kilo-Alpha, Zero.
Drone is back online.
Scouting your route.
Wait out.
Back to chewing
your lucky gum again?
Yeah. You want a stick?
Shit.
Put your head down.
Like you're sleeping.
Don't move.
Zero, Kilo-Bravo. Stand by.
May have a situation
with the Alpha vehicle.
Local cops just rolled up.
Maghreb.
Why are you here?
Going to Marivan.
...Al Qaeda.
They're not
buying the cover story.
Jesus, they want to look
in the truck.
Say the word,
Kilo-Alpha.
- What word?
- "Good night."
They should say "Good night"
before the cops see Brody.
As-salamu alaykum.
Good... night.
Hey...
You okay?
Brody? You good?
Hey.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- I can't do it.
- Yes, you can.
- I can't. No.
- I can't. No, I fucking can't.
- And you will.
I fucking can't. I fucking...
Bit late in the day
for your vagina to chime in.
Fuck off...
You scared?
Are you fucking scared?
Mm-hmm. Mmm. I'm...
- I'm scared. I'm scared.
- Good.
Me, too. I've seen
way too many men
killed out here in this
third world toilet.
I personally shit myself every
time they send me back here.
And if you don't snap out
of this right now
we could all fucking die
here tonight.
Is that what you want?
No.
Tell me you're gonna be okay.
Tell me that this is not
the end of the road for you.
No, no, no...
I need to hear you say it.
I'll be...
I will be okay. I'm okay.
I'm okay.
I'll be okay.
Kilo-Alpha, is there a problem?
Passenger got carsick.
He threw up
and we're ready to roll.
Carsick?
It's a secure sat link.
Can you tell them to just
- cut the bullshit?
- Is he gonna be okay?
Fuckin'-A he's gonna be okay.
Here.
Wipe the blood off your face.
Kilo-Alpha,
Kilo-Bravo, proceed
to alternate crossing point.
Roger.
Alpha out.
Did we or did we not just kill
three Iraqi police officers?
Kurdish-- not to split hairs.
Either way, this isn't something
the President needs to know.
Oh, I understand.
Believe me.
Get me JSOC Commander now.
This whole area is
pretty much a no-man's land
since the Iran-Iraq war.
We got visitors.
- Senator. General.
- Director.
- The White House...
- I know.
- I was told you were coming.
- Let me finish.
The White House sent
General Pfister and me
to advise and observe.
Advise and observe.
The JSOC Commander, to advise;
myself, the President's nomin...
What did Higgins tell you
about the operation?
That this part was meant to be
quick and silent and bloodless.
He told you everything,
didn't he?
Yes, he did.
- Including...?
- Sergeant Brody, yes.
Saul...
whatever this turns out to be,
bold stroke of genius
or otherwise,
I'm destined to inherit it.
So now that it's actually
in motion,
for better or for worse,
I have no choice
but to wish it every success.
A word in private, Senator?
Excuse us, Bill.
Of course.
What about the breathing room
you agreed to give me?
The deal was that I delay
my confirmation hearing,
which I've done.
That obligation
has been fulfilled.
Consider yourself lucky, Saul,
that Higgins called us
and not the President
or his National
Security Advisor.
Copy that.
Copy.
- Ms. Mathison.
- Senator.
How's your shoulder?
Doctor told me you
were very lucky.
I'm fine. Thanks for asking.
All I can say is you must be
one hell of a salesperson
to get Brody to do this.
Here at the Agency,
we call that recruiting.
Here. Take a look.
Border's a click
and a half away.
300 yards past that building.
All it is is a shallow stream,
12 yards across.
Listen... I'm gonna
drive you right up to it
and we're all gonna
be watching you.
You way across that river and you head
up to that treeline on the other side.
Once you hit it, follow
it north for three miles
back to the Iranian checkpoint
where we were
originally gonna drop you.
Hey, where you going?
Piss.
Go with him.
We got potential bogeys.
Two Iraqi army hummers
three clicks south
of our call sign.
Kilo-Alpha, we have
two Iraqi hummers
three clicks south, it's not a
significant threat but be aware.
Alpha Roger.
All right, we got an Iraqi
patrol three clicks south.
It's not that big a deal but
it's difficult terrain out there
so we got to move quick, quiet
and small now, which means
it's just me and him from here.
Rest of you guys stay here,
cover from this position.
Questions?
Ready?
Yeah.
When you were a little kid,
what did you want to be when you grew up?
I don't remember.
Bullshit.
Everyone remembers.
You don't
have to manage me anymore, man.
I know what I'm here to do.
Just making conversation's all.
What's that?
Nothing.
Well, what did you want to be?
I grew up in Texas.
All I wanted to do
was ride bulls.
Yeah, why didn't you?
I did.
Two years.
But my nuts couldn't
take the beating.
So now I do this.
Happy fucking...
What just happened?
Kilo-Alpha,
this is Zero, over.
Kilo-Alpha, this is Zero, over.
Kilo-Alpha, Zero, over.
Zero, this is Kilo-Bravo.
Alpha hit something.
A mine or an IED.
Any hostiles on your screens?
Stand by. Checking now.
Nothing, so far.
Sir, that Iraqi patrol
just turned north,
towards the explosion.
Now we have to call
the President.
Wait.
Let the dust settle first.
No, any possibility of
an international incident
- I must call the President.
- What you must do
is keep a cool head
and take great care
not to panic.
Well, we at least have
to call the Iraqis.
And say what?
Turn your patrol around,
we have a CIA team
we didn't tell you about,
operating in the area?
That drone is armed, correct?
Zero, Kilo-Bravo.
We're one click out
from Kilo-Alpha.
Roger, Kilo-Bravo, be advised
that Iraqi patrol is closing
on your position.
Sir, White House
is on the line.
Put him on the screen.
Mike.
- I may have a solution.
- Please.
That drone has four
Hellfire missiles on it.
You saying we engage
the Iraqi patrol?
I'm saying we just found
an Al Qaeda cell
trying to smuggle America's most
wanted terrorist into Iran
and we take them out
with that drone.
Jesus.
It's a smart play
if they're dead.
- And if they're not dead? - He doesn't
care whether they're dead or alive,
all he fucking gives a shit
about is covering his own ass.
- Bite your lip, Carrie. Bite it hard.
- Fuck.
That Iraqi patrol is,
what, a minute away?
Let me be very clear, Mike.
I will not order
a strike on our own men.
Hang it up.
We've got movement
in the Alpha vehicle.
Either the vehicle just settled
or I have a second
heat signature moving.
The second figure is moving.
They're alive;
they're both alive.
My leg.
Motherfucker...
No.
- My fucking leg...
- All right, sit up.
Sit up, sit up.
Fold your arms.
Okay, come with me.
All right...
Phone, satphone.
- Kilo-Bravo, this is Alpha, over.
- Bravo, send.
We're in the building
to the west of the border,
no enemy fire;
casualty is still conscious
but he's lost a leg
and a lot of blood, over.
Bravo, Roger.
Your location 60 seconds, over.
Get a gun team
up on high ground.
I can treat for shock
and stem the blood flow for now.
Take your time to follow
our exact route in, over.
On it. Out.
Focus on your kids.
I don't have any kids, dumbass.
Making small talk 'cause
you were being a fucking baby.
We're gonna get you out of here.
Smoke.
Here, give me some
of my cigarettes.
I never thought I'd
be this fucking guy.
No, me neither.
I guess I fucked up, T.
Beers on you, then.
I gave him one morphine shot.
He's got one left.
We got to haul ass now.
Grab that.
Here. Here... here.
Roll... back.
Okay.
- Ready to do this, boss?
- Yeah.
All right, everybody
back to the truck.
- Go!
- Let's go, quick.
Iraqi patrol
just joined the party.
Zero, Kilo-Bravo, contact!
Automatic fire from the south.
Platoon or possible
company strength.
Do all you can
not to escalate this.
Suppressive return fire.
Suppressive fire only.
Don't put them in the ground.
Just turn them around.
Zero, Kilo-Bravo,
we don't get Aziz out
- in the next few minutes, he's dead.
- Iraqi call signs
are requesting an artillery fire
mission up the chain.
How far out are
our helicopters?
Eight minutes.
General, advice?
Eight minutes
is time we don't have.
- Either we call the Iraqis and level with
them... - Also time we don't have
and every shade of blowback
we can't afford.
So it's a fighting withdrawal
to a secure LZ,
back five clicks in the vehicle
that they have left.
In other words,
we have to abort.
The intelligence
operation is over.
It's a military one now.
It's all yours, General.
Thank you, sir.
Shoot the boys out of there.
Copy that. Comms.
Kilo Bravo, this is Zero-Alpha.
Bravo, send.
- We're going to push them back
with Hellfire, over. - Roger.
Withdraw with Hellfire
in support on your command.
On my command, roger, wait.
Are they aborting the mission?
Saul.
You had some bad luck.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
At least we have Javadi.
He's still in play.
That's not nothing.
Yeah.
Stand by for Hellfire
mission, over.
You guys ready?
Fall back! Fall back!
- I'm not gonna go back. - What the fuck
are you talking about? Yeah, you are.
I'm gonna walk across that border into
Iran and you're not gonna to stop...
Listen to me! I am fucking ordering
you to fucking move out!
Passenger refuses to withdraw,
and I'm out of time.
Please advise.
Do not leave anyone behind.
We are under heavy fire!
The casualty is priority one,
and the passenger is
non-fucking-compliant!
General, please advise!
Let me talk to him.
If anyone can talk Brody
down off a ledge, she can.
All right.
Put the passenger on the line.
I say again,
put the passenger on the line.
Take this.
Take it!
Brody?
Brody, can you hear me?
- Hey, Brody! - They're trying
to abort the mission, Carrie!
- I know.
- Well, tell them to go fuck themselves.
No, listen to me.
You can't do this by yourself.
I'm 300 yards
from the border, Carrie.
I can make it.
You cross into Iran now and you will
be completely on your own.
Well, to be honest I don't see
much of an option here.
The option is
to fall back, regroup,
and we'll take another shot
at this later.
Come on, Carrie, you know
that's not gonna happen.
You don't know that!
Now, stop and think
this through.
You have no sanction,
no support on the ground,
and no extraction plan.
You will die over there!
No, you're wrong, Carrie.
And you want to know why?
'Cause you're gonna get me home.
No, don't say that!
Do not put that on me.
It's a fantasy.
You'll find a way.
I have faith.
That's all. Out.
No, Brody! Brody!
Fuck!
We are fucking moving out now.
All of us. Let's go.
Not me.
He's gone! Fuck him!
Hellfire, now! Hellfire, now!
Hellfire firing now.
Move. Move now!
Grab him!
- Take it.
- What are you doing?
Get him to the LZ,
then come get me. Go!
Fuck!
Fucking snipers.
Always the stubborn
fucking assholes.
I can buy you 30 seconds
to cross that border
and get to those trees.
Once I start firing,
you start running.
And if you stop,
I'll fucking shoot you myself.
Any questions?
- No.
- Oh, good.
Count of three.
One... two... three!
What is that?
They're surrounded.
Who by?
Are we picking up
anything on radios?
...Nicholas Brody.
_
The Iranians are saying
they have two prisoners.
Are we sure it's the Iranians
and not the Iraqis?
100%.
Jesus.
They got the
casualty out safely.
He's stable, on a bird
out to the carrier group now.
There's something else.
What?
Brody made it across.
How?
He made a last second
run for it--
headfirst
into an Iranian military unit.
He's okay?
Yes.
He made it.
And you, Saul,
are still in the game.
I'll be damned.
Right now, these guys...
uh, they're trained
to treat anybody coming
over the border
as Israeli agents.
You were tortured...
so tell me what to expect.
Expect to break.
How long did you hold out?
I don't know.
I lost track of time
pretty much right away,
but I figure...
seven days?
Enough time to allow the guys
to change their frequencies
and battle plans.
I just...
I just hope
I can give you seven days
to get the job done in Tehran.
Huh?
Hi.
May I?
Of course.
Fara, you're one of the few
people in this building
who knows that Majid Javadi's
an Agency asset.
I didn't breathe
a word to anybody.
I know you didn't--
that's not why I'm here.
But you had a crucial role
in recruiting Javadi.
In fact, Saul says, without you,
it never would've come off.
He's exaggerating.
But thank you.
The thing is...
Javadi's only half the play.
There's another phase
of the operation
you weren't made aware of.
It involves an asset,
whose life depends
on us getting him out of Iran
at the critical moment.
And the fact is
our extraction plan
just went up in smoke.
I'm sorry.
Fara, you have
an uncle in Tehran.
Your father's brother.
- Carrie, no.
- Just hear me out.
No, it's too dangerous.
- All we're asking for...
- You're asking me
to put my family
at extreme risk.
You know you are.
You forget I've seen firsthand
how fast an operation
can go sideways.
Tell the truth.
You would never ask your
own family to do this.
I might.
And from what I know about
your uncle, he's not one
to cross the street to stay
out of trouble's way.
He's a member of a moderate
opposition group.
Not a bomb thrower.
All we need is a place
to meet in the city.
A de facto safe house.
Fara, we have a brother agent
in the field,
soon to be in mortal danger.
Don't we owe him every chance
to get out alive?
Hey.
Someone's coming.
My name is Nicholas Brody...
and I'm formally seeking asylum
in the islamic Republic of Iran.
I know who you are.
Ayman Jassim.
Are you ready?
Ready for what?
To go with me to Tehran.
What about him?
No! You fuck!
- Quiet. Quiet!
- You fucking asshole!
- What did you do that for?!
- Control yourself.
- Fuck! Fuck!
- Calm down!
Calm down.
Now.
We go to Tehran.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com