Please help me!
I can't move!
Help me! I can't move!
Oh my god!
Sarah, save what you're doing and log out. I need you on something now.
What is it?
I just heard from one of our sources.
There's a high probability that someone from our FBI watchlist was spotted in L.A. yesterday.
Thomas Sharek. Who is he?
He's done work with several terrorist cells outside Istanbul.
coordinating several suicide bombings last summer.
Istanbul...
There was some chatter this morning about a possible attack by a group out of Turkey.
Here it is. From Ankarah.
What was the target?
East Coast. New York or D.C.
But the time window passed.
Passed?
The targetted time was for 8 A.M. It's already past 10 on the East Coast.
What if they got the target wrong and it's West Coast time?
Then it's gonna go down within the hour.
Tell Curtis, I'll take this to Driscoll.
I can take it to her.
Why?
I thought you wanted to keep working it up.
You know, you're really transparent, Sarah. Stop trying to be Driscoll' pet,
she doesn't like it.
Have you had voice confirmation from anyone on the train?
No, the signal has just confirmed a bomb.
We're trying to get in contact now.
It's in a remote area but local police are heading to the scene.
Alright.
We have discretionary authority out of Point Magoo.
Have them direct one of their patrol aircraft over the area.
Put the pilot in contact with our people.
Should we monitor emergency services?
No, County will cover that.
A truck loaded with C4 just derailed a train in Santa Clarita.
Free up some of your people. Division's gonne send over data.
That could be realted to what we just found downstairs.
What did you found?
Two things. First, there was intelligence indicating the possibility of an attack
at 8 o'clock this morning.
Bombing was at 7. That's within an hour of the time.
What's the second thing?
A turkish national ont the FBI watchlist by the name of Thomas Sharek
was last seen in the city.He could be related to the bombing.
Okay.
Open up channels with Divison. Start investigating this bombing.
And work up what you have on Sharek.
We'll brief in a few minutes.
What about the Defence Department meeting? It's in a half hour.
Who's secretary Heller sending?
Jack Bauer.
Jack... You sure?
Yeah, he hasn't been back...
well, since you fired him.
Is it gonna be uncomfortable?
What?
Going back to CTU. Seeing Driscoll again.
I don't blampe her for her decision.
How can that be? She forced you out of CTU.
She didn't want a junky on her staff. That's not unreasonable.
You weren't a junky. You were doing youre job.
I was addicted to heroin.
It didn't matter why.
Do you miss your old job?
I could have joined other agencies if I Still wanted to do field work.
But I didn't.
I wanted something different for my life.
It might not seem like a lot to you.
But for me,
to be able to have this kind of connections.
I couldn't do that before.
I'm glad you can now.
We'd better go.
Yeah.
Secretary Heller is gonna be in the lobby in 5 minutes.
Secretary Heller?
Yeah, I called him Dad once in a press conference
so I decided then to use his title all the time.
Audrey.
Your father is a very perceptive man.
I would like to tell him about us before he finds out on his own.
Look...
My Dad is kind of old-fashioned.
Even though Paul and I are separated, he...
he still considers us married.
I understand that.
And I don't want your father to draw the wrong conclusion
and think that I had anything to do with the break-up between you and Paul.
Yeah, but you didn't.
Please Jack.
Let's just give it a little more time.
I'm gonna tell you something and I don't want you to pannick.
I'm falling in love with you.
Look, I dont want you to say anything.
And I don't need you to feel the same way.
I just wanted you to know.
I will see you downstairs.
Alright.
Here is what we have:
a known terrorist named Thomas Sharek
managed through the country undetected.
We  believe there's a likelyhood Sharek helped organized the train attack in Santa Clarita.
If  he did,
he's gonna get out of the country as fast as he can.
Which means we have a small window of opportunity here.
Who's covering airport and costumes?
I am.
I've issued a mandate to LAX, Long Beach and Ontario.
As usual, we can't hear you.
Also, where's your labtop in case you need to pull data?
I'm sorry I'm speak up and
I don't need my labtop, I have everything memorized.
What I was saying is that I have contacted all the airports and security.
Do we have any local contacts with Sharek?
We're looking into those now.
Alright.
Promote everything we receive up to Division.
Let's find Sharek before he leaves the city.
Let's go.
Excuse me, Mrs Driscoll. Don't you think it's a mistake
to assume that Sharek is on his way out of L.A.?
No.
But the timing on the intel doesn't quite match.
It said 8 A.M. and the train bombing happened around 7.
Just focus on finding Sharek.
Yes?
It's Thomas.
Did Dar get the briefcase ?
Yes.
- He's on his radio now.
- Good.
You did well Thomas.
What about Maris ?
He's waiting for you.
He has everything you need.
Berous, are you eating with us?
I'll be right down, mum.
I'm concerned about him.
Concerned? Why?
I think he's still seeing this american girl, Debbie.
You said you talked to him.
I did.
I told him he was no longer allowed to have contact with her.
And he agreed, right?
Yes, but I think he's still seeing her behind our backs.
I'll speak to him.
No.
I'll take care of it.
Berous, we're sitting down to eat.
Berous?
I'm on the phone.
Get off and come down now.
Who was he talking to?
I don't know.
Sorry.
Who were you on the phone with?
My pal, Scott.
You were talking to that american girl.
No, I told you I don't see her anymore.
Don't lie to me, Berous.
I hear your phone calls at night.
I read your e-mails.
You read my e-mails?
That's my business!
Don't you raise your voice to your father!
While you live under my roof, there's no such thing
as your business.
No more communications with that girl.
Do you understand me?
Don't look at her you're talking to me.
Yes, sir.
...horrible tragedy occured a short time ago.
An early morning communer train
collided with a pickup truck
that was apparently crossing the track.
Most of the passengers were severely injured.
NTSP have arrived at the scene and are investigating the cause.
At this time, the authorities are not saying whether this was an accident
or a targetted attack but as you can there has been a...
So far, everything is on schedule.
Have yo spoken to Thomas?
Yes, the briefcase is on its way to us now.
When it gets here,
you'll take it to the warehouse.
Why doesn't Omar take it directly?
He doesn't need to know where our people are working.
That's the safest way.
Berous,
if your father seem sevre,
it's because our job here is a difficult one.
If we are to succeed,
it's important that we are of a single mind.
I understand.
What we will accomplish today will change the world.
We're fortunate that our family has been chosen to do this.
We cannot fail.
Yes, father.
- Morning, Jennifer.
- Morning.
What are you doing here so early?
I'm not here early.
Been here all night?
Yeah.
What are you working on?
Nothing right now.
I'm just stealing some software from Adobe and Microsoft.
You're gonna get caught one day.
Hey, Mel !
Don't tell anybody or I'd have to kill you.
What the hell is this?
W ow!
Melany, come look at his!
Looks like someone's trying corrupt the Internet.
Yeah, but it hasn't start propagating yet.
They're just placing the nodes.
Look at this!
This thing could tank every system in the world!
You've gotta tell somebody.
If I call the Feds from here,
they'll trace the call, they'll know I was stealing code.
Then do it from a payphone.
Yeah.
No, i'm up to speed on the train bombing.
How many confirmed dead?
I didn't know that.
I will. Thanks, Sal.
32 dead.
What's the initial assessment?
An act of terrorism.
When you get to CTu, I want you to find out all the details and call me.
Yes, sir.
And listen,
I don't want anyone except the two of you to know about this meeting with Richard.
Of course.
I tried to get ahold of you last night. Where were you?
I had dinner with a friend.
Anyone I know?
No.
- Jack.
- Sir.
I'll call you when I get to CTU.
Yeah, I'll get it. Hold on.
O'Brian.
Chloé, it's Edgar Stiles.
Edgar, you don"t need to use your last name. You've been here over a month.
- What is it?
- Okay...
I've got someone on the other line who says he's a friend of yours and needs to talk to you.
- Who, Edgar?
- His name is Andrew Page.
- Fine. Put him through.
- Okay.
Hello?
Andrew, you know I can't take personal calls here.
It's not personal.
I found something on the net I think you should know about.
What?
There's a fake NAT table and several large burped routers.
It was loaded this morning.
How would you know that?
I was trying to download some software and I noticed it.
And by download I assume you mean steal. Otherwise you wouldn't even see the NAT table.
Okay, fine. But I hacked deeper and I found all kinds of stuff.
What kind of stuff?
I think someone's positioning code for a major Internet attack.
The thing is that not all the code remarks are in English.
What language were they in?
I don't know.
Looked Middle Eastern. Like Arabic or turkish maybe.
You find something?
Yeah, Cyril's working on the list of known contacts of Sharek.
This is Maris Landstraf. He owns a drycleaners in Studio City.
We dug into the records and found his business is owned
by an holding company based ou t of Ankarah, Turkey.
Alright.
Give this to Ronnie, tell him to get over there and see what he can find.
Excuse me, Mrs. Driscoll.
What is it, Chloé?
I just got a call from an old classmate, Andrew Page.
He noticed that a number of high-profile Internet nodes were compromized.
I think this could be related to our present threat.
What makes you say that?
A computer network virus was launched this morning from a server somewhere in Turkey.
That's where Sharek is from?
Should I start working it up?
No.
The bombing and Sharek are all we should be dealing with now.
But pass it to the FBI.
Excuse me, sir. Can I help you?
Yes I have a scheduled meeting with Erin Driscoll.
Jack!
It's okay, Sarah. This is Jack Bauer.
Oh! M. Bauer.
- I'm sorry.
- No, that's fine.
Chloé, how have you been?
Not  perfect but okay, I guess. How are Kim and Chase?
Good.
They just got a house in Valencia.
Kim is taking care of Angela.
Chase is working for a private security company.
That's interesting.
I mean, I'm interested, I just have to set up a protocol.
Yeah...
Jack.
Curtis!
Is Erin ready for our meeting?
- Almost.
But I should tell you, you're prbably gonna get cut short today.
The train bombing in Santa Clarita.
Among other things.
What other things ?
I wouldn't worry with it.
We're out.
Okay, we'll have you in voice 3, data 4.
- Alright.
- Ronnie, this is Jack Bauer.
Jack, Ronnie Mabel.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hey, Jack.
Ronnie's got your old job, head of field ops.
Yeah, I know. How's it going?
It's busy. Nice meeting you.
Look, would you rather reschedule this?
No, it won't be necessary.
Erin will be free in a couple minutes.
I'll tell you what.
What don't you use the station?
Make any calls.
- It won't be long.
- Okay. Thank you.
I don't know, Max. Let me find out.
I'm on with a representant from Vandemburg.
He wants to know how long he'll be pushed back today.
Don't change anything with Vandemburg.
We'll stick to the original schedule.
Okay, Max, yeah. We'll see you then.
Have you spoken with your brother?
No, I don't think he even knows I'm coming with you today.
That's probably best that he doesn't.
Alright, I'll stay in the car.
Dad, look...
even if Richard does go to this protest. It's not the end of the world.
It's not a page 1 story.
That's not the point. It's an embarassment to me an to the President.
What are you gonna say to him?
I have no idea.
The thing that gets to me
is that he doesn't know the first thing about the politics of all this.
He's just doing it to rebel against you.
When did I become the enemy?
- What did I do?
- Nothing!
Richard's acting like a spoiled child. He's gonna have to grow up some day.
Audrey Raines.
The President is calling for Secretary Heller.
Yeah.
It's the President's office.
Hello.
Please hold for the President.
- James.
- Yes, Mr. President.
James, I'm thinkiong about raising the terror alert level.
Because of the train bombing out here ?
No, not just that.
Langley has picked up some chatter.
We also have intel on some watchlisted individuals who've gotten into the country.
Well, my insttinct is to wait until the NTSP waves in on the bombing.
In the meantime, we can increase our state of readiness.
Alright, I'll take that into consideration.
I'm meeting with the Secretary of State and director Shay in a few minutes.
I'll see if they feel the same about it.
Yes, Mr. President.
Thank you.
Hello, Erin.
Hello, Jack.
I'm sorry Secretary Heller couldn't be here today.
It's just as well.
As I'm sure you were told, we have a protocol in progress.
So, why don't we just go down the items and get it over with?
That's fine with me.
I'll be direct with you, Jack.
I didn't like the budget your boss proposed.
What's the problem?
Well, the Department of Defence is asking for 85% of all inter-agency moneys
which is very little for CTU.
If you want a bigger piece of the pie, you're gonna have to justify it.
I have a proposal for you.
You want to use satellite surveillance for all the traffic at the harbor?
Yes. Problem?
Yes, it's insufficient.
You need to maintain bodies on the ground.
Too expensive.
Not if you utilize intelligence from the other agencies.
I'm not gonna have Secretary Heller sign off on a budget taht doesn't make sense.
I'll  talk to Heller about it myself.
No, you'll talk to me.
We're not doing this twice.
Erin, Ronnie has arrived at Landshaff's drycleaners.
Where's the feed?
It'll be on channel one as soon as he sets the hidden camera.
Excuse me, Jack.
Okay, here we go.
Stand down until I give you order.
Aaron, go round the back.
Sean, you go take the side.
Hello?
Can I help you?
You must be Mr. Landstraf.
Do I know you?
My name is Ronnie Labell. I'm with Los Angeles CTU.
I need to ask you a few questions.
What do you know about a man named Thomas Sharek?
I don't know this man.
Really?
It's in your records that you contacted him in the last few days.
It wasn't me.
I run a legitimate business here.
I never said you business wasn't legitimate, sir.
You can't just walk in here and harrass me.
He's hiding something.
It's beeing handled, Jack.
Erin, listen to me.
This store is open for business but the blinds are closed.
There's no other employees.
This guys is way too nervous. Trust me. He's hiding something.
Turn back a little momment, please.
Says here you open at 6 A.M. Have you been here the entire time?
Yes.
- What's this about?
- Right there.
- Did you see that?
- Yeah.
Tell him to look for something on his right.
Ronnie.
On his right, see if someone could be hiding.
Do you mind i I take a look behind that counter?
Yes, I do mind. Look, this is my store and I want you to walk ou now.
Sir, I'm not walking out of there until I take a look...
Jerk!
Got him!
Great job.
Remember, Dad, we're on a tight schedule today.
Richard.
Dad.
- Hello.
- Hey, it's me.
Hey. Aren't you supposed to be in your meeting with Driscoll?
Yeah. She had to step away.
Listen, CTU's just picked up a prime suspect in the train bombing.
They're bringing him in for questioning now.
My father's still in with Richard.
That's all right. I'll brief him later. I just wanted to let you know.
All right. That's good news.
Yeah. Yeah, I think so.
All right...
um, I'll talk to you later.
Wait. Wait.
What is it?
Look, about earlier...
I don't want you to think that that made me uncomfortable.
It's just that since Teri died, I never thought I'd...
Jack, it's all right.
- I understand.
- No. No, you don't.
I just want you to know that...
I'm falling in love with you, too.
Wow. Um, you caught me off guard.
Yeah. Sorry about that.
Look, Driscoll's coming back. I gotta go.
Then go.
Okay. I'll talk to you when I get a break.
All right.
What's happening with the suspect?
Ronnie's bringing him in.
Who is he?
Fortunately, for you, Jack, it's our problem, not yours.
Right.
I'm going, Dad.
And there's nothing you can to do stop me.
How many cars do you need to get places?
I didn't come here to argue about the environment, Richard.
I didn't ask you to come at all.
I do not want you to attend or to speak at that rally at Lockheed this afternoon.
You don't have any leverage over what I do anymore.
You haven't since I stopped taking your money.
Can't you ever think of anything besides yourself?
If you do this,
it will humiliate the President,
and it will be dangerous to national security.
What could be more dangerous
than 2,500 missile delivery systems?
Oh, spare me your sixth-grade Michael Moore logic.
The world is a little bit more complicated than that, Richard.
We do not live in a utopia.
America has enemies.
Enemies who were our friends a year ago.
And in another year, it'll change again,
unless people stop supporting your psychotic need to control the world.
Psychotic need?!
We serve our country!
We serve the cause of freedom!
What do you do?!
Why don't you just go back to your little motorcade
and drive somewhere where people actually buy the lies you're selling?
Okay, look, look, we don't have to do this, okay? We do not have to.
Fine, Dad. What do you want to do?
Do not disrespect me. I am your father.
Nothing.
It was my friend, not me.
- What's his name?
- Andrew.
- Andrew what?
- Andrew Paige.
Who did you tell?
I swear, we didn't tell anyone. I don't know.
Don't lie to me.
I don't know! He just stumbled on the site and logged out!
Don't lie to me!
Where is Andrew Paige now?
I was just doing my work-- I don't...
You can use station five. Chloe's opened up a socket for you.
You'll be able to access the records volume to look at those budget numbers.
Okay, fine.
- I know this guy.
- Who, Sherek?
We were tracking him when I was here.
We knew him as Jann Bolek.
We linked him to over a dozen complicated bombings in Europe in the late '90s.
Unfortunately, we weren't able to stop him from today's attack.
But we did catch him.
And, Jack, I'm sorry I was abrupt before.
You helped us with the takedown. Thank you.
Erin, listen to me.
This doesn't make sense.
I know this guy's file. He's a major handler.
He wouldn't risk exposing himself here in the United States for a train bombing.
It's not big enough.
We'll take that into consideration when we interrogate him.
Give my best to Secretary Heller.
- Chloe.
- What?
The original data that you pulled up on Sherek,
was there any indication of a secondary strike?
No. Everything supports that he was here for the train bombing.
But there was a time discrepancy.
What do you mean?
There was some high-probability chatter indicating an attack at 8:00 a.m.
The train bombing happened at 7:00.
They didn't give a window? They actually called for a specific time?
Yeah, but the intel was off by an hour.
Driscoll thought it was close enough.
You can't do that.
What's your log-on I.D. for Interpol overnights?
I'm not comfortable doing this.
Chloe, please.
You're in.
Is this the source?
Yes. That's the decipher.
Calls for an 8:00 strike
"...unless target deviates." That doesn't make sense.
Trains don't deviate, they're on a fixed course and schedule.
Sometimes when Interpol's breaking codes and communiques,
it won't use the exact wording.
What are you thinking, Jack?
Sherek didn't come here for a train bombing.
Something's going to happen at 8:00.
That's ten minutes from now.
No, Paul, I don't want to wait.
I'm going to call my lawyer as soon as we get back to D.C.
and we're going to get this divorce process moving.
Well, what's the hurry?
We said we'd take a year apart and see what happened.
Yeah, but it's almost been a year.
I don't want to wait any longer.
Hang on.
Look, I got to take this call. We'll talk when I back to D.C.
- Yeah, fine.
- All right, bye.
Jack.
Hey, I need to speak with your father.
He's still in with Richard. He doesn't want to be interrupted.
This is urgent. I need him to get me clearance
so I can interrogate the suspect in the train bombing.
Driscoll won't let me anywhere near him.
I believe he's got information about a secondary hit, a larger one.
Supposed to take place this morning at 8:00.
Well, it's almost 8:00 now.
I know, that's why I need to speak with him.
All right, hang on.
I'm going to speak at that rally this afternoon, Dad.
And it's not because I hate you.
It's 'cause it's something I believe in.
Did it ever occur to you that these people are using you?
Don't you realize they're letting you speak for one reason and one reason only,
because you are my son!
Well, I wish I weren't.
What is it, Audrey?
I'm sorry, it's Jack. It's urgent.
Excuse me, Richard.
What could be more important than intimidating me?
I didn't know you were hiding in the car.
Richie, why are you doing this to Dad?
- Can't you just back off?
- I'm not doing anything to him.
You know if you go to that protest at Lockheed it's going to hurt him.
Whatever it takes to stop what he's doing.
Jack, if I step on Driscoll's toes and it doesn't pay off,
all of a sudden, I have ton of political fallout to deal with.
Sir, I understand that.
But I wouldn't be asking you this if I didn't believe
there was an imminent threat to national security that I could help avert.
Share your concerns with Driscoll.
- Let CTU handle it.
- Sir, there isn't time.
It's the President.
Jack, it's the President. I've got to go.
Yes, sir.
Damn.
How long you been in Los Angeles?
Who are you working with?
We don't have time for this.
Okay, you listen to me.
Unless you start giving me some answers right now,
you're going to end up in a hole for the next 30 years.
Who are you working with?!
Why did you bomb that train?!
How far can I push this guy?
We have to find out who he's working with.
Should go as far as we have to.
Maybe we should bring Johnson in.
Sorry, sir, this area's off-limits.
Oh, I'm looking for Erin Driscoll.
Jack!
Jack, what are you doing?
Call security now.
What is happening at 8:00?
Son of a bitch, he's jammed the codes.
I am not messing with you.
You are going to tell me... what is happening at 8:00?!
Jack, holster your weapon!
Jack!
I said holster your weapon!
Call Medical.
What is your primary objective?!
I'll order security to shoot you if I have to.
Get that door open.
What is your primary objective?!
Secretary of Defense!
Heller.
- Secretary Heller?
- Yes.
Secretary Heller's the target.
Call Secret Service now.
Call now. Get a team on the way.
Yeah, I'll hold.
The President wants us back in D.C. tonight.
What meetings can we eject?
Not Vandenberg. The media's expecting you there.
Maybe we skip Paradigm,
and handle that with a teleconference next week.
Come on, pick up the phone!
Tell the President we'll we rearrange our schedule
and fly back this afternoon.
Yeah.
Audrey, it's Jack.
- Are you still at Richard's?
- Yeah.
You need to get your father out of there now!
The bombing this morning was diversiory!
Your father is the real target! You've got to get out of there now!
- Target?!
- Audrey!
Oh, my God.
Audrey!
On your feet!
Jack! No!
Jack!
Audrey!
Let her go!
Where we going?!
Jack! Help!
Subtitles: Travis, Kicker & RaceMan
www.forom.com