Hey!  It's about time to go to the airport.
What are you scratching?
It's time to go to the airport!
I'm on my way for the pick-up.
Wow!  Is she nuts?  Seriously!
Everything but the word "Koo" is torn.
Why is Mr. Suen not picking me up?
Toothpick's arranging your press conference.
He's busy right now.
How did you know his nickname was Toothpick?
I know you're Chopsticks.
Chopsticks are from wood and your name is
Forest Koo.
What else do you know?
I know that chopsticks are utensils used for
picking up food.
Toothpicks, on the other hand, are used for
leftovers.
Please keep your hands off my precious sword.
You're a music conductor.
Why do you carry a sword around?
I like to strike the sword after striking
the baton.
You're a renown conductor.
Your baton must be very outstanding.
Can I take a look at it?
I only take it out on performance.
I'm actually very fond ofyou.
I admire you very much.
I've even got your posters!
Like the one where you held the baton.
You look very handsome and sophisticated!
Could you sign an autograph for me?
Chauffeur...pull over here please...
We haven't arrived yet.
What are you doing, Mr. Koo?
I've got my own car.
Will you take me along?
Sorry.  I don't have any spare room.
Please excuse me.
See you later.
Hey, Mr. Koo!
You're always like this.
Rest after every couple of steps.
Of course, I'm like this.  I'm pregnant!
We can never get home like this.
What are you giggling for?
Haven't you seen a gravid lady before?
Want me to teach you a lesson, you little punk?
- Yes...I've seen it before...
He's staring at you.
This stuff is perfect for us to use.
Why don't we buy a karaoke set and take it home?
What's wrong?
- Pain!
What's happening?
I'm having labor pain!
What?  You need to deliver now?
I need some help.  She's now in labor!
Help!
Bring some hot water right away!
Ouch!  Don't touch my abdomen!
I'm deliver right away after one touch.
Bring some hot water!
What are you standing there for?
Come over and help out!
Hurry up!
Hurry!  Over there!
Why are you idling over there?
Aren't you a human being?  Why aren't you giving
any help?     -Don't touch me!
Bring out some ofyour humanity here!
Are you okay, honey?
My stomach hurts!
Does it?
- Yes!
Does it feel better now?
Stand back, everyone!  Thanks!
What's the matter?
She's going to give birth.
Then call the police.
No need.  I'm not giving birth now.
Didn't you just say that you wanted to be
in labor?
I can't give birth right now.
What's wrong with you?
What do you mean by saying what's wrong with me?
A big group of men watching over my wife
to give birth?
Then, tell your wife to give birth!
What the hell?
Let's go!
Lunatic!
- Excuse me!
Nothing to see here.
Please excuse me.
Get out of the car...
Take this...
Don't stand in my way!  Over there!
Let's go!
Sister...
Sister!
- What is it?
Coming here to borrow money again?
Of course, not!  I've got something good for you.
Something good? Are you really my brother?
Yes!
Fellow co-workers, I've brought something good
for all ofyou today.
Ifyou want a good bargain,
please come with me.
Come on...you won't regret it!
Come on...yes, big sister...
Isn't it great?
Original price was $100.  Now, it's $80.
I owed you $500 last time.
This CD playerworths more than a grand.
Now, don't say I've got nothing good to offer.
Did you steal this?
- Steal?
My friend switched to another profession and sold
all of this stuff to me for a very cheap price.
So I brought them over to sell it to your
co-workers.
Hey!  Take...take care of my big sister!
Give her a good discount.
Sister...this...
Who's your sister?
Well, somebody's sister, this one...
Does your mother know that you went out today?
Sure...this one was originally priced at $100.
Now, it's on for sale at $30.  You can't find it
anywhere at this price.  Take a good look!
Hey...dearfellow co-workers...you know what...
You won't believe there's good things being sold
for cheap unless you actually see it with your
very own eyes!
Check it out even ifyou're not buying, fellow
co-workers!
Is there anything nice this time around, Jacky?
Of course, there is!  Why wouldn't there be any?
We've got all different sorts of goods here!
It's cheap and durable.
Is there something for me?
Take a look!
Definitely!  Of course, there's something
for you!
There's something for people ofall ages.
This way please.  Hurry!
Yes...over there...
Check it out before it's all sold out.  Hurry up!
What do you think about this room?
Ifyou don't like it, you can always change
the room.
Besides, I don't have to pay the money.
Come over here and take a look.
This is the reading room, the kitchen, and the
dining room.  Bedroom is on the other side.
You can call for room service ifyou get hungry.
I don't have to pay for it.
But I do have to pay for this.
Thank you.
- Thanks.
I'm sorry.  I gave too much.
This bed is big enough for
you to do anything you want.
You haven't returned for 10 years.
Would you like me to prepare some local chicks
for you to enjoy?
I'm a vegetarian now.
You may be a vegetarian but
how about your little friend over there?
Well?  How do you like this room?
Not bad.  It's pretty quiet too!
I'll open the door first.
Hey, Yip!
Hello!
- Recognize him?
Hey, Yip!  How do you do?
- Chopsticks!
Long time, no see!
That's right.
Is that your little brother?
His wife.  Thanks.
A woman?
It's the blind wonder.
It's been a long time, Chopsticks.
Well?  How's everything?
Hey, Blind Wonder!
- Hello!
Hey!  Why is Blind Wonder completely blind now?
Unfortunately, he never thinks of himselfas
a blind man.
You look better after shaving offthe beard.
I'm Toothpick.  Chopstick's over there.
Hello, Chopstick!  How are you?
You're looking good!
I hear some chicks coming.  I'll open the door.
You don't need to open it.  You're blind.
Hey, Jumbo!
- Chopsticks!
Hey, Chopsticks!  Haven't seen you for over
10 years!
You're keeping a pretty good figure.
Are you talking about these chickens?
I've grabbed two live chickens from the farm
just foryou.
Great!
It's hard to find a "home chicken" to eat
in Hong Kong nowadays.     -It is!
We have guests arriving.
I'll open the door.
You're blind...don't wander around...
Sit down...
Keep an eye on the chicken.
Chewing Gum!
How are you?  Long time, no see!
Did you come alone?
- No.
Hurry up!  This is my wife, Jenny.
- Hello!
My sister-in-law Jackie.
My sons, Jimmy and Johnny.
My youngest son, Joey.
My mother-in-law, Judy and my dog, Bobby.
This is my brother-in-law also named Bobby.
How do you do?
That's his girlfriend.  What's your name again?
Jobie.
- Jobie!
I told you not to do this.
You're known for spitting out gum after chewing.
What happened to you?
He accidentally swallowed it down.
So it's been stuck with him ever since.
Daddy, the baby's hungry.  Where's the milk?
- Coming...
The milk powder's with you.
Oh no!  The chicken has flown off!
My son would also like to drink some milk.
Watch out for the kids!
Please take care of my kid for a while.
I'll boil some waterfor the milk.
Let's play mahjong!
Since everybody's here, why don't we play some
mahjong?
I'll also play.
You're blind.  How can you?
I can feel the tiles with my fingers.
But you guys will have to tell me what you
discard.     -Mr. Chopsticks.
Please look after my dog.
-Count me in for the mahjong game.
Here's no mahjong set.
I have.
Please look after my dog.  Thanks.
And keep an eye on the chicken as well.
I haven't been this happy foryears.
How long will you stay?  A month, isn't it?
Yes.
Then we can party every night.
Not every night.  Just every other night.
This is all foryou.  Take this.
I'll go play mahjong.
We have to attend the press conference.
I'll only play for a couple of rounds.
I'm coming...
Excuse me, miss.  What are you doing here?
I'm waiting for someone.
What's this?
This is all the other stuff.  Where's the pastry?
Sorry, sir.
We don't serve pastry at the cocktail lounge.
But I like it.  I've booked it in advance.
Fine...I'll order someone to buy it for you.
Mr. Koo, I'd like to ask how long you plan to
stay here for.
Approximately, over a month.
Excuse me.
Mr. Koo, I'd like to ask...
Please.  One at a time.
Please excuse me.  Thanks.
Mr. Koo, I...
I told you to stand in line.
Mr. Koo, you've performed in many parts of
the world.
Which ofthese places have left you with the
deepest impression?
My shoelaces are untied!
- India.
What attracts you most about India?
- The food.
After you finish this concert, Mr. Koo,
where's your next stop?
After this, I'll be going to Australia and Japan.
How is it, fellow reporters?
Have you all finished with the questions?
We've still got this four-eyes here.
Me?
Yes.  It's your turn now.
Is it my turn?
Mr. Koo, have you...had dinneryet?
Not yet.
Good answer.  Thank you.  Thanks a lot!
What's wrong?
Can't I show concern for others?
You guysjust keep on asking.  He is hungry.
Yes...let's have some snacks, everyone.
Let's go!
I've got someone to buy you some pastry.
I have one more question foryou, Mr. Koo.
Why does it look all dark over there?
What did you eat?  Why is it dark?
African chicken.
- Really?
Mr. Koo, I suggest that you should head back to
your room and wash up.
Good idea.  Let me help you with the washing.
No thanks.
Don't just hold that sword of his.
Wait a minute!
Sir, can you do me a favor?
I've been chased by some bad men.
Do you mind if I can hide in your room for
a while?
Don't you know how to call the police?
I guess you haven't lived in Hong Kong for
a long time.
Even our chief commissioner gets robbed.
Please.  I beg you.
Otherwise, I'll be dead for sure.
Sorry to botheryou.
Do you live alone?
Yes, but I've had many friends who came to
visit me.
What shall I do?
What do you mean?
What happened?  How'd it turn out like this?
Come in.
Blind Wonder, Yip!
Where are you heading offto, Blind Wonder?
Is anyone in?  Is everybody gone?
Have a seat.  I've got to get changed.
Hey, what are you doing in there?
Thanks for saving my life.
I want to give you a little present.
That's me.
Have you gone insane?
Hurry up and take a picture!
Don't get in my way.
Hey!  What are you doing?
Hurry up!
Jacky, hurry up and take a picture.
What pictures are you taking?
Aren't you that reporter?
Hold...hold it...
Hold onto his legs.
No pictures!
Stop taking pictures!
- Hurry!
Don't let him touch you!
What the hell are you doing?  Stop this!
This is called adultery caught on film.
Ifyou want it back, bring $30,000 to us.
Thirty grand!
Wow!  Are all these people trying to take
adultery photos?
They've even got us in the photo.
Happy birthday to you...
Hey...don't let them go!
They're taking my photos!
Blow the candles.
Ignore them...
Who told you to be poor?
I take risks forwork.  I'll do it...
Why don't you just discard that piece of
junk car?
I'm getting a fever...I'm working my ass off...
Hey...there it is!
Where's Jacky?
- He's inside.
What's the meaning ofthis?
Isn't that enough?  Go away!
Enough!
Hey!  Your sister's coming!
I don't care.  Take her away.  She's annoying!
Hey, punk!
Pipe down, bitch!
Come out!
No way!  What'll you do about it?
Will you come out or not?
Mom!  Help!  She's trying to kill me!
Jack...
You killed me, bitch!
How are you doing, Jacky?
How do I remove this, Jacky?
That hurts!
Just bearwith the pain.  I'll pull you out.
What the hell was that?
It hurts.  It's breaking off...
Punk!
Bitch, you've locked me long enough!
Now it's your turn to be the caged animal!
Open the door!
Done!  What do we do now?
You numbskull!  Obviously, we head out for
some fun.
Let's go!
Open up!
Have fun inside!
Last night, I saw this strange man in a dream.
He taught me a special skill known as
"The Speedy Hands".
Everything from the unbuttoning of someone's
pocket, stealing the wallet,
to re-buttoning again would take less than
a second.
Do you know how long is in a second?
Tick-tock!
"Tick-tock", my ass!
See?  It's gone.  Idiot!
-Teach us!
Don't speak of the word "teach".
We'll do research next time.  Okay...
Remember that moustachio from the other day?
Fine.  Now I'll demonstrate it to all ofyou.
Okay!
Go over there and pretend that you fell down.
Fall down?  It lacks presence and it doesn't
look good at all.
You'll look fine ifyou fall down after wearing
lipstick.
Aren't I right?
Ifyou fall down, his ass will move aside.
Then I can...
I'll time you.
-What's the need in timing me?
It takes a split second to succeed.
Hey, you got it!
Fall down...
Just fall...no need for the lipstick...
you're pretty enough...
Fall down...just fall down right away...
Sorry, sir.  It's too crowded on this side.
Try the other side.
- Yes...
Excuse me, mister.
You made her fall and left her in disregard.
How can you leave like this?
Yeah...
You messed it up!
You don't even know how to trip overyourself.
Go home and sleep!
He didn't even stick out his butt.
Yeah...
Come here, you...
- What?
Get over there and seduce him.
It's so embarrassing.
You're the best at this kind ofthing.
Now go!
- Fine!
Hey, moustachio.  How do you read this word?
Big boobs.
Hey...
What are you doing?
Help!  Help!
Run...
Don't let him get away!
Don't give it back to him...moustachio...
You again?
Aren't you the reporterwho pulled a prank on me
that day?
Give me those negatives back!
Hey!  Didn't you get your wallet back?
No fun at all!
Hand over the negatives!
What negatives?
The negatives...
- No way!
Give it back...     -I won't.
What are you going to do about it, moustachio?
You won't?
Good morning, sister.
Let me introduce you to a friend of mine.
Hey!  Let's go!
Jacky, I haven't got on the car yet!
Alright.
Give me the wallet back.
Take it.  Ifyou lay a finger on me,
I'll shout out the words "sexual harrassment".
Hey!
Come on!  Get over here!
Be careful!
- Get over here!
Forked road up ahead.  Lay siege on her!
That's enough, young lady.
Don't come any closer.  I'll shout!
Where's my wallet?  Give it back to me!
Harrassment!
- The wallet!
Get in the car.  Hurry!
Help!
The wallet!
Jacky, save me!
Hold it!  Freeze!  Come over here!
Stop the engine, step out and hand over your
driver license!
What the hell?
$36.80? That's expensive!
It usually costs me $17.90.
That's right.  Why is it so expensive all of
a sudden?
I'll head in first.
That's the price according to the meter, ma'am.
How would I know ifyou sped up the meter?
Hello.
Officer, I'm Marmadonna.
I've come for my daughter Philidonna.
Who again?
Would all ofyou police officers care to have
a cup of tea?
That's right, officers.  Have some tea.
I'm here for someone.
Forget it...
May I have a piece of that cake?
Hey!  Over here!
After a long day ofwork, take a tea break!
Have some tea!
Don't be shy.
- Mommy!
Mommy's coming, dear.  Don't be scared.
Mommy!
Let me deal with it for you.
Officer, please don't place any charges on her.
My daughter is not a runaway child.
Have some tea and dessert, officer.
Have some tea!
Does your mother bake cakes for a living?
Yes, I'm the owner of St. Madonna Bakery.
We have chain stores all over Hong Kong,
Singapore, Malaysia, North America and Europe.
Ma'am, your daughter...
What happened to my daughter?
This man claims that your daughter has stolen
his wallet.
What?
Hey, moustachio!  My daughter stole your wallet?
Don't let her have it!  It must be your brother.
Have some cake!
Sir, her little brother must have influenced
my daughter to do this!
You should arrest her!  Press the charges on her!
Please make it clear.
Your daughter's the one giving my little brother
the bad influence.     -What?
Isn't it?
Don't you believe this?
Would my little princess ever become a bad
influence to this auto-mechanic pauper?
Please show a little more respect!
Wealth doesn't mean anything.
Are you slamming the table?
- Yeah!  So what?
Settle down, you two!  We know what to do.
What happened, Chopsticks?
You came at the right time!
What are the charges?  Sexual harrassment?
Which is it?
He claims that my daughter stole his wallet!
That's impossible!  Don't you agree with that?
Mom, it was only meant as a joke.
That's right!  The young lady's toying with you
for a joke.
Don't you have a girl as well?
Yes...he has many girls.
Just like his name.
Chopsticks.  It's specially made for picking up
the good ones.
I'm not married yet.
But he's got a naughty little brother.
Tell your daughter to take good precaution.
Who are you?
I'm the head manager ofthe Hong Kong Arts Group.
This is my business card.
I'm also his manager.
Perfect!  This young woman wants to press
charges for sexual harrassment.
Sexual harrassment?
How could you do that to my daughter?
Tell me!
How could you do such a thing to my daughter?
She stole my wallet, I wanted to take it back and
she screamed out the words "sexual harrassment".
It wasjust a joke, Mom.
Baby, this is more than a simple joke!
Ifyou wanted some fun, just tell me.
I've got plenty ofcake shops and department
stores.
I can notify the staff to make the preparations
for you
so you may steal to your heart's content.
That's no fun at all!
Especially when it's been prepared!
Baby, you...
How do you raise that daughter ofyours?
Officer!
John!
What's the matter, Madonna?
Uncle.
Girlsjust want to have fun.
No, ma'am!
Your daughter has committed a criminal offense.
How can that be?
How could my daughter steal other people's
things, John?
Help me out.  The least I can do is, return your
negatives back.
So whose wallet did she steal again?
It's nothing...we're just having fun!
Why did you help her?
Her mother doesn't know how to raise her
properly.
You should give a chance to the young lady.
Everything's fine now, Madonna.
You may leave with your daughter now.
Yes.
Let's go home now.
Thanks, officers!  Bye-bye now!
So, can we go now?
Sure...
Ms. Kam.
What is it?
Can you ask your brother to hand over the
negatives back to me?
What negatives?
He tricked me that other day with a bunch of
people and took some photos of me.
That little bastard!  I'll see what I can do.
How's this, you vegetarian?
You won't pick this one up.
Then, she's mine!
Go back with Chopsticks first.
I've got somethings to do.
Go now...come on...
Where are you going, Ms. Kam?
I can give you a ride.
No thanks.  I've got my own car.
That's great.  I don't.
Why don't you give me a ride?
Are you alright, boss?
Let's see how you'd feel ifyou tripped over
yourself!
I told you not to press on the gas.
It's on fire now!
I never thought that bitch was awful like that.
Who did you say was "awful"?
It's nothing...let's go...
Did you get hurt from the fall?
He's alright.  Let's get moving!
You pervert, you deserved to get blackmailed!
Me?  A pervert?
Hey!  Shouldn't you know your brotherwell?
Alright!  That's enough!
Anyway, I'm getting your photos back.
This fiddle head's surely hard to pick up.
What fiddle head?  It's a fiddle stick!
I'll fiddle you!  Let's go!
Hello.  Is Mr. Koo there?
You don't need to know who I am.
You're someone famous with a reputation.
I'm sure you wouldn't want these embarrassing
snapshots posted around the streets, right?
Then, you should pay me 30 grand.
What?  Don't you know what "30 grand" means?
You're such a fool!
"30 grand" means $30,000.  Now you...
Sis...
How dare you attempt to blackmail someone,
you little bastard!     -What are you doing?
You want to die, kid?
No!  Many people are watching!
It's embarrassing.
You feel embarrassed now, don't you?
Hey!
He's amazing, isn't he?
Isn't he?
Alright!  This section's over.
I'll buy dinnerforyou guys tonight!
Now, we'll practice the 39th section.
Hey...
How long are you going to practice?
I'm in a hurry.
Be quiet.
Hey!  Your photos are here!
Whether or not they're needed, it's up to you.
Ms. Kam!
What is it?
Thanks!
Be careful next time.
There won't be any.
Well, how would I know?
Ifyou've got time next Saturday,
you can come to my recital.  It's on me!
You mean the music you were playing now?
It grates my ears!
Ifyou're not there for the music, you can
watch me conduct.
It's not easy on the eyes either.
Hey!  Why don't we go for karaoke tomorrow night?
Sure!
See you later!
- Bye!
Hey, four-eyes!  How can I find you?
Write down the number to my hotel.  It's 524...
Robbery!
Robbery...
Freeze!
- Robbery!
Thank you!
Robbery...
- Don't run!
Are you okay?
Ouch!  That hurts.
Where does it hurt?
It hurts.  You're stepping on me.
You should have told me earlier.
Do me a favor and shut the doorwhile
you're at it.
Please take a seat.
I'm going to heat up my brother's meal.
You treat your brother pretty well.
Would you like some coffee?
Sure.  Thanks!
Have some coffee.
What's wrong with your TV?  Picture looks
distorted.
It is.  Jacky made it malfunction by pressing
things at random.
Hey, moustachio!  Move it!
Hey!  Move it!  I want to watch the TV.  Not you!
Hey!  Go over there!  Over there!
Help me out here, moustachio!
You can't open it like this.
Get me a spoon.
A spoon!
Hurry!
Hey!  Hurry up!
Hey!  Dinner's ready.
Rice with roasted goose and BBQ pork.  Nice!
Thanks, sis!
What's wrong with you?
How can you lock your brother like this?
He's not your brother.  You won't understand.
This kid is always wrecking havoc outside.
Sooner or later, the police will lock him away.
It's betterfor me to lock him up instead of
the police.
My sister's very nice to me.
I've got food, entertainment and music.
I even get candies every now and then.
Shut your trap, you little bastard!
Drink up the water!     -Yes, sis!
Weird kid!  As soon as you pay less attention
to him, he'll run amok.
It'll be impossible to break free when you keep
him behind bars.
That's where you're wrong.
Even ifyou've given him an iron spoon,
he can make his escape by digging a hole.
That's why we only use plastic spoons
around here.
Thank you.  Now go...
That little bastard made his clothes so damned
dirty.  I'll be washing myselfto death here!
You're pretty weird too.
Sometimes, you treat him nice.
Other times, you hit and scold him to death.
You don't have a little brother.
You won't understand.
Since early childhood, he's been nothing but
trouble.
He doesn't bother with his studies either.
He gets badly influenced by hanging around those
thugs everyday.
As for me, I can't go to school even if
I wanted to.
Why?
Oh, forget it!  Nobody told me to be someone's
elder sister.
Your little brother's actually not that bad.
He's just playful.  He'll be fine ifyou show
him patience.
Don't I need to work?
I work from early mornings to night.
I don't have the time to teach him!
I'm not like you.  You can make a lot of money by
striking your baton.
My life isn't as cozy as yours.
Give me a hand here!
It's not that dirty.
Baby, you always complained about how I never
have time for you.
I've finally come with a solution.
Now I can spend every minute with you.
I can talk to you at any second.
Mom, how about your mahjong sessions?
Occasional socializing is a must, isn't it?
Are you ready, Mrs. Ma?
I'm coming!
Didn't you say you were going to spend time
with me, Mom?
Ifyou're bored, just watch some TV.  Be good.
Mommy loves you!
Hurry up!
Well, you know.  I do all ofthis for my
daughter.
Rolled the dice yet?
It's been rolled already.  It's nine.
You're a canine?  Come...pick your tile.
It's your turn now.
Hi, baby!  Now you can see me and I can see you!
If anything, just call out my name!
As you should all know, my baby relies on me
a lot.
Can't see her any less.
Your daughter's beautiful and she's got a
camera face.
Of course, she does.  Like mother, like daughter.
Where are you going, miss?
What are you doing here?
Madam has ordered me to look after you.
Why are you following me?
This is my home.  Not a prison cell.
Milady.
Please don't run away, milady!
Otherwise, I can't keep an eye on you.
Mommy!
What's the matter, dear?  I'm right here.
Why did you call out for me, baby?
What's the matter?
- It's nothing.
Hey!  Where are you going, baby?
I'm going back to jail!
It's going to be 24 rounds after this game.
Do you still want to continue?
Why not?  We can play till the next morning!
That's great!
Madam...the lady's gone.
What?
I can't find her after searching through every
room.
What?
Wait for me here.
Okay.
Hey!  Where did you take my baby?
Who took your baby?
Your little brother!  He's giving a bad
influence to my baby!
Please get out!  You'd better tell me or else,
I will call the police.
You're standing in my way, fatty!
Who's standing in your way?
I've come to find my daughter!
I've gone to your brother's garage and
they said he didn't go to work today.
You're his sister.  You must know where he went.
Hey!  Are you listening to me?
Don't pretend to be deaf!
I believe you two siblings are like one and
the same!
You're both bad people.  I'm going to sue you.
Hey!
Where are you heading offto, bitch?
Hey!  I'm talking to you!
What's the meaning ofthis?
Why are you hanging me up there?
Hey!  Let me down!
Hey!
Help!  Let me down!
Help!
What's happening?
It's nothing.  Just a fat lady singing up there.
Put me down!
Singing?
- Yes!
Help!
Follow me.  It's upstairs.
Hey!  Why does your home have so many staircases?
Walk faster and close the door behind you.
I've kept my brother locked inside.
How could he possibly kidnap your daughter?
Jacky!
That little bastard!     -See?  Now do you
believe that your brother took my daughter away?
Jacky Kam Chi-Kit!
You little devil!  Put the phone offthe hook!
No wonder my calls couldn't get through.
Where's Jacky?
How would I know?
What are you looking at?
It's not suitable foryou.
Let me see this.
It's not for you!  It's pornography!
Let me see it!  Don't stand in my way!
It's not suitable foryou.
Where is it?
There!
Nothing here.
Yes!  It's right there!
It's here!
That's right!
Hey!  What are you staring at?
I'm staring at what you're staring at.
Dispicable!
If it's dispicable, then why are you looking
at it?
I'm a girl.  Can't I look at girls?
Such a bad figure!  I've had enough.
Back to you.
What is that?
Comic books.
Let me take a look!
You're an adult now!
Why do you still read such pornographic material?
Right!  It makes no sense to read comics when
you have a live person to look at.
What do you want?
I have many things that I want.
Sexual harrassment!
I'm just kidding.  No need to shout!
Don't!  Just stop it!
Otherwise, I'll seriously rape you.
Rape!
No...
- Let me go!
No...don't scream!
Help...
No!  Stop it!
Help!  Rape!
I was only joking with you.
Rape...
No!  I was only kidding!
Help!
No!
What's the matter?
Jacky!
What's going on?
Little Devil wants to rape me!
Where is he?
It's good that you're back, Jacky.
Good?  Like hell, it is!
I won't do it again!
Rape?  How dare you attempt to rape your
friend's girl!  You little bastard!
Rape?  Rape...
Get back in there and rape all you want,
you little bastard!
Philidonna, let's go.  Don't cry.
What are you doing?
Shut up.  I've come to settle the score with you.
Last time, you scolded my mother at the
police station.
That caused my mother to scold me at home.
You gave me a spoon this morning and
taught me how to make my escape with it.
You knowingly understood that I can't stand my
mother's scoldings
and it would cause me to run away from home.
You knew all along that once we leave our homes,
we'll have nowhere to go.
You knew all along that I can't survive without
my mom's support.
Last time, you said that you'll give her
a chance at the police station.
Now we're giving you the chance to give us
a chance.
You'll have to take care of us.
First, you'll need to give us 10 grand.
Sure!
Here's more than the amount.
Hit the road or else, I'll call the police!
Hit him!
I can't.
You hit me before I even started!
Cover me!
I can't!
Very nice, Philidonna!
Go to helL!
The Buddhist Palm?
Hey!  Trying to take advantage here?
Go to hell!
Don't kill me!
That was amazing!  What is this stance called,
great warrior?
The Jaded Maiden Sword Stance.
Get out!
Master, we are willing to be your slaves.
But all our eating and living expenses will be
on you.
You?
So late ofyou to come.  What's the matter?
Do you realize that your brother has run away?
I knew it.
But he won't be so lucky next time.
Hey!  What are you doing?
I'm going to lock up that runt as soon as I
fire up that metal cage.
He won't be able to make any escapes next time.
Are you serious?
You do know that it's illegal to do this,
don't you?
If I don't do this, he'll come out and commit
another criminal offense.
How did you know that my brother ran off?
He just came to see me.
Really?  Where is he now?
I have to get him back!
He's gone.
That runt!  Ifyou see him next time,
don't forget to notify me right away.
Alright...I've got to go now.
Okay.  Hey!  Don't forget to close the door on
your way out.
Hey!  Not this one.  The main door!
Hey!  Could you please grab the keys on the
coffee table and open that door?
That's the one.
See you tomorrow!
Hey!  What are you doing?
Hey...where are you going?
You must have locked people up pretty often.
Now it's time for you to get locked.
Hey!  Come back!
Don't assume you can get away by locking me in,
you lunatic!
Think I don't know how to burn the bars down?
Hey...you'd better let me out!
Hey...eat something first!
I won't!
Wow!  Why do you look so furious?
Take my position and see ifyou like it.
Now do you realize how it feels to be locked in?
Then why do you still keep your brother behind
bars?
It requires love and patience to raise a child
properly.  You can'tjust threaten them.
It's between my brother and I.  This is none of
your business.
Fine.  If it's none of my concern, I'll leave.
Hey...don't go!  Let me out!
I could do that but you've got to promise to
never lock your brother in again.
Fine!  Just let me out first!
Then it's a deal!
Hurry up!
Where's the key?
But you've got to promise me that you'll never
lock your brother up again.
Fine!
Hey...
It's your turn now.
Sorry.  I gave you the wrong key.
This is the right one.
Quit fooling around.
Mr. Koo, your students are having a feast inside.
And they're even performing Chinese opera.
It's entertaining!  Jaded Maiden Sword Stance!
I've been pierced by you.  Pierce...
Hey!  Why are you playing around with my sword?
It is the Jaded Maiden Sword Stance, after all!
This is a real sword.  You can get hurt.
Where's Jacky?
He's inside.
Hey!  Greet the master!  Master...
Master...
Why are you playing with my flute?
Is this a flute?
Higher!  That's how the master taught you!
This stance is called
"The Dual Dragons Out To Sea".
I'll teach you another stance called "Pushing
The Canoe Down The Stream".  Don't come over!
What are you doing?  Why did this happen?
How could you beat him up like that?
Not my fault.
What do you mean by saying it's not your fault?
Why do you two fight each other at first sight?
She's hitting me, master!
Hey!  What the hell is wrong with you?
Does it look nice?  I think it does.
I made this painting, master.
Does it look like you?
Can't you pipe down, you little runt?
Get out!
I am Lyre Demon.  Don't sustain any injuries
through the sound of my lyre!
Stop playing it!  Play with my koto!
That's an antique!
No wonder it looks so old!
My music scores are useful.
Get out!
Get out!  Go!
Hands off me!  I don't really know you that well.
Tell me!  Just tell me if I'm right about that.
Give them a little love and patience?
Isn't that the same?
This little bastard can't be treated nicely.
What little bastard? Are you referring to me?
Shut up!
Go home with me!
Master...
We only thought it'd be fun.  We were wrong.
Give us another chance!
Please give us another chance!
Master!
Master...give us another chance...
Don't do it again next time.
Next time?  And you've let them stay?
It's none ofyour business!
Shut up!
Kids get a little playful.  They'll be fine
after they lash it out.
I'll find something foryou to lash out on
tomorrow.
Why don't you thank the master?
Thank you, master.
Have no fear, o' dying branch!
For I am a thousand year old tree.
I fear no rain or storms.
CrawI up to me!  Quick!
Crow...Crow, it's your number.
What are you?  You're a crow!
Now you look like a chicken!
Crows can fly.  It should fly a little higher.
Wow!  That's it!  Now, that's what I call a crow!
Would letting it out like that change a child?
Art is used for releasing their expressions.
Using broken tires and exhausted pipes as art?
I've got plenty at my garage.
This is too boring for me to watch!
I've got to work on a night shift.
I'm going to leave now.
Let me escort you out.
Okay!
That reminds me.  You asked me to attend
your rehearsal tomorrow night.
Is it artsy?
It is artsy but it won't bore you.
We'll wait and see.
Isn't that amazing?
Yes, very fantastic.
You really don't like music, do you?
Not really but I just don't know how to
appreciate yours.
Listen to it more and you'll learn how to
appreciate them.
So what kind of music do you like?
Did you know about the charity ball coming
tomorrow night?
Who are you asking to be your dancing partner?
Baron Chan's daughter is on the list.
Chairman Ho's sister-in-law, Councillor Wong's...
Enough...
Say no more.  I already have a partner.
So, who's your latest pick-up?
Can't you stop reminding me about the past?
This is for you.
I just bought some new clothes.
It's in preparation for tomorrow's ballroom
party.
Ifyou don't think it goes well with you,
I can get another one.
I'll go and get changed right away.
So she's going to be your dance partner?
I'll leave her to you.
Me?
Oh, I see!
So that's why you reek of petroleum these days!
So are you trying to court that garage chick?
Be a little more respectful!
You look so serious.
You said it yourself.
This is a fiddle head, not a fiddle stick.
Really?  It's not too shabby.
You're gorgeous!
You're pretty punctual.
I've always been punctual.
It's hard to get a cab around here.
Ifyou don't mind, I can drive.
No thanks.  I've got a car.
You've got a car?
Please park it properly.
What took you so long?
Sorry.  Allow me to introduce two people to you.
They're our sponsors.
Don't drink so much, Jim.
It's just a little bit!
Just give me a little bit!
Just a little more!
Mr. Chan was really a great help this time
around.
Thank you.
You've got a phone call, Mr. Chan.
Okay.
Hey!  Do I look beautiful?
You look like a turkey.
Turkey.
- How is it?
So you're trying the turker after the
Afro-chicken?
What chicken?
Still a chick, after all.
Chick?
Let me introduce you to Mr. Siu.
Why does your perfume smell like petroleum?
You're that girl from the motor shop!
You've fixed my car before.
Really?
- Y...yes...
I never realized that you have such a nice figure
underyour usual work clothes.
Please mind your words.
Ifyou got the goods, don't be shy to show it.
She's really not bad at all.
What happened?
Would you like to have more, sir?
Why did you hit me?
Would you believe that I'd beat you up?
Jim, you're drunk!
I've only drank a little bit.
Yes, the fact that you drank bit by bit only
makes it worse.
Mr. Koo!
Mind your own business!
How lovely.
It's perfect for Philidonna and I.
You'll be mine in a minute.
Was I actually that rude?
Not really.  I think you're pretty charismatic.
I've actually scared many of my boyfriends away
in the past.
But you're no match for me.
I'm a pretty good fighter.
What's the use in being a good fighter?
Moustachio hates it when people tickle him.
No, not this moustachio!
Really?
Yes!
Stretch out your hands.  Stand still!
Don't move!  What are you doing?
I'm tickling you.
Don't!
Just admit it!
How about you?
I'm not afraid.
Aren't you?
I'm not!
Then, you'll have to let me give it a try!
Sure!
Don't move.
- Sure!
Here I come!
Stretch out your hands.
Are you really not afraid of it?
Come closer.
Ears?
Nose?
No.
- What is it?
My lips can't stand the itchiness.
Your moustache is making me itch.
One more time.
Don't laugh.
- Be gentle.
Why do you look elsewhere whenever
you kiss my sister?
You're not concentrating, master.
Sorry...did I bother you?
Take your time with the kissing.  I'm leaving.
It's getting late.  I've got to go.
See you later.
Let's kiss a little more.
Feel free to come back for more visitational
kisses, master.
You little runt!
Why did you come back for?
I want to move back in.
Ifyou're moving back, then just move back in.
You don't need to peek at us.
Since you're being so straight-forward,
don't say that I'm not taking care ofyou.
You should go and kiss him while you still can.
My master's leaving soon.
He'll be leaving you.
Come down, baby!  Come on!
What is it, mom?
I've promised to scrap out every TV set.
I won't have anyone to keep an eye on you again.
Why?
You'll find out soon enough.  Look who's here!
Hi!
- Cousin?
Why brings you here?
I've come to take you to England.
I've asked your cousin to take you over to
England for your studies.
Why?
Don't you know that I can't watch overyou?
Your cousin is a police officer in England.
If she can keep the criminals under control,
then I'm sure that she can keep an eye on you.
Don't worry.  I'll take good care of her.
If I'm busy, I'll ask my brother to do it for me.
After all, my brother is the deputy chiefof
a prison ward.
Mom, I don't want to go!
How dare you come back, you little bastard!
You!  You're not a man!
Bearing dirty thoughts on my girlfriend!
I'm telling you right now that I'm moving back
with my sister.
Don't say I'm not being generous enough.
I'm leaving this place over to you.
Are you looking for another fight?
Who are you looking for?
Are you Jacky Kam Chi-Kit?
I am...this is bad...
Don't hit me!  I'm very weak!
I'll die ifyou beat me up!
I'm coughing.  See?  I'm coughing badly here.
Okay!
I'm fine, man.
I'm fine!  Beat me up!
Hit him!
Hit him...
- Damn!
Even though I'm completely wounded,
I was able to save my chastity.
Kneel down!
I'll give you 7 days to pay me a total of $99,900
for medical fees.
We'll remain brothers that way.  Otherwise...
prepare to become a "sister".
Okay.
Oww!
What's "oww"?
It hurts.  Therefore, it should be "ouch".
You're supposed to look like you're in pain but
you can't convey it.
What happened?
Bravo!  Bravo!
Look at Jacky!
His expressions of pain look really convincing.
Look at how his body and soul wince in extreme
pain.
Fellow students, to become a good actor,
you must forget all self-indulgence in order to
portray someone under extreme pain.
Unless I tell him to stop, he will continue to
feel pain.
Your make-up looks great.  Who taught you this?
It looks so real!  Alright, get up!
It's over now.
Help...help me up!    -Alright, fellow students!
Let's continue our rehearsal!
Come and give me a hand!
See how convincingly painful he looks!
I'm afraid you just don't have the talent.
Watch Jacky's performance!
Jacky...where's Jacky?
I'm right here!
I'm really injured.
Help him up first.  Let's take a look...
Are you alright?
No wonder your acting looked so real.
Did you go out for another brawI again, Jacky?
BrawI?
Why didn't you take us along with you?
Bullshit!
- Just hang on!
At the current situation, I'll have to tell
the truth.
I've just done something which I believe that
everyone should learn about.
When I was on my way here,
I saw a one-year-old child.
He suddenly ran to the road and the situation
was very critical.
Guess what I did?
I couldn't care less and I simply jumped over.
Why aren't you helping me up?
Give me a hand here!
I can't tell whether or not you are telling
the truth.
What happened afterwards?
I wasn't holding the child.
Then...then, a truck was over there.
No, it was a container truck coming towards me.
So I rolled aside.
Amazing...
So I rolled over to the other side.
Of course, the child was unharmed.
But I turned out looking like this.
Get the rubbing alcohol.  Help him up!
Be gentle...
- Be careful!
How are you doing?
Here you go!
Come on...
Don't rub too much.
Hey...don't scratch...
Hey!  Come and help out!
Let me do it.  This is how you do it.
You don't do it there.
What do you know?
Hey!  My injury...
Stop shouting! It'll obviously hurt while rubbing
injuries. There's some bruise over there.
How will you heal without rubbing it?
Don't stop me.  Rub it down there.
Over there...
Hey!  I'm fine now.  Help!  Mommy!
Tell us the truth.
What made you like this?
Well, I heroically saved a child's life!
Heroically?
Each ofyou get some rubbing alcohol for him!
Fine...
Even if I said the truth, would everyone help me?
Of course, we will!  We've just helped you even
when you're in this kind of mess.
Sure!  We'll definitely help you!
Yeah!  We will!
Fine!  I'll tell you guys the truth.
I've gotten into a mess with the triads.
But I resisted for the sake ofjustice.
And as a result, they did this to me.
They've even given me a week's time to
gather $99,999 dollars and
have it handed over to them.
Otherwise, they'll kick my ass again.
I'm sure that everyone who's living for the sake
ofjustice
will gather the money in order to help me.
I...
I know you'll all vanish right away.
After you finish covering the hole,
just change the metal door into a wooden one
for me.
Jacky, you're back!
Hey, what happened to you?
How did this happen to you?
I rolled under a container truck after it
ran over me
as I was saving the life of a small child.
Liar!  Trying to deceive me again!
Better tell me the truth!
Phone call!
Just stay here and stand still!
Hello.
What happened to you, Jacky?
Why do you look like this?
What are you doing?
So much luggage.
Okay...I'll be back right away.
Mom's forcing me to go to England with my cousin.
I don't want to go.
That's why I came to see you.
I'll live here.  I won't leave.
What are you two up to?
I'm in a hurry to get to work.
I'll settle the score with you later.
Sis, I need some money...
You runt, money is the only thing you ask for.
No way!
No!  It's urgent!
Urgent?  You never have anything good for me,
you runt!
Here's $200.  $100 for each.
That's it.  Now behave!
No, sis!
Hey!  Do you know I'm in a lot of trouble
this time?
I can't pull myselftogether.
Don't you want me anymore?
Then I'll...
Fine, I'll leave!
Hey...come and visit when you've got the time!
Why don't you make me stay?
Then stay for a while and leave later.
Are you really not going to make me stay?
It's obvious to me that you won't leave.
Why should I make you stay?
You're so incorrigible!
You still hit me while I'm injured.
Don't you love me anymore?
Don't you love me?
I know you still do.
Auntie.
- You little runt!
Where did you kidnap my baby?
Don't scold people at random!
Not only am I scolding you, I'm also going to
hurt you.
Tell me where did my baby go?  Tell me now!
That's enough, you two!
I have to let you beat me after getting hurt by
your daughter.
So what?  You'd better tell me where my baby
has gone.
I was going to give you a call just to
tell you about your daughter's whereabouts.
But I don't want to tell you now.
Forget it...sorry...consider this my apology
to you.
Can you please tell me about my baby's
whereabouts?
Your daughter's packed everything and said
she wanted to run away with me.
But I didn't agree with her.
But ifyou continue to treat her like a prisoner,
sooner or later, she'd run away with another and
it'll be too late foryou to regret it.
I understand...I won't treat her like that
anymore.
Can you please tell me where my baby has gone?
I'm not running away with her.
Where else can she go?  Look over there!
Baby...
Chuen, come over here and grab the lady's
luggage.
Baby, just tell me ifyou're unhappy about
anything.
You don't have to run away.
Mommy won't treat you like a prisoner anymore.
Mom, I won't go to England with my cousin.
That's right.  Consider it granted.
Come...let's go home together.  Get in the car.
Come!  What is it now?
You still can't let go of that rascal?
He's not a rascal, Mom.
He persuaded me to go home.
Mom, Jacky's in trouble.
He owes a debt of $100,000.
Don't run, Jacky!  Where are you going?
I told you not to ask your motherfor a loan.
Why are you in need of so much money?
He's been blackmailed.
Say no more.
Forget it.
I'm the one who've met the wrong people.
Jacky, don't go!
I'll follow you wherever you go.
I can lend him money.
But he won't be able to repay you in a short
period of time.
He just got fired at the garage.
So, are you asking me for the money or
do you want me to lend it to you?
It's just the same.
Mr. Koo's flight has been confirmed.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Here's your ticket.
What?  Don't you want to leave?  Just stay here!
Hong Kong's not too shabby.
Let's go!
Master.
Why are you guys here?
My mother established this bakery shop.
Jacky, I thought you worked at the garage.
Did you switch your occupation?
No!  Her mother has forcibly given me the
new name of"Gimcrack".
She told me to switch to bakery.
Try it.
Alright.
It seems to taste like petroleum.
Yeah.
Bravo, master...
I can give you a ride.
No thanks, auntie.  I can take the bus.
Goodbye.
- Bye!
Get in the car, baby.  Come on!
I want to take the bus with Jacky, Mom.
Alright but you've got to come back earlier.
Bye, mom!
Goodbye!
- Bye!
Wait for me, Jacky!  I'll take the bus with you.
Why take the bus when you've got a Rolls Royce?
Tell me which is more expensive.
A bus or the Rolls Royce?
The bus is expensive.  No need to ask.
Why don't we find some friends and study the
Buddha's Palm and Jaded Maiden Sword Stance?
But Mom told me to come home earlier.
I'll send you home after studying it for a while.
Alright.  But don't run so fast.
Hurry up!  We're running out of time!
Go home!
Excuse us...your questions will be answered
shortly.
Please excuse us, everyone.
Your questions will be answered shortly.
Watch out!
Please excuse us.
Your questions will be answered shortly.
There will be a press conference soon.
Please make way.
Thanks.
Thanks...fellow members of the press...
We've got a farewell party on the 3rd floor
ofthis hotel.
Please don't interfere while Mr. Koo is getting
a change of new clothes.
Many guests have already arrived.
Please hold your questions for later.
Thanks...
Please excuse us...thanks...
Excuse me.  I'm looking for Mr. Koo.
Sorry, miss. Mr. Koo doesn't want to see anyone
at the present moment.
Thanks.
Yes, Carrie's here.
Mr. Koo!
Have you seen a long-haired girl that was
looking for me?
Yes, but she has already left.
What do you want?
Carrie.
Your concert was a success.
Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Where has Mr. Koo gone to?
He has personal affairs to deal with.  He'll be
here once they're dealt with.     -Alright.
Please help yourselves!
Okay...
Cheers, everyone!
What are you looking at?  He's leaving tomorrow.
Here we are!
I'll ring the bell.
You're blind.  How can you ring the bell?
Open up, Chopsticks!
Chopsticks!
It's us.
Hurry up, Chopsticks!
The champagne tastes great!  Hey!
Open up, Chopsticks!
We've bought champagne to bid yourfarewell.
We'll wait foryou!
Dear brothers, sisters and classmates.
We'd better not disturb him right now.
He's handling on something very important
right now.
What could so important?
Yeah!
Love!
Chopsticks...
- Open up!
Please do him a favor.
We are trying to help him!
Yeah!
How can you help him in this kind of situation?
Do not disturb.  That's enough.  Let's go!
Go?
We haven't even seen him in the last 10 years.
Exactly!  Is that all there is to it?
It'll be fast.  He'll be back very soon.
I'm blind.  I can't see anything.
I could help...
Go!  Good riddance!
I'll come back to Hong Kong for another concert
next March.
That's good.
I've got a year to train myself not to fall
asleep during concerts.
Mr. Koo, your luggage is now in the car.
It's time to go to the airport.
Thanks.
You may go first.
Let me give you a ride back.
It's okay.
You'll still have to go after sending me away.
I'd like to stay a little longer.
Quit dilly-dallying!  You'll still have to go.
The plane won't wait.
Take your sword back.
"Swipe the sword ofwisdom to cut the romance."
You don't want to be like Chewing Gum and
remain stuck, do you?
Who are you looking for?
Is this Ms. Kam?
Yes, I am.
Mr. Koo has sent me to deliver your package.
Please sign here.
Sis...
- What?
This time, I've got something good for you.
Something good?  What could it be?
Come!
What is it?
I'm your brother.
I won't play practical jokes on you.
Come on!
I've really got something good foryou.
Come here!
Go on!
Propose.  What are you waiting for?  Come on!
Someone wants you despite your temper.
Just put it on!
What?
Do I really have to marry him?
Don't you want it?  I do!
No way!
I knew you'd be like this.
Bravo!