and you get brunch!
Everybody Gets brunch!
And This is where I do six hours of work behind the scenes
to make what James says magically happen.
Fernando? Hey, girl.
Brunch! I need a favor.
So... drag Queen Billie club is telling me
about her new Sunday night dance party
"Twerk Baton hot dog" At tushes,
and Officer Billy wants to go, but he's po-Po!
You can't have po-Po at "Twerk Baton Hot dog"!
the most fun meal of all the meals,
and you are completely ignoring
your friends who came to visit you
all the way from who cares.
You're right. I guess can I take a break.
So, um, Crissy, Robert,
what are you guys doing while you're in New York?
"Good morning America"!
ah. I've done "g.M.A." What are you promoting?
I'm kidding! I know you're just people! Oh!
Yeah, we're gonna hold up signs outside the window
and get on tv.
Uh-Oh. Better make mine a virgin mimosa.
Oh! Spoiler alert!
I am pregnant!
That's wonderful! James is not the father!
I know. Robert's the father.
That's fantastic.
We conceived on the third night of our honeymoon. Yeah.
The first two nights, my mom was still sharing our hotel room.
Oh, my God.
Excuse me. Um, I haven't drank in a while.
I'm gonna go use the restroom.
Ohh.
I feel a little light-headed.
But it's okay. I'll just segue to tea
and get those files over to harkin.
You landed Yoshida.
But--But the Yoshida meeting isn't until Monday.
Yeah, and today's tuesday.
I--wh-What happened to brunch?
Get this crazy bitch some brunch!
June, congrats on Yoshida!
And I told my husband what you said on Monday, and he agreed.
Canceled the adoption.
Good! A lot happened on Monday, and today's--Today's tuesday.
June, your advice yesterday worked.
The swelling's completely gone!
I got it. Thanks so much, June.
Si, se puede, right?
Mm-hmm! Mm-hmm.
Pick up. Pick up. Pick up. Pick up. Pick up.
Hi.
What happened to me?
Oh. You were blacked out for two days.
Why?! the last thing I remember
was being in the bathroom at brunch.
Yeah, so immediately before that,
I "Black lightninged" you.
What? I put an herb
that I got off the internet called black lightning
into your mimosa.
You've been so Boring and self-obsessed lately.
I wanted to shake you up like a snow globe.
What did I do while I was blacked out?
A lot of things.
Whee!
Can you believe I did that to you?
Pretty crazy of me, right?
So I'm there, about to walk Yoshida through
our conservative investment proposal,
when you roll in, talking high-risk, high-reward...
and you dazzled them.
They wanted safe. You called an audible.
And, lady, that's the kind of thing that gets you promoted
from junior analyst to senior junior analyst!
Huh?! Ha ha!
Thank you! Ohh.
Just got off the phone with the adoption agency.
Baby's canceled!
Good luck growing up in the Ukraine, baby.
You'll be cold, and I'll be drunk!
Whoo!
♪ highway to the danger zone ♪
So loud!
I'm just taking a mind ride, thinking about Crissy's baby.
I mean, how could she be so sure that it's not mine?
Wait. I'm confused.
Do you want the baby to be yours?
I just think it's weird
that with all the wild celebrity sex I've had,
I've never had a pregnancy scare.
You haven't?  Oh, honey.
Even I've had a pregnancy scare.
Yo, I just want you to know
that I'm-a be here for you through this whole--
It's negative!
Oh! That was close, girl!
Crissy can't say anything in front of her husband,
but she says that they conceived on their honeymoon.
We slept together on their wedding day.
That's pretty close.
Now that I think about it,
if I had to pit your sperm against his sperm...
I'll get a D.N.A. Test after the baby's born.
If it's mine, I'll just Sue for sole custody.
Don't touch that. But in the meantime,