Why do people say that New York is such a tough town?
I've lived here a while now,
and I feel like I've got it licked.
I mastered the subway,
how to jaywalk without being hit,
and I've learned a cute new word for Jewish people.
Hello, Hebraham!
The thing that really makes the city feel like home
is having a friend,
someone to talk to and hang out with.
And for me, that's my roommate Chloe.
One day soon, we'll even be in a picture together.
Hmm.
Hey, Eli.
Do you stand there every morning,
waiting for me to open the blinds?
Don't flatter yourself, June. And yes, I do.
Look at that!
One time I mention to Chloe that blueberry is
my favorite kind of yogurt, and what does she do?
She goes and stocks the entire fridge with them.
Well, it's important to have friends in New York.
This city can be hard...
like a lot of things.
I feel bad.
I've been so busy working at the coffee shop
and trying to get another wall street job
that I haven't been able to have a girls' day out with Chloe...
until now !
That sounds fun. You know what's not fun?
Complacency in the face of corporate greed.
Today is my first day off,
so I think I'm gonna ask her to hang out.
Maybe we'll go have a picnic in Central Park or...
Stop talking!
Oh, hey! Somebody's up.
Would you like to hang out today?
I feel like a pig crapped inside my head.
I feel like a pig ate Indian food and squatted down...
Oh. There's a man underneath you.
Hello.
Don't wake him.
I took all of his life force last night.
All right, come on. I wanna see your New York City.
Show me what you love about this place.
Well...
guess there is one thing we could do,
but it might be a little touristy.
And to your left,
you'll see the site of the famous noodle fire of 1927,
They say on a windy night,
you can still smell the lo mein and burning hair.
God, I love New York!
- Synced by yescool - corrected by chamallow -  - www.addic7ed.com -
And that's all they found...
the young nurse's sawed-off pelvis in a FedEx envelope
in that mailbox right there.
When you absolutely, positively have to be dead overnight," huh?
Mitchell, you are too much!
New York!
Here, we laugh at death!
Don't laugh too hard, little girl.
Another young woman
was found murdered in the park this morning.
That makes six this summer. You wanna call her parents
and tell them how funny you think that is?
We... we were just... we all were just laughing...
Okay, who's up for snacks and a pee?
Okay.
I've got cliff bars and tuna fish sandwiches.
Warning... the ice has made the bread moist.
I actually brought my snack from home.
Blueberry yogurt.
My favorite.
Great. It's time for my snack, too.
I should probably do it in the bathroom, though.
There's a lot of cops around.
Welcome, murder fans!
You must be here for our killer zucchini muffins.
It's a joke.
So this is what you're doing on your day off? A crime tour?
It's what Chloe wanted to do.
How great. So the roommate who slept with your fianc?
Perfect!
There's a problem in the bathroom.
Someone tried to flush some kind of plastic baggie
down your toilet.
Ohh!
So today was, uh... it was interesting.
Right?!
Before I took that tour, I didn't know any of that stuff.
I didn't know it!
Well, you know another fun thing for girlfriends to do together
is to have a home-cooked meal.
Wednesday night, I'll make my famous chicken Williams.
Yeah Wednesday works. It's a plan.
Okay.
Toilets are for pees and turds, you guys.
Why do I have to say this every day?
Mark-Paul Gosselaar is building a school in El Salvador.
What an ass crack.
Hmm! Escuela de Gosselaar.
He looks good, all wearing a tank top.
Yeah, swing that hammer,
build that school,
carry that niño. I'm telling you,
the best way to get publicity is to do something selfless.
Uh-huh. How do you say "safe word" in Spanish?
Palabra segura.
So I called my agent,