There are two kinds of folks
who sit around thinking
about how to kill people:
Psychopaths
and mystery writers.
I'm the kind that pays better.
Who am I?
I'm Rick Castle.
Castle.
I really am ruggedly handsome,
aren't I?
Every writer needs inspiration.
And I found mine.
Detective Kate Beckett.
- Beckett.
- Nikki Heat?
- The character he's basing on you.
And thanks to my friendship
with the mayor,
I get to be on her case.
I would be happy
to let you spank me.
And together, we catch killers
we make a pretty
good team, you know?
Like Starsky and Hutch.
Turner and Hooch.
You do remind me
a little of Hooch.
and did you hear?
Our favorite golfer
is in the news again.
Missed a charity tournament
over the weekend.
Really unfortunate
The world's top golfer
had to pull out.
In fact, it's the first time
he's pulled out of anything
In five years.
Ouch. Ouch. What do you think,
Hank? Should I take a mulligan?
No, play through, Bobby. Play through.
I will, my friend.
We have a great show
for you tonight.
Mr. Castle.
Ellie Monroe is here. She has
a new movie opening tomorrow.
Hi, I'm Kayla.
Please follow me.
Sure.
And my favorite writer
Richard Castle's joining us.
Here you go, Mr. Castle.
Deb, the makeup artist,
will take care of you from here.
Thank you, Kayla.
And you're up
right after Ms. Monroe.
Hi, it's Ellie.
Rick.
Can I just say...
wow.
Like, I can't believe
I'm meeting you right now.
Really?
Well, you're, like,
my favorite author ever.
I mean, I've read "Heat Wave "
at least three times.
Can I tell you, I have seen
every movie you've ever been in?
Really?
Oh. Not "Viper Mountain"
I hope.
Yes, "Viper Mountain."
ugh.
You were
the best thing in that movie.
As soon as that snake ate you,
whole movie fell apart.
Folks, please help me
in welcoming Richard Castle.
Rick Castle.
Oh-ho-ho-ho.
Whoo!
Oh, he looks good.
Welcome.
Thank you.
First of all, congratulations
on "Heat Wave "--
"New York Times"
best seller.
Thank you.
And you know what?
I really loved writing it.
Well, the paperback comes out,
uh, July 27th, right?
July 27th. That's right.
And it's being made into a movie.
Nice.
Now you worked with actual
NYPD Homicide Detectives
to research "Heat Wave ."
Yes, yes, I did.
And--and they still
won't let me carry a gun.
I didn't know you worked
with law enforcement.
It's kinda my weak spot.
Hello.
Waiter, check please.
Well, you guys
are single, right?
Well, actually,
not anymore, Bobby.
Thank you very much.
Oh.
Wow. The camera really does
add 10 pounds...
to his ego.
Call me old-fashioned--
When a beautiful movie star
is impressed with
my fake law enforcement
credentials, I'm in.
Do you think he's
asked her out yet?
Your father,
pretty girl like that?
He may have proposed
by now.
And that's our show for tonight.
Stay tuned for
"Late Talk with Mickey Reed."
I'm Bobby Mann.
Remember, folks...
The boys'll
be back on duty tomorrow night.
I always wonder
what they're saying
when they lean in like that.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
They want me dead.
I'm sorry. What?
I'm serious.
You work with cops, right?
They want--
That was
a great show, guys.
I'm so sorry
about segment three.
Next time we put the emu in a diaper.
Mm-hmm.
I'll call you.
Oh, the box-in-box with Justin...
Yeah.
Looked great.
I loved it.
Good, good.
Listen, I think we should...
Um... you're going
orienteering not librarying.
You sure you want to take
that many books?
Overambitious
for a 5-day trip?
You're gonna be responsible
for your own pack.
I think you're supposed
to be more Sacagawea
than a scholarly reader.
Besides,
look at all those pages.
The trees might want revenge.
Richard.
What's wrong?
Bobby Mann is dead.
What? What happened?
They're saying he had
a heart attack.
I'm telling you, the guy said
that somebody wanted him dead,
and then he ends up dead.
That can't be a coincidence.
Bobby Mann had a history
of heart disease,
and on the autopsy reports,
it states that the cause
of death was a heart attack.
That can't be
a coincidence either.
Did Lanie do the autopsy?
No, but she sent it
to me.
Okay, a guy
was walking his dog,
saw Mr. Mann collapse
on the sidewalk alone.
But there'no puncture wounds,
no bruising,
and the tox panel
came back negative.
There's no foul play,
Castle.
I talked to his producer
this morning.
She said that Mann
left the studio at 12:45
in his Bugatti Veyron.
That's a $2-million car.
He collapsed on foot
a few blocks from his house
at 4:50
so?
So where's the car?
He's, like,
a gazillionaire, Castle.
He probably just parked it
and expected someone else
to pick it up
the next morning.
In my book "Gathering Storm,"
the former KGB official
killed with
an undetectable poison
that stopped the heart.
What if that's
what happened to Mann?
Need I remind you that you
make up stuff for a living,
and there is no such poison
in real life,
and if there was,
there would be a whole slew
of angry spouses who'd be
getting away with murder?
Could you just have Lanie
take a closer look?
Please.
You know how many strings
I had to pull for this Castle?
If I'm wrong,
I'll reimburse the city.
To hell with the city
it's me you're gonna owe.
I take spa certificates,
jewelry and cash.
Duly noted. What's that?
The contents of Bobby Mann's
pockets when he was bought in.
I'm gonna go check
on the Labs.
Okay.
What are you doing?
It's called investigating.
You should try it.
I usually wait
until there's a crime.
Cell phone, ney clip.
He stuck a piece of gum
to a paper
before he put it
in his pocket.
One of his last acts
was not littering.
Yes, but there's a word
on this paper--"tory."
Could be a mystery woman.
Wow, Castle.
Cracking this case wide open.
Hey, it's his idea notepad.
This is a joke from last night.
"charity golf.
First time he's pulled out in years."
do you realize
that you are now
investigating a heart attack?
Hmm.
What?
His signature line
of 20 years,
"the boys'll be back
on duty tomorrow night,"
Looks like he was thinking
of changing it.
"the crew will be back
on duty tomorrow night."
Maybe he was trying
to make it hipper.
Mm.
We should have
a signature line.
She's armed, he's dangerous.
No.
How about
a whole new chapter
in crime solving?
Ooh.
Chapter. Get it?
No.
Okay, I ran
every extra tox screen
outside of standard protocol.
All negative, no trace of any
known poisonous substance.
Okay, Castle?
Don't forget to tip your M.E.
on the way out.
Ah, not so fast.
Secondary tox panel
detected traces of Tyramine,
which is harmless,
but it's presence raised
a red flag for me.
So I ran some more tests.
Bobby Mann was taking Phenelzine.
Phenelzine?
A prescription drug for depression.
So?
So Phenelzine
is in a class of drugs
called M.A.O. Inhibitors
That have powerful
contra-indicators.
You mean drug interactions?
In this case,
interactions that can kill.
M.A.O. Inhibitors
contra-indicate
with anything fermented--
wine, beer,
certain kind of cheeses.
Even the smallest amount can
trigger a hypertensive crisis.
Oh! Almost like an undetectable
poison that stops the heart.
Which doesn't mean
that he was murdered.
He could've accidentally eaten or drank
something he shouldn't have.
That's what I thought. So I ran
the contents of his intestines.
In the hours
prior to his death,
he ingested three substances--
Something sugary,
like hard candy...
or chewing gum.
There you go.
Also cranberry juice
and balsamic vinegar.
Which is fermented.
And there was no trace
of anything
that you would find
balsamic on--
No chicken, no fish
no pasta.
Just the cranberry juice.
Which could've easily
masked the color
and the taste
of the balsamic vinegar.
So you're saying
that somebody knew about
Bobby Mann's condition,
slipped balsamic vinegar
into his cranberry juice,
knowing that
it would kill him?
This was no accident
Bobby Mann was murdered.
Well, Bobby, you were right.
♪ Castle 2x20 ♪
The Late Shaft
Original Air Date on April 12, 2010
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
No crime scene,
no clear place
to begin the investigation.
Don't you
just love poisoning?
Especially a poisoning
without poison.
Whoever did this
was very smart.
They chose a murder weapon
that's probably
in half the kitchens
in the city.
Good thing we're smart, too.
Thanks.
That was Lanie.
Based on possible rates of
fatal M.A.O. interactions,
she was able to narrow
the window of poisoning to
between 1:30 and 4:30
in the morning.
That makes
this...
our kill zone--
1:30 to 4:30.
What else?
Well, the lab said that there
was no traces of cranberry juice
or balsamic vinegar in the gum
we found in Mann's pocket.
So he must have chewed that
before he was poisoned.
Well, we know he left
the studio at 12:45.
Which means
he wasn't poisoned there.
And we know that his
home security records
show that he never
made it there.
12:45 to 4:50 in the morning,
leaves in his car,
is found on foot.
So what was he doing
that whole time?
So the vehicle locator
in Mann's Bugatti
is not sending a signal.
Probably in
an underground parking garage.
Which means
it could be anywhere.
Check his cell phone, see if
he made any calls last night,
And then go to his Brownstone.
Castle and I will head
to the studio and see
what we can dig up there.
Oh, guys.
Yeah.
No talk of murder.
The longer we can keep this
away from the press,
the better off we'll be.
I'm sorry.
I don't know where he went
after the show last night.
What is this about anyway?
I thought Bobby...
Died of
a heart attack, right?
We're just tying up loose ends
for the coroner.
How was Mr. Mann
acting recently?
Did you notice
anything unusual?
No. He was great.
Uh... except yesterday.
What happened yesterday?
I don't know.
I mean, he spent the morning
locked up in his office alone.
And then the rest of the day,
he was agitated
and he was acting weird.
Weird how?
Paranoid.
At one point he asked me
if I had heard anything,
and I said, "about what?"
and he just shrugged it off.
Were you aware that he was on
powerful antidepressants?
I mean, he tried to be
very private about it,
but when he went on them,
he had to quit drinking,
and people wondered why.
So word got around.
You don't think that's
what killed him, do you?
Something he ate or--
or drank?
He was very careful.
Like I said,
we're just following up.
I keep looking over
at that curtain, you know,
waiting for him
to walk through...
like this was all
one big publicity stunt.
The two of you
were close, right?
Since before all this.
Since we were just
kids together back in 'Nam.
So he would've told you
if there was anything wrong?
Like what?
Like if he was concerned
for his well-being.
What's this all about?
I-I thought he died
of a heart attack.
Just routine questioning,
Mr. McPhee.
You know, some of the people
said that he seemed
a little agitated recently.
Come to think of it,
he was a little preoccupied.
I asked him about it
after the show last night,
but he insisted he was fine.
Hank.
Man, I am so sorry.
Aw.
Nightmares really happen.
Huh?
Yeah. You know Mickey--
Host of "Late Talk,"
right after our show?
Yes, of course.
I'm a big fan.
I love your whole
"booty roulette" gag.
That's great. I'm Rick.
Castle.
Ah. Saw you
on the show last night.
I'm Detective Kate Beckett.
Nice to meet you.
So do either of you know
where Bobby went
after the show last night?
We're trying to track his last
hours for the coroner's report.
No clue.
I think he said something about
going to see his ex-wife.
Did he say which one?
Mnh-mnh.
How many ex-wives
did he have?
6, ranging in ages
from 25 to 50.
It seems every five years, he
traded in for the latest model.
So he didn't so much
marry them as lease them.
So I ran all their names
through the system,
and guess what popped up.
Seems wife number five here
was arrested
over an altercation with Bobby
at a restaurant Uptown.
She's got crazy eyes.
Well, there's more. According
to the doorman in her building,
Bobby Mann was there
last night after the show.
Mrs. Mann, when was the last
time you saw your ex-husband?
About a year ago...
in court.
He took out a restraining order
against me.
Well, according to
the complaint,
you did threaten to kill him.
Well, I don't really remember
what was said.
"I wish you were dead,
you little weasel."
He was dating a younger woman,
and she looked just like me.
Tell that
to his previous wife.
Were you aware of
his dietary restrictions?
Sure.
Nothing fermented or it could
give him a heart attack.
Why? You think I had
something to do with it?
You tell me, Mrs. Mann.
Acording to your doorman,
Bobby showed up
at your building last night.
He did?
Cindy,
we know you saw him.
How do you know he wasn't
there to see Barbara?
Barbara?
His first wife.
She's got an apartment
in the building, too.
We both got 'em
in the divorce settlement.
Bobby co-owned the building.
Yeah,
I saw Bobby last night.
He came by
around 1:00 in the morning,
woke me up as usual.
Did he often surprise you
in the middle of the night?
I was the one woman
who fell in love with him
before all the fame
and the money.
Whenever he felt insecure,
he came around.
Mostly it was
the same old stuff--
his ratings were down
or... he was getting old.
But last night...
What?
It was different.
He looked... haunted.
He said
something was going on,
something awful.
What was going on?
He wouldn't tell me.
He asked me if I thought
he was a good person.
And I held his hand
and I said, "Bobby,
"you're a lousy husband,
but you're a hell of a man."
Then he left.
At what time?
Around quarter after 1:00.
Did he say
where he was going?
No.
I thought he was going home.
Something awful
was going on.
He knew
someone was after him.
But he doesn't tell his ex-wife
or his best friend.
Instead he tells me.
Maybe it's because he knew
you were working with the cops.
Tell me I'm a good person?
Like he was doing something
he was ashamed of.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Neighbors confirm
Barbara Mann's story.
One of them saw Bobby leave
her apartment at 1:15 A.M.
That's outside of
our kill zone, which means
we need to figure out
where he went to next.
Let's canvass
all the garages in the area,
see if we can find
Mann's car.
And let's also look into
his financials
for the usual secrets--
drugs, gambling, prostitution.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hello.
Ellie? Hi.
Ellie Monroe,
from the show.
Yeah.
No, I know.
I understand.
No, I think that's
a-a great idea.
Yeah.
Okay, I'll meet you there.
Bye.
Ellie Monroe, huh?
Yeah, she's pretty upset about
this whole Bobby Mann thing,
That we were
his last guests.
She thinks
it would be comforting
if we were to be together.
"comforting"?
Is that what the cool kids
call it these days?
Wow.
You are so cynical.
You know,
sometimes after a tragedy,
two human beings just need
to--to be with each other
just for no other reason
than to show each other
some understanding
and support.
Mm! Mm.
Mm.
Mm. I'm just glad
I can be comforting.
Ahh.
Oh! Yes.
Good morning, Detective.
Really?
What?
Lose the "I just got laid"
voice, all right?
What are you talking about?
I am a trained Detective,
so don't bother denying it.
Okay, fine.
Oh, so now you're not
denying it?
You just told me not to.
Hey, guys.
Any news on the car?
Nothing at any of the garages
near Barbara Mann's building.
So we checked
restaurant valets in the area.
Bobby paid the guy
at Mozart's 100 bucks
to keep it close
while he ran up to his ex.
Witness says he left
a little before 1:30.
61st and Central Park West.
Where did he go after that?
Maybe check
traffic cams in the area.
A guy
in a sports car like that
might have blasted through
some red lights..
Yeah. It's a bit of a hail Mary,
but it's worth a try
Maybe we don't need
traffic cams.
Why not just
the man on the street?
I mean, a celebrity
in a Bugatti Veyron? Come on.
People aren't
just gonna notice that.
They are going to talk about it,
or more specifically, Tweet.
And...
Booyah.
37 A.M. Bobby Mann F.T.W.
"just saw him driving
some spaceship car
into a garage
at Broadway and 57th."
Ooh.
On it.
"F.T.W."?
"for the win."
It means, uh, "my Tweet
kicks your Tweet's butt."
Come on, Beckett. You gotta keep
up. Hang with the cool kids.
♪ how much I feel ♪
♪ feel for you, baby... ♪
(am I believe this is for you.
Um, I'll just--
um, I'll just take that.
I'm just gonna... take that.
Mm-hmm.
Pardon me one sec.
Hey, Ellie.
Yes, yes.
Last night was great,
wasn't it?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Tonight? Sure.
All right.
I'll see you then.
More comforting?
Uh--
Parking garage
at 1525 Broadway confirms
Bobby Mann
pulled in at 1:37 A.M.
and he never came back
for his car.
And what's at 1525 Broadway?
The ParkVview Penthouse
of Mickey Reed,
the gregarious and affable
host of "Late Talk."
Oh, Mickey...
Not so fine.
Doorman let Bobby up
to his flat 1:45 A.M.
Neighbors complained of
a loud argument.
Bobby left
a little after 2:00.
So Mickey lied to us.
He saw Bobby somewhere right
in the middle of our kill zone.
You think he was
a good host,
offered Bobby a drink?
This set looks like
an old-age home.
Everything needs to be
updated--no purple, no suede,
no faux finish--and get rid
of this stupid thing.
Measuring drapes already,
Mr. Reed?
Like it or not, Detective,
the network
wants me to take over
Bobby's time slot next week
right after the tribute.
I know it seems callous,
but it's what Bobby
would've wanted.
Even over his dead body.
Excuse Me?
Why did you lie to us about
seeing Mann the other night?
Ay.
Look, I'm sorry,
but I lied because I didn't
want it getting out.
that you two were fighting?
It's hard enough filling
the man's shoes around here.
I don't need the tabloids
writing out us getting into it
on the night he died.
So I lied. So what?
So you lied to a cop.
Let's be realistic.
The guy died from
a heart attack, right?
What?
It was a heart attack
that was a result
of toxins in his system,
toxins that he ingested
somewhere around the time
that you saw him.
So you guys
are saying I killed Bobby?
Why?
Well, it's no secret,
you were supposed to get
his 11:30 slot,
But Bobby
extended his contract.
Maybe you couldn't wait.
You sound as demented as Bobby.
What do you mean?
Last time I saw him,
we're best of pals, right?
The other night he comes over,
he's ranting and raving,
talking about
what a disloyal punk I've been.
Why?
Man, I don't know.
All he kept saying was,
he knew things.
And I'm like, "Bobby,
what are you talking about?"
He storms out saying
I knew what I'd done.
C.S.U.'s at Mickey's apartment
running a sweep for our toxin.
Killing the king of late-night
to take his throne--
It's very "Richard III."
It appeals to the writer in me.
Did you want a bite of this?
Hell, I'll sick God on you!
And you?
I don't ever want to see you
on my network again.
You're banned! And you?!
I don't know you.
You're all a bunch of nobodies!
I could buy this precinct!
Howard Weisberg,
President of the network.
He just found out about
the search warrant
for Mickey Reed.
And he also found out that we
think Bobby Mann was murdered.
How?
Breaking news
on a different network.
The guy got scooped on his
own star's murder.
So much for keeping
the press out.
You two better be right
about all this.
Text giggling? Really?
It's Alexis.
She just saw a loon feeding.
Funny. So did I.
Hey. So... Mann's Bugatti
is still in the garage.
They won't let us touch it
without a search warrant.
$2-million car.
Apparently, it's worth me
than their insurance policy.
You re they ar't
joyriding?
All right, check with the judge.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
If his car is still in the garage,
where'd he go
after Mickey's place?
Well, it couldn't have been
very far.
Hey, Ryan.
Did Mickey's doorman mention
in what direction Mann was headed
when he left?
Uh...
South.
South on Broadway
from 57th.
That's the theater district.
At 2:00 in the morning?
There's nothing playing then.
Well, there'diners,
there's clubs,
there's restaurants.
Well, other than the poison
and the gum,
we know he didn't eat
or drink anything.
Maybe "tory" is a place
he went.
Uh, conservatory,
inventory, purgatory--
Factory! The Comic Factory.
Mann was a comedian.
He went to a comedy club.
Comic Factory is on, uh,
55th and Broadway.
That's two blocks South.
He put his gum in a--
in a piece of paper from
a comic factory flyer.
You're right.
Then from the forenics, we know
he didn't have the cranberry
or the balsamic
before he spit it out.
So he was poisoned either
at or after the club.
Then Mickey Reed
didn't kill Bobby.
He's not our guy.
Hey, guys.
How do you feel about
going to see a little comedy?
The guy's got the most
recognizable face in comedy.
Yeah, I know.
Look, I got a call
on the club phone.
The caller I.D.'s
from Bobby's show.
A guy asks about
one of my comedians.
Couple hours later, guy shows up
to see that comedian,
but he's got
a funny looking moustache
and he's wearing a baseball cap.
It looked like Bobby.
Did he talk to anyone?
Did he have a drink?
No. He sat in the back,
left his drink ticket,
and bolted out the side
after watching the comedian
he came to see.
Anything special about
this particular comedian?
Angel Santana,
the proverbial rising star?
I'm assuming you know about
the incident that night?
What incident?
I'm Angel Santana.
Good night, y'all.
Ms. Santana.
I'm Detective Esposito.
This is Detective Ryan.
Hey.
Oh, hey.
Thanks for coming.
The officer I talked to did not
instill a lot of confidence.
You want to tell us about it?
Not much to tell.
During my set that night,
someone smashed
my bike's taillight,
banged up the fenders
and scratched "late-night bitch"
into the tank.
I mean,
what does that even mean?
Actually, we're not here
about your bike.
Ms. Santana, did you know
Bobby Mann?
You mean personally?
No. Why?
Well, because he came to see
your act
on the night he was killed.
Any idea why?
Wow.
He probably trashed my bike.
I've heard stories about him.
I know guys he's blackballed
just because they did
his competitors' show.
Is there any reason why he might
have wanted to come after you?
His producer tried to book me
on his show last month,
but Mickey Reed
wanted me, too.
I had to pick.
Mickey felt more like my vibe.
Club owner said
Bobby left at 2:30,
and the bartender confirms
he didn't drink anything.
Which leaves us...
Two hours left to account for
and a whole lot
of strange behavior.
Why would Bobby go see
a comedian
who didn't want to do his show
and then bust up her bike?
Aren't famous people crazy
and narcissistic?
I don't know.
Gotta ask Castle.
Where is Castle anyway?
Mm. Mm. mm.
Ah. Mm.
I'm gonna need
some new shirts.
No shirts.
mm. Mm.
Good morning.
It's okay, Castle.
You don't have to pretend
to not be in a good mood
for my sake.
Why should I
be in a good mood?
I mean... I'm a writer.
We... famously brood.
We... I should brood more.
You want to brood?
Forensics on
Angel Santana's motorcycle
are a bust.
There's no fingerprints.
Nothing.
We have no idea
where Mann was after 2:30.
What about his car?
Ryan and Esposito
got a warrant this morning.
But seeing that he was poisoned
after he parked it,
chances are
we won't find anything.
And his financials
were clear.
He pays more in alimony
in a day than I make
in an entire year.
There's no red flags
on his phone records.
And I reinterviewed
all of his colleagues.
No one has any idea
why he was acting so paranoid.
You're not paranoid if someone's
actually trying to kill you.
Hey, Tony! How's my favorite
movie mogul?
Yes. Right?
She'd be perfect for Nikki.
Yes.
Perfect.
Thank you.
That's a "Heat Wave "
producer.
That wasn't about
Ellie Monroe, was it?
Yeah, why?
Oh.
What?
That's why she was
throwing herself at you.
She wanted you to
recommend her for the part.
What?
Oh, and for the record,
she's nothing like Nikki Heat.
Oh, you just can't stand it
that a beautiful actress
is actually interested in me.
Why would I care?
Exactly. That's a good question.
Why would you care?
I don't.
Fine. I'm gonna go
get some coffee.
Fine. I've got work to do.
Break room's that way.
Desk.
Beckett.
Castle.
Check this out.
We just finished the sweep
of Bobby's car.
Mm-hmm.
First off, the Bugatti--
holy shift.
When you start this thing,
you can feel it right in--
But as exciting
as the car is,
I think we figured out why
Bobby Mann was so tweaked.
We found this
in his glove compartment.
That's Kayla. She's an intern
at Bobby's show.
Looks like she was
doing more than interning.
You should check out
the back.
"If they find out,
you're dead."
Blackmail, death threats
and scandal.
That explains why his behavior
was so erratic.
And probably
why he was killed.
It was last week.
I stayed late to help Bobby
with some bits.
Do you have any idea
who took that, Kayla?
Must be someone
who works on the show.
Who just happened
to have a camera
and managed to catch
the two of you in the act?
Or were they
tipped off maybe?
Were you blackmailing Bobby?
Oh, my God. No.
He's three times your age,
and you are an intern
on the show.
That adds up to embarrassment
and scandal,
which I'm sure
he'd pay a lot to avoid.
No, I would never do that.
We were in love.
In love? Really?
And... how long were
the two of you together?
Three weeks
this past Monday.
Um...
Who else knew?
No one. Bobby and I
kept it a secret.
We didn't want my mom
to find out.
Your mom?
Who's your mom?
He was banging my daughter
right under my nose?
I will kill him!
He's already dead.
Well, I will kill him again.
I don't care.
Where's the corpse?
Ms. Marks, we just--
Kayla, my office, now!
Move it!
Mom, you don't understand--
Move It!
You realize, if this gets out,
it'll destroy
Bobby's reputation.
We're not trying to add to
an already difficult situation.
We're just trying to find
the killer.
Bobby wasn't an angel,
but you look at the man
in his entirety.
He deserves to be remembered
with grace.
This business gets clouded
by money, fame, ambition.
The only thing that Bobby
really cared about
was making people laugh.
Well, whoever took this
either works for this show
or had access
to this building.
And maybe it was someone
in a financial jam
who was looking to score
a quick buck.
Or maybe it's someone
with a grudge against Bobby.
I can't imagine
anyone doing that.
He was a great boss.
Everyone loved him.
Yeah, and apparently,
he loved them back.
Okay. Uh, Janine can get you
a list of everyone on the crew
once she's done
yelling at Kayla.
Poor kid. Who knows?
She might have ended up
being number seven.
Excuse me.
Beckett.
What have we got?
Well, once we
suspected blackmail,
I ran through
his financials again.
I thought they were clean.
Well, they were,
but going back, we found this.
He spent 100 grand
on a kitchen Reno.
Totally legitimate,
but we searched his Brownstone--
and he wasn't renovating
his kitchen.
So who was on the receiving end
of the 100 grand?
Zach Robinson.
Ooh. Good bad-guy name.
Snakey "z," hard "k."
even has "rob" in it.
Good bad-guy rap sheet, too.
Former lowlife
private investigator.
I remember this guy.
He had some celebrity clients
back in the day.
He was known for
digging up dirt on folks
and turning it into
a personal payday.
He did a nickel on
multiple counts of extortion,
wire tapping, racketeering
and blackmail.
Well, Robinson must have
gotten the picture
from somebody on the inside.
Sure. Figured it was worth
a fast buck.
But if Bobby paid,
why would he kill him?
Bobby figured out that
Robinson was a blackmailer,
and then he threatened
to take him to the cops.
Bobby pushes,
Robinson pushes back harder.
Let's go pick him up.
Easier said than done.
Esposito already ran down
his last known address.
Robinson's in the wind.
Well, let's keep looking.
Yeah.
You are a bad man,
Zach Robinson.
A dirty, naughty,
no-good blackmailer.
Do you do all your
interrogations in bed,
Detective Heat?
You think this is funny,
Robinson?
Hmm?
Okay, okay.
No, I'll do
whatever you want, Nikki.
Okay. That's more like it.
Mm.
Oh.
Mm. You are so sweet.
And brilliant.
Guilty.
Mm. What are you thinking?
Nothing.
It's ridiculous.
What? Come on. Tell me.
I want to know what goes on
inside that incredible mind
of yours.
Well, since you put it
that way.
I have this... friend
at work
who thinks that the only reason
you're with me is,
you know...
for the part in the movie.
Wow.
Really?
What does this friend
of yours base that on?
You know what? I'm--
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't
have repeated that.
Does this friend know me?
No.
Has he read anything about me
that would make him think
that I would prostitute myself
for a role?
No. Of course not.
You--I--he's an idiot.
Do you have any idea
how hard it is
to be a woman in Hollywood?
Ellie.
I--
Beckett.
Oh, yeah.
He looks like
a Zach Robinson.
Where'd you find him?
The boys
caught up with him
at a craps table
at Mohegan Sun.
Already gambling away his
hard-earned blackmail money?
So how was your date
with your little starlet?
How can you tell
this time?
Like I said, Castle...
trained Detective.
Well...
It went lovely
no thanks to you.
What did I have to do
with it?
You pulled your
Jedi mind trick on me.
You made me doubt
Ellie's honesty.
Foolishly, I told her
what you said, made her cry.
Castle...
She's an actress,
a professional liar.
She's paid to cry on cue.
No.
I've never seen
this picture before.
Really?
You sure you didn't use it
to blackmail Bobby Mann?
Blackmail?
You're fishing
in the wrong pond, Detective.
What about the 100 grand
from Bobby Mann
in your bank account?
Am I in the right pond now?
That was for...
services rendered.
I don't think Webster's
defines "blackmailing"
as a service.
More like a coercive threat,
Mr. Rob-inson.
No, no. No, no.
I never threatened Bobby.
He hired me.
To do what?
My guys say that
you don't have an alibi
for the night that Mann
was murdered.
You can't be serious.
I guess it'll come out when
we go to the murder trial.
Have a nice life...
sentence.
What? No, no. No, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Look, he reached out to me.
Said he needed some work done.
What kind of work?
The kind that you get paid
a lot extra to do.
Something illegal.
W-well...
Okay, look, he thought that
somebody was out to get him.
He said he needed to know,
and so he paid me
to bug a guy's office.
Who?
Howard Weisberg.
The president
of the network?
Easy gig, too. Bobby got me
into the building.
When was this?
Week ago.
What did you do
with the recordings?
I delivered the cds to Bobby.
When?
You know...
The morning
before he died.
Bobby's producer said
he locked himself
in his office that morning.
He was listening
to the recordings.
And then they said he
started acting paranoid after that,
so what did he hear?
Am I good to go?
We found the recordings
in Mann's office
mixed in with
his DVD collection.
Heard anything yet
that would explain
why Mann was listening in
on his boss?
Nah, just a bunch of talk
about setting up breakfasts,
lunches, dinners and drinks with
writers, actors and directors.
Where are we
on the blackmail?
Oh, we got uniforms
running down all show employees
who could've had access to
the studio to take that photo.
Yo. You guys
are gonna want to hear this.
you know what?
To hell with Bobby Mann.
We're losing money on him
every damn night.
I want him out!
our hands our tied.
You can't fire him.
He's got five years left
on his contract.
What if he drops dead, huh?
Seriously. The guy has got
a bad heart.
How hard would it be
to make him go away?
I mean, hell, I got Mickey reed
telling me every day,
he's ready to step in
If we could just get Bobby Mann
out the damn door.
Well, no wonder Bobby thought
Mickey was disloyal.
And no wonder he thought
someone wanted him dead.
Someone did.
What if he drops dead, huh?
Seriously. The guy
has got a bad heart.
How hard would it be
to make him go away?
Looks like you got your wish,
Mr. Weisberg.
Detective,
none of the recordings
are admissible in court.
Oh, relax, Burt.
I didn't kill anyone, okay?
Save it for when
I actually do.
Detective, I wasn't serious.
Bobby thought you were.
Well, then maybe he shouldn't
have been bugging my office.
Hell, in private, I issue
a dozen death sentences a day
on underperforming, overpaid
jackasses at my network.
Now what I wanted was
Mickey Reed pulled to 11:30.
But Bobby had an $80-million
penalty on his contract.
Which still had another
five years left on it.
Yeah. Now what I did was
lean on Bobby for a few months
to appeal
to a younger audience.
But the worst thing that I did
was threaten to fire him
and pay him the $80 mil.
Mr. Weisberg where were you
between 1:30 and 4:30 A.M.
the night of the murder?
You don't have to answer that.
It's fine, Burt. Chill out.
I was at the Essex House Hotel.
Were you with anyone?
As a matter of fact I was.
This actress I was screwing
wanted a part
on one of my sitcoms.
I met her after Bobby's show.
I'm gonna need a name.
Sure. Ellie Monroe.
Thank you for coming by
Ms. Monroe.
Of course.
Weisberg's alibi...
Is good.
Oh, go on.
You can say it.
"I told you so."
No, thanks. I'm actually
not in the gloating mood.
His alibi sets us
back to square one...
Which means we have no idea
who the blackmailer is
And we don't know why Mann
went to the comedy club
and trashed
Angel Santana's bike.
And we have no idea
who the killer is.
Well, the good news is,
I can work all night.
No plans.
You know, it's late,
and I'm kinda tired.
How about we pick this up
in the morning?
All righty, then.
And the boys'll be
back on duty tomorrow,
to coin a phrase...
Which would be inaccurate...
because you are not a boy.
Is this some kind of
a weird come-on?
I think I know what Bobby Mann
was doing at that comedy club.
I think I know why he thought
he was an awful person.
And... I think I know
who killed him.
Mr. McPhee?
Ah.
I was just going over
my notes for the tribute.
35 years of friendship--
It's kinda hard to find
just the right story to tell.
What can I do for you?
We just came by
to give you this.
Bobby's idea book--
we thought you might like it.
Thanks.
We did have a question about
what he wrote on the last page.
"the boys'll be back on duty
tomorrow night."
Actually,
he crossed out "boys"
and wrote "gang, posse"
and "crew."
Any idea why?
I guess we'll never know.
I wouldn't be too sure
about that.
The network was pressuring
Bobby to make a change.
They threatened to cancel him
unless he did.
And the night
that he was murdered,
he told Barbara that
something awful was going on.
He asked her
if he was a good person.
Why would he say that?
Because of Kayla.
Not Kayla, Hank.
Because of you.
He knew
that he had to fire you.
He knew he needed to find
someone younger and hipper
if he was gonna survive.
Someone like Angel Santana.
Weisberg confirmed that she was
on the network's short list.
That's why it wasn't "boys"
anymore, Hank.
'cause Angel's a girl.
This is ridiculous.
Bobby would never fire me.
Then why did you kill him?
I didn't.
We ran your credit cards,
Hank.
The night that he was murdered,
you went
to a 24-hour grocery store
and bought two things--
Cranberry juice
and balsamic vinegar.
It's time stamped.
1:56 A.M.
And I'm betting
if we test your keys,
we'll find metal from
Angel Santana's motorcycle
where you scratched in
"late-night bitch."
He told me...
that night just before
he left the studio...
how he'd heard Weisberg say
they were gonna bury him
unless he made a change.
35 years, I had his back.
He was gonna toss me aside
like one of his ex-wives,
humiliate me in front of
the whole country.
I knew it was coming.
I saw all the little signs,
the awkward moments
in the hall.
I sent him that picture
of him and Kayla
to remind him
of all the secrets I kept.
You know what he said?
The scandal would only
help his ratings.
You bought your poison
and you followed him
to the club.
I confronted him
when he came out.
I told him not to throw away
everything we'd built.
He told me
he couldn't save me.
Weisberg was going younger
with or without him.
Well, if you knew he didn't have
a choice, why did you kill him?
Because he did have
another choice.
Go down with the ship!
We both go out gracefully,
and Bobby
gets 80 million bucks
instead of him continuing
the show with some kid.
I gave him
over 4,000 shows,
laughing at every lousy joke
he cracked,
whether they were funny
or not.
Jeez.
So how did you manage it?
When I knew
I couldn't change his mind,
I told him...
I understood.
We walked over
to the West Side highway,
sat on a bench,
looked out at the water,
talked about
what a great run we'd had.
Then I offered him a drink.
He was my best friend.
You don't do that
to your friend.
Yet another example of
why you shouldn't mix
business with pleasure,
even show business.
Are you talking about the case
or yourself?
Yeah.
Touché, Detective.
So you want to go
for a victory lap
and grab a burger?
Oh, can't. Gotta go.
Big date.
You're kidding, right?
You're going out with
Ellie Monroe even though
you know the only reason
that she was interested in you
was for a part?
Have you lost
all sense of human decency
and self-res--what?
My big date...
is with Alexis.
She's getting back
from her trip.
Oh.
♪
Right on time, Alexis.
Oh, Sacagawea...
has returned!
And you are not
Sacagawea,
but come in.
Thanks.
I'm headed back to L.A.
and I just wanted to...
say sorry.
Thanks.
But the truth is,
I've never had so much fun
being used.
You feel free
to have at me anytime.
Well, I guess you'll rescind
your recommendation of me
to your producers, and that
is the least I deserve--
No, Tony thinks you are
great for it, and so do I.
You are a better actress
than I thought
when I recommended you.
Well, you should know, I wasn't
acting the whole time.
Me neither.
Thanks, Rick.
Take care.
You, too.
Bye.
Hi.
Dad, was that--
My Sacagawea
has returned!
Oh, my God. My best girl.
I missed you so much.
Oh, my God.
I'm so glad you're home.
I missed you, too, dad.
You're not just saying that,
are you?
What--
No, don't.
Tell me you're hungry.
I'm starving.
Come with me.
Tell me everything.
I will.