Everybody. Last year, I've launched
"The Self-Healing Program for
Post Breakup"
More than 120,000 people has joined
In over 40 cities worldwide.
The success rate, is for everyone to see.
But now I think...
Treatment after breakup is not the best.
Therefore, I have start a new program,
called...
"Self-Healing Program for PRE Breakup"
Today, we have a new brother
Who'll share his experience with us.
Hello, everybody.
My names's Bo Yu.
My breakups has been caused by
my family's rule:
The eldest sister must get married first
Or misfortune will come!
No way?
That's what I thought at first, but...
Marry me.
Bo!
Kuen!
And also...
Marry me.
Lynn!
Those were the results of not believing!
I don't wanna hurt anyone else and so...
I never try to love again!
The only way out,
is to wait for my sister to get married!
I deeply sympathize with you.
By the way, who is your sister?
She is awesome.
Good morning, Miss Yu.
Hurry...
What morning?
I pay you to work,
not greeting whoever comes in.
You're fired! Totally out of line...
The nail polish is still wet,
it's not a beauty parlor here
You deserve it!
- Good morning, Miss Yu. - Morning.
Miss Yu, is this design alright?
- Yes. - Thank you.
Miss Yu,
please double check this document.
It's okay. Release it.
Sis... you've got a meeting with
publishers at 1 p.m.
New book signing at 2:30,
tea with advertisers at 4.
And TV reporters have also arrived.
The questions are all about
your new book released today.
They're waiting for you to get ready...
on the balcony.
Alright. Repeat it again.
At 1:30... no, at 1 you've got to...
God. I've forgotten everything.
Hello, hello. I am today's...
You're the director?
Just listen to everything I say.
Hello! I'm the host, Vivian.
Are you the famous writer,
Miss Choo Yu?
It's Chu.
Chu?
Really? They spell alike...
These are the 7 questions I'll ask you
Please read them carefully.
Then answer us concisely.
Don't waste our time.
I have another job right after this.
Plus, you are just doing this promote...
your book anyway.
- Director. - Yes, yes.
- Shooting in high
definition today? - Sure.
Good. I want a lighter makeup.
She's younger. Do it heavier.
What?
Listen to her. It's hard to get her.
Makeup.
Yes! What's up, sir?
Give her a HD makeup.
What is HD makeup?
It means...
Makeup for TV shows, but heavier.
Got it. Okay.
Hello everybody!
Welcome to our show.
We've invited the renowned writer,
who's also an icon for
all independent women.
She's releasing her new bestseller today
It's Not My Fault to Be a Single Woman.
Miss Chu Yu, please!
Miss Yu, you have always promoted
"independence".
What do you think of marriage?
I always believe that
people don't have to get married.
A single women have no constraints.
Work and travel whenever they want.
It's free.
All your works are about being single.
Doesn't anyone try to pick you up?
Why do I want that?
I can pick up guys, if I find one I like.
Everything comes from Earth's gravity,
the gravitation pull of the universe
plus the harmony of yin and yang.
Simply put: Fate.
See how great your daughter is.
Teaching people not to
get married again.
I'm really worried that
she won't get married!
But she's too successful
That's what happens to
successful woman!
I guess. She did get her degree at 20.
Yeah, and became a writer,
chief editor...
at 26.
That's why she's stuck in the middle!
The ones she likes, doesn't like her
And she doesn't like the ones that
like her.
Just like that song by Danny Chan...
What song?
"You're choosing your lover,
and so are they."
Then it's bad!
What if she just keep working...
Sis!
Dad, mom.
Dad. You're back.
You look much bigger.
And you're looking more handsome.
Look at all these muscles.
Hey, look at your face...
Just shut it!
Have you eaten yet?
I'll cook you something.
It's okay,
I'll eat after I finish my work upstairs.
This month's money.
Good girl.
I've seen a pair of
limited edition fly sunglasses.
I know you will like them.
Cool!
I gotta work now.
By the way, I wanna tell you...
I got my degree at 19!
Next time don't talk so loud behind
someone's back
Sorry... we'll talk again in
chat room tonight.
My name is "Musculator"
Really? Mine is "Pass off the Wind".
I have one too, called "Sexy Maggie".
What? You are "Sexy Maggie"?
Yeah!
- Let's eat hotpot after work.
- Good idea!
Come on, let's go to Club Chocolate
The idea's been banned.
Think up a new one.
Get it done tonight or nobody can leave!
I have a meeting now.
I'll bring back food at 11:30.
Anything suggestions?
McDonald's again then!
We're not going to have fun tonight.
Karaoke dinner anyone?
I know one with great hot wings.
We'll suffer,
as long as your sister stay single!
You better find her a boyfriend soon.
Because it won't be hot wings
we are eating next time!
What will we be eating?
Hot asses.
I like hot asses!
Uncooked!
L ~ O ~ V ~ E ~ LOVE
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8...
Over 100 millions results
"Open your heart".
I'm a lawyer, a doctor,
An astronaut, as well as a movie director.
Fraud.
Are you lonely?
Let me open your heart.
Open it! Your heart!
Psycho!
I'm a GCSE student who wants to
try puppy love.
Come on, try me!
What's up with you?
What's with all the singing, you happy?
Yes. I'm really happy!
I'm gonna get married!
Huan, I thought you vowed to
stay unmarried?
It's good to be in love.
It's stupid to be single!
Stupid?
When love finds you, you'll faint
Then the whole world...
turns upside down.
Wonderful!
Turns-upside-down?
This guy should be able to
help your sister.
The love therapist: Dick... Cho?
I haven’t been so happy for 10 years,
until this past month.
That's great! But today is the last lesson!
So fast?
You found me just to
heal your broken heart.
Now you've healed up.
You can now love bravely again!
But I...
Sheila...
Look at you, you dress like a hag,
don't dress like this!
Come on, let's look over here.
Is there anyone you like?
So you like fat and greasy things.
Warm in winter. Cool in summer.
Not bad.
But you must stop acting like a "Mistress".
But I have only ever been a...
Mistress, mistress
123, 321, 1234567
Sheila, from now on
you're no longer a "mistress"
You're a legendary woman,
that only wins in love.
Go and love hard on the count of 3.
1, 2, 3
Give him a big smile.
It's not going to work with this smile
Bigger!
The sun is beaming,
rub some lotion on him.
This big?
It might not be enough for him!
I shall leave now!
Hello. Can I sit down?
Need some lotion?
Sounds good!
Doctor Cho speaking.
I have heard about your situation.
So... how much will it cost?
Generally, 30 to 50 thousand dollars.
Quite reasonable.
As for your sister,
I'll hang up for less than 200,000!
200,000?!
Keep to the side...
Dumbass! Keep to the side!
Excuse me!
1234, the right side. Good.
Miss Yu, time's up. See you next time.
Didn't you talk on the phone for
5 minutes?
Yes, I forgot!
Come on!
Also, I don't think I've sweated enough.
I've heard, there's a session here like...
Love on a Diet...
I can beat a guy up?
Sure you can!
Miss Yu...
Come on!
Does it have to be so hard!
I don't want to bargain!
You're so reasonable.
What's the treatment?
It's a business secret!
You are giving off vibes of a loser in love.
Do you need some treatment?
No. I've already given up!
Don't be silly.
I'll give you the cheapest treatment.
I'll relight your fire with love again!
To relight your passion for love...
First, you need to find the right place.
What is the right place?
Simple, somewhere full of girls!
Any target?
Yes!
First, you must show a friendly smile.
Keep eye-contact with her...
And you must speak to her within
7 seconds.
If you go right in to chat,
it's over if she doesn't react.
Go in from her side.
45 degrees is the best.
Attack and defense as you like!
Go.
Hi!
Hello.
Pickup line
What?
Pickup line?
You've got asthma?
Why are you gasping?
Say something. Anything will do.
Everyday lives!
I have constipation lately!
Really?
You can eat more fiber,
or drink more water.
They don't help at all!
Could it be caused by stress at work?
Maybe. You know...
I need to get up early...
What? Why are you talking with guys?
I lack confidence!
123, 321, 1234567
Bo Yu. You're no longer a loser in love.
You're the coolest gentleman in
this minute.
Every step you make is more stylish
than Clark Gable!
1, 2, 3
Do you think I'm handsome?
I think I am super handsome.
Which part of me do you think is the best?
Every part.
Why don't you take a look with
the lights out at my place.
Excuse me, this is my girlfriend.
I'm handsome.
That's how handsome guys live.
You're so ugly, piss off!
Siu Ming! Siu Keung!
Don't hit my face!
Not the face!
Body only?
Sir
Cheque please... leave it to him.
Just a few punch is enough...
Come in.
Sis...
The interviewees are all here,
take a look.
Why are you wearing a top with
so many pockets?
You really need them?
Don't all photographers dress this way?
Appearance is important,
come back when you get it.
Scram!
Why are all works out of focus?
And the framing is poor!
This is my style!
What style do you have when
you have no techniques?
Scram!
I'm sure you'll be impressed...
with my look and techniques.
Yes, but you lack affinity!
The longer I look at you...
The more I want to slap you.
We are short on employees.
You have 1-month probation!
Sis... he's only interviewing.
He won't work!
What the hell?
Nobody's coming to interviews
these days!
Go go go...
I have him here to make up numbers.
Give me 10 more minutes...
see if I can get more from Kowloon.
Hello, I'm here for an interview.
Leave!
Leave, you've got no chance!
You leave!
Who did you work for?
I'm a freelancer.
I have worked as a war correspondent.
Now, I'm doing some kind of art.
By the way, what perfume are you using?
This, is my natural fragrance.
The "Wax Factor heart beating perfume...
25th anniversary edition"...
Should suit you well!
Psycho!
Take a seat.
This job doesn't pay a lot.
You gotta raise your family?
I'm still single.
Plus I got 2 patents 5 years ago which...
I can live on.
Which means I can focus on
pursuing my dream!
When can you start working?
Up to you!
I have a gift for you to
commemorate our first meeting.
It'll break the rules.
Rules are dead. See you tomorrow.
Case number 72645, Chu Yu.
Level of Difficulty: Above 5 stars.
Phase 2 starts right away.
The ad needs to be shoot,
you have to make a decision.
The outermost one.
The outermost one? Which one?
The outermost tube,
the one that's dimmed.
Have to take off my top first.
Miss Yu,
what is the theme color for the ad?
Bronze.
So... who's the model?
Get me the tube.
Good looking guy.
That's male model only.
No female model.
And the director?
Muscles.
Yes, we'll get Jackie Chan!
Alright. Get back to the ad!
What is it?
Miss Yu.
You don't need to come in tomorrow!
Good morning, Miss Yu.
What is it?
Nothing... I just wanna ask you if...
If I can call you Little Chu?
Of course. I'm actually very easygoing.
Don't worry. In crowded places...
I'll still call you Miss Yu.
Okay... okay.
By the way, You...
What?
Miss Yu has...
Redistributed her!
What?
But I don't know English or computer!
Wouldn't this decision be... a bit risky?
Let me worry about that,
even though you're just a cleaner
But I can totally see that you're a genius.
You just never had a chance!
What about the salary?
Unchanged, of course!
Will she have her own room?
Yes?
The store room!
Good! Thank you, Miss Yu.
Okay, start working and work hard.
- Thank you...
- You'll be a manager soon!
Apart from easygoing,
you have great vision too.
Yes, quite great!
Really?
By the way, what were you asking me?
I... I want to ask...
If you're the type who...
sacrifice breakfast for fitness?
I love breakfast.
- Really? - Sure.
Well, that's great.
I've prepared a breakfast and
left it on your desk.
You'll see it when you get in.
Enjoy it!
Really?
It's delicious...
It's Not My Fault to Be a Single Woman
Has sold over 500,000 copies in Asia.
Bestseller for 8 weeks.
Miss Yu, that's marvelous!
Chu, the company wants you to
write 6 more books
to make a Single Woman,
the Complete Collection.
Okay...
Also, the company wants to publish
a traveler magazine.
The first issue focuses on Qiandao Lake.
I've been Qiandao Lake before.
Fantastic scenery,
rich in marine products.
You'll be overjoyed if...
you like to eat freshwater fish.
The steamed fish head is splendid!
Branding, marketing, packaging,
account servicing...
Do you have any good ideas?
Come on! Spirit!
Why don't we have a tea break first?
Great...
You bastards!
Fried dumplings
It's disgusting.
Tried that last time, this...
That...
That... guy, speak up.
You say it's beautiful there.
Why don't we have
the environmental ambassador...
Julia Roberts to live there for a year,
And invite the world famous director
John Woo
To shoot her life in romantic style while
Releasing doves into the frame.
Free DVD released with the book.
It'll sell itself.
So how much... do you expect to use?
Not much. USD 70 million.
Julia herself costs 20 million!
So what's the price of the book?
HKD 8.
Issue 1 should be cheaper,
to get the reputation.
What a good idea!
Do any of you think it's good?
Applaud if you do.
You guys are right to be silence.
I don't know who employed you.
But I don't ever want to see you again.
Okay?
I think this idea is possible.
You think it's good?
Not practical, but creative!
Chu, you're the Ronaldo of our company
But your judgment can't be too ridiculous.
But creativity cannot be limited by
our imagination.
We can fine tune it!
Even if it's limitless,
it can't be ridiculous.
That... That guy
He's just ridiculous,
I'll definitely sack him!
I think you are getting personal and
not business.
I'm the boss. I like to get personal!
So what?
Alright! If you fire him...
I'll quit! How's that!
Sis... did you argue with the boss?
I have my own reasons!
You're the financial centre of our family.
What should we do if you lose your job?
We're a family!
Can't we share the burden?
Mom, dad and I can't handle it!
Boss!
Can you give her one more chance?
It's my fault.
If she does it again, I'll beat her up!
What are you on? I never said I'd fire her.
What does she has to do?
Boss, I...
Chu, take it easy!
Arguments are good for meetings.
Let that... that guy to do some research
Before talking about anything else!
What are you laughing at?
Go get me that...
Julia Robert's phone number
Okay...
Boss, you must be tired,
let's get a massage together.
Go.
Thank you for supporting me!
I support all creative ideas!
Would it be creative if
I invite you to dinner?
When? And Where?
I want that table!
That table has already been booked...
This is the menu for tonight.
Dim the light for me and
get the air-conditioner going.
Yes, okay!
There're 2 set meals tonight...
I want a lobster meal.
Lobster and lobster soup.
He wants the rib-eye, medium.
And borsch soup.
Little Chu,
can you let me order for myself?
Miss here wants a... lobster meal.
With Lobster...
Little Chu.
Have you not dated for a while?
Who told you? I'll go and fire him!
Just guessing!
You are the career type,
how would you have time?
That's true!
Plus with your talent,
no man is a match for you!
That's true too!
So, what type of men do you like?
Ambitious.
Love my mom, dad... and bro.
Loyal to me.
Handsome.
And humorous!
In the end, it's just someone who's nice.
Honestly...
Thank you, sir!
Thank you, madam!
What did you wanna say? Honestly...
Honestly,
if you can control your temper...
You're quite cute!
I'm cute?
Really, I'm cute?!
I want ice-cream! Ice-cream!
Ma'am, you haven't had main course yet.
I don't care! I'm just a girl who
wants ice-cream!
Okay. Sure!
I'm a teenage girl!
I'm so happy tonight.
I can tell.
No, I mean, I'm happy, too!
Okay, bye.
Bye.
Umbrella for you.
Bye!
L-am-so-happy!
I'm really really happy...
Shit!
This time at Qiandao Lake,
Remember to take photos of
all the islands,
Don't bother coming back without them!
What?
And, a girl called Bucktooth Jane...
will pick you up.
Bucktooth Jane? Is she pretty?
Of course she's gorgeous!
Stop asking questions, just go.
Come with me.
The boss ordered me to finish
the Single Woman series.
I can't go with you.
Take care and don't miss me.
I'll try my best!
Brought enough clothes?
What you doing? Go... back to work...
If you don't have enough,
buy some up there.
Remember
Okay...
Hi!
I think... I'd better go with you.
It's okay!
You... go and write.
How about at home,
I know you'll get inspirations there!
I'll get another one. Okay.
Hey, no...
Where're you driving me to?
Who're you?
You again, Mr. Chan?
Haven't seen you in ten years.
Qiandao Lake Hangzhou
Don't stare at me.
Sis told me to look after you.
Just look at you, how old are you...
Heavily armed just like Rambo.
A total mess!
- What are you doing?
- It's time.
It's Wednesday today.
Let's have some "Monk's Sweet Armpit".
Armpit?
It's Dried jujube cooked with
monk's fruit and pork.
- It's nutritious.
- Right.
Hey, Doctor Cho
My sis has never made any soup
for anyone.
What did you do to her?
Honestly... all those who need my help
Has been hurt by love and
have no confidence.
They've even given up.
I only open their heart, and make them
See the bright side of love again!
But you have opened her heart without
closing it.
Wouldn't she get hurt?
Don't you remember "Phase 6" of
the treatment?
She'll heal up once the treatment is over.
Then she'll enjoy her love life again.
And I'll be out of her life forever.
But obviously you'd have to pay me first.
Understand?
Right, sure.
I thought a Bucktooth Jane would
pick us up?
I have no idea.
You sister send you to look after me,
go and look!
What's with the ordering?!
Bucktooth Jane!
Sorry, I'm late!
Are you Mr. Dick Cho?
You are Bucktooth Jane?
No, I'm not.
I'm her friend, Mandy!
So... where's Bucktooth Jane?
She's sick today!
So I'm here to pick you up, is that alright?
Alright, Bucktooth becomes a babe...
We are on a very tight schedule.
Gotta hurry up. Let's go!
Is this your luggage?
Let... let me get it, okay?
No!
It's my job to take care of you, let me.
Okay. Go ahead!
She's so cute!
Bucktooth Jane!
How can you be so rude?
Rude? You do have bucktooth.
Bucktooth Jane, where're we going?
My colleague is over there.
Where're we going, Bucktooth Jane?
Why are you biting me?
This blossom shaped islet...
has the best view of the lake.
Many tourists take photos here.
This is the Lock Island.
This is the Monkey Island.
And this is the Dragon Island
So what... what's that island?
Maybe...
I know! Is that "No Isle, Dear" (no idea)?
Is it not funny?
I know it's a bad joke...
But I like to tell them!
What's this?
I called it "Love's like a Tide"
It's famous here.
Nothing special!
Take a look first.
Miraculous!
Take a sip.
Tastes good?
Sure!
You are such a weird person.
Always striking a pose and...
talk like they do in movies.
Really? No way!
That must be how you pick up girls.
- No! - Yes!
- Really no! - Definitely!
- I said no!
- I said yes!
This is it!
I...
I really...
had a great time today!
It was just work! How can it be great?
But I really did have a great time!
It's Jane.
She said she can come to work
tomorrow,
She'll be here for you tomorrow morning.
Can I see you again?
Give me a call!
Sure!
Get an early night in!
I better get going, goodbye!
Goodbye!
Mainland's phone number has
so many digits!
Is this 1... or 7?
We just saw each other,
would I scare her if I call her now?
Would it be too late to call her now,
and scare her?
Let's get some alcohol first.
Come on!
That Bucktooth Jane was a fake!
What's up?
Look at yourself!
What's happened?
Your look... tells me you are in
a state of wishful thinking...
Your world is spinning around.
What does that mean?
You feel sweet...
sometimes exited...
and sometimes bored...
You'd feel the phone ring when it didn't...
Hey. Say something!
Premenstrual stress...
You messing with me, bastard!
No!
Girls can feel the same things
you are feeling.
Come on. Tell your uncle Bo
what has happened?
Today, I met a girl called Mandy.
When I was with her...
feel like...
Every time I saw her smile...
When... when I saw her,
I smiled from my heart.
That's it.
So...
You've met your true love!
True love?
True love!
You're a love therapist,
how could you not know it?!
I... I have never dated!
Never? Are you kidding me?
My parents are very strict!
I see a set of teeth!
I'm so sorry!
I was sick yesterday so
I couldn't pick you guys up.
- Bucktooth Jane? - Bucktooth Jane?
Yes!
Who is Dick Cho?
She's smiling at you...
Her teeth're nearly touching your face,
lucky man!
123, 321, 1234567
I... I'm not Dick Cho.
This son of a bitch here is Dick Cho.
This son of a bitch is Dick Cho on...
the count of 3.
1, 2, 3!
Just tell me so if you don't want to go,
stop muttering.
God. Even my hypnotic power has gone.
Let's start working.
Don't get close to me!
Camcorder, camera, map...
Flashlight, compass, and water gun,
and so on...
I forgot to bring mosquito repellent.
You're so fussy.
Yeah, people praise me for it!
Come on!
Bee! A bee...
You're scared of bees?
Yes!
You're a man. You're scared of bees?
What else can a man be scare of,
if not bees?
How can you protect your girlfriend?
Can't my girlfriend protect me?
You act like a bitch too!
People praise me for that too! Alright?
Don't!
Stop it...
Was it fun?
I'm scared...
Fantastic!
Great.
Bravo!
Let me show you.
The Olympic rings! Olympic rings...
What're you doing?
Pretends to be an ostrich,
to lure them over for photos.
You're as dumb as an ostrich!
Their brain is just the size of a thumb
How would they know what you're doing?
It will be easier with food!
Give me your hand.
Go.
Why're you laughing?
Stop!
Don't you hate me,
why are you being nice to me?
I don't know!
I suddenly feel that you're not that bad.
Really?
By the way, there's a water show at
the square tonight.
You can tell Dick Cho to
take Mandy there.
It's romantic!
Romantic?
Many mosquitoes?
Never mind,
I'd better buy some mosquito repellent.
Why are you holding onto me?
Go and chat with her.
I... I'm feeling a bit nervous.
I don't know what to say!
That's true.
Just look at you,
it's a disaster waiting to happen!
Exactly!
Don't worry!
Let me give you an invincible plan.
Great.
Whatever Mandy says
Just nod your head and say "great"!
It's beautiful...
The water show is awesome.
Great!
Have you had dinner yet?
What did you eat?
Great!
Are you not feeling well?
Gr...
Mandy, I'm a little claw without birds.
Do you mean you're...
a little bird without claws?
This is what I just said!
Since I met you, I... I feel like...
I'm a bird with claws coming out!
I'm not telling a bad joke. I'm serious!
Love, is actually simple.
If you really love me, look at me
And I can see myself through your eyes.
That's easy! Come on, take a look...
See if you can see yourself.
What's wrong?
Nothing... sand got in my eyes.
No problem... come on.
Anything? Can you see yourself?
There's nothing.
Want me to blow away the sand?
Go ahead!
Shouldn't have blown it. It's even worse!
Why have you kept your head down
all night?
Great!
Have you had dinner yet?
What did you eat?
Great!
What's wrong?
Everyone does the same!
What are you doing?
- There's bee! - Bee?
Don't be scared. I'll protect you!
Are you mad?
Are you okay?
Just got stung by the bee!
Let me see.
It's okay...
Let me see!
It's okay!
You're quite good, stop pretending.
Bo!
I can't be with you!
Why?
What're you doing?
- It hurts! - Don't move...
Let me take it out.
Don't move...
Softer please!
Why?
Why!
I don't want to hurt you!
Don't go! Don't leave me!
I want to be single.
I am honored to be single.
I am proud to be single.
Mr. And Mrs. Yu,
thank you for trusting our company.
Come on, cut to the chase!
Okay, let me introduce you to
our new product.
"Every spinster with a house"
protection scheme.
Seems like, she is the insured person?
Yes, right!
Wise choice!
I need to ask
some routine questions first.
When was the last time she had a date?
2 years?
20 years?
Can you describe the character of
the insured person?
A, refined; B, affectionate;
C, amiable; D, evil.
Evil!
The last question.
What is the chance of
the insured person getting married?
0 being the lowest; 5 being the highest.
Anything lower than a 0?
I need to recalculate to see if
she can be insured!
But it's okay,
I'll leave her my business card anyway.
So we can get to know each other.
Call me if you have any questions.
That must be your brother.
He's handsome!
Our company have another scheme.
"Sister is single,
there's no problem-o" scheme.
I don't know if...
- You'd be interested?
- Get lost!
I'll leave then.
Daughter... Daughter...
- We just want what's best for you...
- Exactly.
That's why we want that scheme for you.
Since no one wants you!
Not no one wants you,
it's just you don't want to!
- You don't want to!
- Yes... you don't want to.
We're both getting older and
your bro is lazy.
You gotta protect yourself!
You two are ridiculous!
The last Chinese New Year,
you had some exterminators.
They couldn't pronounce spiders and...
kept saying spinsters...
I said nothing!
But we did have lots of spiders.
They were going all over the place!
And now you want me to buy
some protection scheme.
It's called "Every spinster with a house"...
Don't buy it...
- We give up... - Don't buy it...
Who said I'm a spinster?
I have a boyfriend!
Great, good girl... you have a boyfriend.
Of course you have...
I really have!
He's called Dick Cho and
he's handsome!
- Handsome? - Handsome?
Bring him home.
Yes... let us see him.
He's on a business trip in Qiandao Lake.
- Liar! - Liar!
You two won't believe me? Alright,
I'll take you to him.
A trip for you two at the same time!
Why won't they believe me?
The mobile you called is switched off
Why is his phone off?!
Try again later!
I'm Miss Yu. Yes!
Get me a ticket to Hangzhou tomorrow.
2 for my mom and dad on the day
after tomorrow.
Send a car to pick me up
tomorrow morning.
Don't be late, dumbass!
Dicky, let me pretend to call you from HK
To give you a surprise!
Dicky, answer the phone.
How come a girl is coming out?
It's just the cleaner!
Yes, coming.
Dicky...
Where're we going to take photos today?
Wherever you like.
Why're they acting so close?
Yeah, why?
Let's go.
Seen any peacocks? They look beautiful.
Yeah.
Want some water?
Thank you.
You have some too.
Stay calm...
Stay calm and I'll let you go, okay?
You've calm down... right.
It's bad!
What are you doing? Who are you?
You can tell I'm a private detective by
the I'm dressed.
My name is L.
Dick, Cho. Yes, Dick Cho.
Call me as soon as you get his info.
Why're you tracking Dick Cho?
I'm not,
I'm tracking the girl next to him!
Come with me.
What are you doing?
Don't you know how to track?
You'll be discovered like this.
12, 13...
What?
I'm counting the footsteps.
16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22
11, 12, 13, 19
- 23, no, 26 - 22, no, 26
- What're you doing?
- You messed me up!
So did you!
Just let me count, okay?
You spell trouble!
They are over there, look!
They've ran off! What's next?
Calm down!
You do have some power!
1800 dollars per hour, we'll halved that.
Alright.
Cash.
Chinese Yuan!
You spell trouble!
This is the Lock Island,
the place with the most locks...
Okay! Just shush!
Camouflage cloth, 200 for one.
100 each.
Crazy!
Money slave!
This place is renowned for love locks
and marriage stones.
If you write your wish on the love lock.
Let's go that way.
- Then close your eyes...
- Come forward.
And walk in a straight line.
And manages to kick the marriage sone...
Then your wish will come true!
- I've kicked it!
- I've kicked it...
Looks like they have a chance!
You calm down...
Our fates are joint together...
- Let me hang it there. - Alright.
By the way...
why're you tracking Dick Cho?
He's my boyfriend!
Your boyfriend?
Isn't he out of your league,
he's so handsome!
What do you mean?
We're very good together!
That bitch must have seduced him.
Let's go over there.
Look at her smile, what a slut.
Her look disgusts me!
Why do you talk like that?
I think she's nice.
Pretty and kindhearted!
Why are you so uncivilized?
You'll hurt the kids!
They're innocent!
Stop it!
Hope all the couples in the world...
can't be forever...
Be forever...
Damn, we lost them, what should we do?
You lost them, I've got my ways
I'm a pro!
Follow me.
You can see right into Dick Cho's room.
38,000 dollars per day. We'll share it.
Fine!
How can you see from this distance?
Use this.
These are binoculars with...
infrared, anti-shock, auto-focus,
HD and wide angle.
500 dollars per minute.
5 seconds free trial!
12345. Time's up!
Still wanna see it?
Of course!
That'll be 800 dollars per minute!
Dicky, it's Little Chu, what are you doing?
Uploading some photos.
Do you miss me?
What?
Yeah, of course...
Of course I miss you!
How much?
Hello? The... the reception is bad... here!
What're you playing?
"Happy Online"
You better not listen to it.
I have to!
500 dollars.
Okay!
Who called you?
It's that spinster.
The most disgusting and
bitchy woman in the company!
I told you not to listen!
Your boyfriend's info is all here.
Wanna see it?
Each page will cost you.
However much it'll cost!
This Dick Cho... isn't really
picking you up!
He is just a love therapist.
Who helps people with
their love problems!
I think someone has paid him to
mess with you!
This here is free!
Since you're paying half the rent.
I'll let you sleep in the bedroom.
Miss Yu.
Miss Yu?
Ran off?!
Where's your boyfriend?
I don't know what you mean, madam.
Stop pretending, it's Dick Cho.
You are his friend? Do you need him?
Are you two dating?
Have you ever thought,
he might be lying to you?
Madam, this is the first time we meet!
Why are you asking
these kinds of questions?
Answer me!
Are you in a bad mood?
No!
Try this "Love's like a Tide"? It's good.
Fine. I'll write a bad review for it.
Why is it so good?
Feeling any better?
No!
I'm here... to tell you, you...
Never mind, cheque please!
It's on the house.
Come with your boyfriend next time.
My treat.
Thank you!
Mandy... what...
A woman was looking for you.
What did she tell you?
Nothing, but she looked furious!
What happened?
Nothing!
Really?
Really! Trust me.
Thank you.
Where were you off to?
To track down my rival!
And?
Don't mention it!
Shit, mom and dad are on a flight here...
to see my boyfriend.
No problem. Economy or deluxe?
They have come afar,
it should be deluxe.
Great!
Daughter, your boyfriend is so wealthy.
Picking us up with such a luxury car.
Yes, sure.
I'm gonna be bankrupt!
- What did you say?
Nothing... I said...
It's priceless to see you two happy!
Happy, of course we are happy.
Wow! Such a big house!
Welcome!
Wow! So many maids here!
Wow!
Mom, I don't see anything to "wow" about.
I "wow" coz I have a stomach ache!
Take my mom to the toilet, please.
This way, please.
Be careful.
Good morning, sir.
Good morning.
Daughter... this is that
handsome boyfriend you talked about?
Beauty is in the hand of the beholder!
Nice to meet you, sir!
What're you doing?
You want to bankrupt me?
We said deluxe,
I'm already doing this cheaply!
The servants are all actors from
Springtime Productions.
50 dollars per day!
Hey, so, how did the two of you meet?
Yeah, how did we meet?
Yeah! Do you remember?
That time you lost your wallet,
and you need 500 dollars.
Yeah, that's how we met.
Yeah.
Now we mention it,
you still owe me that 500 dollars!
Then you should pay her back.
A man should be trustworthy!
Yes... trustworthy!
Right!
500, right?
I had breakfast on an empty stomach,
I'm hungry again.
No problem, sir.
I've got the best bird's nest soup upstairs.
Really?
Let's eat it upstairs.
Yes, yes.
4,000 dollars for 50 grams,
we'll work it out later!
Doctor Cho, sis brought our parents up
to see her boyfriend.
That's you.
I'll talk with sis after...
I deal with your parents.
But tragically, my move is failing!
If not we could skip to "Phase 6" already!
Don't tell my sis, I hired you
Because I'll be a dead man!
Don't worry. I'm a pro.
I won't betray you until necessary!
How can a house be so big?
Can't find the living room,
after going to the loo.
How stupid of me!
Where am I...
- Where should I go? - Mom!
Bo!
I'm glad to find you here!
Mom, this is Dick Cho,
sister's boyfriend.
Hello, auntie.
Hello, Mr. Cho.
Hello...
Mr. Cho, you're really... handsome!
Auntie, you're also beautiful!
Handsome guy! Handsome guy...
Auntie, you're so... cute...
Why has mom gone for so long?
Where is she?
Sis!
Why're you here?
Mom and dad called to say
they are meeting your boyfriend.
So I've brought Dick here.
What?
Where is he?
Outside in the garden with mom.
Nice palm! Nice palm!
Mom!
Daughter, your boyfriend is...
super handsome!
You're also beautiful.
Come here!
- Come here! - Okay...
I have something to tell you...
You don't need to say a thing.
I know everything about you,
I'll deal with you later!
Also, I know someone hired you to
mess with me.
I will find out who that person is!
Then what?
Chop him up into confetti!
Why do you look so embarrassed?
Nothing... count on me.
I will find out who that this!
A man called L is acting as my boyfriend,
he's with dad.
You two keep acting, don't blow this!
What are you guys
so happy talking about?
Mom, have some tea.
Where's my husband?
He's eating upstairs.
I miss him. I want to see him.
It's okay... I'll get him for you.
- No. Let me look for him.
- Right now...
Sit down, mom.
Have some tea.
Really?
Where's my wife?
She's in the garden.
I can't. I miss her. I must see her.
No problem. I'll get her up here.
Perfect!
Excellent.
Delicious...
- Dad's looking for mom!
- Mom's looking for dad!
Mom.
Where's my husband?
Cutting his toenails upstairs!
Dad.
Where's my wife?
Having a shower!
Chu says she's in the garden.
Having a shower in the garden!
So tempting?
I miss him... I can't take this,
I must see him.
No. There're toenails everywhere.
Move... I miss her. I must see her.
No. Just sit down and wait for her.
Does your stomach still hurt?
I'll give you a rub.
My mom will want to sleep
as soon as she gets a stomach rub.
There are other people here!
It's okay... We're all family.
- Let me massage your shoulder.
- I'm okay!
My dad will want to sleep,
as soon as he gets a foot rub.
Great... come on...
It's okay, hey... do I need to take my pants off?
- Ah... no. - Don't need to then!
The inner sole.
Don't wake him up!
Don't wake her up!
Lift her back to the hotel.
Drag him back to the hotel
Dinner time!
- Dinner time? - Dinner time?
Dining room this way, please
Thank you.
What should we do?
OK...
Dad, mom,
I've brought my friend for dinner!
Alright.
Dad, mom!
- I've brought my friend for dinner!
- Good boy...
Dad, mom,
I've brought my friend for dinner!
Drink a glass of "Jin Liu Fu",
be together forever.
Everybody, cheers.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Is this going to work?
Yes! Dad thinks this guy is
your boyfriend.
Mom thinks Dick is your boyfriend.
It'll be fine unless the cover gets blown!
So, have you thought about marriage?
Maybe 2 more years.
I wanna keep working while still young!
This young man is dedicated to his work!
How about you?
Have you thought about marriage?
Anytime I want.
My dad's wealthy. I don't need to work!
This young man has so much personality!
Yes.
I told you it'll be fine!
What if they start calling Dick's name?
That'd be bad!
Dick.
Does Little Chu bully you?
Dick. Dad...
Don't speak while eating,
you taught us that!
Yes, that's right...
How about this.
Whoever talk from now on...
will be fined 500 dollars.
Agreed?
I do!
Dad, mom,
have and early night in the hotel.
Oh, and Dick...
Have fun till as late as you like.
Let me help you.
Don't come back too early!
Hey, Dick...
- Don't come in too early.
- Dad, give me 20 dollars.
And it's okay to do crazy things!
Mom told us to do crazy things!
Look...
Dick!
Why is he kissing my daughter?
Why do you call him Dick?
He is Dick. Stop laughing!
He is Dick!
He's the real Dick.
- He's the real Dick.
Dad, mom. Listen to me.
The truth is...
Hey, the truth is...
They are twins.
It's not unusual for sis to get mix up!
What?
Twin brothers!
You think I'm stupid?
Daughter, you can't be such a slut.
You have shamed your family name!
Don't go.
Go after the show.
Daughter, you have to be faithful.
Love triangle can easily create
family tragedies!
Falling out every day like soap operas!
Which soap operas are you
talking about?
They are all the same!
You two stop right here. Please work.
123, 321, 1234567
Mr. And Mrs. Yu.
I'm not your daughter's boyfriend.
That "bastard" is her boyfriend.
On the count of 3, that "bastard"
Is your daughter's boyfriend, Dick Cho.
1, 2, 3
Dick, Dick...
You... have to... take care of my daughter.
You... whoever... goodbye!
Goodbye...
I sat through the whole dinner...
without knowing your name!
Oh, Yes...
Dad, mom. Go and get some sleep...
Let them say goodbye first.
- Goodbye... - Goodbye...
Goodbye...
Freeze!
I haven't finished with you yet,
who's behind this?
Sis, who cares about that
Let's just deal with him!
You bastard!
The one behind all of this, is him!
Sis... I just want you get happy. I'll call you.
Little Chu. I'm in a difficult situation too...
Wish you fortune... and happiness.
Goodbye...
This is free!
Get lost!
Don't leave, sleepover tonight!
Sleepover, what do you want?
Just trying to help.
Just see how haggard you are looking.
You'll scare your parents if you go back!
Just the two of us... how can I trust you?
Unless...
Unless what?
I'll give you the draft.
You think I'm scared?
I want to be single.
I am proud to be single.
Miss Yu.
Master wants you to put on a swimsuit...
and sunbathe with him.
Alright!
Sexual harassment!
I said swimsuit, we're not scuba diving
Can't even see your toes,
do you have to be so conservative?
I don't want you to take advantage!
Your bill. Would 100,000 dollars enough?
Luxury cars, villa, actors, crews...
Makeup, hair-stylist, costume, catering...
All need money!
That still won't cost 100,000?
Look how happy our parents were,
it's worth every penny!
OK! I'll go upstairs and
write you a cheque.
Hey... you want to run off again?
I'll change into a leopard print T-back.
Just wait for it!
No way.
Ran off again!
100,000 dollars. He's crazy!
What? This 8th generation shark suit.
It's not only pretty but
it can keep the sweat inside.
If you're interested,
I can sell it to you on the cheap.
Not fooled? Dumbass!
Shit!
The Single Woman series finished early.
Marvelous!
Of course!
You lot are still clapping?
Wanna get fired? Go to work!
Doctor Cho?
I've retired!
"I don't want to give up,
but need to remind myself"
What are you laughing at?
Is...
Is my singing bad?
What are you doing in Hong Kong?
Mandy...
and her family came for business.
I keep them company.
So why come and see me?
I want to see you!
You've seen me!
Your home's beautiful!
Why don't you let me in?
No. I've got guests!
Go!
I know you fancy me!
But I don't get why...
you are treating me like this?
Why are you talking so much? Go!
Someone asked me to tell Dick Cho,
Mandy has a birthday party tomorrow.
If you are free, come along too!
We'll see...
About that!
Don't cry. Let her go!
I'm crying because
I don't want to let her go!
It means you fancy her.
Then you should tell her how you feel!
Yes.
I don't want to see her hurt!
Young people are such chickens...
Remember, love conquers all!
Can love really conquer all?
Maybe?
- That's what TV tells us! - Yeah.
That means I should go tomorrow?
Do we need to chip in?
Don't think so!
- Then you must go! - Yes.
It's thundering outside.
I'd better sleep with you two!
Happy Birthday to Mandy,
Happy Birthday to you.
Mandy, Happy Birthday!
Bro...
I... I don't know what to say to Mandy!
And there's a lot of people...
it's embarrassing!
There's nothing to be embarrass about
in the world of love!
Tell the person you love, how you feel.
Tell her how much you love her,
it's that simple!
Okay!
Go for it!
You too!
Mandy...
- Who is it? - So loud!
Excuse me. Please go back down.
Excuse me. Please.
Excuse me!
You're here?
I wish you happy birthday.
I also wanna tell you...
I miss you so much!
Mandy, I don't know what love is?
But I know, I'm so happy...
when you're with me.
And I feel so sad...
when you're not with me!
I really miss you so much!
So much that I wake up two hours early...
just to miss you.
How about that?
The lines are such clichés!
But they are from the heart!
Alright. You don't believe me?
I'll hypnotize myself and show you.
123, 321, 1234567
Dick Cho, on the count of 3...
You're no longer a... love... therapist.
You'll only love Mandy forever.
Never lie to her!
On the count of 3, the rest of your life...
You, Dick Cho, belongs to Mandy
1, 2...
I don't want you to hypnotize yourself
to love me!
Look at me and tell me if you love me?
Mandy, I love you with all my heart!
What do you...
Want coming here today?
Tell the person I love how I feel,
that's all!
You've looked at me for half an hour,
without saying a word!
If you don't speak up, I'll go!
I...
I want to say...
Jane! Jane...
Jane!
I miss you so much!
Why didn't you look for me?
I scared that you'll get hurt!
Until my sister gets married,
bad things will happen to you!
It's dangerous!
So you're not scared now?
I... I am scared!
Listen to me!
No matter how difficult the road is,
if you want to...
We can overcome every obstacle!
Can love really conquer all?
Yes, love can conquers all!
Are you okay?
Fine. How about you?
I'm fine!
Love... really can conquer all!
Love really can conquer all!
I wonder how Mandy is doing,
let's go downstairs.
Jane, no matter what happens,
I'll stay by your side!
What's that sound?
Oh shit!
You two are so smart,
very quick learners.
Come on... let's bet 100 dollars per game,
that's not too much.
- Alright... - Alright...
This is yours.
You're... here to collect my debt?
He's not here for your debt!
Dick's here to teach us play
"Fight the Landlord".
Yes... he's the Landlord in this game.
Okay. Let's start.
Let's have "The Plane", beat that?
- No... - No...
Ace full house, beat that?
- No. - No.
Three of a kind with 4, beat that?
If not, then I'll win.
What?
- Honey, do you have anything?
- Too bad!
Do you?
So what is this?
Isn't this "Bomb"?
Yes!
Bomb him!
- I'll bomb him. - You go.
1st bomb!
If four of a kind is a bomb,
then this is too!
The 2nd bomb 2nd bomb!
I also have, the 3rd bomb!
Four of a kind again?
This is, the 4th bomb... 4th bomb!
And the 5th!
So... so many bombs?
This is even better, the 6th bomb!
You want me to play a single card?
Great.
2!
Does it need to be the highest rank card?
Now you mention it...
Aren't the jokers the highest?
Yes. They're the highest!
Then that's it!
We won?
We win!
We each win 100 dollars!
100 dollars, we've won 100 dollars...
That's not it!
7 bombs mean 12,800 dollars each!
12,800 dollars?
12,800 dollars...
I'm busy. I've got to go!
We'll play next time.
Great...
Hey... hey...
This is yours.
That mahjong box looks familiar.
It's your dad's. After the bank run...
Yes. I don't trust the banks anymore.
So I took out all my money,
and put it in that box
Then stuffed it under the bed!
So why did you let him take it away?
He bought us some stocks.
Yes...
How much?
One million. One million.
Bastard, I only owed you 100,000,
you scammed 1 million!
Hey! Hey!
The number you have dialed
does not exist
Does not exist?
Conman...
Conman!
Conman ~ ~ ~
She has suffered a heavy blow.
Her looks may change.
Prepare yourself!
Jane! Jane... say something! Jane!
Jane...
Doctor, is this stocking for reshaping
her face?
No!
Sorry. I mixed up!
This is a bank robber injured during
a robbery!
The cops said it's evidence and
can't be removed.
She's next door.
This is your girlfriend!
Okay!
Jane?
Doctor, how come?
God's will, maybe!
Not everything can be explained...
in this world!
But why has she got makeup on?
I was a beautician before
I became a doctor.
It's just occupational habits!
But how could she be looking like this?
You're not satisfied? I can undo it!
No...
No!
Okay? I'm leaving!
Thank you very much, doctor.
Jane.
What is it?
You don't like how I look?
Jane, I'll always remember...
how beautiful you looked!
I guess, I'll just have to settle with
this face!
I have important new,
the company is going down!
And I have made a smart decision...
Jumping ship!
The new boss will be here soon.
I'm already fired.
So, most probably
all of you will be fired too.
That's all!
Hope we'll meet again. Bye.
- What should we do?
Calm down, calm down.
Finished, what should we do>
It's all yours!
You scum!
Why take it out on my family,
I can pay you back!
Why scammed all my parents money?
Listen to me first.
Everybody. I'm boss of "Happy Online",
and your new boss.
You can call me L.
Don't worry.
We won't close down for now.
The company's structure is the same.
Your salary will increase by 20%.
Bravo!
Except for her!
Her Single Woman series...
from the 2nd to the 7th book
With a gift, have sold less than
70 copies in Hong Kong.
I've read them. It's all about hatred,
revenge...
Pessimistic views of life,
incorrect values of love.
They are... just... pure... evil!
What the hell! Putting me down in front of
all these people.
You want a fight!
Let me finish.
But, the special issue on travelling in
Qiandao Lake...
Is really top notch!
She uses the most innovative way
Blending two love stories happen...
at Qiandao Lake,
To describe the customs of the place.
Brilliant!
Therefore,
I wanna put it into "Happy Online".
I believe this new add-on will sell
very well.
The happiest news is,
I've just received a statistic report
The first issue has an order of
2 million copies.
The company rises from the dead!
Miss Yu is great!
Thank you...
To be honest, this book...
Let me finish! What's precious is that...
She reviewed the cup of...
"Love's like a Tide"
Made by her love rival,
and even praised it sincerely.
Which proves she has conscience!
That's is why their boss had to come
and thank you.
Miss Yu, thank you so much!
It's okay.
My daughter.
Your girlfriend?
My daughter!
Impossible. She's beautiful!
Like her dad!
Kid, you dare hypnotize yourself
To fight for Mandy's heart.
It shows your love is true.
I think you know what love is!
Let water go under the bridge and
be good to Mandy.
Or you'll get fired!
Got it!
Yes, you be nice to her!
Just shut it.
You're evil and dictatorial.
A control freak with weird habits...
Have you said enough?
I'm not finished!
For all those cons and...
all those I haven't even said...
I like them, for a long time!
Because I'm your real fan!
What do you wanna do?
Will you marry me?
Where's your wife?
That bitch ran away with another guy!
So I devoted myself to work,
until I met you.
Say yes,
and let me be the happiest man
in the world!
Hey, why did you scam
my parents' money?
He didn't scam us!
The stocks he bought us
Cost 1 cent and
when it closed its risen to 7.8 dollars!
We're rich!
Sis...
Sis, get married,
let me get on with my life!
Yeah.
He's hardworking, loves your family...
Loyal, handsome,
sexy with smooth skin and wear glasses
Worth a try!
Honestly, you two are a perfect match!
Really?
Look at him. You can tell...
He listens to his wife!
Yeah, same as me!
The diamond is small!
I knew that!
I can compromise!
What do you mean?
She means yes!
Are you okay?
Weak in the knees!
We're here to join in the fun.
Yeah...
So many guests here today.
Tom Hanks, and Tom Cruise...
And Julia Roberts.
Really?
Really!
But caught the wrong flight to Russia.
Damn!
Doesn't matter. They're here.
Being a groom again?
Great. Congratulations!
Thank you.
Your bird's nest hairstyle is so cool.
- Congratulations!
- Thank you, thank you...
Mr. Yen! Thank you...
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Thank you...
Congratulations...
Congratulations to you.
Thank you.
Congratulations, boss.
May you have a blessed baby soon.
Who's that guy? So passionate.
Isn't he what... Yen?
Bhutan?
Yeah, why didn't we get marry in Bhutan?
Isn't Qiandao Lake better!
Where ever it is, it's news to celebrate!
Exactly!
Congratulations.
Thank you...
Happy together
Good luck forever
Every day is better
Happy Chinese New Year!
Brought to you by
DLAznMovies.com