Here is the police station.
Now we are  in accordance with the law to interrogate you
for the relevant case.
You have the right to remain silent.
If you give up that right
anything you say can and will be used against you
in a court of law.
Are you clearly？
Umm...yeah
Kitty, do you know the deceased Mark?
Umm....Well....
What is your relationship with Mark?
We....We...We are just friends.
You and Mark are not just common friends.
Ten million dollars are not a penny!
Tell me the truth!
We have found the loan which has
your signature in safe deposit box of Mark.
No！this is not the case！
Let me tell you the whole thing！
I did not kill mark！I just passed by.
Please believe me, I did not kill him！
Trust me！
Kitty, I only asked the relationship between you and Mark,.
I did not doubt you, why are you so nervous?
Oh, hmmm?
Are you guilty?
I am sorry for Mark‘s death,
but we have locked in the criminal suspect.
Once other evidence is collected,
we will provide it to the prosecution immediately.
Officer, please tell me, who killed my son?
Please, please don't be angry.
After our investigation,
we found Kitty has a great suspicious.
Because we found her fingerprint from the Mark's body
and the 10 million HK dollars lent in Mark's home.
The murderer who killed my son is Kitty.
I order you to shoot her immediately!
(Poloceman : How can I push this old man clam down?)
Don't be angry.
Kitty is just a criminal suspect.
According to the law,
the police officer can't shoot anybody at will.
But our officers will try to find new clues
don’t worry and we will give you a fair.
I don't care!
I don’t care what your rules are!
This is blood for blood!
My son is died!
I just need the murderer to pay her whole life！
Mark's father: Why are you here?
Uncle, I'm sorry to bother you.
But today I come to tell you a cruel truth.
It is my husband who murdered your son.
The blind is innocent.
Umm...The cop informed me that my son was murdered
by the bloody blind whore!
Because of money! Money!!!
The bloody whore owed my son 10 million HK dollars!
Why are your husband? Why your husband???
You must tell me everything you know!
This is what happened.
Your son and my husband joined the Morgan Stanley
at the same time.
Bloody Jesus! Jesus!
I'm going to kill this son of a whore!
I'm going to cut up his penis! His Penis!
This cocksucker has no balls!
He is a eunuch! The eunuch has no honor!
He will get burnt in the hell!
Hello
Yes, it is me.
OK, I got it.
Ms, is the deceased Jack your husband?
Yes, officer
Umm....Well..
Ms, please answer the questions truthfully to us.
We will record them.
OK.
Ms, how many years have you married with Jack?
Have you got any children?
We have been married for 8 years.
We have no child.
OK. Do you get on well with him in your daily life?
Umm... Do you have some words with him？
We got on well with each other in our marriage.
He was so busy with working that
seldom had break to stay at home.
And we never argue with each other.
OK, we finished.
Thank you for your cooperation.
OK, officer, see you.
Why don’t you talk to me?
Didn't you have sex with the blind bitch?
How dare you! You call her fucking sweety?
Are you cooking shits?
You gross fatty!
I m talking to you?
Why you don't answer my questions?
(Daisy: Oh, Why my husband doesn't love me anymore?)
(Daisy: I need my handsome lover Mark.)
Daisy: "Where are you, Mark？
Can you meet me now?"
I think we should break up.
Daisy: "What did you say? Why?"
I say, we should break up.
This relationship should be end. Understand?
Daisy: "Don't do this, please!"
You can't do that! You can't! I really love you!"
OK, Stop! Anything else?
Daisy: "Please. Let me see you the last time, okay? Please!"
Oh....Ok, the last time.
( Mark: I'm awesome!)
Daisy: Mark!
Daisy: After I get my husband's property,
we can live togther, and... buy a big house.
Policeman: Yes, we can go to Europe, maybe Italy.
Daisy: That is a good idea.
Policeman: Ok, ok baby, my sweety.
I'm going to give you another glass of  wine.
Please wait for me, love you.