Come on, frank. Old movie,
popcorn--it'll be fun.
ElI, I can't help but notice, we--we seem to
be spending a lot of time together lately and--
are you breaking up with me?
- Look, if you're lonely...
- I'm not lonely.
I have this patient--
fun, great personality...
hey, if I wanted to spend
three hours having a long,
uncomfortable conversation
full of awkward pauses,
I'd go out for a meal with my mother.
What's she seeing you for anyway?
- Acupuncturist/client privilege, dude.
- Come on.
She's trying to quit smoking. Did
I mention she's almost a nonsmoker?
I'm not interested.
Maybe just give her a call.
patti?
Eli, she's innocent.
Who's innocent, patti?
- Down in front!
- What?
Yeah, sure thing. I'll tell him.
- The next joint?
- Yeah, sure.
patti, where are you? I've been trying
you all morning.
Don't worry. Everything's fine.
I just--I-I wanted
to ask you something.
I see you're not at your desk.
This is gonna sound peculiar, but I was
wondering if maybe you needed my help.
Hold on. Slow down. What? Come on.
- you're not making any sense.
- Patti. Patti!
well, I'm leaving now.
I'll see you there.
- Is everything all right?
- I'm taking a sick day.
Are you okay? Who were you talking to?
Angela's roommate.
- Angela was arrested.
- Angela was arrested?
- Another D.U.I.?
- Wh-- another D.U.I.?
Repeat what someone says one more time...
two weeks ago, angela
got pinched for a D.U.I.
I got it kicked, but apparently...
she got arrested again?
The cops came to her apartment.
They handcuffed her and
dragged her out like a criminal.
Now please, I have got
to get to bryant street.
We're coming with you.
Uh, you asked for my help, so...
no, I didn'T.
Well, obviously you need some help,
and you know two great attorneys
who would love to help you,
so we're coming with you, okay? Come on.
Huevos rancheros?
I see your pregnancy cvings have
taken a dramatic turn for the spicy.
Actually, you're the one who was supposed
to be eating them
at your breakfast meeting with jorge navarro.
Was that this morning?
Well, now it's tomorrow morning.
Just make sure and mention how painful
it was when your crown fell out.
It's not like you to
forget a meeting, dad.
These days I'm burning
my candle at both ends.
Between a full day of depositions
and financial meetings,
I must put in an appearance at
the osterhagen benefit luncheon.
Could I interest you in a
half-baked speech followed by squab?
couldn't interest ellen in that one, huh?
No, not this time.
Well, you know how I love a good squab,
but matt and I are going to
find out what's going on in here.
Yes, the sonogram.
Are you gonna find out the sex?
It's a little too early to find out
whether you could buy it a baseball mitt.
It's never too early for that.
case number 0-8-1-2-1-9-7-2,
people V. Scott.
What's he doing here?
Helping you, angie. We both are.
Keith bennett and eli stone of wethersby, stone
& associates for the defendant, your honor.
Waive reading, plead not guilty.
Actually, keith, I think u're gonna
want to hear the charges on this.
Defendant is chargedwith three counts each of
felony drug theft and narcotics trafficking.
The defendant stole
fentanyl,
a highly addictive and powerful synthetic
opiate from a teaching hospital
where she is a medical student.
Our plea still tands. Not guilty on all
charges. Move to release on recognizance.
She's charged with six major drug felonies,
for which she faces very significant
prison time.
She's not going anywhere.
I'll vouch for that.
Like you vouched last time?
All right, I'm setting bail
at $500,000 cash or bond.
I'll post the bond myself.
very sporting of you, mr. Stone.
She's innocent, judge.
Save it for your closing.
www.1000fr.com presents
eli stone  S02 E07
Capture:FRM@ÏÄ·ç
Sync:FRS@»¨
????I am not a drug trafficker.
We believe you, angela.
Mom?
Yes, of course, sweetheart.
Why do they think you stole the drugs?
I don't know. It's all lies.
So you've never been in the drug
supply room at your hospital?
Of course I have. I work at a hospital.
It's what I do every day,
at least a dozen times a day.
Do you remember anything about the
night they say you stole the fentanyl?
I checked out 20 milligram-prednisone
tablets for S.Henderson's arthritis,
100 micrograms of levothyroxine
for mr. Flynn's thyroid condition,
and 600 milligrams of l-dopa
for mr. Zachry's parkinson'S.
Those are some pretty specific memories
for something you do every day,
at least a dozen times a day.
Gee, keith, maybe a good memory's
one of the reasons I'm a student
at one of the top medical
schools in the country.
It's true. She has a
memory like an elephant.
So the school suspended and investigated
you, the police arrested you,
the D.A.'S prosecuting you--
all for no reason?
I don't know what their reason is.
I just know I'm not guilty.
It's not your job to figure
out what their case here is.
It's ours.
taylor, hi. Congratulations.
Thanks, dr. Lenz.
And you must be...
who are you?
- A friend.
- Uh, boyfriend.
Our relationship's sort of undefined.
Uh, basically I'm the guy not important
enough to leave on the intake form.
Well, he's the biological father.
- That makes you plenty important.
- Thank you.
ready to see your baby?
Should I turn away if you
guys want to look down...
right.
oh, my god.
See there? That's your baby's heart.
That's unbelievable.
Everything looks perfect.
you two done good.
- perfect timing.
- You wanted to see me, paul?
Maggie dekker, meet ashley cardiff.
Nice to meet you.
As you know, cardiff refineries is
one of our firm's biggest clients.
That's my father and grandfather.
They're the ones who live to crack open the
earth like a pita and steal all its candy.
But ashley doesn't have
the same family sweet tooth,
since she has asked us to set up a
charitable trust for arctic wildlife
damaged by her family's pipeline.
Well, not every woman likes to eat
moose burgers and shoot polar bears.
No. Good for you.
- Paul, could I talk to you for a second?
- Yeah.
Excuse us.
When mr. Posner and ms.Klein
brought me to this firm
and put me in charge of
the pro bono department,
they agreed that I could
prioritize my own cases.
Is it possible we're sleeping together,
ms.Dekker, and I don't know it?
No.
So why would you think I care very
much about what you like or dislike?
I am the assigning partner.
You will do this, and yowill
do this to the best of your...
well, whatever ability
mr. Posner sees in you.
This job sucks.
Cardiff refineries treats the
environment like a port-a-potty,
and now i have to help daughter
warbucks buy her way to a conscience.
i mean, what is it about
the rich that makes them think
that they can just buy their way
into being good people?
probably the tons of money.
you notice whenever the press
writes about her,
they call her the "heiress" ashley cardiff?
that's what she does.
that's--that's her job.
heiress.
you didn't hear a word of that just now.
taylor and i went to the doctor today.
is the baby all right?
yeah. Yeah. Seeing the little heart go...
it's really in there.
that's a good day, matt.
yeah, it should have been.
it was... Really strange.
whatever the hell taylor and i are,
it would have been nice to know before
going in for something like that.
it couldn't have been
more uncomfortable.
maybe it would help
if you... Defined things.
i asked her to marry me.
don't worry. She said no.
i was trying to do the right thing.
she doesn't need you to do
the right thing, spike.
she just wants you to love her.
that's all any woman wants, really.
that hasn't been????
but i do have those feelings for her.
and in the sense that you've
said the words "i love you"?
not in so many words...particularly,
those specific words.
matt, she's having your baby.
don't you think that she might want
to hear the actual three little words?
yeah, i know, it's just, those actual
three little words are... Big.
you're gonna be a father, matt.
it's all big from here on out.
all right, let's get back to work.
i've told you and eli everything i know.
i'll tell you when you've told
us everything you know.
so did you tell my mom?
about how you think i was doing cocaine
the night i was pulled over?
all right, for the record,
it wasn't me who suspected you of
doing coke. it was in your blood work.
and, no, i didn't tell patti.
attorney client.
plus, what she knows about
you... Isn't my business.
did you tell eli?
what he knows about you is
very much my business.
did you also tell him that the test
results returned a false positive?
i told him that's what you
told me. he even believed it.
it's the truth!
yeah, well, your denials
carried a lot more weight
before you got popped
for possession with intent.
so you do think i'm guilty.
i worked ten plus years
in the public defender's office.
most of my clients
were guilty as charged,
but not one of 'em ever got
anything less than my "a" game.
well, aren't you a big man?
- i didn't say i was--
- i'm not finished.
i want you to believe in me,
not some principle.
and if you can't do that,
well, then you can go to hell.
i saw you yawn. there should be no yawning
on my daughter's case.
ah, don't worry. i yawned because i'm tired,
not because i'm bored.
how are things looking?
good.
shaky.
the d.a.--um, she can make this case.
i-i've seen people go to jail
on a lot weaker evidence.
but their case has holes,
and i'll make them wider.
okay.
how are you holding up?
i went to church...
this morning to pray for angela.
my girl is my reason for being.
everything in my life has been
for her life, and, um...
now they're saying she's a junkie,
and, um...thief.
- i want to believe her.
- we're gonna get through this, patti.
oh, i'm not crying because of that.
i got the message.
- what message were you talking about?
- from you.
the voice mail asking me if i needed help
before i found out that angela was arrested.
you knew i needed help before i did.
did you get a message, too?
like--like with the earthquake
or when you saved jordan?
yeah.
- and it told you to--to help angela?
- not just that, patti, it...
told me...that angela is innocent.
- she is?
- she is.
well, then you get to work
and do as you're told.
- yes, ma'am.
- oh.
???
are stored in automated pyxis machines,
which require a fingerprint i.d. To open.
access to the machine and each individual
drug are automatically recorded in a log.
i imagine that the drug the defendant
is charged with stealing--fentanyl--
is accessed routinely by
many doctors in your hospital.
yes, but miss scott was the only one
to withdraw fentanyl without a m.a.r.--
a medical administration record.
which means what?
she wasn't accessing the drug
for a specific patient.
is that the only reason you had
to suspend miss scott?
angela's behavior had
become increasingly erratic,
her grades were in decline,
and she was persistently
stressed and moody.
these are classic signs
of drug dependency.
so angela scott is the only person in your
ntire hospital who is stressed and moody?
it sounds like disneyland is in danger
of losing its distinction of being
"the happiest place on earth."
object to the sarcasm.
i'm sorry, your honor.
i was going for ridicule.
is it your testimony that
angela scott was the only doctor
seen removing fentanyl from the pyxis machine
on the three nights in question?
in point of fact, no one actually witnessed
the fentanyl being removed.
sounds like an ironclad case.
that was sarcasm, your honor.
your next witness, miss jarrells.
the people call s.f.p.d. Officer
jerome sawyer--
objection.
officer sawyer recently arrested
the defendant
on suspicion of driving
under the influence of alcohol.
- objection. Move to strike.
- move for a mistrial.
evidence of prior bad acts is
not even remotely admissible.
it is, to establish motive.
we believe that the defendant
traded the fentanyl for cocaine,
which was indicated
in the d.u.i. Blood test.
she's saying this crap in front
of the jury, your honor.
move for a mistrial.
i can't do that, mr. Bennett,
because the a.d.a. Is right on this.
The prior charge and the blood test go
to motive and are therefore admissible.
are you doing cocaine?
the night of my d.u.i.,
there was a party after exams,
and someone had coke.
i had never tried it before. i know.
i know it was a mistake.
and getting behind the wheel of a car
--that was another mistake.
i am so sorry, eli.
i know how disappointing this all is,
but it--it was just one time,
one night. It's not who i am,
and it doesn't mean i stole those drugs,
which i didn't.
please, don't give up on me. please?
i-i know you didn't do this,
but i also know that we're gonna
lose this trial
unless you stop fighting us
and start fighting back.
sean binder. that--that's
who gave me the coke.
would he have had access
to the fentanyl?
yes, definitely.
i'll bring h in for a chat.
you don't like me, do you?
what? no. No.
well, i mean, we--we just met,
but no, you seem... Lovely.
dad said he liked this firm
because there were good lawyers
who were good liars.
i'm used to people not liking me,
miss dekker.
um, excuse me. i have to take this.
wealthy heiress, life of leisure,
a father who's been ravaging
the environment,
and now she's trying to buy a conscience
by giving away some of her ill-gotten gains.
truth be told, i wouldn't
like me either.
Sorry.
good news?
oh, it's just.. Private.
he's been trying to find the perfect moment to
finally tell his pregnant girlfriend he loves her.
it's just, for taylor,
i need to go epic.
i don't remember the last time
a guy wanted to go epic for me.
her favorite singer's in town
for a concert,
but it's completely
and predictably sold out.
and i've even been bidding
for a pair of tickets on ebay,
but i have a feeling the guy
with the e-mail "sealtixordeath"
isn't gonna let me
just walk away with them.
seal--heidi's husband?
i could call her for you.
- heidi klum?
- yeah.
- you--you would do that for me?
- is this one worth it?
surprisingly, yes.
if there's one thing i've
learned, you can't buy love,
but you can, at the very least,
comp house seats.
- start liking her.
- heidi, hi.
this is very awkward.
i got a call from ted broden in accounting,
and since we were tightening our belts,
he cautioned me against using the company
credit card to book a hotel room.
i didn't know what he was talking
about at first until i realized
he'd called the wrong wethersby.
and you thought i was using firm money
to finance a pied- -terre
for extramarital activities.
honestly, that was only one of
two possibilities i could think of,
and i was sort of hoping there was a
...third better explanation.
i'm sorry, but there isn't.
i have been living in a hotel of late.
daddy.
your stepmother and i came to the mutual
decision to take some time apart.
i'm so sorry, dad.
after my accident, things were better
than they'd been in some time,
as if we both realized we'd been given
a second chance at marital bliss.
but as i've been--i hope the word is
"evolving"--
ellen and i have...drifted.
dad, why don't you come
and stay with me tonight?
it should come as no surprise that i'm not
the sort of man to "crash" at anyone's pad,
but thank you for the offer.
can i at least offer you a hug?
that would be gratefully accepted.
who are you?
his name's mark young. nice offices.
- where's sean binder?
- we don't need sean binder.
- yes, we do. Angela--
- lied, eli, again, as usual.
so what does he have to do
with angela's case?
tell him.
this is like attorney client
secrets time, right?
i had to ask all of five people
on campus how to find you.
you think the d.a. Can't or won't do
the exact same thing?
or should i ring him up
right now, save him the legwork?
i'm ange's dealer.
at least i was
till she ran out of bank.
and i was gonna cut her off, but then
she offered something to trade.
the fentanyl.
yeah, the stuff's like gold
on the street.
show him.
angela called him
a dozen times last month. Look.
get outta here.
we need to try and plead this.
what if he's covering for
someone else or setting her up?
- what the hell's
- you don't know her, keith.
she's a drug addict, eli.
no one knows her anymore.
i'm not looking to hurt angela,
all right? I like her.
i thought maybe even we...
look, i know you want her not to have
done this, but as her friend, as her lawyer,
you--you can't ignore the truth just
because you wish it wasn't so.
why do you still believe her?
it was...revealed to me.
- revealed?
- mm-hmm.
um, i know you believe certain things,
and--and that's--that's fine...
so long as it doesn't prevent you from seeing
what's right in front of your face.
angela's guilty,
and if you can't see that,
then we can't help her.
didn't i tell you not to show up here again
until you called that girl
whose number i gave you?
well, sorry. I, uh, had a lot on my plate.
finding out that patti's daughter
is a drug dealer with a coke habit
hasn't really left me much time
for blind dating, so...
well, i'm sorry, eli,
but you're not gonna like or even understand
every message you're tasked to deliver.
well, that sucks.
this is gonna destroy patti.
i swore to her that angela
was innocent, but she's not.
how do i deliver that message?
patti's strong. she'll persevere.
she has family. She has you.
yeah, i'm not sure how much good
having me is doing anyone.
anyone who gets close to me gets
kicked in the spiritual ass.
wait a second. is that why you don't
want to go out on this date?
i-i don't need any more soul-broken
people on my conscience.
eli, you've helped a lot of
people through some hard times.
what, like, uh, taylor? i helped her
by breaking off our engagement. Hmm?
or maybe you meant maggie, who i helped
out of her engagement and the firm.
or grace, who i helped
out of the country.
you think any of those people
think that they're better off
for the full and total
eli stone experience?
i do.
????is gonna bring you closer to
people, not further from them.
it's about connecting.
i've always been connected to patti.
she hasn't just recently
believed in eli the prophet.
she has always believed in just eli--
eli the lawyer, eli the jerk, eli,
the friend who is family.
i violated her trust.
i still can't believe
you got these tickets.
well, stone's not the only one
who can perform miracles.
besides, i know a guy
who knows a guy who knows seal.
it's the best gift. thank you.
yeah. Well, you're most welcome.
i wanted tonight to be special.
and why is that?
to tell you...
every night with you is special.
careful. that almost sounded sensitive.
i know this thing of ours hasn't unfolded
in t recommended... Order.
we've skipped some beats.
pole-vaulted over beats,
actually, but, um,
just because it's happened quickly...
doesn't mean it hasn't happened.
i love you, taylor.
ladies and gentlemen, seal.
what do you want me to say,
matt?
uh, i don't know. i guess i was
expecting--call this crazy--
an "i love you, too." that's usually
how this goes.
it does when the other person
feels it, but i...
i just don't know if i do,
and i-i don't think it's fair
to say those words--even--
even with your child inside me--if...
They're not what i feel.
you're the dude.
what?
a hot pregnant dude, sure, but in
our relationship, you're the dude.
okay, i don't--i don't know
what that's supposed to mean.
i'm actually the mature one here,
which is another first for me.
but it's you...
you're the one who's afraid
to share her feelings.
u're the one who keeps pushing me away.
well, surprise, surprise, i'm in touch
with my feminine side.
maybe you should get in touch with yours.
hope you liked the concert.
- matt.
- what's with the face?
the faces? Who died?
does this have anything
to do with angela?
patti, uh, i made a mistake.
- angela is not--
- no.
- uh, she stole the drugs from the hospital.
- no!
she gave them to a dealer named mark young
to clear up a drug debt.
your daughter has
a substance abuse problem.
that's not possible, eli. you told me...
you said he told you--
i'm sorry, patti. you know,
i-i love angie.
i didn't want to believe it either.
believe what?
you look me in the eye, and you tell me
the truth, so help you god!
am i on the witness stand now?
did you talk to sean binder?
- he's the one who--
- stop lying!
now you need help, baby, but first,
you need to stop lying.
okay, mom.
your daughter's a drug addict.
she loves getting high.
this is not you. this--this isn't you.
how would you know, mom?
you don't know anything about me.
all you ever saw was
what you wanted me to be,
needed me to be.
god, the pressure
you put on me to be perfect!
"i'm not raising ordinary kids."
like you're so special.
you're a damn secretary.
yes, i'm a secretary who worked my ass off,
taking crap year after year,
weekends, nights,
so you could get opportunities
i never even dreamed of.
- i didn't ask for any of it!
- you didn't have to ask for it.
- i'm your mother.
- i didn't ask for that either!
if you werehalfthe mother
you think you are...
you would know how unhappy i am.
how...how unhappy i've been
for a long time.
but you didn't want to see it...
because of your own problem, mom.
i guess this apple didn't
fall far from the tree.
patti...
what'd she mean by...
she meant both of us
never needed you more
and were never more wrong
to put our faith in you.
- eli.
- hey.
i thought i was the only one here.
you're here late.
i prefer the office to be empty before i indulge
in my obsession with internet backgammon.
and why are you
burning the midnight oil?
patti.
i've been trying her all night, and she
doesn't pick up or won't.
she has your home number, i'm sure.
used to think that nothing
could get to her.
but today, she was...
she was gotten to.
i'm not in the habit
of breaking confidences, eli,
but you know i love patti
as much as you do.
and given the manner and magnitude
of her daughter's troubles,
you should know something.
she has a problem, too?
yes.
- Alcohol was her particular vice.
- "was"--you mean,
to my knowledge. This was years
ago, before you joined the firm,
back when she was my secretary.
her work had deteriorated,
when she even came to work.
one afternoon, i received
a phone call from a local bar.
patti had overstayed her welcome.
i went down there
and found her inebriated.
i told her she had to get help,
or i'd fire her.
so she got help then?
i believe the term is
"dry, not sober."
she just stopped drinking.
and you think that what's happening
with angela has maybe...
pushed her off the wagon?
i think recovery programs
give addicts tools to rely on
to get them through
difficult times--tools...
patti may not have.
you don't remember the name
of that bar, do you?
why do i get the feeling...
- you're not just going to the gym?
- get away from me, keith.
you gonna send eli the bond he'll forfeit
when you jump bail?
Or how about at least an address so your--
your mom knows which city morgue
to collect your body at?
i'm not going to prison.
you think that's the worst thing
that can happen to you?
Wrong.
you take off, things are
only gonna get worse.
w--your mom's right.
you are not yourself right now.
so tell me, which angela
do you want to be?
the druggiskell who blames her mother for
her mistakes or the woman with brains
and--and spirit, the woman who scored a-a scholarship
to the best med school in the state,
the woman i know can find
her way through this.
look, all the lies you told,
i never believed you,
but that's not the same thing
as not believing in you.
this is not court, keith, okay?
a pretty speech is
not gonna fix this.
no, and you got a lot to fix.
but i know you can.
just stop...stop trying
to prove me wrong.
what?
- what can i get for ya?
- her tab.
well, it's been a long time
since a man bought me a drink.
how gallant.
so...
did jordan open his big mouth, or did god
send a vision i needed a designated driver?
billy ocean got that hit
about driving a car.
how many times did i talk to you about
my father? about his drinking problem?
why did you think
i wouldn't understand?
i am not a drunk, eli.
in case you haven't noticed,
i am having a bad week.
i don't need you coming here uninvited,
trying to make me feel worse,
when all i'm doing is trying to make
myself feel a little better.
so how's that working out for ya?
- my daughter...
- is in trouble, a world of it.
she has a drug problem,
and she may go to prison.
she needs you now. but... Not like this.
she was right, eli.
it's--it's--it's my fault.
i pushed her too much. and look at me.
i'm a fraud.
i am a fraud.
she must have felt
so alone.
i left my baby alone.
this isn't her fault, none of it.
it's mine.
eli...she's innocent.
i've been angry
and--and confused...real angry.
but i'm not anymore, 'cause...
'cause i get it now.
all the people that i've been asked
to help, all those, uh, strangers...
now i get to help
someone that i love.
and i really want to help you, patti.
but you--you gotta want my help.
probation, following rehab.
2,000 hours community service at the free
medical clinic in the mission district.
- but no jail?
- no jail.
what about medical school?
golden state won't take her back,
but if angela really wants to be a doctor,
she'll find a way.
how did you manage all this, eli?
when i was a public defender,
i represented a bad guy accused
of cutting up his girlfriend.
jarrells was the d.a. The cops
couldn't find the knife.
i got the case tossed.
what does that got to do
with angela's case?
the cops recently received an anonymous tip
with the knife's whereabouts.
the d.a. Was grateful.
- so we accept the terms?
- yes. Yes.
thank you... Both.
thank you.
i'm so sorry for what i said.
i didn't mean those things.
it's okay...even if you did.
some of it is true.
i love you, angela...
so much that my teeth hurt sometimes.
okay. you're not a child anymore,
and i cannot fix all of your problems,
especially when i have some big ones of my own.
so... Maybe we help each other.
you were right about angela...
the whole time.
i should have trusted
your instincts.
who could blame you? you know, it's hard
to compete with the big guy.
yeah. maybe god could be a little less
indirect next time.
actually, i meant john lennon.
i'll tell you, though,
what i wouldn't give
to see what you see
just once.
eli, care to join me for dinner?
oh, uh, actually, i...
i'm just--i'm going on a blind date.
- mm.
- i...
makes sense. I appear to have run out of
daughters and associates for you to romance.
are you okay?
It's just--i've--i've noticed
lots of late nights,
and you got nothing better to do
than grab a bite with me.
ellen and i have separated.
wow.
sorry. I... Uh, is there
anything i can do?
a tale of woe for another night.
you have someone waiting.
and, eli,
when you and i do grab a bite, it won't be
because i have nothing better to do.
you're speechless. it's gotta be a first.
i think we've said or not said all there
is to say or not say.
what you said last night--it--it couldn't
have been easy taking a chance like that,
and i'm sorry, i am so sorry,
i couldn't take that leap with you.
like you said, you can't
say what you don't feel.
no, but i should have said what i am ??
i should have said that i...
don't know if i love you...yet.
yeah, there's a reason no one's
ever written a hit song
called "i don't know if i love you yet."
i'm my father's daughter, matt.
sharing my feelings with someone
is very difficult for me.
and the one time i actually did
truly open my heart to someone,
he... Broke off our engagement.
and then came "the dowd"--
a guy i didn't even think i'd give a drawer
to in my apartment, and...
it's taken me a while
to make that switch...
but i'm making it.
i only know one thing,
that you and me...
but especily me...
we're never gonna survive
unless...
we get a little crazy.
how'd you...
i know people who know people who know maggie,
who knows people who know seal.
forget "like." i think i love you.
at's the point of being
a disgustingly rich heiress
if you can't do stuff like this, right?
now this is epic. Thank you.
????
welcome.
welcome to www.1000fr.com
- sorry i'm late. I'm eli.
- i'm ashley.
hi, ashley. have you been waiting long?
no, not at all.
- you look beautiful.
- thank you.