This programme contains
strong language and scenes
of a sexual nature.
I found these keys last time
I was here. Are they yours?
Never seen them before.
And who's Alma Carter?
Is she my mother?
Alma Carter's not interested.
She didn't want you.
Who's that then?
It's Hayley, the fit intern.
She's been flirting with me non stop.
Hayley?
Tell her to take the day
off tomorrow, right? And ring me.
I had to fire her. You
recommended her. She's your protege.
I'm Tess, Chloe's ex.
Who the hell are you? Shona.
Were you seeing her
before you finished with me?
Is there anything
I need to worry about?
You... you and Frankie,
you go back a long way...
She's a friend, that's all.
Is there someone? Anyone?
Cat... It's always been Cat.
Oh, my god!
Oh! Oh, god!
Morning.
I think I love you...
I'm sorry.
No...
I like it.
Do you just like it, hm?
Or...
I need to go to work.
I feel your heat, but cannot touch.
A lonely moon orbiting the sun.
The gravity between us,
The only thing stopping me
from falling back to earth...
Audition script? Sorry.
I wish. No, it's Ed's book.
Well, first draft. It's really good.
You sound surprised. Well,
I'm not, but I mean, really good,
like a proper book you'd
pay money for and everything.
It's about these two scientists
working on a space station...
and he really loves her
but he can't do anything
about it because she might
be from this race of aliens they're
researching and he might be a robot.
It's brilliant. Brilliant...
So, um...
did you and Jay stay up
long after I crashed?
Not really.
Cos I got up in the middle of
the night to get a drink and...
You saw. I couldn't help it.
Yeah, well, it was nothing.
It was Jay! He's a man! He's...
he's got, like, bits. It's just like
a strap-on without the strap.
Aagh! What...
but what about Becky?
How's she going to find out?
Well, I won't tell her. Neither
am I, and I doubt Jay's going to
be shouting it from the rooftops.
We were drunk, it felt like a
good idea at the time. All right.
As long as you're not
going all hasbian on me.
Becky throw you out early
or something? No, no.
I didn't stay there last night.
Thanks.
Everything all right? Uh-hum.
I just thought you two were
in training for domestic bliss.
When did you know?
That you loved her?
Why you asking me that?
When does anyone know?
You're a keeper, you tell me.
Morning.
How's the hangover?
All right, yeah. I think I...
got away with it. I just got to go...
photocopy these things.
I didn't expect you in today.
You walked in on them?
No, the door was open.
They're actually having an affair?
No! Apparently it was
just a one night thing.
Has Frankie always been...
Well, she's always been out with
girls but I know she's fucked
a couple of guys here and there.
Is that...
I mean, have you ever?
And Jay? Jay'd probably
fuck you if you had tits.
What is this?
Early birthday present.
Argh, you remembered.
But you're not allowed to open it.
I'm going to open it!
Ah!
Ah, that's so sweet!
Thank you.
It's you and me, Mykonos '08! Yeah.
Look at your pasty little chest.
So what we doing for it?
Er, there's not much to celebrate.
It's your 30th!
Exactly.
By now I was supposed to be
guesting onstage having already
built up a Hollywood fan base.
Instead it's like I'm in some
shit version of Groundhog Day.
It's not that bad.
Well. So we're what, successful?
There's no point dressing it up.
But what am I doing about it?
What are you doing about it?
You've got this great book...
Did you read it? Yeah.
And? It's brilliant.
But instead of getting it out
there you're here drinking tea.
Where's the drive,
the bloody-minded determination to
push your life to the next level?
I've sent it off.
Oh!
Well done. Just to some agents.
I was going to ask if yours had
a literary division, actually.
No. I don't think so. Um...
I mean, I could ask?
I was going to pop in today actually,
big push and all that...
Hey. Hey.
I'm sorry about last night,
the police and everything.
It's no excuse...
I saw my Uncle after you gave me
Alma's details. And what'd he say?
That she didn't want me.
So she is your mother?
Yeah.
What now? I don't know. It's not
like I've got any way of finding
her even if she wanted to be found.
Well, if you do get another
lead, try leaving me a message
instead of going nuclear.
Yeah, speak to you later. Well...
nice to see you two
getting on again.
The site is an old school
but the developers are doing an
appraisal to turn it into flats.
They've asked us for our input.
No way...
Don't worry,
the orphans have all been rehoused.
No. This is where we went.
You were schoolgirls together?
Yeah, uniforms and everything.
We were a couple of years apart.
I wouldn't mind going back.
I could take some pictures.
The brochure's almost done.
You just need to
choose the photos that you want.
I'll do the school as
part of the same fee.
That's really not necessary...
No, hang on!
Anything that improves the pitch...
Unless you think your
personal feelings could
cloud your judgement again.
They won't. Right. Perfect.
I'll expect something on my desk
when I get back from Germany then.
What's his problem?
Doesn't matter.
I had it in my head that
I wanted a fry up.
So I went to this all-night cafe,
fell asleep, and by the time
I woke up it was time to come in...
Really? Here, I'll phone the
estate agents right now. No, you
won't, cos we're not doing it.
Becks?
I want you.
All this stuff can wait
till we're both ready, OK?
But don't think going AWOL's
the way to get round me...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I love you, OK?
I want what you want. I promise.
I'll see you later. Bye.
See you.
Hey. What are you doing?
Nicotine?
Right. Jay!
It was only a fuck.
Listen. It was a fucking mistake.
Yeah, well, it was both of us.
I didn't have to twist your dick.
I just want to forget about this, OK?
I already have. Hello!
Hey.
Hands up if your head hurts today.
Yeah. What you doing here?
I wanted to talk
about Tess' birthday.
Is my sister around?
I could get a new haircut.
Like a pixie bob, accentuate my
cheekbones, fringe over the wrinkles?
It isn't as if I haven't been
trying for you, Tess, but...
I know. You have seen most of the
casting directors in Scotland.
And?
And the feedback I get is...
you have a tendency to...
What?
Too physical? I don't project enough?
Be a little negative.
What? You did cry at audition.
Once!
Then there was the balcony incident
at the Shakespeare workshop.
Romeo had a hard-on!
So what do I do, Saphia?
Cheer up.
You're an actress...
contort your face into a smile
and be happy!
PHONE RINGS
Hello?
Er, yes,
I'm just finishing with a client...
Oh, Tess...smile. OK!
She said she didn't want a fuss.
She always says that.
But I think that's what
she needs after Lou.
Yeah, well, you are the Tess expert.
What are you thinking? Surprise...
The Dykes of Hazard.
Friday night at Gravity.
Country and western.
Tess does love it. It's got
Kenny Rogered, Billy Gay Cyrus...
Playing to a bunch of
hen nights in stetsons...
Yeah, and how are we going to get
her down there without her realising?
Why not do it at my flat?
It's not like we
haven't got the space.
As long as it doesn't
get too messy again.
Messy how?
The...flat warming last night...
Tess puked. I passed out.
You'd have hated it.
What do you think I am? That
sounds exactly what you'd want
from a party! Yeah, exactly.
Tess has been going
on about the local.
I could take her down there while
you guys set up. Or I could?
I mean, I already talked to
her about doing something...
so if you guys say you're busy, if
she does try to make other plans,
then she'll have no other option.
Fine.
You all right?
Yeah, it's just...
Hayley. I feel like
if I'd looked out for her a bit more
she might still be in a job.
She's a big girl, Cat.
Someone gave her the ketamine.
She didn't say who?
She wouldn't tell me. She thinks
I'm like a teacher or something.
You always were a bit
of a girl scout. Thanks.
No, in a good way!
How's it good?
You think about stuff,
you don't just dive in.
Maybe a bit too much sometimes.
But...at least it means
you make good decisions.
You do the right thing.
I wish I was a bit more
like that sometimes.
PHONE RINGS
Jesus, I remember it
being even bigger than this.
I think we were just smaller.
Well, I was.
I remember you being
pretty well developed.
I think you should
get some pictures.
Oh, God...
So you remember?
Course I remember.
Every break time, you were
up there writing 'lyrics'.
Only cos I knew your
registration room was down there.
I used to get this great
view down your shirt.
We used to wear skirts too remember?
Worked both ways.
I can't believe they're still here.
You were watching way
too much Cell Block H.
I was trying to impress you!
It was my first time in detention.
I thought it's what you did!
You were in here more than you were
in class, you should've stopped me
if it was so lame. It wasn't lame...
I quite like having our
names up there together.
You thought you were so cool.
What was it? "What you in for?
Mine's the usual, smoking."
It was better than yours!
What was it? Flashing the
PE teacher or something?
I was campaigning for girls
to be able to wear shorts.
It was a political protest!
Mum went mental when she found out.
Marching in accusing the
school of quashing free speech.
It was so embarrassing.
Well, that was one thing I
never had to worry about.
Whatever happened with your mum...
we don't know the circumstances.
She was young... She's not any more.
Give us a drag then.
You've given up!
Just for old times' sake.
Cat! What? It's not like I'm
taking up dick again, is it?
This is the part where you're
supposed to cough your lungs up.
Dib, dib, dib.
No! No evidence!
No evidence! Get your hand out!
It's sad it has to change...
Yeah?
I thought you were all for
leaving the past behind...
ALARM RINGS
You did put that
fag out, didn't you?
Shit!
DIALLING TONE
ENGAGED TONE
I can't get through.
He's going to go ballistic
when he gets back from Germany.
They say it's mostly
just smoke damage.
The insurers'll have a field day.
It's not funny.
I'm not exactly employee of the
month after all this intern shit.
Yeah. That wasn't your fault.
Everything's my fault since he
found out I like girls as opposed
to middle-aged fat men in suits...
Two months ago he was talking about
making me partner, now he's looking
to demote me and I give him this.
Yeah, it wasn't your fault, Cat.
It was Jay.
Jay gave Hayley the gear.
I helped him cover it up at
the time but I didn't realise
it would put you in the shit.
What...
what was he even doing with her?
I don't think anything happened.
Only because she passed out!
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
I just didn't want to grass him up.
I'm not blaming you.
Bloody Jay!
So I get this call, and it's this
specialist sci-fi agency asking if I
'do lunch'!? That was quick.
It was the main guy as well.
The company's named after him!
Amazing...
I wonder if he'll have picked up
on the same flaws I did. Flaws?
Yeah.
Like, it's brilliant and everything
but the main guy, whatsisname? Sorin.
Yeah. Why doesn't he just
like, go for it with her?
Well, that's kind-of the point.
He can't...her species forbids it.
Well, he should.
Like, it's better than floating round
space wondering what might have been.
But would she...reciprocate?
Well, you're the writer.
Make it happen.
Right, I make it shots o'clock.
Actually I'm going to leave it.
I want to have a clear head tomorrow
for this meeting.
But it's Wednesday! We always
do shots o'clock on a Wednesday.
Well, I'm having shots o'clock.
Oh, and I was thinking I probably
should do something for my birthday.
Why the change of heart?
Oh, it's my meeting...
Oh, yeah? It went well?
Yeah.
Yeah, it turns out, um... she still
thought I was doing the runner's job,
and now there's like a whole
backlog of auditions. Awesome!
So I was thinking we could
check out your new local?
Hm, I wonder if it
should be something bigger.
Like, really celebrate. I'll speak to
the others and see what they think.
Course, yeah. Go for it.
Thanks for all your help.
Like we never left. Listen, don't
worry about Alistair. It'll be fine.
Uh. Looks like you've got company.
I'll see you tomorrow. Yeah.
Hey. Clarice let you
off with a caution then?
Yeah. Couldn't get you on the phone.
Just wanted to make sure you
were all right after yesterday?
Yeah, I'm fine. Busy day.
I didn't even make it into work.
I can barely remember anything
that happened last night.
It's probably for the best.
You coming up? Yeah? I was only
planning an early night but you
can come up for an hour or so.
I think I'll leave you to it.
Maybe another time.
All right.
Whatever you think.
Night.
Honey, I'm home!
Hey.
You smell of smoke...
Oh, I had a meeting on site.
You know what builders are like...
That smells amazing!
You know, when I was
younger I used to have this
fantasy about Bewitched.
The girl band?
No, I had that one too.
No, I mean the old TV show.
Where the witch marries a
human and then she turns
into the perfect '50s housewife?
Are you seriously telling me
that this does it for you?
Uh-hum. Each to their own.
DOOR OPENS
You're not fucking anyone are you?
No. Come in...
You all right? Yeah, fine.
I was just wondering, are you
doing anything on Friday night?
I was thinking of doing
something for my birthday.
Shit. Sorry, I said I'd work. Ah! I
can try and get out of it, though.
No, no, no, it's OK!
I wasn't going to do anything big.
Sure? Yeah, yeah. It's fine.
Happy, happy!
So I bumped into Ed earlier...
What,
signing books in Waterstones, was he?
It seems he knows
about me and Jay...
Ah!
You didn't seem that
bothered earlier...
It's fine. But you got to tell
him it can't go any further.
OK. It could really mess
things up for Jay and Becky.
No, I'm serious.
All right. Cool.
I didn't know you'd
taken up boxing...
What? FG Boxing.
I auditioned for a self defence
radio ad but apparently
I don't even sound fit.
I didn't hear a fucking bell!
Get back to work!
Can I help? This place just
for boys or can anyone join in?
We do girls too... some of them
are uglier than the boys though.
So how'd you hear about us?
My flatmate has these.
They work here? I don't know.
This is a staff keyring.
I can't believe you stood there
letting me take the flak while
you're the one doling out ketamine
in the first place. I'm sorry.
What about Becky? What about her?
I thought you were leaving all
that snatch-hound shit behind...
I was! I am! Then what were you
doing in the toilets with Hayley?
Listen, you can talk!
Back to school with Frankie,
strolling down memory
lane behind Sam's back.
I was working! Would Sam see it
like that? I am happy with Sam!
I'd never go back!
She gave you head,
made you breakfast and went to work.
What's the problem?
I just...
I don't want to scare her off.
I...she's been a bit distant.
Do you think it's the ex?
I just think you're being paranoid.
Yeah? You like this one, right?
A lot.
I didn't need to tell her though. I
tell women I love them all the time.
Yeah, that's when you're
trying to fuck them.
What if they said it to you?
Mm.
Saying I love you's like
a gun fight.
If you draw first,
you'd better not miss.
Girls' group classes are
Monday, Wednesdays and Fridays.
You should check it out,
they'll love you.
All right? Yeah, sorry. Could you...
could you get me a glass of water?
Yeah, no problem. Back in a bit.
PHONE RINGS
Hello? Hi, Catflaps, it's me.
Erm,
what are you doing on Friday night?
Me and Sam have got gig tickets. Ah.
Why's that?
Erm, er, it's nothing.
Really? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's just I haven't seen you much
since I moved out, but another time.
How's Sam? Yeah...good. Good.
You two must be loving
it without me there.
Sex in the bath, sex on the sofa,
rubbish in the bin.
Yeah, she's, er...
really making herself at home.
Don't sound too enthusiastic!
No, no, I am. I am. It's just...
you don't want to hear about all
this happy-clappy couply stuff.
Why not?
I don't know. Just...
How's the new place working out?
Yeah, good...
Great view.
Frankie not keeping you up
all night with Sadie? Not really.
No? Why you asking? No reason.
So, look, I'm sorry again about
Friday. I'll make it up to you, OK?
Oh, no, no. It's...
it's OK. Look, I'll, um...
I'll speak to you later. Yeah, bye.
Hi!
Erm, I just...
I've just moved in next door.
Um, haven't we met before?
Maybe. Um, well, this is going
to sound really weird but, um...
I was wondering if, um...do, er...
Er, if...do you know any
decent electricians in the area?
Um, my lights have just gone out...
TV, radio, everything!
You're in luck.
I'm a spark.
Right, um...
Um,
you really don't have to do this...
I don't mind.
That's weird. Um...
this was all not working
a minute ago. Er...
MACHINE BEEPS
It's probably just your breaker.
Right... It's a little box?
Usually up high, or built into your
fittings. Do you mind if I just...
No, no, go ahead.
And I'll just, um...
Is it a little box, did you say? Mm.
This is really kind of you.
PHONE RINGS
Oh, um... Do you want me to?
Yeah, yeah...thanks.
Hello?
Yeah, yeah, can I ask who's calling?
Chloe? Um...oh, it's just...
it's my ex... Ex...
flatmate. Girlfriend.
Thanks. I can go...
No, no, no...no! Um...
yeah, this really isn't a good time,
er, my neighbour, um, I just...
Your breaker's fine by the way.
Er, um...
no, no, no. Wait! You, erm...
oh, no!
What do you want?
It's the same guy I met with Jay.
His name's Darren Morris,
I recognise his picture.
If he's lying about the keyring,
he could be connected to my past.
Are you going to go back?
Be careful.
So, this one?
Mm, do you think Tess'll
be able to work the buttons?
It's the future.
Don't tell me you're
still using Milo?
What's wrong with Milo? It rattled!
I'm surprised you could hear
it over your sound effects?!
Um, do you reckon they giftwrap?
PHONE RINGS
Hiya... OK, we'll head back.
Thanks.
Alistair's landed.
Well, she sounded kind-of nervous
but she said she wanted to meet up in
person to tell me something big.
You don't think she wants to get
back together, do you?
Dunno.
But you wouldn't, would you? No.
Not after everything she
put you through? God, no!
I'd tell her to piss right off.
Um, but the way, you didn't say
anything to anyone about the
Jay and Frankie thing, did you?
No. Good. Cos you mustn't.
What do you think I am?
Well, Frankie said you
almost let it slip...
I shouldn't have even told you!
She's unbelievable. Thinking she can
just make up the rules. What rules?
Well, what is she?
Is she les? Bi? Straight?
Well, isn't that a bit out of date?
Yeah, but it matters! Does it?
Doesn't it? I mean, they do say
sexuality's more of a fluid thing.
Well, I don't really want
to think about the fluids.
No, but less
black and white, more of a spectrum.
Well, I guess
we are all just people...
bodies and stuff.
Exactly!
So, technically
anyone can love anyone?
Yeah, I guess.
It was an accident.
But it's not the first one
you've had this month, is it?
I don't know what's
distracting you...
But if your mind's not on the job
then I'll have to seriously
reconsider your position
within this company.
I'm so sorry. It was my fault!
Cat was outside.
She had nothing to do with it.
Frankie... Look, it was stupid.
But if Cat took responsibility for
every stupid thing I'd done
she'd be sectioned.
Maybe that's what the issue is here.
Responsibility.
If she can't look after a
photographer, let alone an intern.
Well, that was me as well. What?
I gave Hayley the ketamine.
Right. Get out!
Yeah, my pleasure.
How much of this did you know about?
I did warn you about her.
Sorry... Dildo.
What the?
# Don't leave the house today
# I've got the fear
# You'll be stolen by bandits
# And taken far from here
# They'll put you in a cage
# Made of skeleton bones
# I get a ransom call
# On my telephone, uh-oh
# We don't have that kind of money
# We don't have that kind of bread. #
Ah! Thanks for coming. It's fine.
You're looking...good.
It's BOTOX. BOTOX?
We're not going to stay
looking young forever.
You should think about it.
Happy Birthday, Tess.
So...
that isn't
what you wanted to see me for?
Sorry. No, no, it's OK.
I'd rather forget about it too.
So, what did you want?
Well...
we did go out for quite
a long time, didn't we?
Yeah. And that's got to
count for something...
no matter what
happened towards the end.
I suppose...
I'm not looking for your approval
or permission or anything,
but you're still a significant
person in my life...
You remember Shona from Spanish?
Yeah... We're getting married.
Aargh!
I know you were never keen on the
whole civil partnership thing but I
felt you had the right to know.
You were never that keen on
monogamy with me! You've...
you've only been with her six months!
It's eight months.
You're just bitter because
I'm moving on with my life.
What? Settling down with
the bride of Frankenstein?
Off to the sperm bank
with your turkey baster?
I should've known you can't
be happy for me. Yeah.
You can't be happy for anyone
cos you're miserable and negative
and think it's funny you're a loser.
That's why I dumped you.
But at least I respected you enough
to want to speak to you in person.
Clearly I was wrong.
Clearly you were. Bye, Tess.
Have a nice life.
Yeah, send me some cake.
PHONE RINGS
Happy Birthday! Woop woop!
Guess what, I've got an agent!
Even bought me lunch.
With champagne. Lots of champagne.
I'll tell you about it in the pub.
Don't be late.
So...
talk me through these new changes.
The astronaut bangs the alien, right?
Well, it's more of a
happy ending really...
# I said I don't know... #
Yes, you bloody will!
Listen to me!
DOOR OPENS
Look, she's...
This is going to come back on you.
Back on you big time!
I recognise his car.
You didn't knock after that?
If those two know each other then
fuck knows what I'm walking into.
Do you want me to see if Sam
can look up this Darren Morris?
No.
God, it's no wonder
I'm such a fuck up.
You're not a fuck up.
I am.
OK, you are, but...
But what?
Tell me...
You know, you're the only one
who's ever really known me.
I should go. Sam's coming
to mine before the party.
Yeah.
Course she is.
I'll see you there then.
Where am I going to get a cowboy
outfit at this type of notice?
Pigtails, blusher.
Sexy Pocahontas.
Is this a party or a role play?
Bit of both...
I didn't think you wanted
to know after the other day.
I've been having family problems.
Who hasn't?
So, are you coming then?
Tell me you want me there.
I want you there.
You were supposed to be here 20
minutes ago, we're going to be late.
I missed you too.
Where've you been?
I got ambushed by my landlady.
It looks like I'm going to have
to find somewhere else to live.
Are you all right?
I didn't say anything.
You didn't have to.
I'm fine.
You've just been a little bit off
with me over the last couple of days,
that's all.
Sorry.
I've just had a really busy week.
It's my best friend's surprise
party, I don't want to be late. Yeah.
Ye-ha!
Lady Luck must be a dyke.
I love this place!
What can I say? I'm a rent girl.
I could probably help you find
somewhere bigger than Jay's if you
want...mates rates, no strings.
BUZZER RINGS
Oh, that might be Tess.
How does she know
what your place looks like?
I don't know.
Hey, cowgirl. Hey, cowboy.
Sheriff... All right?
Nice place.
Yeah, shame about the freeloaders.
Drink? Thanks.
I'll sort this out.
OK.
Is she the one
that stole my necklace?
What? Sadie. She gave it back.
Well, if you want Sadie,
at least act like it.
Cat's taken. Get over it.
You told her what I said to you?
I didn't have to. Listen,
don't try too hard, all right?
Cat told me she's more than happy
with Sam and that's that.
I'm sorry.
Wait, wait... What?
I'm just going to see where
the birthday girl is. Yep.
# Without you I'm just not myself
I was here on time but
there's no sign of her...
No...
Oh, hold on...
Tess!
Who are you supposed to be?
Jackie Onassis on an ASBO?
What happened to you?
BOTOX. It was a birthday treat.
But I had a reaction.
It doesn't look that bad.
I'm not going out.
Come on, it's your birthday.
There's nothing to celebrate! Tess!
Chloe's getting married!
At least it wasn't to tell you
she had Chlamydia.
Hey! Whoa, Tess... What?
Good riddance to her.
Yeah, but why does she have to ride
off into the sunset while I
accelerate into a lonely grave?
Hey, you've got loads of friends.
Yeah, but not tonight though, eh?
All too busy...
That's not true. Yes, it is.
I'm sorry. Hey.
Sorry.
I can't even fucking cry properly.
Arrgh. Ssh.
Who cares about Chloe?
Everything else is great.
You've got loads of auditions.
No, I haven't.
I lied. But I couldn't tell you
because you were doing so well.
Tess...
I got your message. Congratulations.
I don't care about that.
You don't have to lie to me.
I was jealous!
And scared that if you were a
success, you wouldn't want to hang
out with a loser like me any more.
Tess, you're not a loser!
OK?
Tess, you're amazing.
You're beautiful,
you're kind, you're talented.
And you don't even realise how funny
you are, by accident and on purpose,
and if the rest of the world can't
see that then they're idiots.
But I can.
And I'll never leave you.
Because I love you. Ah.
I love you too, Ed.
No. I LOVE you.
Like...
like a man loves a woman.
Tess?
Tess! Tess, you said se...
you said sexuality was fluid.
Fuck!
BUTTONS BEEP
PHONE RINGS
Hello?
Frankie, she's coming...
Tess is coming!
No! No, don't let her in!
Quick! Someone get the music!
Sssh!
Surprise!
Tess?
Hey, what's up?
Hey?
Ssh...
Ed!
What happened? What did you do?
I told her. You told her what?
That I'm in love with her.
Are you?
No wonder you never pull!
Jay... You do realise she's gay?
Well, it didn't stop you
with Frankie, did it?
When?
Is that where you
were the other night?
No...
No!
KNOCK ON DOOR
Don't let anyone in.
Tess? Go away!
I'm sorry. What?
We can still be friends.
I thought we were friends.
But all the time you were...
Just get out. Can both...
both of you just get out.
All right.
Come on.
Ow!
You fucking bitch.
Becks. Don't fucking Becks me.
Is it true?
Becky...
Becky!
We should go.
Canape?
Here...
Frankie, stop.
Come on.
Kiss me.
Frankie, stop.
What? Come on.
It isn't me you want. Is it?
It is tonight.
What?
I really liked you, Frankie.
See you around.
Don't go. Stop it.
I love you.
You could move in with me.
You...you're sure?
We, we...we never gave this a shot.
Who's fault was that?
Dig any deeper, you'll hurt
yourself. Try to find out,
I'll hurt her too.
Some actress has dropped out of
Uncle Vanya at The Tron and they
need to audition a new Sonia today.
Shit. You don't think
it's broken, do you?
Why do you want her?
We're just going to chat...
That's not what I meant.
Subtitles by mencase