向我们伸出援手吧 我们会使出浑身解数 Lend us your help and we will do whatever must be done
推动拿骚的进步 to move Nassau forward.
她同意了 格斯里夫人 She agreed. Madam Guthrie.
我们想要为拿骚做的任何事 Everything we want for Nassau.
但弗林特...她想要我杀了他 But Flint... she wants him dead and she wants me to do it.
他们都对我倒戈 They all turned on me
我要他们所有人为此付出代价 and I want them all to pay for it.
我尝试过一次 I tried once
但我当时没有离间他们的必备工具 but I didn't possess the instrument to make it work.
你有 You do.
再不同也不能让她成为你那战争的代价 Nothing justifies trading her life for your war.
没人说让她去送死 No one is saying that we let her die.
-你不能保证... -我们开去拿骚 - You cannot guarantee that... - We will sail to Nassau.
我们会找到她然后带她回来 And we will find her and we will bring her home.
你对他的计划充满了信心 You're confident in his plan
也许是因为这是个好计划 maybe because it's a good plan.
但也许你会告诉他 But maybe you'll have to show him
你准备好面对失败了 that you're prepared for the failure
还有他想埋在地下的那些财宝... and that a treasure he wanted left in the ground...
不复存在了 ain't in the ground no more.
我想此刻我该提醒你 Seemed only fair that I remind you
我们现在休戚与共 that our fates are now linked.
如果这个计划没有让我拿到宝藏 If this plan to secure the cache ends badly for me
你肯定也不会有什么好下场 you can be certain it will end badly for you.
宝藏在我说的地点 没错吧 It was where I said it would be was it?
盖茨先生跟弗林特的关系真是不一般 That's how close Mr. Gates was to Flint.
他把最心爱的宝贝都藏在他的地窖 Stored his most prized possessions in his cellar.
还有艾弗里的日记 Avery's journals.
尽管他们彼此信任 Despite that measure of trust
最后还不是因为在小钱上起了争执 all it took was a disagreement over a little money
就让弗林特动了歹念 for Flint to kill him.
两个人之间的感情再亲密 There are no two people close enough
也终究会因为某些事而产生隔阂 that something cannot separate them.
某种程度上来说 Some point at which
他们从一开始就没有多团结 they were never fully connected to begin with.
盖茨跟弗林特就是如此 It happened with Gates and Flint.
弗林特和西尔弗也会这样 It will happen with Flint and Silver.
这计划可行 This plan will work.
你不想让这场交易发生在这个岛上 You want the exchange of the money to happen off this island
交易地点最好没人知道 somewhere no one need know of it.
这正好 There it is.
你把他们引过去 You'll lead them there
他们会跟着来的 and they will follow you.
科菲和手下在去往拿骚的路上 Kofi and his men are on their way to Nassau.
然后该怎么办 What happens after this?
他们会从密道走 They'll use resistance routes
以防被总督的卫兵发现 to evade detection by the Governor's soldiers.
此刻他们大概已经快到镇子上了 They're probably already nearing town by now.
那里会有人跟他们接应 They'll find friends there
带他们去马迪被关押的地方 discover through them where Madi is being held
然后天亮之前就会回到岸边与我们碰头 and be back to the beach for us to recover by morning.
只要知道她的下落 Once we know where she is
我们就会采取行动救她出来 we'll move to get her out of there.
这一切行动之后呢 What happens after all of it?
假如你的计划成功 Assume your plan succeeds
把她活着救出来 and we retrieve her alive.
假如你的战争爆发... Assume your war begins...
并向新大陆全面蔓延 spreads throughout the New World.
我见过拿骚被战争波及的样子 I saw what came of Nassau when it was touched by it.
刚开始的时候 In the first instant
只是没有了埃莉诺·格斯里的贸易 it was deprived of Eleanor Guthrie's commerce
杰克·拉克姆带来的繁荣 or Jack Rackham's prosperity
或是伍兹·罗杰斯的镇压 or Woodes Rogers' oppression.
笼罩在拿骚上空的只有恐怖 There's nothing in Nassau but horror.
你说那只是一种转变 You said it was just a transition.
未来很美好 That something better lay beyond it
很有意义 something meaningful.
可如果不是那样的呢 But what if that isn't so?
如果战争的结果并没有摆脱恐怖的阴影呢 What if the result of this war isn't beyond the horror?
如果带来的只有恐惧呢 What if it is the horror itself?
这些你都想过吗 Have you given this any thought at all?
如果我们最终 If we are to truly reach a moment
真的会随着英格兰一同灭亡 where we might be finished with England...
成为新秩序的基奠... cleared away to make room for something else...
那么在实现这一目标的过程中 there most certainly lies a dark moment
肯定会有十分黑暗的时期 between here and there.
这段时期中 A moment of terror
一切都暗淡无光 让人丧失希望 where everything appears to be without hope.
这我知道 I know this.
但我不相信这就是全部 But I cannot believe that that is all there is.
我不相信我们沦落到了这个地步 I cannot believe we are so poorly made as that.
无法在我们长大的土地上生存下来 Incapable of surviving in the state to which we are born.
变得如此地习惯于被压迫 Grown so used to the yoke
以至于没有压迫就不会过日子了 that there can be no progress without it.
实在是很难去... It's a lot to ask...
为了盲目的信心而遭受如此的苦难 to wager so much suffering on blind faith.
也不完全只有信心 Well it isn't entirely faith.
我们有合适的人来带我们度过这一切 We'll have the right people in place to lead us through it
并在世界找到平衡点时让其重归完整 and hold the world together while it finds its balance.
你对我俩的期望太高了 You think so much of what you and I can accomplish together.
是你和她 You and her.
你和马迪 You and Madi.
她像她父亲一样睿智 She's as wise as her father.
像她母亲一样坚强 She's as strong as her mother.
拿骚没有谁 There isn't a man or woman in Nassau
会怀疑她是不是最佳人选 who'd argue that she isn't the best of them all.
宝藏和她都对我们的战争至关重要 The cache is critical to our war but so is she.
能让我们的联盟不瓦解 Critical to holding our alliance together.
我们必须要把她活着带回来 We absolutely must get her back alive.
你认为我是带领众人度过这一切难关的 And you think I'm the one best suited
最佳人选吗 to lead our people through this?
我觉得你是我们之中最合适的 I think that you are the best of us.
你们两个能让世界回归平衡 The two of you together are the world in balance.
无论比利造成了多大损失 For all the damage Billy's done
至少他在这点上是对的 at least he got that right.
好多了 Better.
抱歉昨天没来帮你治疗 Sorry I was not here to do this yesterday.
和格斯里夫人 The meetings with Madam Guthrie
以及她丈夫会面的时间每天都在变长 and her man grow longer every day.
我觉得我正慢慢获取她的信任 I believe I am gaining her trust.
我想我已经让他们觉得我们的提议是合理的 I believe I have persuaded them our proposal is sound
但是他们还是在提问 and still the questions continue.
但是我感觉到了一些东西 But I feel as though something is coming
她好像已经觉得这不再是我们的主意 a moment in which this will cease to be our idea
而是她自己的 and become her own.
如果我能成功达到这一目的 If I am able to reach that moment
并变成她真正的合伙人 and emerge from it a true partner to her
如果杰克能信守承诺 if Jack is able to fulfill his end of the bargain
我开始预见我们的未来了... I am beginning to see a future for us in which...
你为什么要这样 Why are you doing this?
煞有其事地说我们俩的事 Talking about us like it's a thing?
未来 A future?
我不知道谁先毁了未来 I don't know who broke it first.
但它已经被毁了 But it broke.
而且也没办法挽回了 And there ain't no putting it back together again.
你没事吧 Are you all right?
等等 Wait.
你需要什么吗 Is there something you need?
是的 Yeah.
我有需要 There is.
他们等了一小时就散了 They waited an hour before disbanding.
显然"总督正在赶过来"这句话 Evidently that is the lifespan of "The governor is on his way"
只配让人等一个小时 as a viable measure of delay.
解决我们问题的方案 The solution to our problems
是不可能通过内阁会议讨论出来的 is not going to come from a council meeting.
他们快对你没信心了 They are losing faith in you.
他们明白我们重建殖民地所面对的问题 They see the problems we face in rebuilding this colony
以及失败的风险 the dangers if we fail.
他们对你的怀疑与日俱增 And they are growing more and more skeptical by the day
怀疑你到底有没有解决方案 that you have anything in the way of a solution.
我所担心的比那个更糟 My fear is it's worse than that.
我担心他们发现你真正的解决方案 My fear is they will learn what your solution actually is.
我知道你打算用那个奴隶女人 I know you intend to ransom away that slave woman
去和弗林特船长及他的放逐者盟友 to Captain Flint and his maroon allies
交换海盗宝藏 in exchange for the pirates' cache of gems.
你如此明目张胆地进行这项交易 As brazenly as you pursued this bargain
你真以为没人会发现吗 did you really believe that no one would find out about it
我不会发现吗 that I wouldn't find out?
我的妻子促成了这项交易 索姆斯先生 My wife made the bargain for the cache Mr. Soames.
我只负责去拿货 All I'm going to do is collect.
海盗们已经走了 长官 The pirates are gone sir.
他们对我们的威胁已经解除了 长官 The threat that they presented us is done!
海盗们对我们的威胁从未如此严重过 The threat the pirates present has never been greater.
他们的目的是制造恐惧和破坏 Their intent is to cause terror and destruction
直到文明社会土崩瓦解为止 until civilization simply ceases to function.
-威胁不会... -保护文明社会 - The threat will not... - The defense of civilization
不是你的责任 长官 is not your responsibility sir!
你的责任是重新从拿骚获取稳定的利润 Your duty is to restore stable profits to Nassau.
听令尾随你的将士已经 And the men charged to follow you to that end
对您的威信产生质疑了 are already questioning their trust in you.
如果他们看见海盗重回这里 If they see pirates return here
如果他们看见这座小岛上冲突再起 if they see skirmishes begin again on this island
并且得知是你挑起的 and they know that it was because you invited it...
那你就自食这个兵变的恶果吧 长官 then you are going to have a mutiny on your hands sir.
我担心我丈夫的安危 "I fear for my husband's safety
担心他受我的死对头迫害 "From men I've long called enemies
担心他被我曾经的朋友陷害 "From men I once called friends.
我愿扭动乾坤来保护他 "I will move heaven and earth to protect him
但现在这一角色 but while playing this role
让我受到束缚无法施展影响 the limits of my influence are ever-present."
我刚在按您的吩咐收拾东西 大人 I was just packing everything away as you asked my lord.
准备好我的行李 Ready my things.
天一亮我就动身 I sail at first light.
对方一定是趁晚上在我们后面偷偷溜进去了 She must've slipped in behind us during the night.
已经停泊靠岸了 She's already at anchor.
看起来对方已经在等着我们了 Looks like she's been waiting for us.
好像早就知道我们要在哪靠岸 It looks like she knew where to wait for us.
老天爷 看他们船上 Jesus Christ! On their rail!
他抓住他们了 He caught them.
怎么可能 一夜之间吗 How's that possible? Overnight?
全带到甲板上 All up on deck!
拉起中帆 掉头 Back the fore-topsails. Bring us about.
-拉起中帆 -炮手就位 - Back the fore-topsails! - Gun crews at the ready!
-掉头 -你干什么 - Bring us about! - What are you doing?
我们把炮对准他们 We bring our guns to bear
他就会犹豫要不要杀了她 he'll think twice about killing her.
不必理会 Belay that order!
你去 现在就把东西带上来 Go get it. Bring it up here right now.
去干什么 Go get what?
你带了什么东西 What did you bring with us?
你的计划失败了 现在按我的计划来 Your plan failed. We're moving onto my plan.
你的命令别再说第二次 Do not repeat your order.
想都别想 Do not think about it.
带上来 Bring it up here.
放到他们能看见的地方 Get it where they can see it.
给他发信号 Signal him.
快去 Go!
给欧律狄刻号发信号 Signal the Eurydice.
快点 Do it now!
敲钟 Strike the bell!
打开 Open it.
他在收锚 他要去哪 He's hauling up the anchor. Where the fuck is he going?
不管他去哪 我们都跟着 Wherever he's going we follow him.
这应该是好事 This should be good.
我能为我们的总督大人做些什么 What is it I can do for our lord governor?
我不是代表总督来的 夫人 I don't come on behalf of the governor ma'am.
你是罗杰斯总督的女仆 不是吗 You are Governor Rogers' woman are you not?
我是 所以我信任你并且 I am which is why I believe you and I
也许我们能互相帮助 may be able to help each other.
说真的 夫人 找个私密点的地方更适合说事 Really ma'am someplace private may be more appropriate.
没有免费的私密空间 亲爱的 Privacy always comes with a price dear.
咱们先来看看你要说什么吧 好吗 Let's see what it is you have to say first shall we?
总督要破釜沉舟了 The governor moves in a dark and destructive direction.
他的悲痛和愤怒 His grief and his anger...
我相信已经让他远离清醒的判断 I believe have unmoored him from sound judgment
如不悬崖勒马 也会让我们置身于无尽的深渊 and have left us all in grave danger if he is not reined in.
你已经注意到了 对吗 You've noticed this have you?
你被管委会除名 You were excluded from the council.
不再干预其中的事情 On the outside of its goings-on.
我不知道你都了解什么情况 I don't know what information you were privy to--
我感谢你的关心 I appreciate your concern.
欢迎再次光临 Come back when you like.
我也许能帮你重新回去 I may be able to help you get back inside.
回到管委会吗 Back on the council?
继续说 Go on.
我发现了一本埃莉诺的日记本 I found a journal Eleanor kept.
她在里面说到 In it she mentioned that
拿骚上一次面临动荡的困境时 when Nassau last threatened to descend into chaos...
你是她求助以期力挽狂澜的人 you were the one to whom she turned to help prevent it.
总督身边的人 The men surrounding the governor
现在都无法有效地动摇他的地位 now have all failed to challenge him in any meaningful way.
我想着如果我能从内部 I am hoping that if I could provide you
给你提供他办公的一些消息 with information from inside his office...
也许能帮你重回管委会 it might help you maneuver your way back onto the council.
这在我听来很像叛国啊 That sounds an awful lot like treason to me.
政府方面先搁置不论 And what exactly aside from good government
你又到底想从中获得什么呢 do you hope to gain from this hmm?
埃莉诺承诺送我去伦敦 Eleanor promised me passage to London.
我将得以归家 A release from my service
摆脱这一切 that I might return home.
如果我帮了你 If I help you...
你会帮我吗 will you help me?
当你问我我能否帮你打听 When you asked me if I could help you learn
总督的船会去哪儿 where the governor's ship went...
要把弗林特船长引去哪儿 to what place he drew Captain Flint
我本以为我不可能帮上什么忙 I thought it unlikely I could be of much help.
但你肯定想不到刚刚谁来了我这儿 But you will never believe what just walked through my door.
-不是那儿吗 -什么 - Is that not it? - ‭What?
我们不像是准备靠岸的样子 We don't seem to be preparing for a landing.
前面不是我们的目的地吗 Is that not our destination ahead?
不是 No it isn't.
那只是个路标 It's a waypoint.
我们会在那岛上两处做标记 Two features on that island are the markers.
可能是两座山顶上或者海岸线上某两点 Maybe two peaks or some points along the coast.
你连接该两点所得的方向就是 You run a line through them and that direction becomes
总督去目的地所需设定的航向 the course the governor will set to reach our final destination.
你怎么知道的 How do you know that?
我不明白 I don't understand.
如果总督知道我们的终点 If the governor knows our destination
他为什么不能直接在航海图上定点作向呢 why can't he just plot a course directly to a spot on the chart?
因为骷髅岛不在任何一张航海图上 Because Skeleton Island is not on any chart
至少 不在任何一张书面的航海图上 not on any civilized one at any rate.
它很远 Remote.
在所有已建立的商路范围之外 Well outside any established trade route.
这座岛上所进行的交易 It's been used from time to time
往往是任何政党都不愿承认的 for transactions neither party wished would ever be acknowledged.
我当然爱她 Of course I love her.
我照你说的试了 I let you try it your way!
我的确信任你 I did trust you.
但我再也不想赌上她的命了 But I'm through wagering with her life now.
如果安全释放她的代价是交出宝藏 If what it takes to secure her release is to turn over the cache
那么我很庆幸我把宝藏带上了 I'm very glad I brought it with us.
我们本来 We had it.
我们本来大势在握 We had it in our hands.
这场战争本来一触即发 必打无疑 This war was breathing air it was alive.
现在尤利乌斯已经回到营地 Now Julius is back in that camp
指着地上的坑 pointing to a hole in the ground
告诉所有人 telling anyone who will listen
"这就是你信任一个海盗的下场" "This is what it looks like when you trust a pirate."
昨天 他还一无所有 Yesterday he had nothing.
只能对着虚无吼叫 He was shouting at the rain.
而现在是你让他有能力阻止这场战争 Now you've given him all he needs to kill this war dead.
天呐 My God.
那么多次 我盲目地听信你 The number of times I have followed you blindly
盲目地全力支持你 backed you with the men blindly
派人上那狗日的战场 put men in the fucking ground--
牺牲了那么多好人 朋友 就因为你说 good men friends-- because you said
我有办法 别问我怎么知道的 "I know the way. Don't ask me how.
就按我说的做 Just do as I say."
我可能并没明白你的办法 可能也不支持 I may not have understood it I may not have supported it
但我照你说的做了 but I did it!
真该死 现在你就是这么报答我的 And God damn it right now you're going to return the favor!
我们会尽可能在能力范围内 We will find a way to put it all back together
想办法解决这些问题 with whatever we have left at our disposal.
但你别再叫我在战争和妻子之间做抉择 But do not ask me to choose between a war and a wife.
你不会喜欢我的答案的 I do not think you're going to like the answer.
为了确保马迪能安全释放 Whatever must be done to secure Madi's release
我什么都愿意做 I'm going to do it.
我不指望你理解我 I do not expect your understanding
但我要求你支持我 but I demand your support.
作为我的同伴 As my partner
作为我的朋友 as my friend.
你支持我吗 Do I have it?
好 Yes.
你问的事情我查好了 I got what you asked.
这些船要么停在港口要么即将进港 These are the ships either in port or soon expected to be
并且都愿意载客 and willing to accept passengers.
你真的想要离开吗 You really intend to leave...
无论杰克会不会活着回来 whether Jack returns alive or not?
杰克会回来的 Jack will return.
杰克去追击弗林特船长了 Jack went to hunt Captain Flint.
你很可能再也见不到他了 Chances are good you've seen the last of him.
你害死了我的朋友 You killed a friend of mine.
她叫夏洛特 Her name was Charlotte...
而你杀人的理由还与她毫无关系 and you did it for reasons that had nothing to do with her.
我认识一些肯帮我杀了你的人 There were men I knew that would've killed you for me.
我本来想这么做 I wanted to ask them.
都凑够钱了 Had the money.
但麦克斯拒绝了我 But Max refused.
当时看不出来是不是因为她怕你 I couldn't tell then if it was because she was afraid of you.
怕也正常 我当时也怕你 Wouldn't have blamed her. I was.
但也许是有别的原因 Or if it was something else.
但我尊重了她的意愿 But I respected her wishes.
尊重她不管你做了什么也要保护你的愿望 Obeyed when she said we'd protect you despite what you'd done.
你知道为什么吗 Do you know why?
因为虽然她活着的每一天里 世界都在 Because despite the world reminding her every day of her life
提醒她 她没有活下去的资格 that she's undeserving of being given anything by it
她没有价值 that she was unworthy of
连她得到的一点点也不配拥有 what little she'd managed to take from it...
虽然如此 despite all of that
她从来没有绝望过 she never believed a word of it.
那个女人从她出生的那天起 That woman has been fighting the whole goddamn world
就在和世界抗争着 since the day she was born.
赢得那场战斗离她只有咫尺之遥 She's a breath away from winning that fight.
不管为什么 For whatever reason
她愿意和你分享这个成果 she wants to share the spoils with you.
你却离开了 And you'd walk away.
你害死了我的朋友 You killed my friend.
我觉得应该告诉你 I wanted you to know that.
这不是去格雷斯先生的图书馆的路上 We are not going to Mr. Grace's library.
你不是说想让我今天去那儿见一个人 I understood there was someone you wanted me to meet there today.
改变计划了吗 Has something changed?
跟我走 Walk with me.
这就是那些海盗 Those are the pirates.
他们占领了东岸 They've inhabited the east bank
与斯普林格特岛隔海相望很多年了 across from Springett Island for years.
政府保证今年就赶走他们 The governor promises this is the year he'll chase them off
但他们还在 but there they are.
城里七大主要海运都需要通过这里 Seven major shipping concerns in the city here.
再用不到10年 这里将成为伦敦外 In less than 10 years more goods will move through here
英语国家进出口量最大的海港 than any English-speaking port outside London.
这里将建起城市 There will be civilization here.
那么海盗去哪里 Where will the pirates be?
在东岸 与斯普林格特岛隔海相望 On the east bank across from Springett Island.
为什么 Why?
因为运输的商船 Because the shipping concern
要为预防海盗袭击交额外的保险费 charges a premium for the risk the pirates present.
我想总督也是从中获利的 I assume the governor too profits from this.
盗贼是存在 但所有人都受益 There is theft but everyone benefits.
那怎么会有人想结束这种状况 Why would anyone want to end it?
你和我孙女关系如何 How well did you know my granddaughter?
很熟 I knew her well.
她幸福吗 Was she happy?
幸福 Happy?
我也知道一些拿骚的事 There are things I know about Nassau
她的事 about her.
但隔着大海 总还是有了解不到的细节 There are things that are harder to know across an ocean.
我真的不知道 I honestly do not know.
她祖父很久以前与她断绝了关系 Her grandfather disowned her some time ago
觉得和野蛮的人在一起 她也会被同化 assumed she'd simply become one with the wild men.
庭审开始时 When the trial began
格斯里成了伦敦流言中卑劣的姓氏 and Guthrie became a contemptible name to utter in London
只让情形更加恶化 didn't help matters.
但一开始我就一直心怀希望 But I held out hope from the beginning.
幻想着不管我们听说了什么事 A fantasy that despite what we'd heard of her
她也在从中学习 成长着 she was learning growing.
幻想总有一天 她会来找我 And that someday she'd seek me out and...
幻想一个有着年轻时的 a woman who reminded me of myself
我的影子的女人会来波士顿 when I was younger would arrive in Boston
我会和她漫步在查尔斯河边 and I'd walk the Charles with her
教她一个女人在这世界中能有多大作为 and teach her the things a woman can do in this world.
虽然你不是她 我们也不在查尔斯河边 It's the wrong river and the wrong woman
但一个幻想能实现到这一步也不容易了 but perhaps to get even this close to a fantasy is something.
所以 让我们别再谈论经济 So let us assume that we're past conversations about ledgers
对你的考量结束了 我也听了你的提议 and that the measuring of you and your proposal are done
让我们一起开始一场冒险 and that we are partners in a venture
占领 重建拿骚 to acquire and reform Nassau.
现在关于这场冒险剩下的唯一问题就是 So now all that's left to know about this venture
谁将是领导者 is who is going to lead it.
爱德华·霍顿 Edward Houghton.
他们家族银行业务的唯一男性继承人 The only male heir to his family's banking operation.
极其呆板 Supremely uncurious
不怎么聪明 但本性还算不坏 bordering on dim but fundamentally decent.
他主导的投资项目顶多能盈利一点儿 The investments he's overseen have shown modest gains at best
经常亏损 and losses more frequently.
他不是你心目中管理拿骚的人选 This is not the man you would like to put in charge of Nassau.
我倒想让你去管理拿骚 I'd like to put you in charge of Nassau.
但是在这个问题上 But on this particular issue
没人管我怎么想 the world won't much care for what I'd like.
可供选择的人里 这个人还算有点价值 And of the men available this one has merits.
如果他能远离家族事业 His family would be relieved beyond measure
在其他地方开疆辟土 他的家族就解脱了 that he'd found himself a future far away from their business.
他能带来资金 He'd come with money
能敞开大门欢迎新搭档 he'd open doors to new partners...
他还是所有人中 and he'd be most amenable
最言听计从的 to doing whatever else you told him to do.
你觉得他会听从我这个顾问的建议吗 You think he would listen to me as an advisor?
你觉得如果我是他的妻子 他会听从我 You think he would listen to me as a wife.
也不一定得是他 I suppose it needn't be him.
但要想得到你需要的控制权 But to have the kind of control you will need to have
就必须得有人担任这个角色 there will need to be someone occupying the role
他还必须能一次性解决所有问题 and that someone solves a number of problems all at once.
拥有资金 没有野心 Money limited ambition...
有觉得你的故事激励人心并决意改革的父母 and reform-minded parents would find your story most intriguing.
至于你对他的义务 In terms of your obligations to him
无论有没有你的参与 there are plenty of ways for a man like that
他都可以在拿骚 to retain satisfaction in a place like Nassau
找到乐子 with little or no participation from you.
你也可以享有你所期盼的自由 You'd likely retain as much freedom in that regard as you desired.
从你开始崛起 To rise from where you began
走到你现在的位置 to where you now stand
我无法想象你所经历的是什么样的旅程 I cannot imagine the road you've traveled.
那些羞辱 The humiliations
那些牺牲 and the sacrifices
那些失败 and the defeats...
以有那些幻觉 and the illusions maintained
都让你的自主意识付出了沉重的代价 at so great a cost to your sense of self.
但是它将你引领到我这里 But that road has led you to me.
我就站在你旅途转折的起点 I am the gate through which your journey becomes something else.
我可以让你追求的梦想实现 I can make the dreams you have built real.
代价不大 但是你得付出 The toll is small but it must be paid.
告诉我你已经准备好付出了 Tell me you're ready to pay it...
然后我们一起下楼 and you and I will walk downstairs
我会把你介绍给他 I will introduce you to him
若如我所料 and-- as I imagine
接下来的事情你便驾轻就熟了 you'll have no difficulty taking things from there.
我们的合作关系将完全巩固 Our partnership may move forward fully formed.
你准备好了吗 Are you ready to do it?
那人年纪相当大了 That is a very old man.
总督的女人偷听到 The governor's woman overheard
他的船驶向了骷髅岛 his ship was bound for Skeleton Island.
据可靠消息 那个男人 That man I have it on good authority
是这个岛上仅剩的曾和艾弗里出海的人 is the last man on this island once sailed with Avery.
声称去过骷髅岛 Claims to have been to Skeleton Island
可以带我们过去 and can show us the way.
你相信他能做到吗 And you believe he can do it?
以我来看最终就是两种可能 Two possible outcomes as far as I can tell.
第一种 他没找到 One he fails
那我们就四处晃晃 直到筋疲力尽 in which case we sail around till we tire of it
再回大本营 then go back to the camp.
或者第二种 Or two
他奇迹般地带我们找到了那里 by some miracle he actually succeeds in getting us there.
我说不出哪种更好 And I can't tell which of the two is of more concern.
那是什么意思 What does that mean?
杀了弗林特本就是近乎不可能的事情 Killing Flint was already going to be a near impossible feat.
现在我们还得躲避总督和他的手下 Now we need to evade the governor and his soldiers as well.
在这儿坐等总督替我们杀了他 Wouldn't it make a whole lot more sense
不是更有道理吗 to just wait for the governor to kill him for us?
如果伍兹·罗杰斯取得了宝藏 If Woodes Rogers secures that cache
他的位置就坐稳了 he secures his position here as well.
那我们就无法灭了他了 Negates our plan to see him removed.
他就赢了 He wins.
-是 但是 -我们要的东西都在那个岛上 - Yeah but-- - Everything we need is on that island.
弗林特 罗杰斯 我的宝藏 Flint Rogers and my cache of gems.
如果那个老头儿能带我们去那里 If that very old man over there can get us there...
我们为什么还傻站在这儿 why are we still standing here?
如果你留他活路 If you leave him alive long enough
总有一天他会让你付出代价 he's going to make you pay for it.
他不会与我对抗 He won't move against me.
这事会过去的 This will pass.
这个话题也到此为止 And that's the end of this conversation.
如此多的谎言 只为否定一个简单的事实 So many lies to deny a simple truth.
什么 What?
权力不可分割 The crown does not divide.
不可共享 It cannot be shared.
你心里清楚 你也想他死 You know it. You want it done.
你只是还不知道该如何开口 You just don't know how to ask yet.
你给我听好了 Hear me very clearly.
没有隐藏讯息 也没有模拟两可 There is no hidden message and no equivocation.
你不准对他下手 You will make no move against him.
你不许对任何船员提起这件事 You will not speak of doing so
也不许再跟我提起 to any man on this crew nor to me again.
要是违抗我 你将承担后果 Do it and you'll answer for it.
你在外面干什么 Fuck you doing out here?
外面一团乱 快进来吧 It's a fucking mess out here. Come inside.
不进也行 Or don't.
我不在乎 I don't care.
成功了 It happened.
她答应了我和我们的计划 She has committed to the plan to me.
从我们来到这里就一直努力实现的那一刻 The moment we have been working towards since we arrived...
真的成真了 it happened.
这是好事 That's good news.
你为什么这幅表情 So why do you look like that?
我跟她说了我不同意 I told her I could not agree to it.
你拒绝她了吗 You told her no?
她需要一个人去坐总督的位置 She needs for there to be a man
但不是杰克 in the governor's office not Jack.
她亲自选的人 并且要我嫁给他 A man of her choosing and she wants me to be his wife.
嫁给他 His wife?!
只是名义上做做样子 仅此而已 In name only and for appearance's sake nothing more.
这样我们就能掌握权力 The power would rest with us.
只是做做样子吗 Just for appearance?
而你却拒绝了 And you said no?
你为什么要那么做 Why would you do that?
我还记得第一次见到埃莉诺时 I remember when I first met Eleanor
我有多么震撼 how stunned I was.
这个女人言行独特 A woman who spoke the way she did
对这个世界和统治阶级的男性毫无惧意 who had no fear of the world or the men who reigned over it.
我成为她的爱人时 看着她作出那些决定 When I became her lover I watched the decisions she made...
我决心从中学习 and resolved to learn from them.
我成为她的敌人时 看着她犯下那些错误 When I became her rival I watched the mistakes she made
我决心不会犯下相同的错误 and resolved never to repeat them.
可是最终 But at the end
当我觉得自己在各方面都已经超越她时 when I felt I had surpassed her in every way
她似乎还有话 it seemed as though there was
想要对我说 something she was still trying to say to me.
她放弃了自己以巨大牺牲换来的一切 Surrendering everything she had sacrificed so dearly for
就为了不失去所爱之人 because it would have come at the expense of the one she loved.
她试图告诉我 可我却听不进去 She was trying to tell me I just could not hear her
什么才是真正重要的 about what is truly important.
我拒绝了玛丽昂·格斯里的计划 I said no to Marion Guthrie's plan...
尽管我别无选择 despite having no alternative
尽管我全部的努力都可能付诸流水 and at the risk of losing the entire endeavor
因为我不能让一个男人占据那个位子 because I refuse to situate a man in a position
否则他迟早会 where he might interfere one day
对我俩的关系造成影响 with my ability to repair things with you.
你是我认识的最勇敢的人 You are the bravest person I have ever known.
最真诚的人 The truest person I have ever known.
然而我却背叛了你 我自己都厌恶自己 And I betrayed you and it sickens me.
很抱歉 我曾努力保护的东西根本不重要 I am so sorry for working so hard to protect the wrong things.
我没能看清事实 没有你 For failing to see that there is nothing important
一切都失去意义 that does not include you.
我听说 The story as it was recounted to me
艾弗里是第一个发现那个岛的英国人 is that Avery was the first Englishman to find the island.
西班牙人之前在那个岛上 The Spanish had been using it
进行非法交易 已经有几十年 to conduct illicit transactions for decades.
艾弗里打算设下埋伏 偷袭他们 Avery plans to lie in wait for them.
他和四十四个船员抵达后 He and his crew of 44 arrive
驶向内陆 and sail inland.
可是当他们沿着水湾驶入时 But as they move up the inlet
他们见到了最意想不到之事 they see something most unexpected.
一艘西班牙船只 She was Spanish
但不是他们在找的船 but not one of the ships they'd been hunting.
这艘船很早之前就停靠在这了 This ship had been there far longer than that.
船长的日志显示这艘船 Captain's log identifies her having set sail
1636年从哈瓦那出发 from Havana in 1636.
船上31名船员 31 souls aboard.
艾弗里发现了31名船员的尸体 Avery finds the remains of all 31.
惨遭虐杀 Slaughtered.
野蛮兽性惨不忍睹 Brutally so.
迹象表明其中许多人 Evidence that a number of them
活着的时候就被肢解了 had been dismembered while still alive.
他们是岛上居民吗 There were natives on the island?
船上发现了31具直挺挺的尸体 All 31 bodies were found still on the ship
被锁在船舱里 locked inside the hold.
从里面反锁 Locked from within.
活人吃活人 They ate each other alive.
艾弗里声称见过航海日志 Avery claimed to have seen the log.
日志上说船员拒绝上岸 It said that the crew had refused to go inland
搜寻食物和淡水 to forage for food or for fresh water.
第一批上岸的人回来 That the first men in had returned
汇报来自林子里的声音 reporting sounds coming from the forest.
他们说那个声音听起来 The men said it sounded to them
像上帝之音 like the voice of God...
警告他们保持距离 warning them to stay away.
艾弗里故事中的编造成分有待考证 It's an open question how much of this story Avery invented.
但有一点毫无疑问 But what is undeniably true
这个故事十分有效地 is how undeniably effective that story has been
导致了某种结果 in achieving a result.
船长 Captain...
比利的选择并不意外 It's no accident that Billy chose it.
一个有可能让我们失去平衡的地方 A place likely to put us all out of balance
精神失去控制 where our imaginations might run wild
我们心中最邪恶的念头被唤醒 and our darkest impulses
从而让我们难以反抗 somehow made far more difficult to resist.
如果我们这次要死里逃生 If we are to survive this experience...
如果我们的目标是为了活命 if our cause is to survive
我们中一定要有人找到保持理智的方法 some of us must find a way to keep our wits about us
为了那些意志力薄弱的人 on behalf of those who cannot.
克服恐惧冲破阴霾 See the truth ahead of us
找到前方的真理 through the fear and the haze.
西尔弗先生恐怕 Mr. Silver I fear
关于此事有所妥协 is compromised in this regard.
此时此刻 At this moment...
我觉得我需要一个新的搭档 I find myself in need of a new partner.
我就知道会走到这一步 I knew it would come to this.
我试着警告他 I tried to tell him.
我们交恶 We fight
只会有两个结果 only two outcomes I can see--
要么我死要么你亡 I die or you die.
不管什么结果他都会怪罪于我 Either way he's gonna take me to blame for it.
你在他心里的地位就有这么重要 That's how far you've burrowed into his head.
他不会对你置之不理 He won't put you out of it
直到他看清楚你的为人 until he sees you for what you are.
走 Go.
你现在看到了吗 Do you see it now?
你看到了吗 Do you see it?
准备出发 Prepare a launch.
弗林特船长杀了我一个手下 Captain Flint killed one of my men
把宝藏偷走了 and managed to haul the cache to shore.
我来这里是希望可以在你得知消息前 I came in the hopes my presence might buy us some time
攒足时间 before you reacted to this news...
好让我可以对形势做点补救 and until I am able to remedy the situation.
什么样的补救措施 What sort of remedy is that?
我派了六个人追捕他 I sent six of my men after him.
我剩下的人中最好的人手 The best men I have left.
他们的任务毫不含糊 Their orders in no uncertain terms
就是追捕弗林特船长 are to track Captain Flint
夺回宝藏 and retrieve the cache.
还有一个任务 There was another order...
不是吗 wasn't there?
没错 Yes.
你还叫他们干什么 What else did you tell them to do?
我叫他们杀掉弗林特船长 I instructed them to kill Captain Flint.