Hi, I'm Leah and this  is Tuesday morning's Newround.
The Vikings are back  in York, but don't worry!
And check out the largest  maze in Spain.
But first this morning,  around 51,000 children
able to join the scouts,  beavers or cubs.
there's a big shortage of volunteers  in areas like Surrey,
It means waiting lists can't fall  unless more adults join
They also say those who are signed  up currently aren't able
We have had a massive increase in  the number of adult volunteers in
Scouting, which is incredible but we  have also got the longest ever
waiting list for young people.  51,000 young people are waiting to
join Scouting. We need even more  adults to take the opportunity of
volunteering to give those young  people a life changing experience.
One of Britain's biggest  tourist attractions,
the Jorvik Centre in York,  has reopened again over a year
after it was forced to close  because of flooding.
We sent Ricky up for the reopening  and to find out about it.
This is the Jorvik Centre,  one of the most popular
museums and visitor  attractions in the UK.
They are finally reopening the doors  after severe flooding
When those floodwaters  came in there was
In some parts of the museum  it was about one metre high,
Most of us were at home enjoying  Christmas and we got a call,
I got a call to say water  was coming in the back door.
We called in the conservation team,  the collections team, to come and
There are 1,000 objects  here and we had to get
Luckily, everything  in the museum was saved.
Some of the items in  here are priceless.
A lot of hard work,  a lot of people involved.
We decided early on we wanted to do  something different.
Schoolkids have been coming  to this museum for more
Because it is a really cool place  and a lot could have been damaged.
It was amazing how  civilised we were then.
It really brought the  Viking period to life
and there were lots of different  things that were really interesting.
This team have worked hard  to protect the museum from future
flooding so people can continue to  see what the Vikings did
In sport, Crystal Palace  boosted their chances of staying
after beating Arsenal  three-nil.
Arsenal's poor form puts more  pressure on manager Arsene Wenger,
who hasn't confirmed  whether he is signing a new contract
For now, he's staying tight-lipped  about his future at the club.
Tonight I am not in the mood to  speak about that. Wind you think you
will be...? I think at the moment it  is about paying more respect to the
fact that we had a disappointing  result and focus on that and not
find as well excuses that are not  excuses.
The first ever cargo train  from the UK to China
On an epic 7,500-mile  journey over 18 days.
It took loads of things to sell,  like fizzy drinks and medicines.
But what would you see, and need,  if you took the trip?
As the train pulls out of the base  in Essex it will travel
towards the Channel Tunnel,  meaning it
After resurfacing in France  you will travel on through
If you have a sweet tooth,  you might expect it to be
filled with fancy chocolate,  but instead you will see a lot of...
After cruising through  Germany, next is Poland.
It is one of nine countries  in the European Union that
Make sure you take some  Polish coins with you
If temperatures drop and it  snows, it might be worth
picking up a traditional Russian hat  with ear flaps to keep warm.
Kazakhstan is made up of a lot  of flat desert,
That is where Major Tim Peake  and his crew launched to get
to the ISS and landed  safely back on Earth.
China is famous for tea, The Great  Wall and making lots of things
Train bosses say the  7,500-mile trip to the
Chinese city by train is faster  than by sea and cheaper than by air.
And finally, we see a lot  of a-mazing things here
This is the largest maze in Spain -  its made from 4,000 trees,
is over five kilometres long  and it'll take you about an hour
Go online to find out why this  month's full moon is called
That's all we've got  time for this morning,
Newsround's back this  afternoon at 4:20.
Have a great day. I will see you  tomorrow. Goodbye.