[man 1] Nobody move!
[woman] No!
-[gun cocks]
-[woman panting]
My name is Tokyo.
But when this story started,
that wasn't my name...
SUSPECT ON THE RUN
HEIST LEAVES THREE DEAD
That was me.
And that was... the love of my life.
ONE ASSAILANT KILLED
The last time I saw him, I left him
in a puddle of blood, eyes wide open.
[sobbing]
We pulled off 15 perfect heists.
But mixing love and business
is never a good idea.
So, when the security guard fired...
I had to switch careers...
from thief to murderer.
And that's when I ran away.
In a way, I was dead too.
Or almost dead.
[suspenseful music plays]
FOR SALE
I'd been hiding for 11 days.
My picture was in every precinct in Spain.
I'd get thirty years, and to be honest...
growing old in a prison cell
is not for me.
I'd rather flee.
In body and soul.
And if I can't take my body with me...
at least my soul can flee.
[phone line rings]
I was running out of time,
and there were important things to do.
Well, one really.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
[Tokyo] Mom?
Oh, my little girl...
How are you, sweetheart?
What's going on?
[Tokyo] You've seen the news, right?
All the things they're saying about me.
Of course I've seen it.
You know what?
I'm thinking of going on a trip.
Maybe I'll get a job on a Chinese boat.
As a cook.
Didn't you used to say
I couldn't fry an egg?
That way I can learn. What do you think?
I don't know, sweetheart...
What if they only eat Chinese food?
Does this trip mean...
that I won't see you again?
Don't be silly.
Of course you will.
I'll buy you a ticket,
so you can come and see me.
To where?
The graveyard?
Are you alone?
-Mom, are you alone?
-Yes.
[Tokyo] Then go down to the street,
go towards the grocery store.
I'll find you.
That day,
the day I was going to be slaughtered...
My guardian angel showed up.
You can never be sure
of what a guardian angel looks like.
But, what you'd never expect,
is for him to show up in '92 SEAT Ibiza.
Sorry, do you have a minute?
No.
There's an upside
to cooking on a Chinese boat...
You don't have to wash dishes.
[Tokyo] For a minute
I thought about the Chinese...
and how I hate when people spit.
-Who are you? Police?
-Wait. You're heading to your slaughter.
Intervention Task Force
is waiting for you,
-they've been following you for six days--
-Why should I believe you?
[Tokyo]
And that's how I met the Professor.
Pointing a gun at his balls.
May I?
[Tokyo]
The good thing about relationships,
is that we end up forgetting
how they started.
May I?
They're already at your mother's house.
That's why I came to help you.
I have a business proposition.
A heist. A heist quite...
unique.
I'm looking for people who...
Well, who don't have much to lose.
How does...
2.4 billion euros sound to you?
[Tokyo] No one has ever hit that hard.
Not even in New York,
London, or Monte Carlo.
So, if my picture is going to be
in the news again...
at least it will be
for the greatest heist in history.
♪ Now hear our rules ♪
♪ We're not alone in this crazy thing ♪
♪ And here we are ♪
♪ Losing our head, we pulled it off ♪
♪ Use your head ♪
♪ Be a fool
You want it all ♪
♪ Want it all ♪
-♪ Ah ♪
-♪ Use your head ♪
♪ Be a fool
You want it ♪
WELCOME
[Professor] I welcome you...
and...
I thank you for agreeing to this...
-this job offer.
-[Denver chuckles]
We'll live here.
Away from the maddening crowd.
For five months, we're going to study
how we're going to pull off this heist.
What do you mean "five months"?
Are you nuts?
Look... people spend years at school...
to earn a salary,
which even in the best scenario,
is a shitty one.
What's five months?
I've been thinking about this...
for much longer.
So I don't have to work ever again.
Nor will you.
Or your children.
All right.
Currently, you don't know each other.
And I want to keep it that way.
I don't want names...
or personal questions.
And, obviously, no personal relations.
I want each of you to pick a name.
Something simple.
Could be numbers, planets, cities--
Like, Mr. 17 and Ms. 23?
We're off on a bad start,
I can't even remember my phone number.
That's why I tell you.
[Rio] Planets?
I can be Mars and this one, Uranus.
I'm not Uranus, so forget it.
-[man] What's wrong with Uranus?
-Sounds wrong.
We'll use cities. Cities.
We agree on cities.
Good.
[Tokyo]
That's how I came to call myself Tokyo.
That one looking at my ass is Mr. Berlin.
He has a warrant out for his arrest.
Twenty-seven robberies. Jewelry stores,
auction houses, and armored vehicles.
His biggest score:
Champs Elysees, Paris, 434 diamonds.
He's like a shark in a pool.
You can swim with him,
but you're always nervous.
He was in charge of the heist.
[man coughing]
The one coughing is Mr. Moscow.
The first thing he dug
was a mine in Asturias.
Later on, he figured out
he'd go further by digging up.
Six fur shops, three watch shops,
and the Rural Credit Union of Avilés.
He works the thermal lance
and every industrial tool there is.
The one behind Moscow is Denver. His son.
Drugs, broken teeth, broken ribs.
He's the king of bar brawling.
Pure, hot-blooded. In a perfect heist...
a time bomb.
Rio... He's my weakness.
He's the Mozart of computers.
He's been coding since he was six
and knows everything
about alarms and electronics.
For everything else in life,
it's like he was born yesterday.
And then you have the twins,
Helsinki and Oslo.
Even with the most bulletproof plan,
soldiers are necessary...
and what's better than two Serbs.
It's possible they can think.
But, frankly, we'll never know.
Nairobi.
Hopeless optimist.
She's been counterfeiting since age 13.
Now she's our quality control manager.
It's possible she's nuts,
but she's so damned funny.
To think that every day
the news will be talking about us.
That every family in this country
will be asking themselves:
"What are we doing?"
You know what they'll think?
"Those motherfuckers.
I wish I'd thought of that first."
[Tokyo] The Professor.
No criminal record.
Hasn't renewed his ID since he was 19.
For all purposes, a ghost.
But a very smart ghost.
Because we're not stealing...
anyone's money.
Because they'll even like us.
And that's imperative.
It's imperative that we have
the public opinion on our side.
We'll be fucking heroes
to all these people.
But, be very careful...
because the minute there's a single drop
of blood, this is very important...
If there's one single victim...
we'll no longer be Robin Hoods,
we'll just be plain motherfuckers.
Professor...
Miss Tokyo.
What are we robbing?
[Professor] The Royal Mint of Spain.
["My Life Is Going On"
by Cecilia Krull playing]
♪ If I stay with you ♪
♪ If I'm choosing wrong
I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now
Then I'm winning late ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
♪ Lost my time ♪
♪ My life is going on ♪
HEIST D DAY
FRIDAY, 8:35 AM
Who chose these masks?
-[Moscow] What's wrong with them?
-[Rio] They're not scary.
In every single movie,
the robbers wear scary masks.
Zombies, skeletons, Angel of Death--
[Berlin] With a gun in hand,
a nut job is scarier than a skeleton.
-Enough.
-Who's this hick with the mustache?
Dalí, son. A Spanish painter.
A very good one.
-A painter.
-Yes.
-A painter that paints.
[scoffs]
You know what's really scary?
Children's dolls. Those are pretty scary.
-What dolls?
-Goofy, Pluto, Mickey Mouse, all of those.
[Rio] A mouse with big ears is scarier.
-That's what you think?
-Yes, asshole.
-You want me to punch you?
-[Moscow] Hey.
I'm right. Listen...
If some hick with a gun goes anywhere
wearing a Mickey Mouse mask,
people will think he's nuts,
that he's there for a bloodbath,
and you know why?
Because weapons and kids...
are two things you never put together.
Right, Dad?
Well, if you see it that way,
it's more dangerous, right?
More devious.
A Jesus mask
would be even more terrifying.
He's even more innocent.
That's why they said,
"Better two guns than a crucifix."
-"Like a Saint, two guns."
-[Moscow] What's the difference?
[Tokyo] It was obvious this gang
needed more women.
A woman can spend two days
choosing shoes for a wedding...
but not even a single minute
choosing masks for a robbery.
Everything we had planned
was starting now.
In those microseconds
I thought of all the innocent people
whose lives would come to a sudden stop
because of us.
STATE HIGHWAY E-80
9:25 AM
The Professor knew there was only one way
to enter the Royal Mint
with a three-ton arsenal.
That was through the truck
that came in each week
with the new rolls of currency paper
ready for printing.
That was exactly what we were doing.
Getting all the way in,
escorted by the National Police.
DETOUR TO RASCAFRÍA
In Spain, anything guarded by two Zs...
is heavily protected.
[siren wailing]
But if you prevent
any radio or phone communications,
and you point five assault rifles
at the heads of two 26-year-old kids...
regardless how well armed they are,
they'll do what any of us would.
[Berlin] I said get out, damn it!
[Denver] Out of the fucking car!
[Tokyo] They'll shit their pants.
[Denver] You do what say! Understand?
[Tokyo] Courage and heroism
come with a price,
and it's much higher than 1600 euros
a month made by a guy in uniform...
[Berlin] Open the door! Do you hear me?
[Tokyo] ...or by a truck driver.
[Moscow] For fuck's sake! Open it!
[Tokyo] If those men had their daughters
inside the back of the truck,
they wouldn't have opened it.
But who cares about some
rolls of watermarked paper?
[Nairobi] Hurry! Hurry!
Move, dude. Come on!
Close your eyes!
Go! Go! Go! Sit there.
Now, the three of you keep quiet,
or I'll smash your heads.
You'll be driving
with a gun pointed at your kidneys.
So, when they call you on the radio
to check on everything,
you'll answer calmly.
Like everything's going nice and easy.
Is that clear?
[Tokyo] In the middle of all the chaos
with the guns...
I remembered the marriage proposal
I'd had the night before...
and how I'd rather have other plans.
If you give it a lot of thought,
you'll never find a good day for a heist.
Now you know what you have to do.
Don't take your eyes off the girl.
There can be no mistakes.
-Are we clear?
-She's 17.
I think I can handle her.
[laughing]
[phone beeps]
CAN I SIT NEXT TO YOU?
YES
Hello.
Hi.
Do you want to go out with me?
All right, I'll leave you alone.
No, no.
I don't have to think about it.
Yes.
[teacher] All right, kids, we're here.
We'll go directly to the museum's lobby,
where we'll wait
for the rest of the class...
[tour guide] This is the front entrance
of the Royal Mint.
The little lamb just entered.
Perfect.
Berlin, it's your turn.
ROYAL MINT
10:16 AM
[Berlin] Now, be very careful
with what you do.
What's up, Javi? Where's Rafita?
He changed his shift.
[coughing]
[sneezes]
[Berlin] That's very good. Relax.
[tour guide] Let's start heading in.
[unintelligible dialogue]
[grand entrance music plays]
Please put your credentials
around your necks.
They must be visible at all times.
[Arturo] Don't turn around.
When you're near, I can barely breathe.
Well, breathe...
because in nine months,
you'll be out of breath.
Go ahead.
[tour guide] Visible at all times.
All right, kids?
Credentials around the neck.
Lower your voice.
POLICE
Berlin, first camera on your left.
NATIONAL POLICE
You won't say anything?
I tell you I'm pregnant, and nothing?
What you want me to do, Mónica?
Call my wife, tell her to get the kids,
and we'll all go celebrate together?
For God's sake!
[guard] Go. Go.
Okay, okay.
ACCESSING SECURITY NETWORK
[Rio] One...
Ready, Tokyo.
[guard] Go. Go.
ACCESSING CENTRAL ALARM STATION
Yes!
-Alarms disconnected.
-Now.
[guard] Okay, okay.
Just yesterday
you said you couldn't stand her anymore.
-That you've been having problems.
-Like any other couple, Mónica.
The same as any marriage with three kids.
Not that I was leaving her.
Mónica, I had three kids.
All through artificial insemination.
For more than 20 years
I had infertile sex with my wife,
now you tell me this.
You must be Shiva, the fertility goddess.
[tense music plays]
[beeping]
What are you implying?
I'm not here looking for child support...
or for a divorce.
Even less, for a paternity test.
I thought you loved me.
And...
the idea of it seems nice.
Not easy to fit in our lives, though--
A wonderful idea.
-Listen.
-What?
You want to know
what I'm going to do with your child?
Is that what you want?
Listen to me, don't get carried away--
[people screaming]
[Oslo] Don't move!
Hold it right there.
[alarm blaring]
-Don't move!
Or I'll blow you in half!
[guard] That's it! Unload!
[shouting]
[Helsinki] Stay calm!
[Oslo] Let's go!
[Helsinki] Hurry!
[Oslo] Stay there!
Crap.
[man] Let's go.
This way. Let's go.
This wonderful stairway,
-made of marble and granite--
-[Moscow] Don't move!
[screaming]
Stop! Go back! Come on!
[woman] Please! No!
Professor, we have a problem!
[screams]
I can't find the little lamb.
I don't see her! Fuck!
Miss Parker...
where did you go?
[people screaming]
[Nairobi] Come on! Hurry!
Let's go!
Wait.
Okay.
I'm going too fast. I know.
[Ariadna] Please!
We should immortalize this moment, right?
Let's take a pic with your phone. Wait...
Here? It's kind of shabby,
don't you think?
This is our first day.
You look gorgeous.
I can't find the girl.
I can't find her. Fuck.
Unbutton your shirt, make it sexier.
It's on your phone.
You can delete it if you want.
This is just for us.
Here we go, okay.
[camera shutters]
With this picture,
you'll be killing it on the Internet.
Give it back! Give me the phone!
[Alison] Give me the phone!
I told you to give me the phone!
Give me the phone!
Give me the fucking phone!
[Alison screams]
[increasingly tense music plays]
[people whimpering]
[Berlin] First of all...
Good morning.
I'm the man in charge.
And first of all, I want...
to offer my apologies.
[Denver] PIN? Name?
This is not a good way to end your week.
But you're here as hostages.
[Denver] Cell phone.
If you comply,
I assure you you'll get out alive.
-[Denver] Name?
-[Alison] Alison Parker.
-[Denver] PIN?
-[Alison] Two-zero-eighteen.
[Denver] Cell phone.
[Berlin] It's okay.
-It's okay.
-PIN?
What do you need the PIN for?
Give me the fucking PIN,
or I beat it out of you. You decide.
How many months?
-Eight.
-Eight months?
PIN.
One-two-three-four.
You look all clever,
and that's your shitty PIN?
What an idiot. Name.
-Arturo. Arturo Román.
-What else?
Arturo Román. Very well. Arturito.
You're our safe passage,
so I will protect you.
Hey.
Give me your hands. Let go.
Let go.
What's your name?
Ariadna.
Ariadna...
Come with me. It's okay.
Feel my hands.
-Are those the hands of a monster?
-No.
Because I'm not a monster.
I know exactly how you feel.
Dry mouth, out of breath.
You need to try to calm down.
Breathe, breathe.
Breathe.
That's it.
Please, everyone, breathe with me.
Breathe.
Slow, slow.
Take control of your breathing. Exhale.
That's it.
[phone ringing]
Miss Mónica Gaztambide, please.
Don't move, please. Don't move.
They won't touch us.
Okay.
Miss Mónica Gaztambide!
Would you be so kind as to step forward?
That's me.
[metal clangs]
[clicks, then beeps]
[clicks, then beeping rapidly]
[Denver] You're the man, Dad.
You're the bomb.
You get to sleep great in here, Dad.
Like a king.
Dad, Dad!
To fuck, here...
Boom, boom, boom...
Stop being silly and let's get to work.
Come on.
This smells fucking great.
Better than roasted lamb, Dad.
-Come lay down here.
-Damn it.
When have you had a bed like this before?
Not in the slammer.
Have you seen where we are?
We're big time!
We're very big time!
Kid, don't be mistaken.
We're small.
Can you do anything else?
Have you ever had a proper job?
Have you taken your résumé anywhere?
Damn it.
A résumé?
What for?
To get you out of jail?
Do you think I'm proud of that?
Going in and out of prison
for twelve years.
You know why?
Why?
Because I'm not very smart, son.
Neither are you.
But, in this job,
someone else is putting in the brains.
If we're lucky, and you don't fool around,
you'll get out of here
with your life sorted out.
-What you mean by fool around?
-Come on, damn it.
Fill up those.
[phone ringing]
I want you to answer the phone
and convince them
we're shut down due to technical problems.
Got it?
Yes.
I have no choice
but to point a gun at you.
-Can you feel it?
-Yes.
All right.
Now.
-Royal Mint, can I help you?
-[woman] May I speak with Arturo, please.
I'm sorry, Mr. Arturo
can't be reached at the moment.
The system is down.
No, I can't ask him to come upstairs.
No, he's not able to answer the phone.
No, it's not possible.
No--
[woman] I don't understand why.
Because, I don't know--
I don't know where he is right now.
I don't know if he's in the mint,
the museum, or the cafeteria.
Besides, that's not my job, miss!
That performance deserves an Oscar...
Miss Gaztambide.
[clanking]
[Tokyo] Twenty minutes in,
we started wiring
our analog communications system
to talk to the Professor.
[singing indistinctly]
Cellphone free. No radio frequencies.
So no one could hear us.
We sealed all the doors,
and the alarms haven't gone off yet.
We're in a kind of limbo.
Without anyone knowing
that we've seized the Royal Mint.
And during that sweet calm
before the storm...
it simply seems...
like just another day.
You're actually handsome.
[knock on door]
-Who is it?
-[Rio] It's me. Let me in.
What are you doing, Rio?
If the Professor sees us, he'll kill us.
I know. Come here, I need to talk to you.
-Come here. Sit down.
-What's going on?
What's going on?
The heist is tomorrow.
We have no fucking idea what will happen.
I want you to know
that I'm serious about you.
And... I completely understand that--
That you're a woman of certain age...
and it's possible you're looking
for a more serious commitment.
That's why I want to give you this.
I didn't get you a ring
because we're stuck in here.
But when I'm out of here,
I'll get you the king of all diamonds.
You'll have to put your hand
in a fucking wheelbarrow.
What is this?
An engagement plaque?
Now, at least you'll know my real name.
Yeah, but knowing our real names
is not allowed.
Well, don't look at it.
But it's yours.
How can I tell you this?
What we have has been very good.
Okay? Awesome.
-We've been together a few nights...
-A few nights?
Damn, every night.
Except for, what, four or five?
Honestly...
I don't think we're meant for each other.
-Don't we have good sex?
-Yes, we have good sex.
Well, that's a good start, right?
But it takes more than good sex
to make a good couple.
Are you saying this because
I'm 12 years younger than you?
I'm getting 300 million euros.
I'm not a kid. My life's sorted out.
-Really, Rio, I wish it was love, but--
-Hey, don't say that.
There was love. I was there.
There's somebody else, right?
Not anymore.
Look, Rio...
When this is all over,
we'll go to Tahiti together,
and we'll see how that works.
But tomorrow
I only have one thing on my mind:
Not getting killed.
Rio.
Rio, no...
No, no.
One of the phones in buzzing.
Turn it off.
The vault is open.
Put on your vest, and be ready to leave.
When you're ready,
we'll activate the alarm.
Berlin, get ready to open the doors.
Hostages!
For your own safety,
move three steps back!
A little bit more this way. That's it.
There you go.
Everything will be all right.
A little bit closer.
Everything's going to be okay.
-[Monica whimpers]
-Shh.
Relax.
Calm down. I'm looking at the bags.
They're filled with money.
They'll be out of here in no time.
[radio static, beeping]
[alarm blaring]
[woman] We have a 10-33 at the Royal Mint.
[man] Z-24, on our way.
-We'll be there in two minutes.
-Two minutes.
Two minutes.
Why did the alarm go off?
I don't know.
They're just standing there.
I don't understand.
-Why not just take the money and leave?
-I don't know.
One minute, 40 seconds.
One minute--
What's your name?
Arturo.
-Arturo, right?
-Yes.
I haven't seen anything!
-I haven't seen anything, I swear!
-Look at me.
-I haven't seen anything.
-Come on, Arturo. Look.
-No.
-Look at me.
Look at me. Hey, hey.
Come on.
Hey.
Do you like movies?
Do you?
Yes.
I'm very fond of movies.
Okay, and have you noticed
how in horror movies...
at the beginning
there's always this nice guy,
just like you, that makes you think...
"He's going to get killed."
Yes.
And then it happens.
He always gets killed.
Believe me, Arturo...
You're going to get yourself killed.
[man] Z-24 to Central,
we're 30 seconds away.
Thirty seconds.
It is imperative that the police
have no idea what we're doing.
We'll make them believe
we are there to rob the place.
We were caught with the money,
and everything got screwed up.
We pull out the guns
and fire without warning,
as though we didn't have
any other choice...
than to back down.
And then...
without having hurt anyone...
We go back inside.
Let them think...
that we're cornered like rats.
Let them think we're winging it.
[Tokyo] Now!
Tokyo! Tokyo, wait! Damn it!
Tokyo!
[Tokyo] Go out, drop the money,
start firing without warning,
and get back inside.
I heard that more than 30 times.
What the Professor didn't tell us
is that they would also fire
without warning.
Rio!
["My Life Is Going On"
by Cecilia Krull playing]
Bloody hell!
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
Rio.
Rio!
The fucking first rule!
Fuck!
♪ I don't care at all ♪
Rio.
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
Fuck!
[man] Requesting immediate back up
at the Royal Mint.
We've taken hostile fire.
Man down. I repeat, man down.
[Tokyo] The bullet of a M16 fires
at 2100 miles per hour.
Faster than the speed of sound.
So, if they shoot in you in the heart...
you won't even hear
the bullet that killed you.
That's how I knew
that I fucked it all up...
in one microsecond...
and in the same way as usual.