My name is Barry Allen, and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
Run, Barry, run!
My father went to prison for her murder.
Then an accident made me the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, I use my speed to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find who killed my mother...
Mom! And get justice for my father.
I am The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
If you ever need anything,
I will race over in a heartbeat.
Same. Well, as fast as I can run.
Advanced Technology Operating Mechanism--A.T.O.M.
What are you gonna use it for?
To protect the people of this city.
You think Dr. Wells killed Barry's mom?
I don't know yet.
But I do know that Wells keeps secrets.
The way that he described running--
feeling the wind and the power--
it's like he was talking from experience.
Harrison Wells is The Reverse-Flash.
Eddie, we need your help.
Pedal to the metal.
We've got a 10-31 in progress.
Shiny Diamond, 18th and Olive.
That's only a few blocks from here.
Has every crook in Central City gone crazy?
This is the third attempted robbery tonight.
Barry. We got another one.
Hello.
18th and Olive.
Got it.
Who's this?
Oh. Indecent exposure. Powell Park.
That ain't something you should be showing people.
They're getting away, guys.
They're not getting away, Eddie.
Let's get these bozos up ahead of us first,
and then we'll worry about the idiots at the Shiny Diamond.
All right.
We're gonna run out of room, though.
I'll take care of that.
What do you think he meant by that?
Oh. That's what he meant.
I think we lost them.
Oh, no, you didn't.
And by the way, you're under arrest.
We need to go. Now. Come on!
Uh-uh. Freeze.
You guys missing these?
On the ground. On the ground.
So, uh, I'm just curious, but...
have you guys not heard of me, or what?
Nice work, detective.
- Good night, Dr. Kang. - Good night.
Victim's name is Lindsay Kang,
engineering professor at Hudson University.
Just got tenure.
So, her whole body's covered in these puncture wounds
you see on her face.
Bite marks maybe.
Whatever it was, she must have gone into anaphylaxis.
- Damn. - Yeah.
The blood sample should tell us
everything we need to know.
I'll run tests back at my lab.
They can do it faster at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Well, yeah, but, I mean, it's just...
It's just what?
It's kind of weird being there right now.
Barry, you know we have to play it cool with Wells.
If he finds out we suspect him--
I know. I get it.
I just think that we should tell Cisco and Caitlin.
They could help us.
The more people who know, the more chance
Wells is gonna find out we're on to him.
I mean, what if one of them slips up?
Or panics?
- Or what if... - What?
What if they're not on our side?
No. Absolutely not.
They're not involved in whatever he's planning.
I mean, Wells is their boss, their mentor.
They've been with him for a long time.
I've seen plenty of people make the wrong choice for loyalty.
Please do not include them until we can be sure.
All right.
Death by apitoxin.
Honeybee venom.
Bees. Why did it have to be bees?
Y'all, I don't do bees.
Ain't nobody got time for bees.
But when a honeybee stings,
the stingers are literally torn from their abdomen,
and they die.
But there were no stingers in the body
and no dead bees in the car.
A honeybee can only deposit 0.1 milligrams of apitoxin
when it releases its stinger.
And yet, Ms. Kang was found
with enough venom in her system to kill a herd of elephants.
It appears not only is a meta-human controlling these bees
but also increasing their toxicity.
Bees communicate by releasing pheromones.
Maybe this meta's controlling them through secretion?
Anyone want to join me in getting a beekeeper suit?
I'm pretty sure I can outrun a bee.
Just don't run into a lake.
Bees will wait for you to come up for air
and then they'll sting you.
Discovery Channel. Turns out there's a lot to discover.
Felicity, what are you doing here?
Can you guys come outside for a sec?
What exactly are we waiting for, Ms. Smoak?
Up there.
Is that a bird?
It's a plane.
It's my boyfriend.
Hi. I'm Ray.
So he seems a little tall for you.
Barry Allen, are you jealous?
Je... no. No, I'm not jealous.
I just-- I really wish you would've called
before flying in.
Oh no, He flied, I drove.
I'm serious, all right?
Now is not the best time.
Why? What's going on?
Well, my ears popped, so that's something.
You're lucky you didn't break your neck.
What is it with billionaires being superheroes?
So have you... picked a name yet?
I'm kind of partial to The Atom.
You married to that, or...?
Your A.T.O.M. Suit...
it's quite the technological achievement, Mr. Palmer.
I'm impressed.
And he is never impressed.
Well, thank you,
but I can't quite seem to keep it up.
He means the suit.
- Yeah, I mean the suit. - Yeah.
I can attest that everything else works just fine.
There's nothing we need to fix in...
that area.
No, no, no. The sex is great.
God, there's two of them.
I know from Felicity that you have been very helpful
with Barry and the Flash suit,
and I was hoping to get another set of eyes on my...
- Problem. - Problem.
Any friend of The Arrow's is a friend--
- Hell, yes. - Guys.
We kind of have a lot going on already.
There's the meta-human killer
that can control a whole swarm of bees?
Cool.
I mean, awful.
I'm sure Caitlin and I
will provide ample support, Barry.
And I will be happy to sit this one out.
You...
Ray, why don't you stay here and work on your suit
while Barry and I run to Jitters for some java?
Sounds like a plan.
- Coffee? - Sure.
- Hey, Detective. - Iris.
What are you doing here?
I am following up on my story
about crime in Central City.
Or lack thereof.
Could someone be working with The Flash?
No. Of course not.
You caught a flasher,
armed robbers in a getaway car,
and two jewelry thieves last night.
I'm just that good.
What is going on with you lately?
You've been acting really weird and withdrawn.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd think that you were hiding something from me.
Iris, I'm-- I'm not hiding anything from you.
Do you ever go to work?
Oh, you're funny.
Okay, I can't keep lying to Iris about The Flash.
You have to.
It's really starting to affect our relationship.
We haven't had sex in two weeks.
Which you didn't want to know about.
Keeping her in the dark keeps her safe.
I don't agree.
Well, I'm her father.
And I'm her boyfriend.
When does my vote outweigh yours?
When you become her husband.
You know I left Starling City
to get away from the mood and brood,
but it looks like it followed me here.
I know. I'm sorry.
It's like I said before,
now is not the best time.
Barry, I have been through enough with you
to know when you're holding something back.
Is this because I told Ray your secret?
Because he is trustworthy, Barry.
He wants to help people, just like you.
I know, that's not what I'm worried about.
It's...
I really don't want to put anyone else in danger.
In danger of what?
Barry, hey.
Eddie, hey.
- You remember Felicity. - Of course.
Great to see you.
Yeah.
What is wrong with you?
Is everyone in Central City in a bad mood?
I thought Central City was supposed to be the fun one.
It's...
- It's not... - Felicity knows.
So everyone but Iris.
It feels that way.
How do you lie to everyone you care about?
For starters,
don't think of it as lying.
Think of it as protecting her from getting hurt...
with a fib.
But Iris can tell I'm hiding something,
and it's putting this distance between us.
I have an idea.
Why don't we all go to dinner tonight?
A little wine and dine is sure to bridge the gap.
Come on, we all had fun last time.
Sure. Why not?
Barry Allen, fifth wheel.
Well, I can't make my 3:00 meeting this afternoon.
also, confirm my dinner reservation for tonight.
Last time, they couldn't find it,
and that was unacceptable. Thanks.
You see that bad man over there?
Tell your sisters it's time.
So you put solid oxide fuel cells into the belt?
Yeah, it's the only place to hide the hardware.
Well, they should be generating enough energy
to power the suit.
It could be the operating temperature.
I mean, you're essentially--
Overheating the system, yeah. I figured.
But if we insulate them
with a ceramic compound...
We may improve the operating efficiency.
You really are quite clever, Cisco.
Some would say I'm the reverse.
You're incredibly clever, Cisco.
How do you turn this thing on?
Cisco? You okay?
Yeah.
I haven't been getting enough sleep...
Cisco, we need you up here.
Killer bees are at it again.
Get a hold of Barry.
Another bee attack. Folston Tech.
I'll see where Joe is.
- Bee careful. - For real?
Bad pun. Sorry. Just don't die.
I'm too late.
Where are the bees?
I don't know. There's no sign of them.
Found them.
How do I get out of here?
Take the northeast crossway.
It's the quickest way out of the building.
Guys, they're everywhere. I'm surrounded.
Barry!
Barry.
He's going into cardiac arrest.
Barry, stay with me.
Cisco! Barry doesn't have a pulse.
- Step away from him. - What? Why?
We need to jumpstart his heart.
There's a defibrillator in the suit.
Charge it to 360 joules.
Charging in three, two, one.
Hit him again. 400 joules.
Barry.
Joe.
That is it for the defibrillator.
It is completely fried.
You're lucky to be alive, Mr. Allen.
I was very specific that you not die.
Yeah, that's a pretty big thing for her.
Cisco, what happened out there?
I followed your directions exactly.
I'm sorry. I led you the wrong way.
The schematics that we had,
they... they weren't up to date.
What, they weren't up to date?
What do you mean?
That's never happened before.
What, you think Cisco was trying to get you killed?
No. Why would he do that?
That doesn't make any sense.
I know. That's why I was joking.
Barry, it's our job to protect you,
and today, we failed,
but that'll just serve as a warning
for all of us to be more vigilant in the future.
Good news -- the apitoxin is out of your body.
Your levels are back to normal.
Terrific.
Ray, Felicity. We're gonna be late for dinner.
Are you sure that's wise, Barry?
You just died.
Maybe you should order in tonight.
Yeah, we could totally cancel.
I'm fine. Alive. Hungry.
All right? Let's go.
That was weird.
Yeah. Why didn't we get invited to dinner?
Thank you.
Hey, guys.
Wow, Iris. Check you out.
Hi, Felicity.
Hello.
Guys, this is Ray Palmer.
Nice to meet you.
Lovely to meet you.
- Nice to meet you. - Barry.
Bienvenue chez Massimo Restaurant.
Mr. Palmer, your table is ready.
Great. Shall we?
Yes.
Hey, how did he get a reservation here?
We've been trying for months.
I don't know.
Here's your table, sir.
I thought it'd be nice if it was quiet,
so I bought out the entire restaurant.
Too much?
Just a tad, sweetie.
Joe.
Oh, Cisco.
You just saved me a trip to S.T.A.R. Labs.
I got some info on our second victim.
Name's Bill Carlisle.
He was recently hired at Folston Tech
to beef up their Robotics Division.
Robotics?
That's just like the first victim.
That is weird.
That's not why you stopped by.
No, I wanted to talk to you about Barry.
Okay.
Is there something going on with him?
Something he's not telling us?
What do you mean?
He hasn't really been himself lately.
Not that I'm aware of.
It's like something is just really bothering him.
Well, I think he's got his mind trained on
catching the bad guys, Cisco.
And he's probably worried about
when The Reverse-Flash is gonna show his face again.
Oh, I'm not like The Flash at all.
Some would say I'm the reverse.
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah, no, I'm fine.
It's just--I've got this crazy headache.
Thank you for the file and the talk.
So how did you two meet?
Work.
Well, actually,
I bought the company where Felicity was employed,
and so she was forced to join me at Palmer Tech.
It's not as creepy as it sounds.
So you two work closely together?
Interesting.
I guess you guys share all of your thoughts
and feelings and...
Yeah... I share everything with Felicity.
It's nice that you guys have that level of communication.
Oh, well, no, not every-everything.
I mean, sometimes it's good to just shut up.
I get that.
Some things are better left unspoken.
Really?
I-I don't find that to be true.
Oh, thank God. It's the food.
Food's here.
Our first course on the tasting menu
is a quail egg frittata.
Bon appetit.
Barry.
I got to admit,
I envy you spending so much time at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Harrison Wells is, like, a personal hero of mine.
I mean, it's amazing just to actually
be in the same room with him.
I'll be right back. Just excuse me.
Okay.
Well, I, um...
have to pee.
Okay, you've been acting super strange
ever since Ray and I got to Central City.
What is going on with you?
And don't say it's a bad time.
Oliver might be joining the League of Assassins,
Laurel's the Black Canary,
and Thea's training with Malcolm,
so I know about bad times.
Okay.
Joe and I found out that Wells isn't who he says he is.
He...
He is the man that killed my mother.
Oh, my God. But he's been helping you.
Get faster, stronger. I know.
- Why? - I don't know.
I don't know anything anymore,
especially who I can and can't trust.
So you think Cisco and Caitlin are helping him?
That's impossible.
Is it?
Yes. They were trying to save you today, Barry.
They did save you.
Wells has also saved me.
Many times.
I thought that Wells was a great man,
and I was so wrong about him.
What if I'm wrong about everything else too?
Hey, guys.
Uh, things are getting a little intense in here.
Please can't we just have a nice evening?
Okay, so it's my fault
that we're not having a nice evening?
I am your girlfriend. Who you live with.
I shouldn't have to beg you to talk to me.
If I could talk to you about this, I would, believe me.
But I can't.
You know what? I am not hungry anymore.
- Iris. - You know what?
When you are ready to act like
we are two people who love each other,
call me.
I'll be at my dad's.
Thank you for dinner. I've got to go.
Uh, emergency at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Go.
Sorry.
Well, only 17 more courses to go.
Containment breach. Foreign object detected.
Did I get it?
I think I got it.
Where is he?
Thank you.
Let's see what makes this bee so poisonous.
You saved my life.
That is one odd-looking bee.
That's 'cause it isn't a bee at all.
It's a robot.
No way.
Unbelievable.
This bot's got a 360-degree vision system.
I mean, we're talking multiple micro-cameras
all coming from various angles at the same time.
Which means...
It can see all around the room at once.
That is...
Amazing.
Disturbing.
It's also next-gen hardware that'nowhere near the market.
So we're not dealing with a meta-human?
It's just a mad scientist.
Cisco, you said the second victim,
Bill Carlisle, was a robotics engineer.
Let's cross-reference his previous employers
with those of Lindsay Kang.
Allow me.
Mama's been away from a keyboard for far too long.
Okay.
They both worked at Mercury Labs.
Let's call Joe.
I think it's time we paid a visit to an old friend.
Twice in one year, Harrison.
You really are vying for comeback scientist of the year.
Always a pleasure, Christina.
To what do I owe this visit?
Did you finally find my tachyon prototype,
or are you here to blackmail me for another one?
Do you have another one?
We came here for information.
Bill Carlisle and Lindsay Kang.
Former employees who were recently murdered.
My God. I wasn't aware.
Stung to death by robotic bees.
You're looking for Brie Larvan.
Brie Larvan?
A quite brilliant roboticist who once developed
miniature mechanical bees for agricultural use.
Kang and Carlisle warned me
that Brie was weaponizing the bees for military use,
so I terminated her.
Well, it seems that you would
be on her hit list too, Doctor.
You've got to let us keep you safe.
I'm all too familiar
with your inability to protect things, Harrison.
I can take care of myself.
Good day, gentlemen.
Thank you.
Okay, so we found our queen bee.
Brie Larvan. She's a roboticist.
Joe is running a trace on her current location,
but so far nothing.
Good.
Where is Ray?
Oh, he's working on his suit with Cisco.
I like Ray.
He seems like he's a really good guy.
He is a good guy.
Just like Cisco.
And Caitlin. Girl.
Is that why you called me here?
I know that you're in a tricky situation,
but that's when you need your friends to have your back.
And how can they if you won't let them?
It's not that simple.
What if Joe is right,
and I tell them, and it backfires?
Wells isn't just their boss, Felicity.
He is their mentor, their hero.
My hero.
Look, it's...
I don't know what to do.
When I first met Oliver,
before I knew he was The Arrow,
he would--he would ask me to do weird things for him,
like decrypt a bullet-ridden computer,
or hack some company.
And when I would ask him why,
he would come up these ridiculous excuses.
And I always knew he was lying,
but I would help him anyway.
You know why?
Because I knew Oliver was a good person with a good heart.
And Cisco and Caitlin?
They're no different.
So you're really staying here tonight?
Tonight. Tomorrow night.
The night after that.
Do you think that Eddie is cheating on me?
No. Eddie's not that kind of guy.
Well, then I don't know what else
he could be hiding from me.
Iris...
Remember when we were kids,
and Joe would come home from work
with that blank expression on his face?
Yeah.
The "Earth to Joe" Look.
How could I forget?
I never understood that look
until I started workg for the CCPD.
Showing up at crime scenes and seeing someone murdered--
it can be ugly work.
And I'm lucky.
I get to hide behind the science of it
and just stay in my lab,
but Eddie,
he's out there every day in the darkness.
I just--I think that maybe
if he doesn't want to talk to you about his work,
it's probably because he wants to keep you in the light.
What?
I'm just surprised.
You going out of your way like this
to help me see Eddie's point of view.
I mean...
Eddie makes you happy.
All I ever want is for you to be happy, Iris.
Welcome home.
It is so fun to watch grown men play with their toys.
You're so lucky.
Ray is so nice and smart and hot.
Yeah, it's kind of like I'm dating Barry
but in Oliver's body.
A sentence you will never repeat to anyone.
Your secret's safe with me.
It must have re-activated.
And if it's being controlled wirelessly...
I can trace its signal and figure out
where it's trying to go.
- Oh, no. - Oh, boy.
What?
The swarm is headed for Mercury Labs.
Brie Larvan's going after Tina.
Hello, Dr. McGee.
You gonna open the window, or should I buzz myself in?
How do we stop them?
She's got to be remotely piloting
those bees from somewhere.
We need to stop this bug-eyed glasses woman.
And her mini bandits.
Bug-Eyed Bandit.
Got her. She's in an abandoned greenhouse.
Barry, you have to take out Brie.
It's the only way to stop these nano drones.
What about Dr. McGee?
The defibrillator in your suit is broken.
You cannot risk going near Mercury Labs.
Bees can't penetrate my suit.
I'll go.
We haven't tested out the new power system yet.
We'll do it now.
- I'm following you. - I'm driving.
And I'm kissing you.
Dr. Wells...
Mr. Palmer will protect Tina. Go.
You fired me, destroyed years of my research.
You took everything from me.
What you were doing was wrong.
You wanted to harm people, not help them.
I did what I had to do.
You mean ruin my life?
Sure.
Now I'm doing what I have to do.
Found her.
Felicity, can you jam their frequency?
I already tried, but I might be able to redirect them
onto a new target.
Ray, get ready for incoming.
We have the technology.
It's over, Brie.
I know you're trying to kill Dr. McGee.
You think that she betrayed you.
I can imagine how that feels.
You think you understand the sting of betrayal?
I'll show you what it means to be stung.
Barry.
Barry, I hacked into the bees' frequency.
I'm controlling them.
I'm the queen of this hive.
Oh, she's good.
She's like my nemesis.
I've never had a nemesis before.
I kind of like it.
Okay, Cisco. Now what?
Ray, get to the ocean.
If the bots follow you into the water,
their electronics will fry.
Got it.
Wait. But so will my suit.
Cisco, I'm fried.
I'm losing propulsion control.
Can you see the van?
Yeah.
We'll catch you.
- You will? - We will?
We will.
All right.
Keep it steady.
The Atom lives.
Let's work on some softer gloves for next time, okay?
Sorry.
Oh, you want to bring it?
It's been brought.
Rude.
Felicity, right now
would be a good time to do something.
Stay away from Barry Allen.
- Felicity! - Got it.
Boom. Drop the mic.
It's metaphorical, of course,
because I don't have a real mic.
Brie's restrained.
Call CCPD.
Some kind of team you have here.
Helps to have friends in your corner.
Are you okay?
Cisco!
Come on. Please.
Wake up.
Cisco's been stung. He's going into shock.
I'm on my way.
Come on, stay with me.
Hold on. Back up.
I'm gonna try something.
Cisco.
Either my fear of bees is over or it just got a lot worse.
Thank God you're okay.
I've never had anybody take a bee for me.
- Thank you. - You're welcome, bro.
Cisco, you're a hero, man.
- Dr. McGee. - May I come in?
Yeah, of course. What can I do for you?
I wanted to apologize.
I should have listened to you when you warned me about Brie.
Perhaps next time I will take the CCPD's offer of protection.
After we lost your tachyon prototype,
I can understand why you were hesitant to trust us.
Thank you.
Can I ask you something?
I couldn't help but notice some tension
between you and Dr. Wells.
That's all in the past.
Do you mind if I ask what happened between you two?
I ask myself that same question all the time.
15 years ago, Harrison and I were thick as thieves.
We were promising young scientists in Starling City.
He was such a kind man.
Then everything changed after Tess died.
They were gonna get married?
I understand how grief can affect someone,
but this was more than that.
It was like, after that day,
Harrison Wells became a completely different person.
Good day.
Bye.
Doctor.
How's Cisco?
Happy to be alive.
And sad that Ray is leaving.
It was a really brave thing he did, risking his life.
Selfless.
Yeah. It definitely was.
And another end to another exciting adventure in Central City.
Yes, thank you.
Ray, thank you for all your help.
And I hope you figure out the problem with your suit.
I already have, actually.
All this time, I've been looking at
the power source the wrong way.
I kept thinking we needed to go bigger.
But the solution, as always,
is simply to go smaller.
Great.
You okay?
I'm gonna be.
Thank you for your advice.
I won't even charge you the 5 cents.
Bye, Felicity.
Bye, Barry.
What's up?
I...
I spoke to Barry last night.
Oh, yeah?
He was trying to help me understand
why you've been so off lately,
why you might be having trouble connecting with me.
Really?
What did he say?
It was a good explanation.
Valid.
But the truth is, it doesn't matter,
because when you love someone,
you tell them everything.
So if you love me, Eddie,
you'll tell me what is going on with you, or...
Or what?
You know what.
All right, all right, who's ready for some...
karaoke.
We are not going to karaoke, are we?
No.
This is everything we know about my mother's murder
and The Reverse-Flash.
I've been gathering information on him for a long time.
And this is everything we know about Dr. Wells.
I don't understand.
What do Dr. Wells and The Reverse-Flash
have to do with each other?
They're the same person.
That's impossible.
Look, Caitlin,
it took me a long time to believe it too,
but it's him.
Dr. Wells is a speedster?
He's paralyzed.
Is he, though?
And why would he kill Barry's mother?
It doesn't make any sense.
Cisco. Say something.
I've been having these dreams.
Mostly at night, but sometimes during the day.
But they don't really feel like dreams.
They... they feel real.
What happens in the dream?
Dr. Wells is The Reverse-Flash.
And...
he kills me.