[ MUSIC ]
DEMICHELE: Hi, I'm Dan from the IBM
Enterprise Marketing Management Group.
Today's marketers are tasked with sifting
through an unprecedented amount of data
to better understand their customers and
in turn deliver a superior experience
and favorable return back to the business.
Nowhere is information overload more
prevalent than in the digital domain.
The IBM Enterprise Marketing Management Suite
helps marketers navigate these challenges via
its Digital Marketing Optimization Solution.
With these capabilities, marketers
can finally understand the what,
when and where of customer behavior; measure
the impact of digital marketing efforts; and,
optimize or retarget based on those insights.
Let's see how a digital marketer will use the
IBM Digital Marketing Optimization solution
to tame the digital information firehose with
powerful marketing tools for engaging customers
across channels and seeking
out better online conversions.
Our marketer's first challenge is
familiar to most organizations.
She lacks a single view of the customer
across their organization's different digital
and offline channels, vendors,
data sources and departments,
most of which don't currently
talk to each other.
This not only hinders the
effectiveness of all of the marketing,
but it makes precisely targeting customers
through digital channels especially problematic
and risk missed opportunities
and customer attrition.
Thus, we want to create truly
cross-channel customer profiles
that leverage historical information, offline
interactions,and lifetime digital behavior
across Web, mobile and social as
well as offsite third-party data
to truly understand customer behavior.
Our first step is in IBM Digital Analytics,
which automatically builds a rich
customer profile data set from Web site
and marketing program performance monitoring.
A marketer can track and segment
customer behavior over time
and across key customizable milestones
such as cart openers or first-time buyers.
She can import offline data like transaction
histories and link it with digital behavior
for more visibility on how digital is
influencing offline interactions --
for example, e-mail promotions
and brick and mortar sales.
Then, she can layer in or add mobile
reporting and social interactions
into her customer profiles to better
understand how her customers are engaging
with her brand and content.
Now our digital marketer has a single view of
each individual visitor and customer which pulls
from all available online and offline channels
so she can best target visitors and customers
where and how they interact with their business.
Next, our marketer suspects that her site
has an underperforming conversion rate.
She wants to improve customers'
online experience across Web,
mobile and social channels and make
it easier for them to convert --
say, to book a travel itinerary
or download a key prospectus
or contact a live seller -- but
she isn't actually sure how.
Using IBM Digital Analytics, she's able
to capture Web and mobile interaction data
to highlight where users are struggling or
dropping off, measure and compare marketing ROI
across all digital channels and make appropriate
changes in site or application design
to help streamline their path to conversion.
Next, she compares key site KPIs to
industry peers and competitors to identify
which specific metrics she
leads in or lags behind on.
For example, using the benchmark tool, she
can look at how her social sites compare
to other companies in her vertical.
Next, she investigates customer behavior,
convergent pathways, abandoners and bounce rates
to uncover which promotions are working,
which sites are not performing and so forth.
By doing this, she can discover which landing
pages, messaging products, channel combinations
and more are most effective in driving
customers through to conversion,
thus improving performance by
leveraging those marketing tactics.
Now our marketer can make data-driven
marketing decisions based on live metrics
across all her digital marketing channels to
identify weaknesses and areas of strength.
Our digital marketer is now
ready to engage her customers
and leverage her enormous digital
analytics resources with experience,
optimization and marketing execution tools.
She not only wants to reach customers through
display ads and marketing e-mail channels
but also present them with personalized,
targeted promotions and content
to optimize response rates
and boost convergence.
Building on her earlier customer analytics, our
marketer now understands what segments she wants
to retarget for promotions and can create highly
tailored and personalized e-mail, advertising,
search and recommendation content.
Then she pushes targeted e-mail and
display ads to recapture visitors
with integrated in-suite execution tools.
She also uses automated personalized product or
content recommendations for each visitor based
on browsing histories and
wisdom of the crowd data.
Using new Tealeaf technology, she can
also drill into specific user sessions
and replay each user, Web, or mobile
interaction in context to help visualize
and analyze UI improvements and better
understand individual customer experiences.
And now, we're finally able to
optimize each customer's experience
across their digital lifecycle and
retarget based on deep individual analytics
and cross-channel visitor profiles.
Beyond digital marketing, IBM Enterprise
Marketing Management also offers unmatched
marketing capabilities for cross-channel
campaign management, marketing operations
and planning and price and
promotion optimization.
Today, EMM provides integrations
with popular solutions
like WebSphere Commerce and
Portal, SPSS and Cognos.
More are planned with Tealeaf and
other IBM solutions in the future.
The IBM Digital Marketing Optimization
Solution is a complete set of capabilities
for digital marketing that's praised not only
by industry analysts but more importantly,
by our clients and their customers.
For more information on how you
can make your marketing smarter,
contact your IBM representative
or visit ibm.com.
[ MUSIC ]