(Barry)
My name is barry allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother killed
By something impossible.
Run, barry, run!
(Barry)
My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident made me
the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
But secretly,
I use my speed to fight crime
And find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother...
Mom!
(Barry)
And get justice for my father.
I am The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
(Barry)
Last night, on my way
to the morgue,
I saw something.
Taxi!
Oh, come on!
I'm gonna
be late!
Simon Stagg,
remember him?
Hasn't been seen
in, like, six months.
You're saying Wells
knows where Stagg is.
(Mason)
No, I'm saying wells killed him.
I have evidence in
a secure digital file
That will explain everything.
There is a Tsunami
heading for the city.
You need to get as far
away from here as possible.
I have not been able
to stop thinking about you.
Go!
Aah!
[gasping]
[dogs barking]
No, no...
Taxi!
Oh, come on!
I'm gonna be late!
Oh, boy.
(Cisco)
Hey, what's going on?
- Dude?
- Yeah, Cisco.
I'm... Here...
What happened?
Why'd you stop?
I just got
a little disoriented.
Well, you need to
make up some time, man.
You better hurry up.
Hurry?
What are you...
Hurry, as in
get to the morgue.
The morgue?
I was there.
Yesterday.
What are you
talking about?
Come on, you gotta go.
[camera shutter clicks]
Hey, Barr.
What's with all the water?
Did the sprinkler system
go off or something?
What? No, I checked
the sprinklers.
They're all
intact.
But the water
has ice in it.
And the bruises
on the coroner
Aren't just on
his face.
Check...
Look at his torso.
Whoa.
How the hell
did you know that?
He was killed
by hail.
We have to listen
to the recording.
Recording?
(Thawne)
Joe, we got something.
The Coroner's office
just installed
An Automated
Dictation System.
Listen to this.
(Coroner)
Please... No more...
(Mardon)
I'll stop when you tell me...
(Coroner)
Just stop!
(Mardon)
Who killed him?
It's Mark Mardon.
He wants revenge.
[screams of pain on recording]
And I really
don't wanna go.
He's your brother,
Cisco.
Not by choice.
Okay, well, how bad can
a birthday party be?
Um, my folks think
dante's stink don't stink.
Doesn't matter how much
he screws up,
Or how many times
he gets into trouble.
In their eyes,
he can do no wrong.
And yet, they never
fail to remind me
That I can
do no right.
What if I came
with you?
What?
Seriously?
Absolutely.
You've done so much for me.
Let me be there for you
for a change.
And I could look at
old family photo albums
And see what little Cisco
looks like
Without long hair.
I'm rescinding
your invite.
Clyde Mardon has a brother?
So, both mardon brothers
survived the plane crash
And then the dark matter
released
By the
particle accelerator explosion
Affects them both in...
(Barry and Wells)
Virtually the same way.
That's right.
Only Mark's not
like Clyde at all.
He can do things that
You couldn't even imagine.
You mean
he's sort of like a...
(Barry and Cisco)
Weather Wizard?
Yeah.
[slurps]
Mm.
(Barry and Caitlyn)
Trigeminal Headache?
Mr. Allen.
A word please.
Yeah.
(Wells)
You ruptured the time continuum,
didn't you?
You're experiencing
temporal reversion.
- Yeah!
- How long?
Uh, a day
and some change.
It's like I'm living it
all over again.
Yeah, well that's good.
That means there's
Not too much you could've
messed up yet.
How did this happen?
I... I don't know.
I mean,
I was running faster than
I've ever ran,
And the first time
that I lived this day
Some really horrible
things happened.
There was a tidal wave
and...
No.
Do not tell me.
I do not want
to know anything
About the future
you experienced. Nothing!
Okay, but Dr. Wells,
I...
Barry.
Time...
Is an extremely
fragile construct.
Any deviation,
no matter how small,
Could result
in a Cataclysm.
Now here's what
you're going to do.
Everything
you did before.
Every word
you uttered,
Every step
you took,
You're going to
do again.
And you're not going
to tell anyone
This happened.
[sighs]
Good day, Dr. Wells.
Time will tell,
Gideon.
Show me the future.
(Gideon)
As you wish.
The future remains intact,
Dr. Wells.
If anything
changes,
Alert me
immediately.
(Gideon)
Of course, doctor.
[indistinct chatter]
Hey.
What's going on
with you?
How'd you figure
all that stuff out
At the morgue?
Lucky guesses,
I guess.
Look, I'm
telling you,
I'm gonna get mardon
if it kills me.
Joe, um...
I gotta
run an errand.
I'll see you later.
All right?
I didn't know there was
anyone else like me.
(Mardon)
I'm gonna break out of here!
I'm gonna create a tidal wave
that destroys your entire city!
(Cisco)
So, I still don't understand.
How did you find him?
I just had a hunch.
That's gotta be
some kind of record.
[laughs]
Yeah.
Well, there goes
my excuse
For bailing on
my brother's birthday.
Do you have any idea
what you've just done?
Yeah, I do.
I just saved
a lot of lives.
I warned you not to mess
with the timeline.
Dr. Wells, if you
would just let me
Tell you
what was gonna happen,
You'd understand
why I did this.
Whatever tragedy you think
you've just averted,
Time will find a way
to replace it
And trust me, barry,
The next one
could be much worse.
Don Santini, they're here.
(man)
Move it.
Oh, love the paneling.
Mahogany?
So glad your house
is made out of wood.
It's gonna be a pleasure
watching it burn.
Aah!
Refreshing!
What are you doing back
in central city, Snart?
This is my city.
Our city.
I told you if I ever
saw you again
I'd put the hurt on you.
You stir up trouble.
Trouble is bad for business.
It's time for you
and your family to pack up.
Leave town.
Retire to warmer climates.
Finito.
And if we don't?
You will all freeze.
Or burn.
I heard about your guns.
I also heard that you lost them.
So, tell me, Snart.
What the hell are you and
your pyro friend
Gonna do without
your fancy weapons?
This.
[fighting efforts]
[grunts]
Now that was fun!
Fun. Fun. Fun.
Go.
Tell the rest of
the Santini family
There's a new
godfather.
And his name is Cold.
[spanish party music playing]
- Hola.
- Coma esta.
Wow.
Your parents really
went all out with the cake.
Oh, well... It is
Dante's birthday.
The most important day
of the year.
Mi Hijo was invited to play
carnegie hall
When he was just
13 years old.
They invited the entire band,
mama.
(Mrs. Ramon)
That doesn't make it
any less worthwhile.
[chuckles]
Hey.
What's up, man?
- Hey.
- Glad you could make it.
Of course.
Hi, I'm Dante.
This is my friend,
Caitlyn.
Hi, Caitlyn.
- Happy birthday, Dante.
- Thank you.
Here, I...
I got you this.
- Oh...
- I think you'll really like it.
- It's...
- Thanks, man.
- Yeah.
- Excuse me.
[panting]
I don't get it.
I've been running
just as fast as I was
When it happened,
and nothing.
I'm still here.
Any number of things could've
triggered the wormhole
That allows you
to repeat your day.
Your emotions,
your circumstances,
Your cortisol levels,
all of the above.
Well, I mean, my adrenaline
was super high
Since Iris and
the entire city...
No, no, no.
No details.
I told you.
All right,
I'm sorry,
But Mark Mardon's
already locked in the pipeline
And nothing bad
has happened.
Yet.
[knocks]
Detective.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
So when were you
planning on telling me
You took down
Mardon?
I... I just haven't
had a chance yet.
You got sidetracked,
you mean?
No, joe,
you can't be mad.
I'm not mad.
But I am curious.
I mean,
You were acting so weird
at the crime scene.
I always act weird.
Okay.
Weirder.
Look, joe, there are just
Some things that
I can't tell you,
And you're gonna
have to trust me.
[phone vibrating]
Hey, Linda.
Yeah, I know.
I'm so sorry.
I... I lost track.
I'm gonna head
that way now.
All right, bye.
I have a lunch date
with Linda.
I gotta run.
And I don't suppose you're
gonna fill me in either?
No.
Mm.
[upbeat piano music]
Que Linda, Dante!
Well, here is one
who was touched by God.
Ah, I was
a little rusty.
I haven't played
in a while.
Oh, well...
If that was what you
sounded like rusty,
I can't imagine what
you sound like
When you've practiced.
Oh, for you, I'd practice
morning, noon, and night.
[laughs]
That means you'd actually
Have to get up
in the morning.
So, mom tells me
you're still working
At S.T.A.R. Labs,
huh?
Yeah.
Why?
No reason, man.
Guess it was just hard
to find another job, huh?
Oh, I wasn't looking.
I actually like working
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
And we couldn't do what we do
without Cisco.
Oh, he's loyal.
Just like a dog.
Oh, come on.
Why are you so serious, Mi Hija?
Happy birthday.
Hey! I am here.
So sorry, again.
[exhales]
Well, you get a pass
considering you're never late.
Hey, um...
What's going on
with you lately?
Nothing.
Come on.
Give me
a little credit here.
[sighs]
I've just been
dealing with
A lot of things
lately.
I like you, Linda.
And we really get along.
Relationships should be more
than just getting along.
Your heart should
ache for me.
Does it?
You're not upset
with me?
No one did
anything wrong.
I really do feel
a lot for you, Linda.
It's just...
Just not as much as
you feel for someone else.
Go get her.
"The Flash, speeding his way
into our lives."
It's a little bit on
the nose, don't you think?
I have something
to show you.
Simon Stagg,
remember him?
Hasn't been heard from
in nearly a year.
Hey, Iris.
Mr. Bridge, hi.
Do I know you?
Oh, no, we
haven't met yet...
Fully, you know, um...
Iris, can I talk to you
for a second?
Uh, yeah, sure.
- We'll catch up later.
- Yeah.
Nice meeting you,
strange young man.
Is everything okay
with you and Linda?
Uh...
No, that's done.
Oh, I... I am
so sorry.
No, no, no, it's okay.
We're gonna be friends.
Um, yeah, no,
it's gonna be awesome.
Uh... Anyway,
are you...
Are you free
tomorrow?
Do you want to
get some coffee
And we can just talk
and just
Tell each other
stuff...
I don't know,
stuff we got
Rolling around
in there, you know?
I don't know.
O-okay, yeah, sure.
It sounds great.
Okay, great.
Great!
All right,
I'll see you.
I know you think
Harrison Wells
Had something to do with
Simon Stagg's disappearance,
But you're wrong.
[rock pop music]
♪
- Hey.
- Oh, hey, man.
Thanks for
meeting me here.
Even though...
You can't get drunk.
[laughs]
No worries.
So, how was
your day?
Great.
But...
Linda and I
did break up.
That's the first time
I ever heard anyone
Use the word "great"
to describe a break-up.
I have a feeling
that I'm about to
Move forward with someone
really special.
Okay.
Go ahead, Barry.
[laughter]
Hi.
I don't normally
do this,
But I was
watching you, and...
Can I buy you
a drink?
Uh... Wow.
I mean,
I'm really flattered, but I...
Actually, I was
talking to him.
Um...
I'm... I'm sorry,
You said... you said
you were talking to me?
Yeah, I just told
my friends over there
That I thought you
were cute
And they dared me
to come over here
And talk to you, so...
Please talk to me.
Yeah. Yeah, I suppose
I can talk to you
For a little bit.
[mutters suggestively]
Yeah, no,
I was just leaving.
Make me proud.
[clears throat]
I'm Lisa,
by the way.
Hi, Cisco.
I'm just in town for
this Symposium at Mercury Labs.
Really? You...
What do you do?
Oh, I'm a
structural engineer.
Why do you look
so surprised?
Can't a girl
be an engineer?
No, of course.
That's...
You just don't look
like an engineer.
I can't help
how I look.
I... I mean,
it's good.
It's a...
It's a good look.
It's a great look.
Well, you don't look
so bad yourself.
Am I being pranked
right now?
♪
What do you think?
(Cisco)
I can't believe this.
The day started out
Pretty terrible, but now it's
turning out pretty damn good.
- I'll say.
- Wow.
Look at this.
These are nice things.
Oh, we're just
squatting.
We?
Yeah.
Me and my brother.
Hello, Cisco.
What exactly are
your intentions with my sister?
Oh, come on.
I should've known better.
I am not that lucky.
Please don't kill me
for kissing your sister.
You kissed him?
You're not dad,
Lenny.
I know.
Dad's in jail.
Sterling role model.
What do you want, Snart?
Guns. Heat and cold,
to be precise.
There's no way I am
making weapons for you.
Never again.
Mick.
[muffled moaning]
I know I would do
everything in my power
To protect my family.
The question is,
will you?
Dante.
Dante, just keep cool,
okay?
- Let me do my thing.
- Oh, really?
And what?
You're gonna save us
With your mechanical engineering
skills?
Right now, my skills
are the only things
Keeping us alive,
So if I were you,
I would shut up.
You shut up!
Ah!
There she is.
I missed this baby.
Here it is. All finished.
You gonna let us go now?
You know, I took the
first gun you made me apart
Dozens of times.
Learned how it ticked.
What went where.
Thought you could tamper
with the firing pin
Without me noticing.
Nice try, kid.
[weapon whirs]
- Yes.
- Lenny?
Where's my gun?
Girl's gotta
defend herself.
Besides, why should
you two have all the fun?
My sister needs
a weapon.
Something that suits
her personality.
Make me something
pretty and toxic,
Like me.
How about something
with gold?
Gold.
[short laugh]
[indistinct chatter]
- Hey!
- Hey.
One incredibly
heavy cronut
And one americano
with an extra shot.
- Just the way you like it.
- Just the way I like it.
Yeah, I know.
I know you, Iris.
[clears throat]
So... What is
going on with you?
You're acting like
christmas came early.
[laughs]
Uh...
Yeah, no, I guess
it did, kind of.
Look, Iris,
um...
I still think about
you all the time
And I know you've been
thinking about me too,
So let's just
stop thinking
And start doing.
- Barry...
- I know.
I know that we both
have awful timing,
But we were
meant to be...
Barry, what are you
talking about?
You and me.
We like each other.
Barry, we've been
over this.
Okay? Nothing has
changed for me.
No, but it has.
How do you know that?
I just...
I just know
some stuff somehow.
I don't know,
maybe it's like
ESP or something, but...
Barry.
I love Eddie, okay?
I'm sorry, but nothing
has changed for me
Since christmas.
And you can't keep
springing this on me.
Okay?
It's not fair
That you keep
making me the bad guy
Who keeps telling you no.
[sighs]
[knocks and sighs]
What?
No whoosh-in?
I needed
the walk.
What happened?
Nothing, uh...
Linda... Iris...
I don't want to
talk about it, actually.
Okay.
[sighs]
Have you talked
to Cisco?
I've been trying him
on his cell,
But he's not
answering.
Kind of...
Worried about him.
He had a rough night.
Trust me,
it got better.
[phone vibrating]
Hey, Joe.
What's up?
Yeah, Snart's back.
Wait, Cold is back?
(West)
Yeah, he was spotted at the
santini crime family casino.
If he's hitting the santinis,
we could be looking at
The beginning of a mob war.
[sighs]
Well, this day just keeps
getting better, doesn't it?
[sighs]
[exciting music]
♪
You killed my brother.
You shouldn't have messed
with my family.
(Lisa)
That's funny.
I was gonna say
the same thing about ours.
All that glitters...
[screaming]
[gunfire]
This is sick.
Well, you wanted us
to spend more time together.
[gun shots]
How many times are we
gonna go through this, Snart?
Until the best man wins!
Drop the gun!
We both know you're not
going to do anything to her.
Oh, by the way,
meet my baby sister.
Lisa, Flash.
Flash, Lisa.
(Snart)
Cisco has been very, very busy.
Unless you want me
to mail
Small, frozen pieces
of him back to his family,
I'd take your hands
off her.
Let him go, snart.
I'll think about it.
Barr.
Witnesses reported
seeing The Flash.
They said you had
snart dead to rights
But you let him go?
Why?
Cisco.
Snart and his sister
have him.
Oh, man.
Okay.
Get to S.T.A.R. Labs.
I'll get there
when I can.
All right.
Allen.
Yeah, Eddie, I...
- [grunts]
- Whoa.
Stay away from Iris.
What the hell is
going on here?
Hey, if you two have a beef,
you take it outside.
You know what
the worst part is, Barry?
I thought you and I
were friends.
[exhales]
So there's Cisco getting
into a car with Snart's sister.
And the license plate
is iced over.
All right, Dr. Wells,
you were right.
I... I... I screwed with time and
now time is screwing with me.
Cold is back, he kidnapped
Cisco, and Iris is...
Stop right there before
you cause another disruption
To the timeline.
(Barry)
Please, Dr. Wells.
Please, I have to
talk to someone.
Go ahead.
In the previous version
of today,
Captain Singh
is seriously injured,
Joe is in danger,
And Iris said she
had feelings for me.
And now Cisco's life
is on the line,
And Iris has no idea
she confessed those feelings.
But she still
has them, right?
The unconscious mind,
Barry,
It...
It's a powerful thing.
It sounds like it took
this apparent disaster
To jar those feelings loose
And without a disaster,
those feelings
Remain deeper down.
Unaccessed.
I don't understand.
I thought that
I was helping people
By stopping mardon.
Yes, but this
new ability of yours,
Barry, is dangerous.
You only traveled back
in time one day.
What if you
traveled back decades?
Centuries?
Imagine the havoc
you could wreak.
But I will
have the opportunity
To travel back in time
in the near future
And save my mom.
Or... You're saying
I shouldn't?
I'm saying
How many more people could die
If your mother lives?
Did you guys find Cisco?
Most people think
the hottest part of the flame
Is the white part.
They're wrong.
[blows air]
You gonna admire those
or you gonna drink 'em?
Both.
[both speaking spanish]
I told her you wanted
to become a priest.
Broke her heart.
Why'd you do that?
Because I was
jealous of you, man.
I mean, even then I...
I knew exactly where
my life was headed.
- Nowhere.
- Dante.
That's not true.
I live at home.
And I work a crap job
for no pay.
Yeah, but you
still manage
To be
mom and dad's favorite.
[scoffs]
I don't even know why.
It's because they...
They still think of me
As their son,
the concert pianist.
But you, man, they never
understood your talents.
Never understood that
you pursued your passion
No matter what.
And me, I was
just too scared
To even try.
[speaking spanish]
Dant...
Dante...
No!
Aah!
[glass shatters]
[fighting]
Oh!
Mick!
Mick, calm down!
We need them!
Mick?
Baby?
It sounds like
you're hungry.
(Lisa)
How about you and I grab
some dinner?
I like you, kid.
You're smart.
You pulled yourself up
From humble beginnings.
You seem like
a good brother.
You too.
Debatable.
You answer one question
for me,
I'll let you
and your brother walk.
What's the question?
The Flash.
Who is he?
I swear... He always
wears a mask.
Aah!
No!
No! Stop!
[cries in pain]
This is first degree
frost bite.
Your brother could
recover with proper treatment.
If not, all his tendons,
blood vessels, and nerves
Will freeze.
His fingers will need
to be amputated.
No more concertos for
the ramon family holidays.
Now tell me,
Who is The Flash?
There's nothing on
the Satellite Thermography.
You were right.
This is all my fault.
How is this your fault?
Brave heart, Barry.
We'll get Cisco back.
(Cisco)
I'm back.
(Caitlyn)
Oh, my god.
Are you okay?
We were so worried.
What happened?
How did you escape?
I didn't.
Snart just let you go?
Why?
He, um...
He tortured my brother.
And he said
he was gonna kill him
If I didn't...
If I didn't
tell him...
Tell him what?
Who The Flash
really is.
(Cisco)
I, honestly, man, they...
They could've killed me.
But they were gonna
kill my brother.
I couldn't let him
do that.
[cries]
Hey.
I'm sorry, Barry.
- No.
- I'm so sorry.
I put you in
that position.
I'm the one who's sorry.
Where are you going?
I don't deserve
to be here.
I won't be the one
to put you in jeopardy.
Not again.
Never again.
Hey.
What?
What a surprise.
- Oh.
- [chuckles]
As big a surprise as
Eddie punching barry
At a crime scene
this evening.
Oh, my god.
Is Barry okay?
Yeah.
He... Heals fast.
Look, Iris.
This got complicated.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Barry was too late.
I'm with Eddie.
Let me ask you something.
Who do you love?
I mean,
I love Eddie.
Okay. You need to
make them believe that,
Because right now, I'm not
sure either one of them does.
Okay?
Okay.
Did I ever tell you
how wise and amazing you are?
Not enough.
See you later.
- Bad time?
- Yes, actually.
[sighs]
Don't worry, I'll be
out of here soon.
Well, before you
shuffle off forever,
May I show you something?
I get it.
I failed.
(Wells)
No, no, no. Now, you're an
incredibly clever guy, Cisco.
So why don't you tell me
Why would I bring you
down here?
Because we all failed
that night.
But we kept going.
We kept trying to
protect each other,
And Barry,
In spite of
the setbacks.
Making a choice
Between two people you love,
That is the hardest dilemma
you will ever face.
Well, you won't have to
worry about me
Making the wrong decision again.
All you proved
today, Mr. Ramon,
Is that you're human.
All you proved today
Is that you love
your brother.
And the reason that
we all want you to stay
Is that we love you too.
Now, I am not
a parent,
But, in many ways,
You have shown me
what it's like
To have a son.
(Caitlyn over intercom)
Guys, you should get up here.
Shall we?
The casino wasn't the target.
Then why did he
do it?
Casinos keep tons
of cash on hand
To cover their markers,
not to mention
The money that they make.
But if they're
under attack,
The protocol is to relocate
the money outside the casino.
So, that was snart's plan
all along.
- To trigger the move.
- Okay, where is it now?
[indistinct chatter]
Get ready, we got company.
Aah!
[gunfire]
[tires squealing]
[weapon whirring]
Oh!
[crashes]
Good to see you...
Barry.
We have to talk.
(Barry)
I know Cisco told you who I am.
Can't really blame
the kid for giving you up.
You or his brother?
Come on!
I put him in
a tight spot.
Same kind I got you in
right now.
Can't really stop me now
that I know who you are.
I could speed you
to my own private prison
Where you'll never
see the light of day.
You could, but then
I won't be around
To stop my own
private uplink
That'll broadcast
your identity to the world.
So, the million dollar
question.
What to do with me now,
Barry Allen?
I won't let you
keep stealing
Whatever you want,
whenever you feel like it.
- It needs to end.
- Can't do that.
It's what I do.
Then find
a new line of work.
Don't want to.
Why is that?
The same reason you keep
running after guys like me.
The adrenaline.
The thrill of the chase.
I love this game.
And I'm very
good at it.
Then go play it
somewhere else.
Leave Central City.
Can't do that either.
I love it here.
[inhales]
This city is my home.
[scoffs]
You've seen
what I can do.
You know that
I can stop you.
You want to keep
pushing your luck,
Go for it.
But from
here on out,
No one else dies.
If you're as good
as you say you are,
You don't have to
kill anyone
To get what you want.
That's true.
And if you, or anyone
in your rogues' gallery
Goes near any of my friends
or family again,
I don't care who you tell
my identity to.
I'm putting you away.
I guess
your secret's safe...
Flash.
For now.
Oh, I don't suppose
you'd give me a ride
Back to town, would you?
The rogues.
Cute.
[party music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
♪
I...
I am so sorry, pal.
It's not like me
to hit anyone.
I don't know
what came over me.
Uh... Thanks, eddie.
It's... it's okay.
You poor thing.
I had no idea.
Is that right?
Um...
What exactly did you
have no idea about?
I was just explaining
to Iris and Eddie
About your lightning psychosis.
My what now?
Your lightning psychosis.
How your recent
odd behavior
Is a side effect
of being struck by lightning.
Mood swings,
sudden outbursts of affection,
And other lapses
in judgment.
He has had
all of those things.
He told me that
he had ESP.
Yeah, it's a very
uncommon
Neurological
Phenomenon.
We're really only
just now
Starting to research in
Kerauno-Medicine.
That's why Barry's been
Spending so much time
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
I just... I wish
you would've told me.
I didn't... it hardly
feels real sometimes.
We're just glad you're
getting help.
Yeah.
So, we're good?
Yeah, we're good.
- Coffee?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- You are welcome.
[typing]
[thunder rumbling]
Come on.
Hey.
(Reverse Flash)
Harrison Wells.
What do you know about him?
Ooh!
[whimpering]
(Reverse Flash)
What do you know?
Everything I know
is in that drive.
I swear.
Oh!
Ugh!
(Reverse Flash)
Everything?
Everything!
Just take it!
[panting]
You really were on to the story
of the century.
Well...
This century, anyway.
Do you think
I made a mistake
Letting snart go?
I think you did what you felt
was right in the moment.
And really, Barry,
That's the best any
of us can hope for.
Now, let's be thankful
the timeline remains intact.
Oh!
I keep forgetting.
I've been meaning
to ask you.
It's about Simon...
You were saying, Mr. Allen?
Uh...
Nothing.
Sorry.
Night, Dr. Wells.
Good night, Barry.
[thunder rumbling]
Barr, what's up?
Why'd you want to
meet up here so late?
I think that maybe you were
right about Dr. Wells.
Which part?
All of it.
(man)
Greg, move your head.