This is BBC world news today, with me Philippa Thomas. Egyptians are
being urged to vote yes to a new constitution endorsed by the
military. We are watching the turnout and the turbulence, we will
have the latest from Cairo on day one of the vote.
When all the votes have been cast it looks certain to be approved by a
comfortable majority. But the key issue is the turnout.
President Hollande tells packed news conference this is not the place nor
the time to discuss his alleged affair, private means private says
the French President. Also coming up, how the booming
property market in London is directly affected by economic and
political crises from Spain to south Asia. We will talk to the man
charting the impact of global affairs on property prices in the UK
capital. Poor fellow shot dead lying in all directions. The horrors of
World War I, in the words of the soldiers themselves, now their
diaries are being published on-line. Hello and welcome, Egyptians are
voting on a new constitution which could pave the way for the head of
the army to run for President. This is the first vote Since the elected
President Mohammed Morsi was he overthrown in July. The Muslim
Brotherhood has been named a terrorist organisation since then
and its supporters are boycotting the referendum. Since voting nine
protestors have been killed. In central Cairo an eager queue before
the polls opened. This is the third constitutional referendum in as many
years. And many hope it will bring an end to turmoil and unrest.
This woman, a housewife, who was one of the first in line. She told us
she would have queued all night, because the constitution will help
Egypt overcome a crisis. I want to for all the people in Egypt to come
now and say yes and this is the best for our country. It is the first
time Egyptians have gone to the polls since their elected President,
Mohammed Morsi, was ousted last July. He was removed by the army in
a popular low-backed coup. The military wants this vote to endorse
his removal. There is steady team of people coming to cast their ballot
and more queueing to get in. The referendum is a key test for the
authorities. They say the constitution represents the new
democratic Egypt. Now when all the votes have been cast it looks
certain to be approved by a comfortable majority. But the key
issue is the turnout. Especially for the army chief, General Abdel Fattah
el-Sisi, barely visible in the throng as he inspected a polling
station. A convincing result in the referendum could kick-start a
presidential bid. He's already shaking hands like a politician. The
constitution bolsters the economic and political power of the military.
It allows military trials for civilians. But it also promises
improved human rights. People were arrested because of these posters.
Opponents say they have been silenced and harassed. Putting up
these posters calling for a "no" vote, has meant arrest and terrorism
charges for seven political activists. Moderate Islamists say
the authorities are giving voters no option. As long as they are pushing
to one direction, which is one choice only, only "yes", it is not a
referendum or not a democratic process at all. You won't vote? We
will not vote. And supporters of the Muslim Brotherhood are not voting
either, they have been protesting in several locations. The organisation,
now declared a terrorist group, has called for a boycott cott of the
vote, saying the constitution is stained with blood. If it is passed
as expected, it may harden the divisions here, not heel them. We
have a Middle East expert with the Brooksings Institution and the Royal
United Services Institute and he joins us via webcam from Cairo.
Thank you for being with us on world news today. We heard Orla there
talking about the turnout being key, what is your reading of the way the
turnout is looking and how high it would have to be for the general to
run for President? It is a little bit early to say what turnout
actually looks like, keeping in mind that most of the coverage we have
seen thus far is really on Cairo. It is not around the country. Polling
has stopped for today, it is 9.00, tomorrow is still another day, it
will be a full day and I suspect we won't really be able to tell what
turnout is like until tomorrow. Some people are comparing turnout at
certain polling stations and parts of Cairo today, with what it was in
2012, but there are different numbers of polling stations this
year as well. So I think it is early for us to start talking about
turnout. In terms of what is required I don't really know if
that's the correct question. Regardless of turnout over the next
couple of days, I think that General Abdel Fattah el-Sisi has made his
calculation and will follow through with it regardless of the turnout.
It has been hard to put it mildly, to campaign for a "no" vote, there
has been repression of that campaign? Absolutely. This is
something that people need to be very aware of, that while there
isn't any evidence of ballot box stuffing and things like that a fair
vote, this definitely is not. The last few days has seen people get
arrested for campaigning for a "no" vote, and being released eventually,
but still being arrested for campaigning in that fashion. The
apparatus, state TV and private TV has been very, very clear about its
only presenting one side of the argument, which is to vote for a
"yes" vote as opposed to a "no", a "fair" referendum it can't be
called. Do you have a view on whether this constitution is better
for the people of Egypt than the last one they were presented with?
There is some marginal differences there are some points about rights
that are in this new constitutional draft that weren't there in 2012,
the military has at least the same amount of protection and autonomous
position that it had in 2012 as well. That is not particularly
different. There are a couple of adjustments there, I don't think
much in the way of that either. You still have military trials for
civilian, you still have basic autonomy for the military, from the
executive and so on. And the articles are not really the issue
here. For me the process is far more important, and incidentally people
are not voting on this constitution, yes, no or boycott, on the basis of
the articles. That accounts I think for a small proportion of the
Egyptian population. People who are boycotting and generally boycotting
because either they don't recognise the legitimacy of the process that
brought the vote forward in the first place, that accounts for the
brotherhood and their allies, or they are voting "yes" as a sign that
they support the military and they oppose the Muslim Brotherhood and
looking for a more stable situation in Egypt. There hasn't been a
referendum in Egypt over the past three years it has come near a "no"
vote. "Yes "presented as the next stage of doability. Over the last
few years a huge number of voters want exactly that. Thank you very
much for joining us. Thank you. The French President, Francois Hollande,
has faced hundreds of journalists at his first news conference since a
magazine accused him of having a secret affair with an actress. But
that is not quite the situation it seems. This was his annual
conference in which he spoke in great detail about the French
economy and the Press Pack chose to pose just a single question, on
whether his official partner remains the French First Lady. The glamour
of the big screen, Julie Gayet, the French actress who has stolen the
heart of the President. Cast in this drama as the femme F atale. Today it
was Mr Hollande's turn in the spotlight with the annual meeting
with the press. The official subject was the economy, cuts of 50 billion
years in public spending -- euros in public spending. But the big
question, what will become of the First Lady, Valerie Trierweiler.
TRANSLATION: Everyone in their private life goes through difficult
periods. It is true, these are difficult moments, but I have one
principle, private matters should be dealt with privately, that's the
same for everyone concerned. So this is not the place nor the time to
discuss it. But so long as the confusion surrounds the First Lady's
position it is likely these questions will continue. Valerie
Trierweiler is still in hospital, still "resting". We don't know how
many of these secret nights there were, but photographers who tailed
Mr Hollande, on his moped, say no-one ever tried to stop them.
TRANSLATION: We were there every night, the President was in an
apartment without any security. Even outside. I even saw the President
walk around the block. The public and the private, boundaries blurred
by the unnecessary risks Mr Hollande is said to have taken. Right now it
is the President's judgment that is being debated, not his choice in
women. Now also in Paris for us, the French cultural commentator. Thank
you for joining us, when President Hollande gave his non-answer,
answer, at the news conference, was that appropriate to French ears? It
was certainly not surprising. We didn't expect him to suddenly open
his heart to the French people. We did expect, perhaps a statement,
before the press conference, just to clear the way, a way to clarify his
position. But because his partner, Valerie Trierweiler, is still in
hospital, that was deemed not the right moment to actually issue that
statement. It did, however, and that's probably the most interesting
point on that topic, during his two-and-a-half hours of press
conference, that he would clarify his personal situation before going
on an official visit to Washington. That is in three weeks time. We
should know very soon if indeed Valerie Trierweiler remains France's
First Lady. Will the public mind or care whether he goes alone to
Washington? No, of course not. And perhaps, you know, perhaps he
regrets having introduced his partner to the nation at large. She
could, probably should have remained in the shadows. It would be easier
for him, also don't forget that the concept of First Lady is viewed as
an American concept in France, and doesn't have any clear status and is
a very ill-defined position. It depends on the President in exercise
whether to give the first partner any staff or any public function.
And yes, let's get to the issue that may well matter more to the French
people themselves, much of this lengthy news conference was about
the economic programme for the country and we're talking about cuts
in public spending, cuts in taxes, is this what was expected or does
that come as something of a shock? I'm very glad you mentioned the most
important part of his press conference. Because he had prepared
a lot for the third press conference of his presidency. And yes, he did
announce some interesting policies. You know, there has been talk that
for a long time that he's not a socialist really, but a social
democrat. I think that was the first policies, Social Democratic policies
that he was announcing for the first time since being elected to power.
Indeed he has announced 15 billion euros of cuts in public spending.
But also a big chunk of social charges that are quite hefty in
France and paid by employers that would be simply scrapped. So a lot
of things. He also talked about Europe, he talked about
unemployment, about anti-semitism in France and also about military
operations in Mali and Central African Republic. Let's give you a
brief look at some of the day's other news. Reports from south Sudan
say at least 200 people have died in a ferry accident. They boarded the
overcrowded boat while trying to escape fighting in the city. Rebels
loyal to the former deputy President claim they have since captured
Malakal from Government forces. A new survey of lions has found they
could face extinction in west Africa, fewer than 400 are left in
the region. The research was carried out in 17 countries, from Senegal to
Nigeria, taking more than six years. With fewer than 250 lions of
breeding age left, there are concerns the entire population could
disappear. A doctor in northern China has been given a suspended
death sentence for stealing new born babies and selling them to child
traffickers. The obstetrician convinced the parents that their
babies had serious health problems and should be cared for by the
state. Paraded in front of a courtroom, Dr Zhang Shuxia was
convicted of selling seven infants to a child trafficking ring. She
received a suspended death prison, usually changed to life in prison
after two years of good behaviour. It was at this hospital where the
respected obstetrician had lied to new parents, telling them their new
borns were seriously ill. If they handed their children over to the
state, families were told, the babies would receive the expensive
medical care they needed. When police broke up the ring, seven
healthy new borns had already been sold, leading to multiple arrests.
And several triumphant home Cummings, as police returned the
abducted children to their rightful parents. All except one child, sold
for just $165, abandoned by the traffickers. Some outraged Chinese
citizens argued that the doctor should die for her crimes. In this
country where child trafficking is relatively common, a suspended death
sentence is too lenient, they said. The Nigerian authorities say 30
people have been killed by a bomb explosion in the north eastern city
of Maiduguri. The blast ripped through a packed market in t early
afternoon, causing panic as people tried to flee the scene on foot and
by car. Some reports suggest the bomb was planted in a motor Rick
saw, or a sack abandoned by a stall. The Islamist group, Boko Haram said
it carried out the attack. The British Government has ordered an
urgent investigation into whether the UK was involved in deadly raid
on a Sikh temple in the Indian city of Amritza in 1984. Recently
unclassified documents suggest that an SAS officer advised Indian
authorities prior to the storming of the Golden Temple where hundreds
died. The storming of the Golden Temple in the area angered Sikhs
around the world, who blamed Indian troops for violating their holyist
shrine. Now documents released under the 30-year rule, apparently show
the British were involved. One Foreign Office letter says "with the
Prime Minister's agreement, an SAD officer has visited India and drawn
up a plan, which has been approved by Mrs Gandhi". There appears to be
a typing error that should read SAS. The letter warns it could increase
violence in India and warns it might also therefore increase tension in
the Indian community here. Particularly if knowledge of the SAS
involvement were to become public. Some MPs believe all the evidence of
British involvement must now be released. I think there are further
documentation, what we want is a full, candid, disclosure of all
explanations so we can get to the bottom exactly what happened here.
Even after 30 years Sikhs here in Britain want to know the truth about
what happened at Amritza, we are told neither David Cameron or the
Foreign Secretary, William Hague, were aware of the documents
suggesting Britain's involvement until they were published. But that
they do understand the very legitimate concerns that will be
raised by the revelations. At the largest Sikh temple outside India,
in Southall west London a community leader welcomed the Prime Minister's
decision to ask the cabinet secretary to investigate. This is a
holy place. For any religion, it is a heart-breaking thing. These things
do not go out from your mind. It is not a small thing. That is why if
the truth has come out, at least people know. Last year David Cameron
became the first serving British Prime Minister to visit the Golden
Temple. He is keen to focus on the historic and cultural ties with
Sikh, but now he's under pressure to uncover more about Britain's role in
an event which is seared into their history. London is a property hot
spot, viewed by many around the world as a safe bet when it comes to
real estate, now a new study has found that conflicts, turmoil and
general instability outside the UK have a direct impact on the price
paid for bricks and mortar here in the British capital. The study was
put together by the Business Cool of the University of Oxford, they found
that property here recorded the largest increases. The same patterns
can be seen with troubles in Egypt and Greece, another part of their
research looks at London's wealthiest areas, places like
Knightsbridge, the study concluding that China had the biggest impact on
the city's highend real estate prices. Instability in Russia and
Libya also pushed prices up in London's premier property market.
With me is a representative from the Business School of the University of
Oxford. You co-authored the report, we know about the idea as property
as a safe haven and safe investment, you go beyond that don't you? That's
right, our launching off point is London is not a big non-know lithic
eptity but composed of many little region, because we all live in parts
of London, we don't live in the whole place. You can link and map
particular parts of London to particular foreign countries, either
by using things like the language, the principal language spoken in the
regions or the share of residents that originate from those countries.
That is our launching off point for this particular thing. Some of the
research that you have come up with, for example, looks at southern
Europe, Italy, Spain, Greece and normally people talk about maybe the
Chinese or Arab money, but southern Europe and the euro crisis features
highly? One of the ways to think about this is when political
uncertainty went up in Spain, the prices came up in London across the
board, but specifically regions linked to Spain, such as high-income
areas, such as St John's Wood, would have appreciated. But areas like
King's Cross would have appreciated at the same time, they have also a
high share of Spanish residents. So it is an uncertainty, as you say, in
southern Europe, because it is a large factor in the real estate
prices. It is not just the real estate priority, looking at the
Shard in London, it is owned by Qatar, but you have also looked at
lower income areas, and they are still influenced by nationalities
who tend to cluster. Absolutely, that's right. You do see the usual
effects that you would have expected to see in Mayfair or Knightsbridge
or the popular areas and wealthy areas, but you also see effects in
areas which are also inhabited by clusters of regional communities.
One of the reassuring things of the research is we show the effects are
not permanent. One of the things people tend to think about safe
haven effects, that they push prices up and prices stay up forever. That
is not the case. When political uncertainty rises prices go up, when
the uncertainty dissipates prices go back down over one or two years.
That suggests a pattern of people moving their capital in and out of
London and not taking up residence in London. Which means you get back
to what Londoners say that a lot of homes are not actually homes? That I
suppose is a very true statement that you are making there. Another
way to sort of portray that, perhaps, is the fact that while
these effects are temporary on the prices of houses. It reaches the
local community which is the internationalisation of London,
which perhaps is a very nice thing about this. It is fascinating,
London is one of those global cities, thank you very much for
coming to talk it all through with me.
Now it was called the war to end all war, those who fought it lived
through brutality that was almost impossible for families back home to
imagine. But now, for the first time, many of the diaries written by
soldiers written on the frontline are being published by the National
Archives here. 300,000 pages of personal testimony released so far.
A picture of the war itself. "Here I sit outside our headquarters' trench
in the sun. All should be nice and peaceful and pretty what it actually
is, is beyond description. Trenches, ammunition tool, caps et cetera, et
cetera, everywhere, poor fells shot dead are lying in all directions."
Thousands of war diaries, 1. 5 million separate documents. Once the
fodder for authors and researchers, now they are available for the first
time at the click of a mouse. "The order to retire was at last given...
" These are the last days of the men in a giant army, the attacks, the
food, the horrific casualties, neatly typed on to official military
forms and stored away for decades. The names carved on to our local war
memorials are the most obvious reminders of the war, all of us will
have a direct connection with somebody who served in this
conflict. The hope is that these diaries released into the public
domain will give more and more people the opportunity to follow a
personal trail. This is Operation War Diary, under way at a school in
Southampton. Students reading the unseen documents are tagging names
and events, adding to their own knowledge and improving the
archive's search engine. They talk about their supplies from the battle
for their cooking. From the sounds of it they are getting quite annoyed
because their supplies aren't reaching all the way through. It
just shows you what happens behind the scenes and how these men
actually lived and what the quality of their lives were at that time.
You read it and you take it in but when you then have to specifically
point out things, it again just immerses you even more. Holes where
shells had struck, branches torn off trees by the explosion. Everywhere
the same hard, grim, pitiless sign of battle and war. I have had a
belly full of it. Ghastly, absolutely ghastly.
The eyewitnesses have left us, but they survive through the curling
pages of their final observations. Just time to remind you of our main
news, Egyptians are voting on a new constitution that could pave the way
for the head of the army to run for President. It is the first vote
since General El-Sisi overthrew Egypt's elected President, Mohammed
Morsi in July. Muslim Brotherhood supporters are boycotting the
referendum. And we have been reminded on the programme that it
has been very difficult for those opposed to the new constitution to
air their views in public. Thank you for joining me on World News Today.
Much more cloud across the country, outbreaks of rain for