Previously on
"The Mob Doctor"...
As long as you're in Chicago,
I own you. That's the deal.
If you don't leave right now,
I am screaming for a cop.
I am a cop.
Constantine's plans
are bigger than I imagined.
- What part of "off the case" don't you get?
- Got to find a way back in.
I'm Dr. Devlin. You had me paged.
I heard that you see patients off the grid.
It seems our old friend
Russell King is back in town.
My FBI handler wants me
hooked up with another crew.
Otherwise,
he's gonna pull me out.
King needs a guy.
That's me.
By tomorrow morning, I'll be rich,
and you'll be connected.
Franco crewed up with Russell.
It's gonna be challenging.
I like a good challenge.
You know, there was someone else
there with him -- Grace.
She helped Franco with Russell.
I'll deal with Grace
in my own time.
- Good morning.
- What took you so long?
You called an hour ago.
Roll up your sleeve.
Let's go.
This isn't a medical issue,
so you can put your bag away.
- Sit down.
- Okay.
I've been waiting for you
to come to me and explain yourself.
What are you talking about?
What the hell were you doing
with Franco?
You, Franco, Russell King --
Christmas Eve
outside the auction house.
Russell King is my patient.
He collapsed.
If I hadn't gone to see him,
he would have died.
And Franco?
He just happened to be there, too?
Yeah, that's right.
So it was Franco who
referred Russell King to you?
I don't know,
but I would assume so, yeah.
- You should have called me.
- Why?
So you can kill Franco?
Look, I don't want to be
responsible for anybody's death,
including Franco's.
If this is all you need from me...
You want things to be strictly business
between you and me, that's fine.
But you're gonna tell me
everything you know about Franco.
Is he working for Russell King
in Detroit?
I have no idea.
You see him again,
you get ahold of me right away.
And you're right.
I do want him dead.
Hey. I was just thinking about you.
Constantine knows we were together.
He asked me if you and Russell
were in Detroit.
Well, what'd you tell him?
I said I didn't know.
I don't think he believed me.
The thing is I'm not in Detroit anymore.
I'm on my way back to Chicago.
No, you can't come here.
It's not safe.
Detroit's economy's in the toilet, Grace.
There's no money there.
If I get Russell
hooked up in Chicago,
I find a way back in,
and I get his protection.
But if it weren't for you,
he would be dead. Isn't that enough?
Unfortunately, saving his life
doesn't put money in his pocket.
I need to prove I'm an earner.
The FBI wants me
on the inside, Grace.
Otherwise I'm useless to them.
It's just if anything
happened to you, I, um --
hey, it's you and me
versus the world, babe.
And I'm betting on us.
Where you going, twinkle toes?
A bet's a bet, and you lost.
Can't I give you each 20 bucks?
We'll call it even?
Come on.
Nobody wants your money.
- We want to see your fat ass dance.
- You're a jerk.
Shut up and shake your money maker.
Like you mean it.
- Do it for me.
- I love this! Very good!
Nate.
What's up?
Whenever these idiots
are done screwing around,
I want you to go with
Louis and Gio on some pickups.
Cool.
You're moving up quick, kid.
Keep up the good job.
The sky's the limit.
Cut that crap out.
Don't quit your day job, Benny.
I've been trying to get ahold of Tony M.
For a month.
Haven't got an answer back.
You make one phone call, and all of a sudden,
we get an invite.
Yeah, we go way back.
This guy can chop up a car
to the bolts in less than an hour.
If he's even half as good as you say,
you got a permanent spot
on my crew here in Chicago.
I'm counting on it.
Hey. Tony M.
Hey. Franco.
- Nice to see you breathing, kid.
- What's up, man?
Good to meet you.
I'm Tony M.
Franco says you're the real deal.
Is it true you boosted
the first truckload of vipers out of Flint?
- How'd you hear about that?
- I'm from Detroit.
Screw you.
Franco, I'm out.
- What's his deal?
- Let me go talk to him.
- What happened there?
- You never said he was from Detroit.
So what?
You know the Pistons knocked the Bulls
out of the playoffs three times in a row --
'88, '89, and '90.
I can't be around that guy.
Bad memories.
That was like 20 years ago, man.
It's not like he played on the team.
I lost 100 grand
on those games,
and I vowed never to work
with anybody from
that piece-of-crap city!
End of story!
He's a die-hard Bulls fan.
He was born and raised in Chicago.
- Hey, Russell. Where were you born?
- Humboldt Park.
Before or after the Mexicans moved in?
There ain't no Mexicans
in Humboldt Park.
It's all puerto rican.
But nice try.
Who's your favorite
all-time Bull?
And don't say Jordan.
Norm van Lier.
Stormin' Norman.
Now that's what I'm talking about.
Yeah, butterbean love.
Mickey Johnson.
I'll have you set up
in 24 hours.
Eight lifts, two box trucks
to move parts through the city.
And I got extra offices
in the back.
How about I get us box seats
to the Bulls game next week?
I think he's a couple quarters
short of a dollar.
Yeah, I'm more interested in the c-notes
we're gonna be bringing in.
Welcome aboard.
Dr. Devlin to trauma room 4.
Dr. Devlin to...
Everything all right,
Dr. Devlin?
Oh, yeah, I was just, uh,
paged to see a trauma patient.
- A priest.
- Yeah.
And you're standing out here
because?
Oh, it's just after my last confession,
I was supposed to
say 10 Hail Marys as penance,
and I haven't really
gotten around to it.
How long ago was that?
Before med school.
I'm sure he'll forgive you.
Try saying the rosary sometime.
It never hurts.
Hello, Father.
I'm Dr. Devlin.
That's quite an infection
you have there.
Yes, I-I should have come in sooner,
but I kept hoping it would
get better on its own.
Well, can I ask you
what happened?
Of course. But it --
it may sound strange to you.
I've heard it all before.
You can tell me anything.
I've been performing an exorcism...
and two days ago,
while blessing my parishioner
with holy oil, I was attacked.
Attacked?
Yes. I was bitten by the demon.
www.1000fr.net presents
The Mob Doctor s01e10
Sync:µ¤æ¤@FRS
All right, so we're gonna
drain your wound
and then give you
some intravenous antibiotics.
Thank you, doctor.
Judging from the teeth-mark impressions,
I'd say it's a human bite.
So, when you say...
"Demon"...
Well, I've been working on
my parishioner for a week now.
She would never deliberately harm me,
but the demon used her
as a vessel to lash out.
I've -- I've heard of exorcisms.
I was raised catholic.
But I've never met anyone
who's performed the rite.
Well, I'm one of several priests in the state
sanctioned by the Vatican to exorcise.
I let my guard down,
and I gave the demon
an opening to come after me.
Oh, Father Doyle, this is Dr. Robinson.
We'll be working together.
Hi.
Let's see here.
It's a two-day-old human bite,
surrounding cellulit.
It's pretty deep.
Okay, we're gonna have to do a facial C.T.
To make sure the infection doesn't track into the brain.
The nurse is gonna take you for your scan,
and I will meet you
back in the patient room.
Okay, see you soon.
An exorcism in 2013?
It's an attempt to eradicate evil.
In theory, there's nothing wrong with that.
This guy thinks demons are real.
Demons -- the things
that take over your body
and puke green-pea soup
all over the place.
Okay. That's enough.
Are you taking this guy seriously?
I don't know if demons are real.
I know evil exists.
- Russell.
- Hey.
I'm glad you decided to meet.
I see you got your appetite back.
Yeah, I didn't realize
how much I missed Chicago beef.
Well, I'm glad you're
enjoying the local cuisine.
If you like, I can get you
a little water to wash that down.
Water. Yeah, that's funny.
You tried to drown me
the last time I was here.
I warned you,
but you didn't listen.
I want to tell you something...
Out of respect.
Me and my crew
are setting up shop.
Not without kicking up
to the syndicate you're not --
- my syndicate.
- No, no, no, no, no.
You're South side.
This is downtown.
It's no man's land.
I'll stay out of your way.
You stay out of mine.
Russell, you know why a thief
never robs the same home twice?
Because if he goes back,
the owner's gonna be ready for him.
This ain't your home.
What's it gonna take
for you to learn?
Look around! We're downtown.
Come after me again,
you better bring an army with you.
My whole crew's moving in.
Ain't nothing you're gonna do about it.
Enjoy your day.
Okay, I'm just gonna pack the wound.
I'm not gonna give you stitches
so that it can continue to drain.
- Hey.
- Hello. I have good news.
Your facial C.T. is fine.
Your infection is localized.
- Does that mean I'm cleared to go?
- As soon as Dr. Robinson's finished.
Just need you to come back tomorrow
so we can change the packing.
I am... All done.
Thank you both.
- You okay?
- My leg is numb. I've just been sitting too long.
- Father Doyle, you all right?
- I can't move my leg.
- Grace, you're bleeding.
- I know. The scalpel.
All right, we got to deal with that.
Go to exam room "B." I'll be right there.
- You got it? I'll be right back.
- Come on.
All right, here we go.
Come on. Here we go.
- All right, let's do this.
- Oh, slow down, buddy.
You're gonna hang back on this one.
You can put that away.
Look, you never send everybody in to collect
because if you do and something goes down,
you need someone at the wheel, right?
So you're gonna hang with me.
We're gonna get him on the next one.
Yeah, that's 'cause at the next stop,
you got a thing for that waitress with the huge rack.
That's my future ex-wife
you're talking about, pal.
Keep the car running.
Shut your mouth.
Joey Riso, the guy who runs this place...
I took his daughter to prom last year.
- Prom?
- You're like 28.
Yeah, he was not too happy about that.
Throws me out of the limo
and stabs me with a fruit picker.
- Fruit picker?
- A fruit picker.
If the -- if the fruit is
too high up in the tree,
they get that claw out, and they
claw it down with a fruit picker.
Left a scar on my ass.
Nate, Gio! Grab him!
I got him! I got him!
He's just a kid.
What the hell, man?!
The cash ain't here!
Is he alive?
He has a pulse!
What happened?!
I went in there. I see this big guy.
He goes running out the back with a gun.
I turn around, I see Joey shot between the eyes
with an empty envelope in his hand.
- And this kid goes running out the front.
- All right, we got to get out of here.
We can't just leave him here. He knows
who shot Joey and who stole our money.
Pay-up was 5 grand.
All right. Then we shove him in the car,
and we get out of here. Nate, bring the car around.
- Nate! Now! The car!
- Make it quick!
You're bleeding me dry,
Dracula.
We got to run lfts,
a hepatitis panel,
and a rapid h.I.V. Test.
You know that.
How long will Father Doyle's tests take?
A few hours. But that guy's a priest.
I'm sure he's fine.
Sadly, that doesn't reassure me.
I miss you.
Hey, how you doing, Grace?
Oh, I'm -- I'm fine.
How is Father Doyle?
The strength is back in his leg.
Must have been
a transient ischemic attack.
Order an MRI?
And carotid studies.
It's in process.
You are taking the rest of the day off.
Body-fluid exposure.
Go home and relax --
hospital policy.
- Are you sure this place is cool?
- Yeah.
My uncle bought it at auction.
He's rehabbing it to flip.
We got to call Constantine
and tell him what happened.
How's that gonna look, huh?
A guy under his protection's dead,
and we're 5 grand short?
Right. This kid's the only shot
we got at saving our asses.
Well, what if the kid
doesn't wake up?
If the kid don't wake up, we find an incinerator,
and we toss him in it.
Whoa. Slow down.
You know what --
uh, let me call my sister.
- Hey, Nate.
- Hey.
So, uh, hypothetical question.
If somebody falls and hits their head
and then they're not waking up,
- what should you do?
- Did somebody actually fall, Nate?
Yeah, but I'm sure he's okay.
Okay?
I mean, he's got a pulse.
That's good, right?
Nate, tell me where you are
right now.
Brain MRI looks normal.
I don't see any evidence of stroke.
Stroke? I came in for a bite.
An infection increases the risk of clotting,
which could explain your weakness.
We also need to rule out
meningitis and encephalitis.
Which is why we need to collect
and examine your cerebral spinal fluid.
Could you please sit up and hang your feet
over the side of the bed?
It's also possible that
my condition is not medical.
You think that
you're possessed now.
Well, a demon can only
possess one person at a time,
but it will often attack
the exorcist during the rite.
Most priests are strong enough to fend it off,
but I've already shown that I'm vulnerable.
- I realize how that must sound to you.
- I don't think you do.
May I ask --
do you attend church?
When I was a kid.
With my mom.
Not lately.
No disrespect, but explaining
what I do to a nonbeliever is --
it's difficult.
Father, you don't need
to defend yourself to us.
I need you to lean over that.
All right.
Feel for the interspace at L4...
and advance in a cephalad direction
till you feel a pop.
We don't take our duties lightly.
Before we begin the exorcism rite,
we insist that
the person see a doctor.
We pray on the matter for days.
We consult with our bishops.
We exhaust every possible cause
of the affliction.
No one's questioning your faith.
We just need to do our job
as doctors.
I'm gonna need you
to stop moving, please.
I am the vessel of the lord,
and you are a disrespectful heathen
who will burn!
Father Doyle, I need you
to put the needle down!
You have no authority over me!
- Security!
- Security...
The devil is real. He's among us,
and he is coming for you!
This is a move that is long overdue
and unprecedented
in modern times.
Now, with the lake to the east,
our territory's surrounded.
That's why I say
downtown should be ours.
Call it by divine right.
You already run the entire South side.
How much more do you need?
Look, this is not about me.
This is about outsiders like
Russell King coming to Chicago
and setting up a chop shop
and not paying up to us.
It shouldn't happen.
But downtown is too high-profile.
Every crime that happens
downtown winds up on the news,
and the cops need a face to pin it on.
And it's not gonna be mine.
I'd love to pin something on your face.
- You are a pig.
- All right, listen up.
2,000 years ago, Rome was
being attacked from all sides,
including within its walls
by corrupt politicians.
- Sounds a lot like Chicago.
- That's why three men --
Marcus Crassus, Julius Caesar,
and Pompey the Great --
they got together,
and they formed the first triumvirate.
They took the city back,
and they made it magnificent again.
Easy there, Julius.
The risk still doesn't match the reward.
I agree. I ain't doing it.
I got to take a leak.
Celeste, I think this is the chance for us all
to expand and build together.
What do you think?
I think forget about downtown.
I think there's too many problems.
Besides,
I don't like the company.
In fact, why don't I say my goodbyes now
before he gets back?
I doubt he even washes his hands.
No blown pupil.
- How long has he been out?
- About an hour.
No blood behind his eardrum.
Who is he?
According to this,
his name's Sam Cooper.
This I.D.'S from a local teen shelter.
He's a runaway.