What is it about?
The Northern Desert is scared
Send some treasure to me
Beg for peace
My chief extends greetings to
Ashile Tegin
Is this from Pu Sa?
Yes
The Northern Desert is reckless and ignorant,
and makes public anger
My chief feels very regretful,
and begs for Ashile Tribe's pardon
So with this,
my chief hopes two Tegins
would say something favorable
for the King of the Northern Desert
We'll provide a big present
after my chief is pardoned
OK
This is very precious
Tegin Sun should cherish it
Let me have a look
What is it?
Don't worry
My chief
would be equitable to both of you
Why is my gift so small?
This one is better
It's so big
I've never
seen one so big
You keep your small stone
Damn it!
Take the treasure
to my tent
OK
I'll divide it up to all of you
I'm the fairest
Let's go
She's made so much effort
just for a private meeting?
She would have something very important
I'll meet her tonight
You stay here
What do you mean?
干什么
You just write back like this?
Isn't it OK?
不行吗
She is dating with you
Sun
Have you heard a sentence
which is "transfer love by a flying letter  "
We are together in minds
We don't need it
Yes,you are right
But you can write more in your letter
So tell me what I should write in the letter?
No way
Should I teach you how to do that?
Just write down
what you want to say to her
OK,I won't see
Just write down what you want to say to her
Don't peek
OK,OK
Just write
I won't peek
You do it so fast
Why don't you write more?
There is no need
Don't read it
OK,I get it
Ashile Tegin said
he will meet you on time
So what is it?
I've no idea
He told me to give it to you
Thank you
Chief
Did you check the box?
What's hidden in it?
I'm surprised that
the well-renowned Ashile Sun
is so sentimental
Mr. Qin had told me that
you decided to stay in the Northern Desert
If it weren't for saving my people,
I would take you back
as quickly as possible
What's wrong?
Do you paint face powder?
Zhen Zhu uses it
Maybe I touched it accidentally
Does it smell good?
I think
this girl's taste is mediocre
I'll tell her not to paint it anymore
Let's get to the point
Why does the Eagle Division come here?
That is military order
Let soldiers just recovering from plague fight
让大病初愈的人上战场
It looks like the capital
wants to
destroy the Eagle Division's troops
Changge
You know I don't want to
assume the worst condition
But this is the fact
If you want me to
betray the Ashile Tribe
and Great Khan,
I can't do that
He had fostered me,
and given me a new life
I can't
betray him
So
What about the Eagle Division?
I have no choice
Yes,you do
I come to you tonight
and want to tell you that
except betrayal and neutrality,
you have another way
Has he agreed?
He'll reply in two days
I am warning you
If I don't get
what I want
in two days,
I wouldn't let you
see the third day's sunrise
Sun
The Bear Division
needs to talk with us
说有要事要商议
Let's go
Why does your face look so bad?
Didn't you sleep last night?
Let me in
I want to meet Sun Tegin
Mimi
Let her go
You can't stay with the Bear Division,
or you'll die
Sun
I 've checked that
Mimi is right
The Bear Division's arrows and slings
should aim at the direction of the Desert
But now their angles are adjusted lower
There couldn't
appear so much error
It's obvious that they target us
Say something
now
Let me think over it
Why are you so hesitant?
Tu Kashe was not so bold
before
He is supported by someone in secret now
Shut up
Even if we defeat him this time
就算这一次打赢了
we live,
and he spares us
What about next time?
What about the third time?
They wouldn't stop
unless the Eagle Division is destroyed
You go out
Let me stay alone
Let's go,Mimi
Mimi,I have a question to ask you
I know what you want to say
I have something to tell you
I know these plans,
because I'm a mole
sent by the capital
And then?
And
the boy who had infected
the Eagle Division with plague,
looked like
my younger brother Bu Zhen so much
She knew I would save him
So...
You have a younger brother?
They'd caught him
as hostage
They even force me to set fire on comfreys,
or they'll kill him
You've saved the Eagle Division
You are the savior of the Eagle Division
I promise you
I'll do my best
to save your younger brother out
I don't even know
whether he is still alive or not
No matter what happens to him,
I'll give you an answer
Sun and I are gonna
meet Tu Kashe first
Don't think about too much
You are the family of the Eagle Division forever
你永远都是鹰师的家人
You are my Mimi
是我的弥弥
Mu Jin
Let's go
So I'll go first
Here you come
Is that all food?
Maybe it only satisfies three days for the army
Are three days not long enough
to deal with those rats?
What do you think about submission and
presenting treasure of the Northern Desert
We take treasure
The war still goes on
You keep your words
so much
I'll start an attack tomorrow,
and command my 10,000 troops to annihilate
5000 cavalries of the Northern Desert
And with favorable victorious condition,
we'll take down the city of the Northern Desert
How do you think about the plan?
This is good,
But not good enough
So what better plans do you have?
You'll attack next day
This means you would give enemies
the whole night to prepare for battle
The enemies have one-night to strengthen
Then the battle of tomorrow
will be uncertian for victory
You mean...
Prepare for battle tomorrow
as scheduled
But the time we start the attack
is tonight
Surprise attack ?
We should raid the enemies
during its lax
and defencelessness
So we'll act
with your plan
Khan Junior
Get aside
I want to see the Great Khan
I'm sorry
The Great Khan is convalescing
He has ordered
nobody can't disturb him
I'm here to ask about khan's sickness
OK?
Please,don't give me a hard time
She'er
Mother
Wait
Khan doesn't allow me to meet him privately
This order has been cancelled
What?
When?
Why does nobody tell me?
The Great Khan has told me
just now
What's wrong?
Nothing
I...
I just don't get used to it
all of a sudden
You will
You are my son
We
shouldn't be separated
But why does the Great Khan
agree suddenly?
Maybe
he is sick so badly,and
has realized the importance of relationship
I haven't see him in a long time
So I'd better see him
In addition
I have something to ask the Great Khan
He just took medicine
and slept
You could tell me
what you want to say to Khan
Tell me,what do you want to ask?
Khan has sent the Eagle Division and
the Bear Division to suppress the Northern Desert
鹰师和熊师出征漠北
What about the Wolf Division?
So what do you think about it?
This opportunity to make honour should
belong to the Wolf Division
In the Battle of Weishui
The Wolf Division made no achievement
It was ashamed
in front of all tribes
Now the Wolf Division needs a battle
to prove itself urgently
I come here
to ask Khan to let me fight
I'll take down the Northern Desert
for my Khan
She'er,do you remember
what I told you when you were young?
No small tolerance would ruin big strategy
What you should do right now
is to reserve your strength
As long as you are powerful enough,
and hold on to last minute,
the opportunity would come to you
The Great Khan sent me to the border
to inspect the military
But when I came back
We are gonna move capital,
but suppress the Desert at the same time
I think all of them
lack of consideration
It's not like the Great Khan's order
I want to show you something
The seal...
The great Khan is in critical condition
He has transfered the seal
to me
From now on
I'll be in charge of
the whole capital
So..
Do you think I
have no ability to take charge?
No
I  just...
She'er
You should be happy for me
In future,
I won't submit to scary and humiliation
You can come to me if you want to
You can go anywhere if you want to
Isn't it good?
The Great Khan is sick seriously
He can't deal with affairs anymore
From now on
Maybe the seal,
the capital,
and the whole grassland
will be yours
You must get prepared for it
OK,go back to rest
Don't think too much
Is everything ready?
Yes,Tegin Sun
Tonight relies on
the Eagle Division's
performance
We'll assist you
I'll lead the Eagle Division to charge from the north
The Bear Division charges from the south
We'll launch attacks from two directions
Great
Attention,the Eagle Division
Yes,sir
Charge with me
Would Tu Kashe fall into this trap?
Can we succeed?
Don't worry
Everything is under plan
The sun is going to set soon
Do you think
you could see the sun of next day?
The sunset is beautiful
Chief has no need to say such words
ruining this pleasant atmosphere
Report
Chief,the envoy from the Eagle Division comes here
Bring him in
Yes,sir
Mimi
Changge
Why are you here as a messager?
It's a long story
I met with Tegin Sun just now
He wants you to take a message
to two chiefs
Just tell me
Help the Eagle Division make a fake defeat
He'll help the Northern Desert
make a big victory
What are you waiting for?
Get that Chief Yi Nan
up here now
Do you want me to call him by myself?
Tegin
When would we attack?
Just wait
The more they lose,
the easier
we get rid of them
Bear Division
Yes,sir
Follow me
Charge
Stop
Where is the Eagle Division?
Where is it?
Ambush!
We get ambushed
Why the enemies are here?
Damn it,we get trapped
Get back
Retreat
Report
Come on in
What's the status in the front line?
Ashile's Bear Division
had been taken to ambush circle
The two chiefs
led their armies to attack from two directions
The Bear Division couldn't stand
What about the Eagle Division?
It just made bluff
in battlefield
Then its army moved out of the battlefield
with no casualties
The battle plan
was made so perfectly
within 6-8 hours
We can't underestimate the Desert's power
Their tactics are from Chinese
这是中原人的打法
Pu Sa and Yi Nan don't know about them
Is it Changge's plan?
So terrible
Sun
You should think seriously
Her IQ is so high
这女人的心思太可怕了
I worry you would be played by her
You've thought too much
Tegin,something is wrong
Tu Kashe rushs out of the circle
with help of the Bear Division
We can't let him escape
Hah
Who is it?
Sun
Why are you here?
Do you want to betray the Great Khan?
I just want to live
I want my Eagle Division to survive
Do you deserve to live?
You son of a bitch
You are just a slave
You couldn't live today
without the Great Khan's mercy
I'll never forget
the Great Khan's fostering love to me
I'll repay Great Khan
with my own way
in the future
Bah
Do you repay him by this?
There is no good guy in the Eagle Division
And you,Mu Jin
You are the most shameless
You'll be dead men
I'll report everything
to the Great Khan
You both will be executed
You are so cocky
That's all right
Tu Kashe,I'll kill you tonight
The chiefs send me here
to tell you that
the plan has succeeded
Just wait for the Eagle Division coming back
with relief
Thank you
Now that
the plan was done,
I should go back
Where do you go?
The Eagle Division or the capital?
Mimi
I once wanted to ask you that
how did you know
the Bear Division would destroy the Eagle Division
You a kind girl,
or you wouldn't
speak it out
If you have any trouble,
you can tell me
We are together
to find ways to settle it
I'd told you
I have a younger brother
You've told me this
your family was ruined
by the Ashile Tribe
Your younger brother died
Is he still alive?
你弟弟没死
You mean...
He is in the capital now?
No he's in Dingxiang
Yi Cheng did this
She threatened me
with my younger brother,
and forced me to
get in the Eagle Division
Changge
I had no choice
I only want to die now
Mimi
You didn't hurt the Eagle Division,
You've helped it
Now the Eagle Division is "dead"
You should get relieved
How?
If my younger brother is still alive,
he would wait for me to save him
Mimi
We'll talk about it
when
everyone comes back
You just remember that
the Eagle Division has been destroyed
You are dead,too
Nothing
can threaten you
Forget
past
We'll start a new life
in future
Start a new life
Can I really start a new life?
The past Mimi has been dead
The future Mimi
will be a new Mimi
You can do what you want to
boldly and freely
Wait them back
Let's find some ways together
to save your younger brother out
Sun
Wait
Give me your helmet
We should leave something as evidence
for deaths of the Eagle Division and the Bear Division
Mu Jin
You don't have to do this
Sun
Some one should go back to report
We were never separated before
Only if I go back alone,
and tell them you are dead,
they would believe me
You must live well
Don't worry
The plague hasn't taken my life
I won't die so easily
So...
you won't meet
Mimi in a long time
It doesn't matter
I go back
for another personal purpose
Take care of yourself
Hah
Mimi
Where are you going?
Look
I am back to
make the guys in the capital
to believe me
You can't go back
They won't let you go anymore
Mimi
Trust me
I'll come back
I've promised you
我答应过
I'll find some ways
to save your younger brother out
But Dingxiang is guarded tightly
How do you
save him alone?
Let me go with you
OK?
Mimi
I'm a man
A man should
do what a man can do
Promise me
Live well
Wait for me back
You are mine
You should care about me
So you must come back
When I come back,
I won't leave you anymore
Hah
I waiting for you back
It's all over
I come to get you back
Last night I was worrying that
the plan would change,
Tu Kashe would see through our plan,
and something bad would happen to you
But...
I thank you,Sun
You have won
I'm back
The Eagle Division won't
exist anymore
The Tegin of Eagle Division won't exist,either
Do you feel regretful?
The current result is the best
The Eagle Division won't be disturbed
by selfish desire,
and won't be used by others
as a killing knife
做杀戮之刀
Although the Eagle Division has gone,
不过虽然鹰师没了
you can't forget
但有笔账
your promise
What is it?
When you recommended yourself
as my military counsellor
You promised me
to do 3 things
Do you keep your words?
I'm surprised you still remember that
I always
keep my words
Since you mention it,
I think you have worked out them
Tell me about them
I don't know how to say
but I have been thinking of
the first thing long enough
Would you become
more girlish in future?
You mean...
I'm not like a girl?
No,no
How can I think like that
I just care about you
You always
fight regardless of your life,
and work hard to plan
Military counsellor
Give me a chance
Let me fulfill a man's responsibility
I'll protect you
But I know that
You are like a wild horse that can't be tethered
You have your own world
I respect your choice
I won't stop you
from doing what you want to
No matter what kind of situation we are in,
you can't risk yourself alone
You can't leave silently
No matter what happens,
we'll go thought it together
No matter dealing with hardship
or risking life,
I would undertake all
Do you understand me?
Well
I'll think about it
Sun
Sun,don't scare me
Someone coming here
Someone
Sun
Who are you?
The Eagle Division and the Bear Division
have been completely annihilated
Why do they demolish the capital?
They want to move the capital?
What the hell is going on?
How could two main forces
be completely annihilated?
What does Ashile Sun
want to do?
What can a dead man
intend to do?
Sun is dead
I don't want to live,too
If you want to kill me,
just do it
Sun is the god of war in the Grassland
Nobody can kill him
Though he is very heroic,he can't prevent
knives from stabbing him from behind
Too many people
want to kill him
Nevertheless,
Sun ordered me to come back
before he died
He let me report to his father,our Khan,that
the Desert has united together
The Ashile Tribe must be stay alert
The Desert
That's good
I'll let them
pay for Ashile Sun
My Queen
Get up,please
It's such a pity about
the Eagle Division and the Bear Division
I worry about Khan
who can't get over the pain of losing son
It'll be bad if his sickness gets worse
So we'll tell him
when his body gets better
Our Great Khan is sick?
It has been in a period of time
He can't even
speak now
What kind of disease?
I have no idea
Great Wizards are trying to find some ways
It's a pity that
we haven't told
Tegin Sun this in time,
he and his father are
separated forever
So...
对了
You just said that
Tegin Sun's death has other reasons
This...
Don't be scared
If it's ture,
The Great Khan will claim justice
for Tegin Sun and the Eagle Division
My Queen
There existed a traitor in the Eagle Division
All people were murdered
by that traitor
It was my fault
I shouldn't take her
to the battlefield
She attacked Sun from behind
Who is she?
I don't know
As I was about to interrogate her,
我准备问她的时候
she committed suicide
Untill now,
I don't know who sent her to kill Sun
I need to tell these stories to
women and children of the Eagle Division
Please,submit it to Great Khan
Khan sent
the Eagle Division and the Bear Division
to suppress rebellion
But they got ambushed
What a pity
Khan,
are you familiar with this?
Look at it carefully
It seems that Khan's sickness is not serious,
You can recognize that
this is Ashile Sun's helmet
阿诗勒隼的头盔
You miss him every day and night
So let him
stay with you forever