NICKY: I gotta give the guy credit.
I mean, he does the most obvious thing.
This is the only town in the country
where a bookie joint is legit.
So why not take advantage, right?
So he took bookie joints off the street...
and opened them up inside the casino.
Within a few years, he had...
every casino on The Strip
trying to copy off of him.
SAM: Between my innovations...
and Nicky's dedication to his job...
I soon had the best operation on The Strip.
Watch yourself. There's a lot of heat on you.
Why, somebody is complaining?
I'm hearing things from security.
They're all ex-cops.
The sheriff wants to put you
in the Black Book.
That Black Book is a bunch of bullshit.
There's two names in it
for the whole country...
and one of them is still Al Capone.
They put you in that book,
you're gonna be in trouble.
You won't be able to walk into a casino.
I'm trying to make a living, that's all.
I'm just telling you.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
[Upbeat swing music]
PHOTOGRAPHER: Mrs. Rothstein,
straight ahead. Very nice. Thank you.
[People chattering]
PHILIP: For his hard work and dedication...
and the new life blood
he has instilled in Las Vegas...
Sam has established himself
as an indispensable member...
of the gaming community.
As the head of
the Tangiers Gaming Corporation...
it's my pleasure to welcome
Sam Rothstein...
to the Vegas Valley Country Club.
[Applause]
SAM: Back home, they'd put me in jail
for what I'm doing.
But out here, they're giving me awards.
It is with great pleasure that I accept
this certificate of appreciation...
from the Charitable Foundations
of Greater Las Vegas.
Congratulations, sweetheart.
Sam raised more than
we've ever raised before.
SAM: But my greatest pleasure
was watching my wife work the room.
They all loved her.
How could you not love her?
She could be the most charming woman
you ever saw.
People loved to be around her.
You've got to bring Amy
to Sasha's birthday party.
LADY: We'd love to have her there.
3:00, Saturday.
-Yes, okay.
-Great.
SAM: She made everybody feel good.
-Congratulations, Sam.
-Thanks.
Hello, Mrs. Rothstein. How are you?
You're one of the most gorgeous women
I've seen. You're a lucky man, Mr. Rothstein.
Thanks for that compliment.
SAM: He was a young kid
from the casino. Nice kid. Bright boy.
What balls on this fucking kid.
The next day I fired him.
Ginger had that effect on people.
I think she even encouraged them.
GINGER: Do you wanna see this one?
[Ginger exclaims]
GINGER: Daddy gave me all this jewelry
because he loves me so much.
SAM: But as much as they loved her...
GINGER: Fabulous.
...they didn't know what really moved her.
GINGER: Look at this.
GINGER: Daddy gave me....
SAM: With Ginger happy, I was
able to concentrate on what I knew best.
Loose machines are right back over there.
What are they doing back there?
You can't even see them.
Okay.
What about the progressives
with the high jackpots?
These are our best machines.
They bring all the action.
No wonder the drop is off.
The action is in the front.
-Bring them up front.
-All right, I will.
Listen carefully.
There are three ways of doing things here.
The right way, the wrong way,
and the way that I do it.
-Understand?
-I do understand. I'll get right on it.
-Thank you.
-Don't thank me. Just do it.
You're the slots manager.
I shouldn't have to tell you this.
Dang, you are right. I'm so sorry.
SAM: So I ended up working 18-hour days.
Ginger was the one who wound up
enjoying the best of Vegas.
Come with me, please.
I have a better table for you.
What did you say
to that fucking jerk, anyway?
I told him that I was Mrs. Sam Rothstein.
You might as well get something out of it.
SAM: It wasn't long before what I was afraid
was gonna happen, happened.
Nicky managed to get himself banned
from every casino in Vegas.
From then on, I couldn't be seen talking
to him anywhere in or near Vegas.
NICKY: What the fuck is
that supposed to mean?
"...detrimental to gaming and...
"he will be ejected from
any casino in Las Vegas.
"And the casinos can be fined
as much as $100,000...
"every time he shows up."
-You believe this shit?
-Yeah, you got banned.
"Because of notorious
and unsavory reputation."
Motherfucker.
[Nostalgic country music]
-Is there any way around this?
-No, there's no way.
Let's say, for instance...
I want to go into the restaurant,
which happens to be in the casino...
to get one of those sandwiches I like?
Forget it. You can't even
set foot in the parking lot.
That's how serious it is.
-in other words, I'm fucked?
-in so many words, yes.
SAM: It didn't sink into his head
about the Black Book and what it meant.
Not being able to go into a casino
is just one thing...
but being in this book etched your name
into the brains of every cop and FBI agent.
You're listed in there with Al Capone.
But Nicky didn't care.
I gotta do something.
They ain't getting rid of me.
They're not getting rid of me.
I'm staying here. Fuck them.
NICKY: So once they pulled that shit...
I started doing my own things in Vegas
nobody had thought of doing.
To keep an eye on things, I brought in
my kid brother and some desperados...
from back home and started knocking over
high rollers, casino bosses...
bookmakers, anybody right here in town.
I had a good fucking crew going for me,
I'll tell you that.
I had Sal Fusco, a great second-story guy.
Jack Hardy worked for a safe company
before he did a six-year bit.
Then there was Bernie Blue.
This guy could bypass any alarm for me.
It was like old times.
I opened up my own jewelry store, too.
The Gold Rush.
Sometimes I used to go along on a heist,
just for the fun of it.
I didn't like the people
I was ripping off looking at me...
so I turned their fucking pictures around.
NICKY: What's taking so long?
JACK: This is a motherfucker!
It's working.
NICKY: Learn to open these
instead of taking them.
NICKY: These stones got
a lot of niggers in them.
If that fucking Pepe's
switching stones on us...
he better take a fucking camel
back to Nigeria.
[Phone rings]
-They're in Penthouse "K."
-Check in alone?
-They checked in alone.
-Are they out now?
-Yes. Don't worry.
-All right. Thanks.
SAM: He had tipsters
all over town. Bellmen...
-You got to hurry.
-Okay.
-...valet parkers...
-They're just checking in now.
-I'll tell him.
-...pit bosses...
Room 1230 at the Scirocco.
-1 230. Right.
-...secretaries.
-Mint condition coins.
-Mint condition? All right.
SAM: They all got a piece of the score.
MAN: Car's coming.
[Energetic rock music]
SAM: They were very careful.
They always bypassed the alarms,
or else, if not...
they'd drill enough holes to knock through
the walls with a sledgehammer.
Nicky was grabbing everything he could.
Nobody out there was expecting
a guy like him.
For Nicky,
Las Vegas was the fucking Wild West.
I just got a shipment of diamonds
from Israel.
NICKY: What the fuck did they
expect from me? I had to earn, didn't I?
-This diamond has flaws in it.
-There's no flaws in it.
Don't tell me. I'm doing this for 25 years.
You better clean your loupe,
because there's no flaws in this diamond.
NICKY: When we got local merch...
we'd usually send it to Palm Springs,
or Arizona, L.A.
I had a couple of sand niggers out there.
You know, Arabs.
Are you gonna have a meeting
or buy some diamonds?
I know his language. I'm talking with him.
$40,000, you buy the whole package.
$20,000. That's my final offer.
He suddenly talks English.
Let's talk turkey. $25,000.
NICKY: I actually turned my bedroom into
a bank vault where I kept the choice stuff.
I couldn't leave it at the Gold Rush
in case we got raided by the cops...
or if my crew got cute.
I had the only key.
Jennifer didn't give a fuck.
She fell asleep on the couch
watching TV every night.
This stuff was all mine.
I didn't send any of this back home.
Actually, I couldn't,
because I wasn't supposed to be doing it.
The bosses were making
so much money with the casinos...
that they didn't want anybody
making any waves.
You've all given your crew a piece of that?
I took care of everybody.
NICKY: That's why there was no real
organized street stuff in Vegas before I came.
But how much cash could I bury
in my closet, right?
You have to understand,
and I'm sure you do...
that in a venture of this kind...
you must be prepared
to take some kind of loss.
NICKY: I put some money in legitimate
deals with Charlie Clark, Ace's banker.
-You will try to push it through, won't you?
-Yes.
You got to understand,
I'm giving you $50,000 cash.
NICKY: Then I put more money
in some legitimate places, like my restaurant.
DOMINICK: Is that the last one?
COOK: Yeah.
NICKY: I had my kid brother,
Dominick, run it.
Fuckers.
DOMINICK: Here you go, guys.
-Thanks a lot.
-Enjoy it. Have a good time.
-Choke on it, motherfucker.
-Hi, Dom.
How you doing?
SAM: Yeah, Nicky loved restaurants.
He was a real restaurant buff.
And over the years,
he always made money with them.
In Vegas, he had the Leaning Tower.
It was a very popular spot.
He had politicians, showgirls
and movie stars hanging out all over.
That show at The Flamingo
gets better and better.
By the way, Sammy said whenever
you have a minute, give him a call.
-Made you a messenger, too?
-I'll do anything for a buck.
-He does it to everybody. Enjoy your dinner.
-Thanks.
SAM: I got to tell you, the thing Nicky
liked most was the showgirls.
To them, Nicky was the movie star.
-You walk past me?
-This is Shelly.
-Hi, Shelly. How are you?
-Hi.
This is Stacy.
-This is Nick. Wanna have dinner? Come on.
-All right.
Let's check the kitchen first.
Excuse us one second.
NICKY: Come on, I'll show you.
I fly stuff in fresh every day.
I get bread from back home.
I get fish from California.
You can always tell a great kitchen
like ours because of the milk-fed veal.
That's the secret.
See, milk-fed veal is pure white.
Out here, they got that pink veal.
Slide over, honey.
Now, pink veal you can pound for two days.
NICKY: It'll never ever get tender.
You know what I mean?
AL: I left here with the money.
Got muscled on the street.
A couple guys, I owe them.
So I gave them the money.
-That's what I did.
-Yeah?
You call yourself a man?
You know you're a lying lowlife,
motherfucking gambling degenerate prick?
You know that's what you are?
Two small kids at home.
I gave you money to pay the fucking rent...
and buy groceries, put the heat on.
You know your wife called Frankie
and told him the fucking heat's off?
You didn't gamble that money?
Can you tell me that?
-No, you didn't?
-I didn't.
Don't fuck with me, Al!
Don't make a fuck out of me.
You wanna make a fool out of me?
You didn't gamble?
Tell me you gambled the money and
I'll give you the money to put the heat on!
Did you gamble?
Fucking degenerate, you.
Fucking kids at home.
Here. Get the fuck out of here.
AL: Thanks, Nick.
NICKY: Yeah, thanks.
If I find out you fucked up,
I'll leave you where I find you.
NICKY: How many of these you gonna eat?
NICKY JR.: Two.
SAM: At around 6:30 a.m.,
when he finished his day...
no matter where he was
or what he was doing...
he always went home to make breakfast
for his son, Nicky boy.
NICKY: I know you like this.
NICKY: A little butter, right?
Not a lot. You know why, right?
NICKY: Why?
NICKY JR.: 'Cause it clogs up your heart.
What a smart kid you are.
NICKY: Okay, eat.
NICKY: Every couple of weeks,
I sent Marino back to the bosses...
BACK HOME
with a piece of what I made.
Not a big piece, but what did they know?
They were 1,500 miles away, and I don't
know anybody who can see that far.
Their drop was a truck stop garage...
where Remo and the guys
used to hang out and count their millions.
The cops knew, but they didn't give a fuck.
They worked it out.
Nicky sends his warmest regards.
NICKY: I knew how to keep
the bosses happy.
Whenever they gave me little jobs to do,
you know, to send a message...
I would carry things out to a "T."
Like the time Tony Dogs, who was supposed
to be the new maniac tough guy in town...
shot up one of Remo's bars.
Here's a fucking guy
who kills two of Remo's guys...
and a poor fucking waitress
who was just working on her night off.
This guy's just begging
to be made an example of.
I want the names of all the other people
he had with him.
I don't care what you have to do to them
to get them. You understand?
FRANK: I'll take care of it.
NICKY: To be truthful with you,
I had to admire this fucking guy.
He was one of the toughest
Irishmen I ever met.
This son of a bitch was tough.
For two days and two nights,
we beat the shit out of him.
We even stuck ice picks in his balls.
NICKY: Hope he gives me a name,
or I'll give him yours, Frank.
FRANK: Thanks a lot.
NICKY: But he never talked.
NICKY: I know you would've ratted by now.
NICKY: In the end,
I had to put his fucking head in a vice.
NICKY: Can you hear me?
Listen to me. I got your head in a vice.
I'll squash your head like a grapefruit
if you don't give me a name.
NICKY: Don't make me do this.
Please, come on.
Don't make me be a bad guy.
Fuck you.
Motherfucker. You believe this?
Two fucking days and nights.
Fuck me? You motherfucker!
Fuck my mother?
Is that what you're telling me?
You motherfucker!
Oh, God. Give me the fucking name!
Charlie M.
-Charlie M.
-Charlie M?
You make me pop your eye out your head...
to protect that piece of shit?
You dumb motherfucker!
Kill me, you fuck!
You motherfucker!
Frankie, do him a fucking favor.
SAM: Word got around that finally...
there was a real gangster in town.
Nicky was the new boss of Las Vegas.
NICKY: Charlie M.
[Coins clinking]
SAM: Four reels, sevens across.
Three $15,000 jackpots.
You have any idea what the odds are?
It's gotta be in the millions. Maybe more.
Three jackpots in 20 minutes?
Why didn't you pull the machines?
Why didn't you call me?
It happened quick. Three guys won.
I didn't have a chance.
You didn't see the scam?
There's no way to determine that.
Yes, there is. An infallible way. They won!
It's a casino. People gotta win sometimes.
You're pissing me off.
You're insulting my intelligence.
You think I'm an idiot?
Somebody had to get into those machines
and set the reels.
The probability on one machine
is a million and a half to one.
On three machines in a row,
it's in the billions. It can't happen.
SAM: What's the matter with you?
Didn't you see you were being set up
on the second win?
-You didn't see that?
-I think you're overreacting.
Listen, you yokel, I've had it with you.
I've carried your ass ever since I got here.
Get your things and get out of here.
-You're firing me?
-I'm firing you.
-You might regret this.
-I'll regret it if I keep you.
-This is not the way to treat people.
-If you didn't know about the scam...
you're too dumb to work here.
If you did, you were in on it.
Either way, you're out. Go on.
The guy is history as far as I'm concerned.
You can't fire him.
His brother-in-law is County Commissioner.
Everyone out here with cowboy boots
is a commissioner or related to one.
I'm sick of this.
This is his state. His uncle's Chief Judge.
His brother-in-law runs
the County Commission.
There's gotta be a way to work him back in.
You're in the finances, upstairs.
You don't see what's going on.
I've got thousands of players.
I got 500 dealers.
They're all looking to rob me blind
24 hours a day.
I have to let them know I'm watching
all the details all the time.
That there is not one single thing
I will not catch.
SAM: Look at yours. Look at that.
SAM: Look at this. There's nothing.
Look how many blueberries your muffin has.
-I have nothing.
-What are you talking about?
If you don't do it yourself,
it never gets done.
PHILIP: Where are you going?
SAM: From now on, I want you to put an
equal amount of blueberries in each muffin.
An equal amount of blueberries
in each muffin.
Do you know how long that will take?
I don't care how long it takes.
Put an equal amount in each muffin.
Just a little. That a girl.
SAM: Wanna go to Mommy?
GINGER: Wanna come to Mommy?
It's all right, sweetheart.
GINGER: I need to talk to you.
I need some money.
-What do you need?
-Got her?
I need a lot. I need more than usual.
Why don't you take it out of your account?
I would, it's just that...
I need more than that. I need $25,000.
$25,000?
-For yourself?
-Yeah.
SAM: Why do you need that much?
What's the difference? I just need it.
I gotta ask you. That's a lot of money.
It's not a box of popcorn.
We don't have to turn this into a big deal.
We don't have to have a fight.
GINGER: It was important to me. Forget it.
Something I wanted to do.
Who's fighting? Tell me what it's for.
Why can't you tell me what it's for?
Now I want you to tell me.
My wife comes to me and asks me
for $25,000. Do you want a coat?
GINGER: No.
SAM: If you want a coat, you got it.
It's not the money.
It's just, why do you want it?
Am I not entitled to ask that?
I've been independent all my life.
I never had to ask anybody for anything.
Now you're making me beg you for this.
-What are you talking about?
-Okay? And you're embarrassing me.
Why make me feel so bad?
SAM: You're asking me for $25,000.
I'm not out to make you feel bad.
I want to just be able to trust you.
It's about trust.
I have to be able to trust you with my life.
Do you understand?
Can I trust you?
Can I trust you? Answer me.
You can trust me.
Good. So then you can tell me
what the money is for.
[Sentimental jazz music]
She's leaving the bank now.
I'll follow her.
LESTER: What is that?
I know that look. What does that look mean?
GINGER: It means I got the money.
How are you doing? It's Lester, right?
Sam.
From my recollection,
aren't you the card shark...
the golf hustler,
the pimp from Beverly Hills?
SAM: If I'm wrong, correct me.
I never knew you to be a heist man.
But if you are, you know what?
Here, take mine, too.
Take it. You already have hers.
She's my wife.
SAM: Look at me.
You did know that, didn't you?
You knew she's my wife?
SAM: Look at me.
LESTER: I know that.
SAM: You do, yeah?
If you ever come back again...
to take her money, next time bring a pistol.
That way you got a chance.
Be a man, don't be a fucking pimp.
Now, you want to do me a favor?
Get out of here.
I wanna be alone with my wife.
Get the fuck up and get out of here.
SAM: Fucking piece of shit.
Remember when you called him that night
and said goodbye to him?
He didn't say, "Don't get married.
I'll be right down."
-He didn't say that, did he?
-No, he didn't.
What did he say?
"Fuck him.
Take him for everything he's got."
Come here. I want to show you something.
[Men shouting]
[Car horn honking]
GINGER: Make them stop it!
[Ginger screaming hysterically]
It's not his fault! It's my fault!
[Ginger continues screaming]
THUG: Piece of shit.
LESTER: Do it yourself,
you chickenshit cocksucker!
He's such a prick.
He had some guy from the hotel
beat him up.
He didn't want to do it himself.
He didn't want to get his own hands dirty.
Why did he have to do that?
Tell me.
NICKY: It wasn't a nice thing to do--
GINGER: No shit.
You gotta understand it. He doesn't know
if this guy is shaking you down.
I told him all about this guy
before we got married.
-This is no fucking surprise.
-You did? I didn't know that.
He's just a friend of mine
I was trying to help. So what?
The first time I ever saw you guys together...
I never saw him so happy.
NICKY: I know he's a crazy Jew fuck
and everything...
but I never seen him act like that
with anybody else.
I think he's crazy about you.
He really loves you.
NICKY: He does.
GINGER: Come on.
I went into this with my eyes open.
GINGER: I knew the bottom
could drop out any time.
I'm a working girl. You don't think
I'm gonna go into a situation like this...
if I don't think I'm covered on the back end?
Sure, I can see that.
So he put aside some jewelry for me.
A lot of jewelry.
A lot of expensive jewelry?
About how much?
You want to steal it?
No. I'm just curious. I was wondering...
how much he would put
into a thing like that.
I'm told it's worth about $1 million,
maybe more.
NICKY: There you go.
What does that tell you?
$1 million in jewelry.
Does that tell you he is crazy about you?
I should have never married him.
He's a Gemini. Triple Gemini. Duality.
Gemini is the snake, you know.
You can't trust a snake.
I mean it.
I know what you mean. Listen, Ginger.
This is probably not....
I don't have the answers anyway.
-This is probably not what you want to hear.
-I do.
You're a little upset, and I understand that.
But try to make the best of it now.
Go slow. See what happens.
He could've killed him!
He didn't have to hit him.
I'm not sleeping with the guy.
He makes me sneak around
to see my own friends.
What the fuck is that all about?
I guess it's 'cause he loves you so much,
he's jealous and worries.
Who gives a fuck what I do?
I'll try to find out what the hell is going on.
-When I see him, I'll talk to him.
-Okay.
-All right?
-Yeah.
Thanks...
for putting up with me.
Take it easy with this shit.
This can only make matters worse.
You're a beautiful girl. Don't ruin that.
I've seen a lot of girls
get shot to hell from this stuff.
You're so nice.
Come on, now.
I don't wanna see you unhappy.
Thanks.
It's all right.
[Phone ringing]
County Commissioner Pat Webb
is here to see you.
-Give me a minute.
-Okay. Just a minute.
RECEPTIONIST: Can I get you anything?
No, thank you, little lady.
Send him in and call me four minutes after.
Mr. Rothstein, I'm Pat Webb.
How do you do?
-It is a pleasure.
-I heard a lot about you.
PAT: Thank you, sir. House is doing well.
All that money is rolling in.
I appreciate you taking the time
to see a poor old civil servant.
SAM: Why don't you have a seat?
PAT: Thank you, sir.
PAT: I come here personally
to smooth over...
any fracas about a certain matter.
Maybe you didn't know it...
but Don Ward is a very well-liked man
in this town.
He's got lots of friends. His family
and their money go back many years.
Friends vote, family and money votes.
That's important to me and you.
If you'll think about our little problem
along them lines...
and you'll forgive me for saying it...
maybe he did not deserve to be fired.
He knew about our getting hit...
on three big machines in a row,
and he did nothing about it.
Either he was in on it
or, forgive me, he was too dumb to see it.
Either way, I cannot have
a man like that working here.
Before we point the dirty end
of the stick at old Don...
we better be sure
we can prove them charges.
Believe me, if I could prove it,
he'd be under arrest.
Are we certain that you want
the Gaming Control Board...
eyeballing your record
and your gangster pals like Nicky?
I think you're way out of line
talking to me like that.
What you're saying is libelous. You're
in no position to challenge my expertise.
I went way out of my way
to be helpful and courteous to that kid.
He's weak. He's incompetent.
He jeopardizes the whole place.
There's not much more I can do for him.
You have got me there.
Old Don is as useless as tits on a boar.
[Pat coughs]
But he is my brother-in-law...
and I would look on it
as a personal favor...
if you'd think some more
on hiring him back.
I can't do that.
I appreciate the fact
that he's your brother-in-law.
I do want to help you
and I like to do favors.
And I know who you are.
But I cannot do that.
Could there be any position...
farther down the trough?
I'm sorry. I can't do anything.
He's too incompetent.
The bottom line is he cannot be trusted.
[Phone ringing]
SAM: Okay, thanks a lot.
That's it. I'm sorry.
Mr. Rothstein,
your people never will understand...
the way it works out here.
You're all just our guests.
But you act like you're at home.
Let me tell you something, partner.
You ain't home.
But that's where we'll send you
if it harelips the Governor.
-Thank you for your time.
-No problem.
-Sorry.
-You bet.
SAM: What happened to my pills?
Isn't it bad enough you drink too much?
You're taking my pills, too?
GINGER: I didn't take your pills.
For my ulcer, I take a half of one of these.
That's when I have extreme pain.
I had a three-month supply.
What did you do with them?
GINGER: [Crying] You didn't have to
beat him up.
SAM: What?
GINGER: I was just trying to help him.
GINGER: Like I'm sleeping with the guy.
Yeah, how do I know?
GINGER: You can't make me stop
caring about people.
SAM: What?
GINGER: I said...
you can't make me
stop caring about people.
SAM: Listen...
I'm trying to make the best
of everything here.
I mean, you're my wife, for Christ's sakes.
People look up to you in this town.
You know what, Ace? I don't give a shit.
I'm getting out of here.
SAM: You gotta get a hold of yourself.
GINGER: Okay.
SAM: If not for me, at least for Amy.
SAM: Understand? Your drinking's
getting way out of hand.
I'm gonna get you into a program.
They got plenty of good ones.
-I don't need one.
-Yes, you do. It's very discreet.
There's no names in the papers.
That's all you care about.
GINGER: You don't care about me.
SAM: Yes, I do.
GINGER: No, you don't.
How could you say that?
You're a beautiful woman.
You're destroying yourself.
You don't need that stuff,
that fucking leech living off you.
I know you better than you know yourself.
You're a tiger. You're stronger than I am.
When you set your mind on doing
something, you do it better than anybody.
You're gonna do it.
Oh, God.
[Ginger sobbing]
I'll try.
GINGER: I will.
Don't be mad at me, okay?
NICKY: No matter what
the problems were outside the count room...
it was all worth it.
The cash kept rolling in...
and the suitcases kept coming and going.
And let me tell you,
the fucking bottom line here is cash.
The only problem was that after a while...
the bosses noticed that
the suitcases were getting a little light.
Wait a minute. You mean to tell me...
that the money we're robbing
is being robbed?
Somebody's robbing from us?
We go through all this fucking trouble
and somebody's robbing us?
Like I said, it's part of the business.
It's considered leakage.
Leakage, my balls.
I want the guy who's robbing us.
NICKY: Even John Nance,
that's the guy who ran the scam...
he knew there wasn't much
he could do about it.
You gotta know that
a guy who helps you steal...
even if you take care of him real well...
he's gonna steal a little extra for himself.
Makes sense, don't it? Right?
You go try and make these hard-headed
old greaseballs understand that.
What's the point of skimming
if we're being skimmed?
It defeats the whole purpose
of what we're doing.
They take this money because they're
my guys, so give them some leeway.
NICKY: But the bosses never believed
in leeway...
so listen to what they do.
They put Artie Piscano,
the underboss of K. C...
in charge of making sure
nobody skimmed the skim.
BOSS: What were you doing?
I was with my cumari.
BOSS: What were you doing
with your cumari?
I gave her a schiaffo.
NICKY: The only trouble was,
Piscano was a disaster.
This guy could fuck up a cup of coffee.
BOSS: What you been doing?
ARTIE: I'm out there more than I'm here.
NICKY: Little did anybody know
where this would lead.
If they did, they would've
been better off making fucking novenas.
You gotta go back there and talk to that guy.
-My expenses weren't paid for the last trip.
-What expenses?
I'm laying money out of my own pocket,
and I never get anything back.
You gotta go back out there.
From now on,
I'm gonna start keeping records.
What are you gonna do with records,
pay taxes?
I can't keep laying out
my own fucking dough for these trips.
What the hell are we doing over here?
You're going to Las Vegas and having
a good time at my expense.
What the fuck? I mean, after all....
SAM: No matter how many
novenas you could make...
nothing was gonna stop
what came up next at the casino.
PHILIP: I can't believe you're doing this.
ANNA: We made a deal.
SAM: It turned out Phil Green,
"Mr. Integrity"...
had a partner nobody knew about...
and when she showed up
and demanded money from Tangiers...
-Why are you doing this to me?
-Because you're wrong.
ANNA: I'm not.
PHILIP: You are.
No, I am not wrong.
...Green tried to stonewall her.
ANNA: I will see that
you don't get away with this.
So, she sued him in court.
The court will now hear the matter
of Anna Scott...
against Tangiers Corporation
and its President, Philip Green.
OBERON: Oberon on behalf of Mr. Green.
LOGAN: Logan on behalf of Anna Scott.
JUDGE: Mr. Oberon, you can proceed.
OBERON: Thank you.
I believe he was fair,
and I'm delighted with the decision.
We got a problem.
It didn't go too well.
Green has to open up the books...
has to show how he got the financing.
That's not good.
NICKY: She was doing pretty good
with her lawsuit.
But before she could start
counting her money...
the boys back home decided
to settle the case out of court.
So they sent me.
REPORTER: Any comment on
the murder of Anna Scott?
What are you talking about?
REPORTER: She was found last night
shot in the head.
MAN: Was this just
a real estate partnership?
MAN 2: Her lawyer said you were partners.
We were involved
in minor real estate deals many years ago.
It was never a partnership.
MAN: Did you ever hear
of the.22 caliber killer?
SAM: Now, Instead of the cops
only looking at Nicky...
they started looking at Green, too.
And he was supposed to be
our squeaky-clean front man.
I had to start giving interviews
to make sure everybody knew...
the casino was on the up-and-up.
So how often do you really fill in for him?
Green's here about two or three times
a month...
and he's busy
with other real estate deals, and things.
So in Green's absence,
then, you're the boss?
I serve at the pleasure
of the Chairman of the Board.
My responsibilities are
to run the day-to-day operations.
So day-to-day, then, you're the boss?
Well, in a sense, you could say
that I am the boss...
when Mr. Green is away.
You could say that.
PAT: Have you read this?
About Mr. Rothstein.
It says, "The Midwest bookmaker
with mob ties...
"says that he is the real boss
of the $100 million Tangiers casino empire."
PAT: Do you believe that?
OFFICIAL: Did he really say that?
Why, of course he really said that.
It's right here.
Has that man even filed for his license yet?
I don't know. We have to check the files.
Without getting your shorts in a knot,
would you do that?
And check closely, 'cause we may
have to kick a kike's ass out of town.
PAT: Thank you.
A Gaming Control Board investigation
of Tangiers executive...
Sam Rothstein's application
for a gaming license is underway.
Rothstein, who heads the Tangiers casino
operation and is a boyhood friend...
of Las Vegas mob boss Nicky Santoro...
could lose his ability
to work in the casino....
[Phone rings]
Hello?
I gotta meet Charlie the Banker
right away at your house, okay?
I gotta meet Clean Face right away.
What about the Chez Paris?
You gotta make a reservation.
It's all booked up.
NICKY: No, it's okay.
I don't want a meeting at my house.
It's impossible. It's booked up,
and it's very difficult to get in.
I'll come in from the golf course side.
See you at six.
It's okay, I'll use the service entrance.
I'll see you at nine.
All right.
The battle between state gaming
officials and Tangiers casino boss...
Sam "Ace" Rothstein is heating up.
Tonight, a look at Ace Rothstein's
attempt to get state licensing...
despite law-enforcement allegations of
Rothstein's organized crime connections.
Will Sam Rothstein's friendship
with organized crime figure, Nicky Santoro...
keep Rothstein
from running the Tangiers casino?
And can the integrity of state gaming laws
be jeopardized by a boyhood friendship?
SAM: Why don't you take it easy
on that stuff?
Come on. Let me help you down.
We're talking about some stuff.
NEWSCASTER: At 6:00,
will a boyhood friendship...
unseat Rothstein
as the Tangiers casino boss?
Exclusive on the KBBO special news report.
Go down. Just go downstairs.
You can't let this concern you, Ace.
Don't worry about that stuff.
It's just a political witch hunt.
SAM: Do you want something to drink?
-Charlie, you want a refill?
-Yeah, that would be great.
I don't want nothing. Hi, Mr. Clark.
I've been trying to reach you.
-You're tougher to get than the President.
-I've been busy.
Yeah? At least you could return
my phone calls, though.
Listen, Nicky, we talked about this.
And I explained to you that you might
have to take some kind of loss.
Yeah.
I think I want my money back.
What are you gonna do, strong-arm me?
I think you've gotten
the wrong impression about me.
I think, in all fairness...
I should explain to you
exactly what it is that I do.
Tomorrow morning I'll get up nice
and early, take a walk to the bank...
and walk in and see,
and if you don't have my money for me...
I'll crack your fucking head
wide open in front of everybody.
And just about the time
that I'm coming out of jail...
hopefully, you'll be coming
out of your coma.
And guess what? I'll split
your fucking head open again.
'Cause I'm fucking stupid.
I don't give a fuck about jail.
That's my business. That's what I do.
We know what you do.
You fuck people out of money
and get away with it.
You can't talk to me like that.
NICKY: You fat Irish prick!
You put my money to sleep.
Get it, or I'll put your brain to sleep.
Never mind Sam. This is personal.
I'll be there in the morning.
You can try me, fatso.
-You think he got the point?
-What are you doing?
He's a square guy, for Christ's sakes.
He's gonna run to the FBI.
That prick's been dodging me
for three weeks.
-You're trying to tell me what to do?
-I'm not trying to tell you what to do.
You're way out of line. Where's your head?
Where's my head?
Where's your fucking balls?
I'm trying to put something big together.
You know what I'm talking about.
If you're acting like this now,
how can I depend on you?
A lot of things gonna change.
If you wanna be there with me...
you're gonna have to go my way.
You got to understand my situation.
I'm responsible for thousands of people.
SAM: I got $100 million a year
going through the place.
It's all over if I don't get that license.
Believe me, if it goes bad for me,
it's gonna go bad for a lot of people.
Forget about your fucking license.
I plant my own flag out here,
you ain't gonna need a license.
I don't know what it is,
but the more I talk to you...
the more I feel like you just
don't want to go along with me.
-No, I don't want to come along with you.
-All right.
I don't want to be involved
in anything you're talking about, okay?
I want to run a square joint.
I just want my license.
I want everything quiet. That's it!
Quiet like this?
"I'm the boss"? That's quiet?
It's taken out of context. I had no control.
Ronnie and Billy will tell you
exactly what happened.
Back home that looks bad.
Looks bad? Every time you're on television,
I get mentioned. That looks bad.
What the fuck happened to you?
-What happened to you? You lost control?
-I lost control?
You're fucking walking around
like John Barrymore.
A pink robe and a fucking cigarette holder?
I lost control?
I don't wanna bring this up, but you treat
people with disrespect. Even your own wife.
My wife? What does she have
to do with this?
She was upset about a lot of things,
especially that Lester Diamond incident.
You're the shoulder to cry on?
Did you tell her about your role in that?
No, that's not the fucking point.
The point is, she's upset,
and you've got a problem.
I'd appreciate it if you'd stay out
of my personal life.
You wouldn't like it if I did it to you.
She came to talk to me.
Was I supposed to throw her out?
Stay away from her.
It's none of your business.
A week ago it was. Now it's not.
When you need me, you need me.
Right, the way you need me
to vouch for you as a citizen.
I'm gonna have to straighten out
what you did with this guy.
This guy's gonna run to the FBl.
NICKY: Your head's bigger than your casino.
That's your problem.
SAM: I knew what he wanted
and I didn't want any part of it.
He wanted to take over.
He wanted to go after Gaggi,
the skim, everything and everybody.
He also stopped asking permission
from back home for every little thing.
A casino boss and his wife were killed.
The bulls questioned Nicky.
A dealer from the Scirocco.
They questioned Nicky.
Stool pigeons wound up in the trunks
of their cars. They questioned Nicky.
A lawyer.
They questioned Nicky.
When some guys who didn't pay
their shylocks began disappearing...
Nicky's name was in every newspaper.
Nicky was questioned in two dozen
murders, but they always had to let him go.
There were never any witnesses.
NICKY: The coppers blamed me
for everything that went wrong.
Watch yourself.
You're gonna get runned over.
NICKY: If a guy tripped over
a banana peel, they'd bring me in for it.
Be nice.
NICKY: The bosses were no better.
They complained because things
don't run smooth.
In my line of work,
things don't run so smooth. I'm sorry.
I'm dealing with degenerate
animals out here.
The bosses, what do they give a fuck?
They're sitting on their asses
drinking anisette.
Meanwhile, I'm the guy in the trenches.
Fucking bosses think it's
a fucking free lunch out here.
Frankie, they found
a guy's head in the desert.
You know about that?
I heard.
Everybody's talking about it and making
a big deal out of it. It's in all the papers.
What are you gonna do?
That's no good.
Tell him to take care of things a little better.
I'll tell him, Remo.
NICKY: Fucking bosses
smoking their Di Nobilis...
and eating trip' and fucking soffrit',
fried pigs' guts...
while if I wanna talk private,
I gotta go to a fucking bus stop.
-What do they care? Long as I send money.
-They're complaining.
Let them complain. I'm the one
who's here. I do all the work.
NICKY: Somebody don't like it, fuck them.
FRANK: It's up to you.
NICKY: They want a fucking war? I'm ready.
If I take care of five of those guys,
the rest will fall into place.
NICKY: Peek-a-boo, you fucks, you.
I see you, you motherfuckers.
SAM: Nicky was not only bringing heat
on himself, but on me, too.
The FBI watched every move he made,
but he just didn't care.
NICKY: If they're gonna watch me,
I'm gonna watch them back.
I spent a few bucks. Top dollar.
Who gives a shit?
I got the latest anti-bugging equipment
from the same places that sell to the CIA.
I had all the special police frequency radios,
FBI de-scramblers, night-vision cameras....
So, the miserable sons of bitches never
caught me doing anything I couldn't handle.
SAM: I got my job on the line,
he's having the time of his life.
He has every cop in the state watching him,
and he's out playing golf.
And at the worst possible time for me.
I had my license hearing coming up and
I didn't want to leave anything to chance.
If I can't work in Vegas,
where am I gonna go?
You've been very open with us
with the books and papers.
That'll mean a lot
when you go before the commission.
-All I ask is a fair hearing.
-This honesty will guarantee it.
[Plane engine sputtering]
We'll move on to....
SAM: I want to hear about Kansas City.
What the fuck is this?
Where's this fucking guy gonna land,
in the fairway?
They're fucking agents, Frankie.
Look at this.
SAM: The Feds were watching
Nicky play golf for so long...
they ran out of gas.
Just what I needed,
right in front of the control board.
$100, whoever hits the plane.
SAM: If things weren't bad enough...
in comes Piscano,
the Kansas City underboss.
He ran the grocery store in Kansas City
where they brought the suitcases.
Fighting over those suitcases again.
You know what that means?
I gotta take another trip to Vegas.
It's gonna cost me another couple grand.
SAM: He ran it with his brother-in-law...
but he mostly complained about his trips
to Vegas to his brother-in-law and mother.
You gotta lay down the law,
or they'll make a fool out of you.
I write it all down.
Every fucking nickel goes down.
-What's the matter with you?
-Everything's here.
-Since when do you talk like that?
-I'm sorry.
Nance gives me trouble, I'll
take the eyes out of his freaking head.
-Again.
-I didn't curse, I said, "freaking head."
-That's enough.
-I'm sorry.
SAM: What happens next,
you can't believe it.
Who'd believe the FBI
had a wire in the place...
looking for information
about some old homicide...
about some guy who was whacked out
God knows when over God knows what?
What prevents him with the suitcases
from taking what he wants?
Nance brings back two suitcases from
the Tangiers. What about three or four?
We've got nobody in the room to watch.
That's the law.
We can't even go into the count room
to watch our money.
He's got his people in there.
They could all be in on it together.
I'll find out. If it's Green himself,
I'll bury that bastard.
I never trusted him.
I got eyes behind my head.
They trust that scumbag. I don't.
I'll hit the two of them
in the head with a shovel.
MA: Take it easy.
Ma, I'm sorry.
They're beating me left and right.
ARTIE: I'm sorry. I'm upset.
I know, but that's enough.
You know what they're doing to me.
I can't take this no more.
MA: Take it easy. You'll get a heart attack.
ARTIE: I know. I'm too upset.
SAM: The damn thing is,
they hear all this stuff...
about Las Vegas, casinos, and suitcases...
and that's it.
[Sentimental swing music]
ARTIE: Everything's coming out
of my pocket. I gotta pay.
SAM: Would you believe this could happen?
ARTIE: I'm in this to make money, not lose it.
SAM: Every FBI man
across the country had their ears open now.
ARTIE: If you want something done right
you gotta do it yourself.
SAM: Piscano, this guy,
basically sunk the whole world.
MA: There are some that are good
and some that are bad.
COUNSELOR: Members
of the Commission...
Mr. Rothstein is pleased to be here today.
SAM: When the day finally came, I was ready.
I felt so confident that all I had
to do was present my case.
COUNSELOR: We have documents, one of
which is a report by retired FBl agents...
which completely absolves Mr. Rothstein
from any wrongdoing.
-Counselor, before you continue...
-I want to have this marked....
...this Commission acts on a motion
denying the Rothstein application.
COUNSELOR: Denying?
SENATOR: Do I hear a motion seconded?
Mr. Chairman, I second the motion.
Do I have a vote on the motion?
-Aye!
Aye!
The ayes have it. This hearing is adjourned.
-You have to be kidding.
-Adjourned? What do you mean?
Senator, you promised me a hearing.
You didn't even look at the FBl reports.
When you were my guest at the Tangiers
Hotel, didn't you promise me a fair hearing?
SENATOR: I was never your guest.
SAM: Never my guest? I never comped you?
I don't comp you
at least three times a month?
I'd like to answer that at this time.
Mr. Rothstein is being very typical
to this point. He's lying.
The only time I was at the Tangiers
was a dinner with Barney Greenstein.
Was I at the dinner?
SENATOR: You were wandering around.
SAM: Was I at that dinner?
SENATOR: You were wandering.
SENATOR: You were in the building.
SAM: I was in the building?
You know damn well I was there.
You swore I would have a fair hearing.
Did you not?
Tell me I was at least at the dinner.
Allow me that much.
SAM: Give me that much at least!
SENATOR: Yes, you were.
Thanks for not calling me a liar,
you son of a bitch.
A routine licensing hearing
turned into bedlam yesterday...
when the flamboyant Tangiers Casino
executive, Sam "Ace" Rothstein...
accused top gaming officials of corruption.
...promised me a fair hearing
when you were comped at my hotel?
And you asked for copies of your bill
to put on your expense account.
In a wild outburst that followed his gaming
license denial...
Bullshit!
...Rothstein followed several...
stunned commissioners into the hallway
where he continued his harangue...
until his own lawyers and friends
urged him to leave.
You have a past. I have a past.
My past is no worse than yours.
You guys think you have
the right to pass judgment!
NEWSREADER: Long suspected
of running Tangiers without a license...
yesterday's hearing was to determine
if someone with Rothstein's history...
was qualified to officially hold
a top gaming post.
REMO: Fucking hypocrites!
-What the hell's he gonna do now?
-I don't know.
What's he doing?
He knows all those guys he yelled at
are friends of ours.
What's the matter with him,
making all this mess?
Maybe he could run things
with another job title.
Won't be the best,
but what are we gonna do?
REMO: However he runs things, it's gotta be
quiet. Let him hide upstairs in the office.
Say he's a janitor. I don't give a shit.
But please, whatever job he takes,
make sure it's something quiet.
ANNOUNCER: [On TV]
Ladies and gentlemen...
the Tangiers Hotel
proudly presents the all-new...
Sam Rothstein show, Aces High.
Tonight, taped live
from the all-new sports book...
we present the premiere showing
of Aces High...
with the Sasha Semenoff Orchestra...
and the Sam Rothstein dancers!
Mr. Rothstein is a professional gambler
and the best U.S. football handicapper.
A man who will take you inside the real
Las Vegas as no one has ever done before.
Now, the new entertainment director
of the Tangiers Hotel Casino...
Mr. Sam Rothstein.
[Audience applauding]
[Band playing upbeat dance music]
Welcome to the Sam Rothstein show.
We're happy to have you here this evening.
The young lady to my left is Trudy...
who is a lead new dancer
in our fabulous show from Paris.
Our first guest this evening...
is Frankie Avalon.
PAT: Keep an eye on him.
FRANKIE: I've got a large family.
SAM: How many kids do you have?
I'm very proud to say, eight children.
-That's amazing.
-There's nothing to it. It was my pleasure.
[Audience laughing]
PHILIP: Ace, don't do it.
Jesus.
He's juggling!
SAM: Let's not take County Commissioner
Pat Webb too seriously.
I recently challenged him to a debate
on this program, and he declined.
What are you worried about, Pat?
You don't have to send me any questions.
You can ask me anything you want.
ANDY: What the hell is he doing
on television?
He's on all night, screaming about
taking his lawsuit to the Supreme Court.
He really must be crazy.
He's gonna go to Washington with this?
He's out of his fucking mind.
It's a pity we have such hypocrisy.
Some people do what they want.
Other people have to pay
through the nose. Such is life.
Andy, go see him. Tell him
maybe it's time he should quit.
SAM: First, what they did
was totally unconstitutional.
SAM: We're on the list to be heard before
the U.S. Supreme Court.
These guys don't care
about the Supreme Court.
They want things to quiet down.
They want you to walk away.
Walk away? Andy, you can't be serious.
Don't you see what's at stake?
The old man said maybe
your friend should give in.
When the old man says "maybe,"
that's like a papal bull.
Not only should you quit, you should run.
Every time they mention my name
in the papers, they mention Nicky, too.
How the fuck does that help?
The heat he brought down is murder.
The police department was cooperative.
They're pissed off.
Nobody can make a move anymore.
What do you do about that?
-What are you proposing?
-I don't know. He doesn't listen to me.
Maybe he should get lost for a while.
Would that be so bad?
-They ain't sending Nicky nowhere.
-If he took a break...
it would give everybody time to maneuver.
I would forget about the maneuver.
I would just get out.
[Sighs]
I can't do that.
SAM: Of course, as soon as Andy got home,
Nicky heard about our talk in the car.
Next morning, bright and early,
I get the call.
I've got to do some shopping. Want to go?
SAM: Getting a call from Nicky
wasn't easy anymore.
Even the codes didn't work.
So we figured out another act.
If a phone's tapped, the Feds can only
listen in on the stuff involving crimes.
On routine calls, they have
to click off after a few minutes.
GINGER: I got a sprained fucking elbow.
Meet me at 3:00.
-At Caesar's?
-100 yards further down the road.
-Why?
-Don't ask questions. Just be there.
Suzy Cream Cheese has the same outfit.
GINGER: I saw something.
Something very cute.
AGENT: Okay, he's out. It's the ant.
Brown unit.
He's with the bogey. I think it's Frankie.
SAM: Nicky started out before me...
because it wasn't that easy for him
to get around anymore.
Nicky couldn't even go
for a ride without changing cars...
at least six times
before he could shake all his tails.
Because of the planes,
he had to use underground garages.
[Upbeat rock music]
SAM: Meeting in the desert
always made me nervous.
It's a scary place.
I knew about the holes
in the desert, of course.
And everywhere I looked,
there could have been a hole.
Normally, my prospects
of coming back alive...
from a meeting with Nicky
were 99 out of 100.
But this time, when I heard him say a
couple of hundred yards down the road...
I gave myself 50-50.
[Sentimental instrumental music]
Where the fuck you get off
talking to people behind my back?
-What people?
-Did you think I wouldn't find out?
I don't even know what you're talking about.
You said I'm bringing heat on you?
I gotta listen to people because of you?
You're ordering me out? You better get
your own fucking army!
I didn't order you or anybody.
I told Andy Stone that you had heat,
and that was a problem.
You want me to get out
of my own fucking town?
Yeah, let the bullshit blow over
so I can run the casino.
Anything goes wrong
with the casino, it's my ass, not yours.
You know that you only have your fucking
casino because I made that possible!
I'm what counts out here.
Not your fucking country clubs
or your fucking TV shows.
And what the fuck
are you doing on TV anyhow?
I get calls from back home every day.
They think you went batshit!