Over 2000 years ago, ancient Chinese scholars observed the changing patterns in our natural world climates, the turning of the seasons and astronomy. The scholars measured and divided the sun's annual movement
into 24 equal parts, creating the Twenty-four Solar Terms which was used to govern agriculture in ancient China. Even to this day, this invention still guides the lives and traditions of hundreds of millions of Chinese.
Every year around February fourth the Chinese people welcomed the first solar term: the Beginning of Spring, wearing silk flags in their hairs and tying carrots with red cords to the trees. All the villages
celebrate the very first night of spring together.
Hello, my name is Dominic. I'm originally from the UK but I came travelling to China almost 25 years ago, and I've stayed here ever since.
In 2016, something called "China's 24 Solar Terms" was included on UNESCO's list of intangible cultural heritage of humanity.
Now, as I mentioned before, I've been in China a long time but I'd never heard of the Solar Terms. what are the Solar terms? And what significance do they have in today's China?
2000 years ago it was a simpler time; (it) would be eons before science reproduce modern technological comforts that we enjoy today, but despite the simplicity, the Chinese of ancient times
were highly observant, especially when it came to astronomical atmospheric phenomena. Taking into account the changes in the shadows cast by the sun throughout the year, along with the length of the days and nights,
they charted and divided the annual motion of the sun into 24 equal segments. Each segment is one Solar Term and the full cycle of 24 Solar Terms repeats itself year in and year out. Once this cycle was conceived,
the ancient Chinese were allowed to clearly plan a year in advance, especially when it came to agriculture. Is there any use for the solar terms today? Are the 24 Solar terms still the concept
that are being passed down to other generations? With these questions in mind, I impart a journey into the unknown.
Shi Qian is the first destination of my missions to understand the solar terms. Located in the mountainous and undulating landscape of southwest China's Guizhou province,
Shi Qian has numerous waterways that wind their way through its rugged mountain landscape.
Twelve ethnic minorities number among the 460,000 people who've called this place home. The area's unique traditional culture and its road system, don't make it the easiest place for tourists, but they certainly contribute
to an authentic in comparable ambience. In my experience, any attempt to quickly grasp the city's history,
culture and customs should start with a visit to a local museum. I arrived at Shi Qian museum, hoping to find traces on the twenty fourth Solar Terms. There are countless
examples of traditional crafts, art and folk culture on display at the Shi Qian museum, but as younger generations increasingly seek their fortunes farther afield, many of these traditions may be fated to exist only in a museum.
One particular folk culture tradition, however is luckily still being practiced today.
Shuo Chun (Telling Spring).
Shi Qian country 2017 Ceremony of Announcing Spring, an intangible cultural heritage of humanity, starts now. Li Chun,
or the beginning of Spring, as it's known, is the first of the twenty-four Solar Terms. It marks the starting point on the wheel of the four seasons when the world is all revived.
In Shi Qian every year on Li Chun, the ancient custom of Spring Announcer begins.
In April the summer begins and until Grain Full Day, every family is busy with ploughing. The people who have played a central role in the gathering and its associated
ceremonies are known as the Spring Announcers. They are the ambassadors of spring. In the past, farmers counted on string announcers to announce the arrival of spring
and the beginning of spring ploughing.
Feng Wanming is admired in his county. He continues to carry the torch of his ancestors as the fourth-generation Spring Announcer.
The history of our spring announcers
is to advise local people to carry out farming tasks every month. They are told specifically which job to do each month.
It can be dated back to Tang Dynasty whose emperoro Li Siming waged a war here. After winning and returning to the capital, this emperor asked us which title our people would like to claim. Our ancestors picked this one: Telling Spring Officer.
Telling Spring Officer is Spring Announcer.Feng is at his busiest each year on the ten days before and after Li Chun.
At this time, he walks the streets and goes from house to house to announce the arrival of spring in order to ensure everybody knows that it's time to start ploughing.
But announcing the beginning of spring isn't that simple. Essential tools and cultural artifacts like spring calendars, seals and carved spring oxen need to be prepared in advance.
Spring calendars are carved onto wooden blocks and contain the twenty-four Solar Terms and applicable farming information for each term.
Spring cattle is sculpted from wooden blocks.
Is this an ox?
Did you carve it? Yes, I did. Very nice. (It's) for ploughing. We wouldn't survive without it.
Do you bring this sculpture along when announcing spring? That's right. Mr. Feng has run a publishing house here. Are you printing spring calendars? Yeah.
In spring calendars, you know about four seasons,
like which month is longer and which one shorter. There are 24 solar terms,
and you know which month is the time for seeding, planting
or weeding. Each month is meaningful.
That's the way.
Right.
Turn it over and put it there. Oh, it's the most beautiful calendar ever.
How's it done? OK. Good.
The Spring Teller was an occupation authorized by the emperor in ancient China. A hat and gown signifying their rank was their uniform, representing their status and level of knowledge.
I'm the first foreign spring teller. You're terrific!
Everything is ready, but before setting out Feng pays his respects to heaven, earth and his ancestors. He seeks the blessing of his work and looks to empower his chanting to benefit farmers.
Good wind and fine rain.
The Chinese use joyful colors in farming ceremonies, showing their respect and appreciation of nature. Oxen have helped Chinese farmers for nearly 3,000 years. With this in mind, the Chinese.
also have a custom in which they show respect to cattle. One of the activities associated with spring chanting is for the spring announcer to stir the paper-made cattle, using colored wooden sticks.
This is meant to rouse the cattle from their subdued winter states and encourage the farmers to prepare for spring ploughing.
On the second strike, an abundant harvest of all crops. On the third strike, a prosperous country and peaceful life. All return to the original places.
Look at that. Now is the time!
Wow, after the ceremony, the real cattle are also warmed up. The strongest cattle in the county begin to set out on their first foray into the fields under the command of the most experienced farmer,
signaling the start of a new year and working on the land. Spring ploughing is a top priority for farmers. My task now
is to follow Feng from door to door to announce the beginning of spring.
Every year at the beginning of spring,
Feng Wanming traverses the mountainside and visit all the villages around Shi Qian.
He will typically greet more than thirty families every day.
A more appropriate name for this practice should be spring singing
as the words are actually sung out loud rather than chanted.
(Singing)
(Singing) I printed this calendar. May you be happy and prosperous.
Showing at the right time is essential for reaping a good harvest. The essence of a spring teller's lyrics are the 24 Solar terms. These include the terms for
wedding,
the term for sowing and the terms for harvesting. Feng know those intricate solar term lyrics by heart.
(Chinese)
(Chinese) Flourish in populationa and pass on in generation.
The lyrics are not written in stone, and he occasionally add lives to his lyrics and wings it with improvised blessings tailored to different situations and conditions for every different family. Feng spreads cheer to all
that welcome him.
Nobody wants to miss out on a blessing to kick off the year (Chanting)
Have a drink and you'll be rich.
(Singing)
There is a strice timeframe for chanting spring. Ten days after Li Chun,
the practice is over for that year. Feng then goes home and rest for a while, rewarded with tribute money.
Brand new? It's spacious! Three stories? Do all the family members live here? How many of you? Six!
Take a seat. Wow, the look of a new house. It's great.
When did you move in? Five years ago. Who is this handsome man in the photos? My grandson and granddaughter-in-law. Are they newlywed? Yes.
How much can you earn in a year? Me? Now I can't make much money. Every year he makes a lot of money in announcing the spring. See? He's telling the truth. Before the spring telling there are ten days and after that another ten days. Totalling as 20 days, I make 200 yuan every day. So 2,000 yuan.
Who paid you? The host family. We go to one family or another, and the owner would pay us, such as your family.
He pays you. How much would it be if a family pays you the highest amount?
As much as more than 100 yuan. Chanting spring provides a good source of income for the spring announers. These payoffs encourage spring announcers to pass on this tradition.
The Chinese believe that spring is a key time of year, and whether or not the year will be a success depends on a good start in spring. Solar terms to Chinese farmers are about more than simply timing; they are a representation
of natural cultural heritage.
When farmers start their spring ploughing, Feng's job is done.
He stores the tools and props in his old house on the mountainside.
Chanting spring, when did you start it?
Since I was about 5 or 6 years old,
Our parents have been teaching us.
Most of the time the lyrics would be taught to boys rather than girls.
(music)
I love the old houses like yours.
Right. I built it myself.
I assembled them myself.
When did you build it? 55 years ago?
55 years ago? I was 18 years old then. Are you a carpenter, too? Yes. Did you make a living as a carpenter?
Yes. Totally depended on that. 5 yuan a day.
5 yuan a day? Aye.
I earned 5 yuan a day. How about this job now? Now I would make 200 a day with great ease. Right now as a spring announcer, you would be quite busy around Li Chun period. Right. You would sing. That's true.
I love this poster. When did you buy it? It was bought decades ago. Decades ago? How beautiful it is!
I, a foreigner, just love this. What about this? It's a coir raincoat. Farming in the field, you would wear it on your back on rainy days to keep the rain off. Now there're raincoats, but back then we wore this.
This is an antique which I shouldn't throw away. But you shouldn't throw your house away. Your house is still here. I have sons and grandsons.
But if they don't want the house, it's their business.
Since most young people from this countryside are moving to big cities to seek their fortunes these days, a lot of these old traditions
are not being carried on.
To help pass this tradition on, the local government here has set up a spring chanting class as Shi Qian's primary school. Feng tells me that every year
two graduates will join the spring telling team to pass on the tradition and knowledge of chanting spring and the 24 Solar Terms.
I believe the reason why this tradition has been carried on for thousands of years is Shi Qian's people's age-old dependence on the land and their deep respect for nature. Their understanding
of nature and the Solar Terms continues to help nourish the tranquil countryside and industrious farmers of Shi Qian.