Brought to you by Ramen Soup Subs!
Translators: athille123, suebee, nxh, angelyrique (soompi)
[Before shooting]
Timers: melijay, aznhoneychik, warunee123, swtsrwlove, katchan1, saffron, khai, pekkles
Editors: swtsrwlove, melijay
[Jongshin the musician is composing something.]
Encoder: melijay
Raw Provider: K-Aigo Media
He's calling.
Yes~ Jaesuk?
Hello, Family members. It's Jaesuk.
[The information for the
twenty-first destination.]
This week, we'll be going to Kyungbook Province Sungjoo Hangae Village.
[Kyungbook's Sung Joo county Hangae Village]
Please come next Monday at 9:00 am sharp in front of the city hall.
[9:00 am]
[Meeting in front of the city hall]
Information finished.
[Hangs up]
[Jongkook playing soccer in Shoot Dori]
We're going to eat melons...
[Ah~~]
9:00?!
Hello? Hello?!!
[The new Family is already losing her temper.]
Manager! Why didn't you tell me?
Do you think you'll be able to go there by 9:00?
HEY!!
[Everyone in the Family receives an information call.]
[The day of shooting]
[They're going to Kyungbook's Sung Joo county!]
[At the city hall]
[Sooro is here.]
[Jongshin seems uncomfortable(?).]
Hi.
[Hyori comes with a bright greeting.]
[Chunhee is very busy because he's shooting a movie.]
You're here.
Yeah.
Oh, Park Yejin.
[Happy Yejin]
Hey.
It's Daesung.
Daesung!
[Daesung, the youngest has also arrived!]
[Everyone is loud because they're talking about Jongkook's concert.]
It was a big hit!
I know!
Eunhye was there, Eunhye.
-You saw her, right?
-Yeah, I did.
[The sisters did not receive(?) an invitation.]
[Jongkook comes now.]
He only invited Yoon Eunhye.
[Overreacting?]
Jongkook.
[Jongkook is unaware of the situation when he arrives.]
You're so unfair.
What?
In the end, you only invited Eunhye.
No! It's not like that.
[Ironic]
You didn't invite us.
Yeah. I was surprised.
[The arrows of hatred(?) are being shot at him.]
Everyone is busy...
It's because he's afraid that he might hurt Eunhye's feelings.
[He didn't invite(?) them because of Eunhye.]
It's not that, other celebrities came, too.
There was Park Shinhye...
You're a player!
[Now he's a player(?)]
Listen everyone. Today, my friend is coming.
Oh yeah.
[Jaesuk's friend, the new Family is coming slowly.]
Today is Jaesuk's friend.
[Anticipating]
It's been a long time.
[Who is Jaesuk's friend?]
[The pleasant girl, Kim Wonhee]
[The girl who took over the   Family.]
[The Family's Queen Wonhee.]
[New power(?) in charge]
[Never seen before, the enthusiasm of the Family is exposed]
Today, since our mistress Wonhee has come...
[Burden]
[Should they be worried about meals??]
She made dumpling soup for her husband for a month...
[The brutality(?) of mistress Wonhee is being revealed.]
Now since Wonhee is here, let's go.
[Now, they're going to grandfather and granmother's house!]
[The rough map goes to the new Family.]
This map looks like a squid!
[Now they're going to find the house!]
[The scent of the flowers are spring]
[They can feel the warmth of the village.]
[The pride of SungJoo, they are famous for their pigs and melons]
[The Family is staying in Hangae Village!]
Hyori is a bit awkward with Wonhee?
Since she's an unni...
I can't make fun of her like I do to the oppas.
Try once.
[Hyori's new side will be revealed, it'll be something you've never seen before.]
-There?
-I think it's that.
[They found the house thanks to the squid-looking(?) map.]
[They're easily finding the place.]
[They're walking into the gate of grandfather and grandmother's house...]
[The tradition is living inside of the traditional Korean house.]
Hello.
[  Grandfather: Lee Soohak  ]
[  Grandmother: Jo Jungja  ]
You're from a very rich and historical family.
Hello.
[Everyone is greeting each other happily.]
[Descendant of a minister in the Joseon Dynasty.]
[Right now, he's basically a minister.]
Yes.
Everyone is very polite today...
[Everyone politely gathered their hands together.]
Since he's very rich.
Hyori is very polite and calm today.
[Hyori became a modest lady today.]
So you're Hyori~
[He couldn't realize who it was because she had no makeup on.]
She doesn't have makeup on.
It's an honor to stay at your house.
[It's an honor to stay at this awesome house.]
I hope you become a great amount of help in the fields...
Yes, and both of you have fun on your vacation.
[The elders are going on vacation now.]
Have a safe trip.
[We hope you have a safe and sweet vacation...]
[Family's chores!]
Pick melons and take care of the pigs.
Then, can we eat SamGyeop Sal (Korean BBQ wrapped with lettuce)?
We're supposed to take care of them, you're going to eat them?
[Pick melons and take care of the pigs.]
[Episode 1: The melon and pig Family]
What's with the bag?!
Why did you bring a bag?
[She brought a purse when they're going to work.]
Just in case.
Does this suit me!!
[Mrs.Wonhee doesn't know the atmosphere of the Family yet.]
Should we pretend we're going to the mall?
I'll buy one pack of these!
[Guile]
Wow, look!
[It's Sungjoo's famous melon field!]
I've never seen one before.
[Amazed]
[They grow in the green houses in the cold winter.]
[And now Sungjoo's melons are yellow and ripe!]
[It's very wonderful to be able to eat melons in this kind of weather.]
Since the 21st century, everything can be raised in green houses.
[Every fruit is able to be grown in green houses now.]
Oh, this is very suitable for you.
Do I seem like Goo Joonpyo (of Boys Over Flowers)?
Why do you say that?
[Whirl!]
Who are you calling Goo Joonpyo!!
[They arrived at the melon green houses.]
Wow~
[Green]
[They pick the melons and put it in here.]
[They don't have to carry the baskets, so it's easier~]
Just put them in here.
Wonhee, put your bag somewhere...
[It's like putting your purse on a shopping cart...]
Wow, there's a lot here!
[There are so many ripe melons...]
[Fresh~]
This is the famous Sungjoo melon!
[Everyone knows the truth already...]
[Jaesuk takes a bite!]
[Thud]
[... You're going to break your jaw...]
You can break it with your fist.
Let's see if your a true man!
[Thud!]
[Wow~ the manly Jaesuk! With just one shot~!]
[Everyone is interested!]
[The melon is very full~]
[The oldest hyung will try it first.]
Let's try it.
[Bite!]
Is it good?
Mmm, it's good!!
It's very sweet.
[The honey bees pollinate the melons, making it have a sweet taste without using pesticides.]
It's so sweet.
[When are you going to pick the melons?]
We should start picking them.
Push the cart please, the shopping cart.
Wow, look at this.
It's so yellow~!
[They can just grab fresh melons with their hands.]
[Mrs.Wonhee is trying her best~]
It's my first time seeing melons that are so yellow!
[The color makes it look so tasty.]
I don't think we need so many people in here.
[Crowded]
Five people can stay here, and the other five can go to the pigs.
[It's crowded for 10 people to be in a green house~]
[Hyori's Suggestion: They divide the groups, and one team goes to the pig farm!]
Yeah, the guys should go to the pigs...
The girls can stay here.
You can go with the people you want to go with!
Just like we did with Yoona?
Our mistress Yoona...
Mistress Generation! Mistress Generation!
[They're trying not to get picked.]
Chunhee seems healthy!
[He shouldn't have pretended to be working.]
Come with me.
I have to bring the grasshopper with me, too!
[Jaesuk got chosen, too!]
[Pig Team: Wonhee*Sooro*Jaesuk*Chunhee*Yejin]
Let's go.
The pigs here eat the melon seeds...
[So they have to bring a pack of melon seeds.]
Let's go already.
Stay here, and keep on picking.
[Lightly~]
[Jaesuk naturally gets Madame Wonhee's bag.]
[... It's not like he's her secretary...]
Turn on the engine on the car!
[Eloquent~]
[Melon Team: Jongshin*Jongkook*Hyori*Daesung]
(To the people going with her) She doesn't work very much so keep an eye on her!
I'm powerful too!! Don't worry!
We don't need anyone watching over us! We work well on our own!
[  The three guys worried
bout being left with Hyori...]
He definitely needs someone watching him.
Hurry up and carry this!!
[Because the Queen unnie isn't there, right away!]
[Her true self]
[The Pig Team]
- What is that?
- Chunhee's about to die.
[Loves to work(?) Chunhee carrying the melon seeds alone...]
- Chunhee-ya! Why do you always do things yourself?
If you're tired, ask Yejin or someone for help.
Yea, give it to Yejin.
[(You want me to carry it??)]
[The other side]
[The pigs waiting for their food]
[Please give me my food~]
[Everyone amazed at the clean and spacious stable]
These look like cartoon pigs!
It's really clean here.
Piggies~
[Just hurry up
with the food...]
- Are these wild boars?
- No.
[...Why would these be wild boars...]
They're really clean.
They only have young pigs here.
They're really hungry so let's hurry and get their food ready.
[I'm hungry]
Is this a spaceship?
[Not a spaceship but a large feed container!]
If we go in we can just take off.
They said melon seeds have a lot of vitamin E.
What's vitamin E good for?
Your teeth (wordplay).
[...of course...]
- Vitamin Nose is good for your nose. Vitamin Mouth for your mouth.
Yejin-ah, shut his mouth for me
We have to mix the feed with the melon seeds.
This is good...
- Get one for home.
- I want to.
- For your rice.
Seriously.
I'll carry this, Jaesuk. I should at least do this much.
[While Jaesuk keeps carrying her purse]
These are ground melon seeds.
It smells good! It smells like melons!
Hyung...
- Do the run!
- I'm not a grasshopper...
I'm being Ultra Man right now!
- This is being a grasshopper.
- Do the run!
[(You're a grasshopper after all...)]
- What does the ratio have to be like?
- Just whatever you think is right.
[Mixing the feed and melon seeds however they want]
[The Family completes the melon seed feed~]
[Put it in the feed
container and OK!]
Oh, in here~
[Hey~
food's here~]
[Chunhee, what is he doing instead of feeding...?]
[Ah~ Ventilating the stable during feed time!]
[Chunderella finding work to do...]
[I smell
food here...]
[A genuine pig feeding frenzy]
It's okay~ It's okay~
[Lady Yejin speaking tenderly to the pigs]
- Yejin really loves pig meat.
- So do I.
[Sweet (So cute...)]
[Savage (So tasty...)]
[Putting in every last grain]
[This really is a frenzy...]
[Move~]
[Family finished with feeding the pigs]
Why are those two fighting?
Should I stop them?
[While everyone just watches... Yejin steps in]
[Gulp!
It's Lady Yejin!]
No!
[Yejin, pulling by the tail!]
[...Now even stopping pig fights...]
[The stable manager here to do a check up]
We finished feeding them.
I have to give them their health shots. Why don't you each grab a pig.
[To make them healthy, periodically gives them nourishment shots]
[Everyone hesitates!]
Do you administer it on their butt?
[The stable manager first gives a demonstration]
You just have to grab them like this.
[Will calm down when you grab their ear...]
- You have to mark them after the shot.
- So keep holding them until it's all done.
[Lady Yejin totally excited]
She's practically skipping!
Come to unnie!
[The Pig Unnie(?), is a natural]
[Amazed]
[With one try!]
[As expected from Sweet & Savage Lady Yejin...]
[The stable manager administering the shot for safety]
- You caught the pig very well, you can mark it with your name.
- Where? My autograph?
[Sweet Yejin with a heart]
[(Will we be able to do it well...)]
[Yejin's pig, done!]
[This time it's Madame Wonhee's turn]
[Went in with a push]
[Because they're still young they're very strong...]
Just grab one by the ear as hard as you can!
[Her method is to pull by the ear(?)!]
[Oh~ Wonhee grabs one easily!]
Hurry!
[Not sure if it's Wonhee or the pig screaming...]
[Their expressions...]
[With the shot done all she has to do is mark it]
[Quiets down when Yejin reaches over~]
[The Great Pig Unnie, Yejin!]
Jaesuk! It's so much harder than I thought.
They're all trying to run away since they know what's coming.
They're all trying to hide here.
[Nervous about the impending shot]
[I hate shots...]
[Which one will Jaesuk get...?]
You! You, you, you! You? You're going to get a shot no matter what.
[Slowly getting frustrated...]
Grab it by it's stomach!
[Of course...]
[Pathetic]
- It might bite my hand.
- I'm going to tell Hyori unnie!
I'll grab it in a flash!
[The moment she brought up Hyori]
Do you want to go?
- They're looking at you like you're easy. Hurry up and catch it.
- They're just eating.
[Will he be able to catch it within the day...]
[Finally... he caught one!!]
[Frightened]
[Pathetic]
You're so stupid!
[   Both of them frozen!   ]
[Of all things,
being caught by
the grasshopper...]
[Jaesuk, still miraculously succeeds]
[Chunhee too succeeds through the ups and downs!]
Hyung, you seem a bit scared!
[Sooro, as expected in one try!]
[ Totally frozen ]
[Scattering sawdust on the floor when done]
[For them to comfortably sleep on]
[They fed them, gave them shots, and put sawdust on the floor...]
[It was hard, but the Pig Team is all done with their work!]
[On the other side, the Melon Team...]
[After a few minutes in the greenhouse...]
Oh check out Kim Kookjong's muscles!
[Hidden for 6 months because of the autumn weather]
He's picking melons with those muscles.
[About the size of a melon]
It's like the salted roe of a pollack.
[...Nice metaphor~]
- The village is really famous for their melons.
- This is my first time seeing a melon this color.
I've seen melons that were slightly yellow.
- This is totally a golden yellow.
- And it looks more swollen, too. Like really natural.
What?
Why are you laughing?
- Am I funny to you?
- No.
It's just that when Wonhee nuna's around you don't talk at all...
- Me?
- And now you're talking so much.
- Hyori's just holding back.
- That's right, since she's our guest
- Exactly.
- But you're having a hard time though, huh Hyori?
- (formally) Yes, I'm usually intimidated by female seniors
Try to get close with her by tomorrow.
(formally) I really do like her though. She's #1 of the people I want to become close with.
But nuna, why are you all of a sudden speaking so formally?
- I am, huh...
- It's because you're thinking of Wonhee.
[Also in a moment...]
[In their lifetime... seeing the invincible Hyori like this...]
I can't be like that in front of the oppas...
[Hyori's humiliation...]
[Doesn't know what's in store for her]
This is so yellow.
Just because the camera's on you...
Quit watching me!
Hyung, did you see that? Because the camera was on her, she was trying to be pretty.
The viewers like it when you do things like that!
- We need to wash these.
- Let's bring them out then.
[Pushing them out like a shopping cart]
You guys look like a retired couple.
[Jongkook and Hyori, an elderly couple back on the farm?!]
[Wash them in water]
- Do think melons sink or float? They float.
- Oh, they do.
- So you have to do all this, too.
- I know, I thought you just picked them and ate it.
[Dry in the sun]
- It's so pretty.
- It's like a picture.
[Like bright yellow spring flowers]
You think I'll look pretty washing these yellow melons?
You think you can compare?
[Sort by size]
We have to do all this, too?
[Carefully sorting one by one...]
We're done!
[Melons given by the village chief!]
- Let's go.
- Yoohoo! I'm so happy!
Yoohoo?
I haven't heard that in a long time.
- We're at the kitchen garden. I heard the Melon Team's work wasn't that hard...
- That's not true!
- We suffered a lot.
- You ate melons, huh?
- Do you know how hard it is to peel melons?
[You thought peeling melons to eat was hard...]
On top of work, we had to attend to the Madame here.
- She brought her stupid bag with her.
- That big bag.
I checked it in.
Since we have to water the kitchen garden, we can do it while playing our game.
See this here? We're going to balance buckets of water on our heads and jump over it with both feet.
- That's impossible! With buckets on our head?
- Why does it have to be with both feet?
- So that you'll trip and spill water.
- Exactly.
- We have to water the garden, after all.
- I guess it's time for my cleansing then...
So our team leaders...
- How about between the two friends here?
- Should we? Ok!
[Yoo Jaesuk vs Kim Wonhee]
Why are you coming in late?
- Rock-paper-scissors! Rock-paper-scissors! It should be like this!
- But you just won...?
Oh, I did?
- Chunhee jumps well.
- Ok, then Chunhee.
[He's tall, but clumsy...]
- Why do you do scissors like that?
- What's wrong with it? You can tell what it is.
She'll be funny at this. Hyori!
Someone funny? Daesung.
- I'm funny too...
- Don't be unreasonable.
Go over here for now.
[Less important than cold rice]
[And now even being called unlucky...]
Out of everything, I'm unlucky too?!
That's the first time I've heard you being called unlucky.
What? Everyone else is on our team?
No, one more person.
[Madame Kim wins again]
The unfavorable Yoon Jongshin
Our team looks so much stronger with Jongshin gone
Since we have 4 and you have 5...
One person falls out from our team
Rock, paper, scissors
[First hears that he's unfavorable, then gets cut from the team]
[Ends up as the turning point...]
[The Elder is really unlucky today...]
Let's start the first round.
[Jaesuk vs Hyori]
Make it funny!
Don't even worry about that
PD: Should we put the audio here or there?
We can't really get everyone
Move it over there
We don't really need to get audio here
[We don't really need to get audio here]
[Not important enough for the mic...]
[Moving the audio right away]
He said audio is unnecessary for me
Put your hood on
[Everyone here has audio]
Hyung, it's because you're unlucky
[But now you can't tell... what's being said here...]
This is a lot of water
It's perfect, huh?
On your marks!
[also sounds like 'count your teeth']
1, 2, 3, 4...
[Such a corny joke...]
So annoying
Hyung! She's just muttering 'so annoying'
I'm not going to high five something like that!
[Shocked]
You want a high five for that joke?!
[Very strict about her gags, Madame Wonhee]
Ready!
[Running across the uneven garden]
[Trying not to spill the water]
[Very careful~]
Both feet!
[Jumped over one foot at a time]
[Hyori has to do it again]
I didn't do it with both feet?
I did!
Do it again!
(AH! It's cold~)
[Feeling his pain]
[The Nation's siblings squabbling at the turning point]
[Which ends up soaking the Elder]
[Now running at full speed!]
[The little sister]
[The big brother]
[All personal feelings are set aside!]
[The excited Madame Wonhee]
[A close draw]
[In the end]
[   Hyori wins by
a slight margin   ]
Hyori wins!
I won?!
[Suddenly looking like a drenched mouse]
Turning point, sit down
[As if getting baptized...]
[The lonely turning point]
Next up...
Game Devil Sooro and Chunhee!
Start!
[Both going at a stable speed]
[The long legged Chunhee at an advantage with the jump]
[King of speed, Sooro]
[Family showdown!]
[Long legged Chunhee, jumps]
[As expected, he may be tall but he's clumsy...]
Chunhee's like an irrigation
[The game continues]
[He may have lost already, but he tries hard til the end...]
[However Sooro still wins]
He really is lacking
Yejin and Jongshin
Yejin, win without hesitation
Kim Jongkook oppa!
Even though I'm not Yoon Eunhye, will you still let me borrow your waterproof jacket?
He won't lend it to you
Why wouldn't I lend it to her? You can borrow it, Yejin
If Yoon Eunhye was here, who would you give it to?
I'm Yoon Eunhye
[Huh?]
Unnie, I don't want to know
Was that too much?
I think that remark just traumatized me.
'I'm Yoon Eunhye'
Yejin looks cute!
[Cute and precious rain gear girl]
[Did the fake scandal turn into a real scandal?]
You've just been going all out lately
No, the outfit
Just the clothes are cute?
No, it's cute on you
Only Yoon Eunhye will do?!
[Jaesuk subtituting
for Jongshin   ]
[Water interference right from the start]
[Lady Yejin, foul play]
[After overcoming the foul play...]
[In the end loses strength in his legs...]
[Unlucky... so unlucky...]
[Manages to soak Jaesuk on his way down]
[His little brother resents him]
[Even his shoe came off]
[The Elder, defeated again...]
Don't put in that accordian music!
[Can't tell from his back...]
Good job, you at least tried your best
Jongshin hyung, good job and all but we have one more round left.
Can you go back to being the turning point?
[He may be tired but he still has work to do...]
If you stay with us it changes your theme
[Actually, he has been left alone a lot]
Just stand there
[Yejin shaking out Jongkook's clothes]
[The main characters in the fake scandal]
I just can't stand him anymore
What?! What did I do?!
Let me dry it off first
No, it's okay
No, no  you'll get cold if it's wet
No, I won't get cold
If she offers to dry it off, just say okay then no one will suspect you of anything more
Oppa! I'm Kim Eunhye. Let me wear it.
[Madame, even you...]
Jaesuk oppa and Wonhee unnie for this round
The close friends should at least play once
Why do I have to keep playing against strong women?
I never play against guys. Always women!
That's your character!
Show us why you're the fantasy combo
What do you mean?
The funniest fantasy combo
Should we bow to each other like this?
[An idea expected from the from the fantasy combo]
That's just too much
I'm not going to go easy on you
What?
[Running at full speed from the start]
[Not caring about the water in their bucket]
[Already soaked by the first half]
[Madame Kim pouring the rest of her water on the turning point]
[The truely unlucky turning point!!]
[The fantasy combo running as if their life depended on it!]
[Jaesuk wins!]
[The game is over and their clothes are soaked through]
That was fun!
How is this fun?
Who's game are we playing?!!
It's over! It's over!
Our team, victory!
What is that?
[Seungri (of Big Bang) also means victory]
Our team, victory
[The Family doesn't know just how strong it'll get]
[Ch. 2: All hail Queen Wonhee~]
It's time to start dinner. Do you plan on going somewhere?
Why did you bring all your luggage out?
I feel like I'm presenting my offerings to the king
I'm usually not like this
They said you have to make your own food here?
Honestly, have you actually watched Family Outing?
Truthfully, I've never watched the show
[So that's why...]
She thought you just carried everything around with you
I even brought my laptop
Regardless, it's time to start making dinner. So maybe you should put your luggage into the room.
Should I?
Want me to do it?
She's just getting the person next to her do it
[The Queen's (?) power to getting someone else to do it]
Jongkook is such a good person
That actually suits Jongkook oppa
Wonhee, you can just stay here
I heard the pig meat has marbling?
The village chief gave us pig meat
One of the pigs that feed on melon seeds
[Marbled pig meat?]
[It really does!!]
[It seems there might be a fight over the pig meat...]
I heard the pig meat is really delicious here
- I want to be on the House team
- I call House team!
I'm in the House team no matter what!
[No one wants to leave because the people that stay might eat it all...]
House team!
- Me too!
- You can't make me leave
I'm never going to leave!
[In position]
[Then what about Queen Wonhee?]
[Scared because she heard her name...]
What's with you today?!
Out of the women, I'm the oldest
How about everyone that didn't eat the meat last time stay home?
Ok, ok
- No!
- Yea, the Meat Team!
I heard this village is famous for their pig skin
And pig skin has a lot of collagen, so it's good for the skin
So someone has to go to the market and buy pig skin
If you keep talking about it, then I have to end up going to get it
Let's send our Queen to the market then
I don't even know my way around here
Oppa, give her two attendants
[Right hand Chunhee]
[Left hand Jongkook]
I want a sedan chair
We can be your sedan chair
Carry her around the market
Then who will be the vegetable team?
- Hyori has to get the vegetables no matter what
- That's not my style
I heard Hyori cooks well
Hyori does cook well, but she can be a bit gluttonous... so...
I'm gluttonous?
You ate all the meat last time
How about we hide the meat somewhere?
Or we can split the meat amongst us so we can't eat it all
How about we take the meat with us?
No no no!
[First handing over the beef ribs...]
No! Oh, yea take that one
[Lady Yejin, urgently gathering the seasoned meat!]
You can't get this
[With that...]
[Meat War 2 breaks out!]
[The House Team defends]
[While the Going Out Team is on the offense!]
[Battle Demon]
Why are you being like that?
[Is this...
Family...]
I can't give this meat up!
[Lady Yejin's excessive love for meat!]
[And then...]
[The Going Out Team slowly banding together...]
Yejin, let's just eat it all together
Yejin we have to eat it all together
We do, so why do you have to take it?
Because we're going to be out getting vegetables
You think it's possible to cook meat at the vegetable garden?
[Such is the atmosphere]
[Unable to let the meat go...]
So we're off then
Will it be okay...?
[My loveable meat...]
[Slowly getting further away...]
[Watching the departing meat...]
[Heartbreaking moment~]
[Pierced by this uneasy feeling...]
It'll be okay Yejin.
This is the first time I've seen you like this.
I'm dizzy...
We still have to marinate it and everything
Don't go and buy the kids clothes and stuff!
She's like that. She just wants to buy things for young people.
Jongkookie. You know that bag shaped like this?
The first one?
This shape.
This is a first...
[In the whole universe to see Kim Jongkook with a lady's purse...]
Chunhee, go start the car.
[Queen Wonhee's honored visit to the market has begun!]
It's like my birthday today
[Uneasy for some reason~]
When are you going to start carrying me?
Whenever you want us to
I see
[The haughty Queen Wonhee]
[Also in a moment... a regretable situation...]
Please exit
[The attendants acting as bodyguards]
[Wow, the way she gets out...]
We should do the sedan chair now?
No.. well..
Now?
[Resisting just once...]
[The sedan chair Queen Wonhee requested...]
Now that I'm up here I can see all the people...
[Everyone just watching]
[Embarrassed]
The people over there...
[Still she gets on again!!]
Where do I hold on to?
- Here?
- Yes, grab that.
One, two, three!
Going forward...!
What is this!  Is this a reward or a punishment?
All the people are staring, look!
Where are you going to go...?
Go straight!  Quickly.
Are you guys okay?
-Yes, we're okay.
-We're okay.
I'm also less embarrassed now... Oh my, what'll I do...
Wow, look at the people!
[Here also, staring]
Won Hee noona, are you too embarrassed?
[Go!  Go!]
I told you to go straight!
[Why'd you ask to get a ride...]
This is too tiring...
This is humiliating.
We're here because we heard that the pig skin here was famous.
[Somehow now
holding the bag...]
We came to buy pig skins.
Yes...
Ah, this looks like the skin.
Oh, if you fry this, it'll look like fried fish.
[The owner, freely giving to no end.]
This is good for the body, right?
Of course...
You're giving us too much!
That's fine, sir!
You've given us too much.
It's because I wanted to give it to you.
Because we have a financier today...
Jong Kook, give me my wallet.
[What will Madam's wallet look like?]
[Iridescent]
You carry around a jeweled wallet!
Thank you~
We'll eat it well.
It was nice meeting you!
Thank you for cutting the price a lot for us.
This side is good, too...
I...
You wear worn stuff here!
I brought some, but...
It seems like formal wear.
Oh, it's not.
But since we're out, why don't we... over there...
What's it...  Something like a training outfit?
[Since they're out, buying a training outfit?]
I think I need to wear something comfortable.
-Noona, you want to buy one?
-Because it'll be until tomorrow...
I think I need to.
-We're where...?
-There...!
-Is there...
-Here!  Here!
-Can you please stop the car here?
Uniforms for women and children!
[Will Madam be able to purchase a pretty training outfit?]
-Hello!
-Hello.
Do you have comfortable pants?
Yes.
Where...?
-Please come this way
-Wow!
[Baggy pants(?)]
Ah, should I get one in tiger skin?
[What?!  A tiger skin pattern!]
-Isn't this okay?
-Yes, it is.
Yeah, it looks good!
What do you think about this?
Why don't you two also wear one?
We're okay...
Since you two helped me shop, I'll...
We also gave you a ride in a sedan chair.
Noona...  Oh, the sedan chair...  Think of it as payment for the chair.
[Madam Won Hee, baggy pants present?]
-I'll buy you one each.
-The price of the ride.
What about this one?
[Chun Hee, what a strong pattern...]
The color is slightly...
-...slightly different, isn't it...
-This is...!
-It really...
-Zebra, zebra!
And it's a difficult color...
Purple... Purple zebra!
This is flashy~
Are these roses?
Doesn't this look like a golf uniform?
If I wore it with those pants.
[This time, a golf uniform?]
I think the color slightly matches.
See, doesn't the color match slightly?
[Jong Kook coordinates it for her with the blue rose baggy pants...]
Bring the purple.
Hold it up for her!
[He is still tightly clutching this bag...]
Hold it up for her!  That's right.
-Oh, it's good.
If I really wanted to be fashionable, I'd choose this pants.
In black.
Cubic??
You two, break up to go wear it.
Come out now guys!
[Soon...]
Guys!
[How'll it be]
[Too short pant length]
[A fantastical match between
white socks and a zebra pattern]
This is really comfortable!
[If model Chun Hee looks like this...]
[Tights style]
The feeling of wearing it so different.
Jong Kook, you need to... a bit more...
-...to change that.
-Isn't it cool?
Doesn't it look like Big Bang?
I picked one that compromised both of your choices.
Zebra and flowers.
That one is better!
That looks good on you!
[They're going crazy complimenting each other...]
How's this good??
This is fashionable these days. Come here.
[What is with the baggy pants and the necktie...]
I think you're being a bit too greedy...
I think the viewers will like this because we've ruined our images...
Wow, this...!
That's because he's a model!
Does this look good?
We didn't just go...
Wow, it's suave.
It's suave!
[  Woman's bag  ]
[Cougar patterned baggy pants]
[  Red neck-tie  ]
Does it look better like this?
Don't just pass this one - it's very suave.  I'll go try mine on.
Noona, I think I'll start wearing this a lot in the summer.
After seeing your pants, hyung, I would like to change this to another...
No, you look pretty!  It's no joke!
[Entrance!]
[This is madame's baggy pants]
Am I pretty?
They have to be jealous the second they see it!
If you match your top to a purple...
If I were to be truthful...  It kind of looks fashionable.
Bring the 'daengdaeng'.
It looks fine!
[Viewing one's self...]
I think these pants are better than the previous.
This one is better, noona.
This one is better?
Yes, it is.
You have to go this far.
[The return of the jeweled wallet]
We're ready to purchase - please give me the total of all of these.
Yes.
It's $50.
$50?
I'm short $10...
[She's short $10!]
There's another wallet in there, right?
Why do you split your wallets?
The leather wallet.
Yes, leather.
You carry around two wallets...
-How much?
-$6...
$6?!
It's exact.
I have $3 left!
Mr. Owner, thank you.
We spent so much time here...
[At the house...]
Yejin!  Why are you like that?  It's okay!
The pig ribs are better!
That's right!
You guys are really...
We had to defend that then...
Exactly!
You think they'll cook it in the vegetable patch when they're picking vegetables?
[Doing what they thought was impossible...]
Noona!
[The vegetables they picked]
[They're cooking the meat!]
I bet they're cooking it at the garden
[Bingo...]
[A borrowed frying pan...]
[Pretty good skills...]
Should we cook some of the ribs then?
Do you think we can?
We'll just cook a few pieces
Okay
[Making do by cooking some of the ribs to eat...]
Hyung, we have to grill with briquets today
Grilling with briquets is the best for pig meat!
Exactly
So we have to get the briquet
This brings back memories
[The briquet used back in the days!]
[Skillfully placing into the fire...]
I haven't smelled this in so long
Yea, it's been awhile
[Piercing stare...]
I can see a little red...
[How long will they keep this up...]
It should have turned red already
Blow on it
[Pathetic]
Jang Hyukjae PD is going to yell at us if we can't light this!
Hey! Why isn't that working?!!!
Who's idea was it to use briquets?!
Bring one over that works!!
Yejin, that was good
(Yejin... you're right...)
[Trying another briquet now]
When I was young we cooked all our meat with briquets
Me too. All briquets
Yejin, we have to put garlic and stuff in here and fry it
[Finally, it's time to make braised pork ribs]
Oppa, then boil the water
[1. Put garlic and ginger into the water]
[2. Put the prepped rib meat into the water and cook]
Let's make the marinade then
Oppa, you're in charge of that
[The Gourmet Student will make the marinade for the ribs...]
Okay
[1. Cooking wine]
[2. Soy sauce]
[3. Add... sugar, minced garlic, red pepper powder,
and starch syrup and mix together]
Sooro oppa, after you're done cutting that you have to put salt on it
[Lady Yejin barking orders today...]
[Sooro slicing cucumbers for the chilled soup...]
- Oppa.
- What?
I'll keep an eye on this and let you know when it's ready. For now, go and cook the chilled soup.
Yejin, are you planning on doing anything?
I've always done the work. Today I'm just going to be your supervisor.
Are you making sugar crackers right now?
Yea
[Acting like it's absurd...]
we have all the ingredients
[But sitting right down next to her...]
[The things they do now...]
[Mix sugar and soda and hold over flame!]
[Will this work?]
[Oh~ It's working!]
[Using a frying pan to cool]
[That's it]
You have to press it
[Messed it up...]
Just leave it alone
It tastes pretty good.
It's good.
I'm going to make more.
If I eat this now my tongue is going to get stuck.
[40 years old and you're that excited to eat sugar crackers...]
[The briquet finally lit...]
Why isn't it coming out? It came out easily last time.
It shouldn't stick like this...
[A close shave]
I'd still eat it off the ground
Me too. I had already planned to pick it up and eat it if it fell.
[All that boasting...]
[Creating memories that warm the heart with the sugar crackers!]
Wow, look at the pig ribs.
This is really good quality meat.
[3. When the meat is cooked, take out of the water]
[4. Mix in with marinade                                          ]
[5. Braise in a small amount of water            ]
Now we're even able to make braised ribs
[The Family that had a hard time making
ramen can now even cook braised ribs...]
I have a feeling this will smell so good
Braised ribs don't usually smell like this.
Why does it smell so sour?
Why does it smell sour? I didn't put in any vinegar...
[What they thought was cooking wine]
- That's vinegar!
- That's vinegar?!
[Oh My God]
[You can tell from the smell...]
Hyung! Why did you...?!
[The ribs ruined...]
I thought this was how it was supposed to be, but then Yejin was like...
[The drained expression of the actress...]
[Though painful... another look...]
[Whatever the case, what about the ribs...]
The good thing is, the vinegar will cook itself out
So let it then
Yea, so just keep cooking it
Let's have a taste
It's not bad
What are you talking about, it's sour!
Well if you just ignore that part...
[At this moment]
What is that?!
[All hail Queen Wonhee~]
Wonhee bought you guys neckties
Attention!
At ease!
[Changed into their new pants]
[Ordered them to do this but cracking up by herself...]
What is this?
Why? Jealous?
I told you not to do this
How much did you spend?
I spent 50,000 won!
I got the pig skin, drinks, and pants. I couldn't say no to the neckties now, could I?
Why are you the one carrying the purse?
The Mistress...
She's the mistress now?
She only has 3,000 won left
[Queen Wonhee wants a taste right when she arrives...]
Why isn't Hyori back with the meat?
It's pretty good
[A relief that she can't taste the vinegar...]
I'm not too shabby with the marinade
You guys did a really good job.
This isn't easy to make.
Wonhee, stop eating it.
It's just one piece. This is the first proper piece I'm eating.
Earlier I just grabbed the end of a piece.
There's no point eating this much
Oh, this is so good!
This is mine, you know?!
Is that how it is between us?! My meat and your meat?
Hey, we're back!
What?! What are you eating?!
[Urgently]
- What is she eating?
- Wonhee nuna!
She's just seeing if it's ready
Get over here!
We didn't eat any!
- You ate it, didn't you?
- It's right here!
Why would we eat it?!
Open your mouth
Why would we eat it~
what a joke, seriously!
There's less of it!
I was cradling it earlier!
Quit lying!
Bullshit!
Did she just say that?
[Agitated]
This is really important to her
They ate it...
Daesung, you ate some didn't you?
We really didn't!
We should be able to smell it in his hair
(A little bit...)
You ate a little, huh?
He said he ate a little
Kang Daesung ate it by himself
[Suddenly tense(?)]
Hey! Did you eat it or not?
[Queen Wonhee has appeared!!]
[In the whole universe, grabbing Hyori by the collar!]
Did you eat it or not?
I ate it...
[Immediately confessing!]
Get over here! Get over here!
[Wild enthusiasm]
[The Family's high power Hyori]
[Knocked down by Queen Wonhee]
[Even the proper Kim Kookjong...]
[and the timid Yoo Jaesuk...]
I can't look like this in front of the oppas...
Did you see her?
I've never seen Hyori grabbed by the collar!
Wow, Hyori by the collar...
Once she grabbed her though, she was powerless
[Can't complain in front of her unnie...]
Because a strong unnie is here she can't even...
Quiet down! You're so noisy!
Fine
They're both used to being the tough ones
Hyori, go wash the vegetables
What?!
Chunhee-ya. I told you to say it strongly.
[Long legs]
You go wash them!
[Retreating right away!]
Kim Kookjong, go wash the vegetables!
[With the strong Queen Wonhee behind him...]
[Hyori vs Jongkook. The results? An eternal grudge(?)]
What's with this look?
[As expected, quickly dominates Jongkook!]
[But]
Hey, I bought him those!
[Grabbing Hyori by the collar again...]
I bought all these for them.
[The Queen's troops organized!]
I'm sorry...
[In the end, apologizes!]
Did you just apologize?
Get away!
Move! So I can go wash the vegetables!
What are you yelling at us for?!
[Walking over valiantly...]
[Bow~]
[Once she saw the Queen unnie's gaze...]
Now that Wonhee's here it's gotten so comfortable for us!
[The excited fan appears]
That's excessive, Jongkook!
She said that's too much!
[While everyone is happy like this...]
[At the corner of the yard...
A grieving woman...]
I have to suffer this kind of image...
[The deliciously cooking pig meat!]
Hello?
Should I give you guys a real present now?
What is it?
This is good to have when your throat is parched
[Yogurt drink!!]
You got exactly what I wanted
Since you're an MC, I got for you especially...
[A drink good for your throat!!]
[The two attendants passing out the drinks]
Is Wonhee campaigning or something?
Where's the straw?
Just drink it...
Oppa why are you like this?!
[This time it's Yejin vs Jongkook...]
She keeps asking for a straw
Hey! Give it back then!
[First it was Hyori and now it's Yejin!]
No unnie, it wasn't like that
I only asked JongKook Oppa where the straw was, I didn't order him around.
No ordering around...
She did order around...
What are you doing?
Hyori-ah, after washing the leaves, come and drink some of this!
Okay.
[Obedient]
Totally like a mother-in-law
You need to cut it a little shorter.
[Anyway, they need to prepare the naengchae (cold vegetable dish with various seasonings)..]
The naengchae, order YeJin around...
Yejin-ah, are you dreaming?
Quickly, after finishing, do the naengchae!
[Why is it like that?]
[The guys get their revenge!]
Kim Won Hee!
[One shot(?)]
[The sisters who enjoyed one year of dominance... Disintegrated like that...]
Yejin, what happened?
I'm really irritated!
Won hee Unni?
She said that to me.
I'm going to say something back to Won hee Unni!
[Hyori confronts Madam Kim?]
But Won Hee Unni is a senior...
Although Won Hee Unni is a senior, but in the family... What about me?
Wait and see!
Yejin!
[No answer when called...]
[Eventually Hyori sets off!]
Won Hee Unni
[What is going to happen?]
It's all washed!
[Maybe... this sentence is...]
[Getting a little worried..]
I thought she was going to grab me like that
[Shoves the basket]
- Hyori, have you drank the fermented drink?
- No.
[Thoughtfully prepares the drink for her]
- Chun Hee, give her a bottle.
- Okay.
Wow, with one word from Won Hee.
[Adds a humble bow!]
Everyone immediately does as told.
Unni, what about the stuff you wanted to tell Won Hee Unni?
I said it already! I said I finished washing.
- All these meat should be enough.
- Yes enough.
- Naengchae...
- Start moving!
- Jaesuk.
- Yes.
Look after the barbecued meat
[Now, he naturally speaks politely "yes"...]
- I'm not sure myself why I said the polite form of 'yes'.
- Still speaks politely to his friend..
[In name, they're friends..]
I don't know why I did that too.
[Everyone waits around for the meat to be cooked...]
It's going to be nice.
[The pig belly meat which looks delicious!]
Hyori, bring some salt here.
What for?
[Senior citizen, thinking of how to clean up the mess...]
- To sprinkle some on it.
- I see.
[What is Hyori threatening to do...]
Let other people get it!
Won Hee, she says to ask someone else to get it.
[Immediately rats on her]
No such thing.
[Don't think... Hyori is going to...]
Where is it? Where is the kitchen?
You don't even know where the kitchen is.
I'm cool.
I like doing it that's why I'm doing it!
[Where did we hear this from so many times...]
This is so familiar.
The rice needs to be scooped and the soup is ready.
The soup was supposed to be done by Yejin.
Where is it?
[Rats on her] She's sitting here!
Daesung! Didn't I just tell you to
prepare the soup together with me,
[The time is now! Daesung was too much...]
why are you not listening to me!
Kang Daesung you come here.
Yejin! Let Daesung rest!
Unni, you're biased against guys...
Unni, we work like that everyday.
You get lost!
Unni.
Let Jaesuk go!
Unni, we're doing work like this and the Oppas are resting!
It's not exactly like that.
[Mutters]
Yejin... Hyori...
You betrayer...
[Immediately grabs his clothes!]
Yes, Madam.
[The last of the muttering betrayer]
[Even the barbecue tools are also...]
This, use this.
Unni, I would like to try this person to do...
The soup... I...
[Stuttering]
Say it in one sentence, one time!
[Miss Yejin is so anxious..]
Yejin! Say it all at once!
Unni, I will mix the ingredients and
prepare the naengchae ingredients...
but the one who cooks...
Please decide on one!
I know Hyori can cook soups well.
- If not, I'll just put everything in the pot.
- Go with Jongkook!
Go with Jongkook, aren't the two of you very awkward, go together then.
[Lucky Kim Kook Jong!]
Jongkook Oppa, let's go.
No.
Make him disintegrate, Yejin.
The tie was bought by me.
The two of them are lovers, aren't they?
- The two of them are lovers, aren't they?
- Yes.
Are you trying to act cute with your slippers?
[Madam Kim interferes!]
Not this, wear others.
Yejin, wear mine.
Oppa, I will take them off and you can carry me!
It's already like that?
[Fuss!]
It's not like that.
I can't walk without shoes.
- Carry her.
- Yes Madam!
[Gives a 90-Degree bow]
Hold it, Oppa.
I'll bring the table.
[Jaesuk who is enjoying everything]
Why do you walk like that? What kind of action is this?
For some reason, I am very happy.
[Grabs quietly]
Hyori~
Hyori, come here please.
[With one word, Hyori come back]
[How irritating... inside me...]
[At this side, Jongkook is already in Yejin's hands]
You should know this, although
Won Hee Unni is leaving tomorrow...
Hyori and I are the people you are going to continue seeing..
Yes, I also thought about that.
I think I thought wrongly.
But its not like that, at least I have to be good to Yejin.
What a playboy!
Think it over, whether you will listen to Won Hee Unni or listen to me, Yejin.
[Like this, Yejin brainwashes...]
Of course I'll listen to Yejin.
- Is that true?
- Yes
No matter what, I'll still see how you perform...
- Jongkook!
- Yes.
[Immediately answers!]
We're done washing.
[Yejin was still speaking and yet he...]
Wow~it looks good.
[The twist of fate]
Think it's better fried.
Please come again next week.
Tomorrow, when you leave, please go to the photograpy centre to get a photo of yourself!
You take it for me?
[The photo that the guys are going to bring around?]
Even when you go, when we are bullied, we can paste it on our heads immediately.
You're all dead meat!
Let's eat quickly, if not it'll turn cold.
Get the rice here!
[Queen Wonhee's one word]
Rice?
And bowls...
[The Family's men start moving!]
Look at how organized we are!
[Organized passing system]
- Go! Go!
- Go! Go! Go!
Come and get it!
- Jongshin!
- Yes.
[The sickly and uncomfortable senior citizen is also..]
Daesung! Not too much!
(Hoity-toity)
This is so exciting.
[Jaesuk who remains UP no matter what]
Jaesuk, you've become so excited.
I've not been that loud for quite some time.
Childishly expressing your feelings.
[After that... Even does Seungri's ceremony...]
(You watch out, Yoo Jae Suk
We've totally won, because of Won Hee!
Today's our liberation day!
Today's is really fun.
I'm so irritated.
Is the soup ready?
Hyori, quickly prepare the stew.
[After emerging victorious, he treats Hyori who's cooking the kimchi stew like a servant?!]
[Stares!]
Won Hee, did you see Hyori's eyes?
[Shaking one's head~]
No.
Her eyes immediately went from a devilish one to gentle one.
Hyori, have you finished?
Please wait a while longer, Unni
[Hyori actually has times like this...]
Today is really too good to describe...
- Let's scoop the rice.
- Let's!
- You ate it all?
- No, I didn't...
It's a little bland...
We can't have it like that.
Hyori, come here! The stew is about to dry!
[Hyori, who went to the kitchen after settling the soup]
Wait a moment.
I'll go and supervise.
Haha, I'll go and supervise.
Hold her while she's walking.
[Queen WonHee taking difficult steps...]
- Where are you going? I'll go.
- No need, I'll go and get it.
Hyori, is it done?
[Blink]
[Queen Kim enters!]
Hyori Unni, Won Hee Unni went into the house.
- Where to?
- The house.
All of you, stand right where you are! What did you say to me just now!
[The men's emergency alarm sounds]
Won Hee!
- Noona!
- Yoo Jae Suk.
Won Hee!
Noona!
[Anxiously calls Queen Won Hee to come out..]
Be quiet!
Stop shouting! Yejin, grab Jaesuk Oppa quickly.
Yejin, what are you doing!
[Serious]
[This is~   Really~]
[Perfectly]
Won Hee, don't go anywhere.
- Help with the other chores quickly.
- Okay.
[Won Hee goes to the kitchen once again...]
[Hyori! Gritting her teeth!]
Jaesuk you come here! Come over!
I got it.
[You complain anything to Won Hee Unni, you're dead]
You listen carefully.
[Obeys immediately]
I get it.
- Kim Kook Jong!
- Yes?
[Naturally speaks politely..]
Your polite 'yes' came out so easily.
- Everyone better be careful!
- I got it.
Today, we shall all eat facing the front.
[The extremely lucky guys today]
[Madam Kim comes out...]
[Today's leading lady]
Today's leading lady Madam Won Hee is out.
[The Family guys' ultimate saviour]
[Queen Wonhee]
The way she bites on the carrot looks so sexy!
Of course
(*similar to 'carrot''s pronunciation)
[Whatever...]
Tonight's leading lady Madam Won Hee is coming out.
[The guys chasing her offer her their hands...]
It's totally different from the situation just now.
Yejin, when can we start eating?
We can start now.
This is not the soup we wanted.
As we already have hot soup, I changed it to a melon side-dish instead.
[Replaced the side-dish with melons since there is already soup]
It looks really delicious.
Why is everybody standing.
Today's leading lady Madam Won Hee hasn't even sat yet.
Won Hee, you can use a special spoon to scoop your rice.
- Hyori, are you done?
- I'll bring it over soon.
Today, Hyori is Jang Geum.
(Note: Jang Geum is from a drama. She cooked inside a palace)
[Today as Hyo Jang Geum!]
To replace the ribbon-Cutting ceremony, we have the cutting of the pork.
Madam Won Hee, please.
We haven't had such a sumptious meal in ages and today's family guest Madam Won Hee,
please do us the honour of cutting the pork.
Do we need to assist you in getting up?
It's really something memorable.
Before the cutting. Let's give a round of the applause to the food.
[Even now, he is emcee-Ing]
What should we use as the celebratory music?
There's no cello music?
At this time, we should have the cello music in the background.
[Just as they mentioned it...]
It's there, take a look!
So we'll have it performed like that...
Playing the cello.
Give me an introduction!
5 years ago, she became the wife of someone else,
at the 9th position of South Korea's wives
and what a super, multi-Talented wife she is!
[At last the pork-Cutting ceremony]
Now, we start the pork-Cutting ceremony.
[To celebrate the presence of Queen Won Hee]
Cue! Cue!
[They can't not...]
Really looks good.
Let's eat.
- Today's main dish.
- Yes, Queen Won Hee.
This is the best meat ever.
Does it suit your appetite?
It's first-class standard.
Thank you for the praise.
Queen Won Hee, a meat wrap for you!
Sit over there.
I'm supposed eat dinner in the middle...
[Hyori is supposed to sit where Wonhee is...]
[Grandfather and grandmother are having a good time feeling the spring breeze.]
Oh, the soup is very sweet.
The soup is good, and the melon is good too!
[Now you say it...]
Oppa did really well~
Eating the melon like this is tasty, too.
It's because the pork is delicious.
[They're having a comfortable dinner because of Queen Wonhee.]
[But the guys are nervous of not having Wonhee here anymore next week...]
[Episode 3: The Family SONG has outed!]
Jongshin oppa made something for us.
What did Jongshin hyung make?
[The oldest has prepared something for the Family.]
Our Family song is on the Internet.
I saw it.
[The Family song is roaming around the Internet.]
They made a song and then made a music video for us.
[One fan made the lyrics and composed the Family song and made a music video, too.]
I never saw it.
I made up a melody, but we should make the lyrics.
[They're going to make a Family song.]
Our Jongshin oppa made it for us?
[Our oldest who is a famous composer composed the Family song.]
Yes, yes.
[Everyone is going to help make the lyrics.]
Let's see the one on the Internet.
Look.
[They have outed!]
[Every Sunday night at 5 : 20
on Good Sunday]
Outing~
[Yoon Jongshin picks up used gags.]
[Agree]
[The youngest of dumb and dumber
Daesung's greed of gags.]
[A face that doesn't look like an idol's]
[The son of a rich farmer, Kim Sooro]
[Lee Chunhee is good at cleaning
up. The stupid, gaunt Chunhee.        ]
[The lyrics are based on the Family's characters.]
My song is not as good as this...
[Big Ppun's C-Dragon Yoo Jaesuk.
He has no sensitivity and is just noisy.]
I'm so sorry but I love you~
they're all lies~
[The editing must have been very difficult.]
[6X5=30 Lee Hyori.
Eyebrows, strong, clumsy Hyori.]
[The sweet voice of Park Yejin. The girl who is good at cutting, the scary Ms. Yejin]
[Good Sunday: Family Outing]
[Moved]
[NakTA's composition and lyrics suit perfectly to the Family of the Family song.]
This person made this for us, so we should, too.
Can I remake my song?
I did it in a rock style.
So, someone came to help us.
[A teacher came to help them make the Family song!]
[You hear guitar chords in the dark night.]
[He's very good.]
[Who is the special teacher that came to Family?]
-Huh?!
-Who is it?
[As expected?]
[The king of rock: Kim Taewon]
How did you come all the way here?
I came to visit!
I thought it was the grandmother...
[The symbol of rock: he tied his long hair...]
I'm sorry. I saw you from afar and thought you were the grandmother...
[What a big discourtesy...]
When I was young, they debuted as a rock band and were so famous.
[The living god of rock! The legendary guitarist!]
We asked if you can make a sound of a bell.
[A bell on the guitar?]
Could you play the "ding"?
[He made it?]
[This sound... is guitar...?]
[He is the legendary guitarist...]
Will it work with an acoustic?
I specialize with electric guitar.
If you want to feel the guitar, you have to see someone play live.
Where can I go?
-Can I say it?
-Yes, yes.
April 18-19th...
[Huh?]
[He's preparing a concert...]
It only works for electric, but I'll do it on the acoustic for the first time.
[He's going to do it on the acoustic for the first time!]
If it doesn't work, then too bad!
[Huh? Hand...?]
[Bam!]
[Di~~~~ng~]
[But the sound is somewhat...]
That's one o'clock!
[It's the sound of a grandfather clock!]
One o'clock!!
Jongshin composed a song.
We're trying to make a Family song.
[They're going to try and make lyrics with Kim Taewon!]
But making lyrics is pretty hard.
When you make lyrics, what do you usually do?
[The legend of rock: How does Kim Taewon write lyrics?]
How did you write 'The Last Concert'?
Can we listen to a part of it?
You have to adjust the tone...
No Problem!!
Gi~ Girl~
I'll take it out!
[He lost his shape...]
I told you it was too high.
[Lyrics*Composition: Kim Taewon's most famous song <The Last Concert>]
[The lyrics and melody play with your heart.]
[Fascination]
[The highlight of 'The Last Concert'!]
Yoon Jongshin!
Outside~
Aww, you suck!
[Complain]
This is what you did!
[Jump]
[Sooro's try!]
[Oh~ His husky voice!!]
Good!
[His talent has been realized!]
You sing with your heart.
Ah~ this is very warm...
The song is warm?
This is very warm.
[He has been immobilized by the hot pack.]
[Now the one man is going to try!]
She left outside~~~
There's a mosquito! Mosquito!
[The voice of the mosquito has come already?]
[ He's very amused . . . ?]
[Wam!!]
[...Uh huh]
[Spray~]
We heard this song, could you sing another song?
[The unforgettable song: <As You Love>]
This song is a true story!
[... Huh? True story?]
You must forget your ex-lover as much as you love her.
That is why the song is called 'As You Love'.
[Touched]
[I don't see her for awhile...]
[Ding!]
It was good.
[The cough of the teacher]
[It's cold.]
[He has a runny nose.]
[The Family song is almost complete.]
Lift your eyes and look at the sky.
[The second day at Sungjoo]
[Morning Mission: The one who can't jump over must feel the pain!]
[Family Game: The shoes are flying!]
[The chickens are coming!]
[The menu of the Family's breakfast! Chicken!]
[Will the three cowards be able to catch the chicken?]
[The second day of the obedience to Madame Wonhee will come!]