Brought to you by Ramen Soup Subs!
[Before filming]
[Chunhee sleeping soundly]
[While he's trying to rest...]
[Who's call is waking him up?]
Hello?
Hello Family, this is Yoo Jaesuk!
[Reporting the 24th destination]
For this outing we will be going to Bibongneh village in Kyungnam Sacheon
Please meet at Gimpo Airport at 7:00AM
Over and out! Bbyong!
Hello? He-hello?
[Who is the new Family member?]
We're going to Bibongneh village?
[J style Lee Junki]
[Disheartened by the long road ahead]
Why am I doing this?
[While the well experienced Jongkook, bravely takes off]
[The Family gathering at the airport]
[Arriving at Sacheon]
I think the weather is going to be warm from now on
I know, huh? It makes you want to jump into the water
Sooro hyung! Your hat...
I thought I'd try...
He only has the whorl of his head covered
And Yejin got a perm!
[A lot to talk about since not seeing each other for 2 weeks]
My drama finished so I permed it
Alright, all aboard!
Junki said he's coming today
Oh, you know Lee Junki?
No one here knows Junki?
I know him
You've met him? Are you close?
Well, he always used to run up to me and bow and greet me
[Eh~ It sounds like all they did was say hi...]
So do you talk to him?
I don't know his phone number
[Arriving at the village]
[Getting off the bus feeling restless]
It's summer now!
[In the beautiful Bibongneh village]
[Junki still hasn't arrived yet]
[A car slowly pulling up]
[Finally the car door opens...]
[The New Family Lee Junki is finally here]
[Happily greeting his close friend Hyori]
Oh hello, it's nice to meet you
Junki, did you put on cologne?
Huh? Oh yea I did. It's been awhile since I've gone out so...
It smells nice!
Of course, stars should smell like this
We smell good, too
Why are you on the edge attracting flies?
Your shirt is so bright it's bringing flies over!
Look at Junki and how naturally he dresses.
[I'm jealous]
Junki, just use the map to find the Grandmother's house
Actually, it should be held like this
It seems like Jongshin hyung is a little tense, too
Jongshin hyung hates it when young guys come on
You guys are all nervous around Junki, huh?
Of course
I think you're the coolest out of everyone
Really?
All of a sudden he's making his way forward
Wow Yoon Jongshin...
Did you hear?! Lee Junki said I was cool!
[Arriving at the house in no time]
Hello! Hello!
Welcome!
[Moon Pilim] [Kim Sunwol] [Sung Hwangi] [Che Samsoon]
[The Grandma joyfully greeting them]
Hello
So all 4 of you are friends?
You're prettier in real life
[Tough...]
You guys should get on your way
You should take advantage of this beautiful day!
Bye! Bye!
Take care of the house!
[Taking off for a very special vacation...]
[Things to do!]
'Hey you guys! We have a great uninhabited island! Go visit it!
So I guess we'll go check out the island
[In a moment]
[The picturesque unihabited island waiting for the Family]
[Island mission]
[Find the 7 buried treasures!]
[The Family goes through the entire island to find them]
[Will the Family be able to find them all?!]
[Four self-sufficient men go to the ocean!]
[While Chunhee is abandoned in the ocean!]
[The Family's island adventure starts now!]
[Ch 1 Family Island Treasure Hunt]
[Heading to the island the grandmother wanted them to see]
Junki looks like he's heading off for MT
I don't think he knows what's in store for him
Once you get submerged in water...
You'll be like "Oh! So this is how it is..."
It's just for one day, it'll be ok!
[Arriving at the wharf in no time...]
So where did you grow up?
Over by Busan
[Junki, grew up by the sea]
The smell of the ocean is so nice
Yea, we smell this every two weeks...
He looks so happy right now
Check the show when it airs. Right now you're glowing and eager...
No, it won't change
How do you feel right now?
I'm so happy!
[Glowing]
[But even before an hour has passed...]
[Submerged in water...]
[Climbed trees...]
[Catch fish...]
[Mind and body exhausted...]
[A man on a deserted island]
[All aboard on the boat]
[And now heading for the island]
[The southern seas surrounding the island]
[In all that wide space...]
[The Family takes off]
[The village residents out to catch a glimpse of the shoot]
[Waving happily]
As soon as I waved a lot of them stopped waving
[But as soon as Daesung raises his hand]
So you really are an idol after all
See, I told you so!
[The Elder also waves]
[Only one man waves back...]
Jongshin oppa is trying to steal the love
[It's a lonely life...]
When Daesung put his hand down his went right up
Chunhee, push Yejin over
[Going further away from land]
[The mysterious shores with no human trace]
It really does feel like we're going on a MT
I think it's because we're going to an island
Hey, it's an MT. Watch out Hyori.
This is like the opening of a movie
[That sunbae that shows up every MT...]
We're all happily heading off to camp and then bad things start to happen
Like a horror movie!
Exactly!
[Disappearing on the island]
But the first person to go...
The character type in the movies that always dies first is Sooro hyung
[Because he always goes off on his own]
I just thought of a scenario!
What?
I have a crush on Junki, but he asks me to set him up with Boa
So I follow them to the island
And then put a mole right here so he won't recognize you!
[Sounds familiar...]
(singing the theme for Temptation of Wife)
So Hyori will kill us off one by one
Yea and then knock Junki unconscience
Yea! It's only you and Junki left alive!
And the next morning this place will be swarmed with tourists... They'll be so shocked.
And then I'll be here like this only playing dead
That's such a plot twist!
[Such an absurd plot twist...]
[After going out further]
[The island slowly coming to view]
[With their destination finally in sight]
[In wonder]
[Not tainted by humans]
[Like a beautiful painting]
[Arriving at the island!]
[Their first step on the island!!]
[The floor littered with empty shells...]
This really is uninhabited!
If this is messed up, they'll pick us up right?
Your tone is slowly starting to change from before
[Slowly losing is previous confidence...?]
It's nice here!
Let's try to plan now
Let's set up a canopy here
Yea, we need some shade
[Setting up the canopy]
[Combining their strength]
[With perfect teamwork]
They actually know what they're doing...
Of course! I've been camping 300 times!
[But it's not staying up...]
[And falling still...]
I'm too nervous to stay under this!
[Going over each part again~]
[After 2 hours]
I think we did it!
Oppa, how are we going to all fit in here?!
Just stand right here
[Only a small amount of shade]
Just gather around for now!
Is it necessary to sit?!
Why did we do it here? It's so much better over there
We spent 2 hours on this and that tree over there gives more shade
Whoever wins the game gets to rest by the tree
[If there was shade already then why the tent]
[Resting before the game]
[Only getting shade on their heads]
[But still offering a small amount of happiness]
Ok!
Don't get up!
Let's go
Go where?!
Grab him!
Where do you think you're going?
Let's play a game!
Even if you trap me you guys will still have to play the game
[Chunhee even grabbing rope...]
As long as we trap him, we can rest
I swear you'll end up in the water laughing and having a good time
You talk too much!
[The frightening curse of the Game Maniac...]
[And of course, after a moment...]
[Getting ready to start the game...]
So we did end up on this
Of course, that's how it goes
Pretty much each team is trying to shove the other team off
Basically the same game from X-Man
Let's divide the teams with rock-paper-scissors
So we have to win rock-paper-scissors
Of course!
So Junki and who?
You
Me? Oh goodie
[Junki's team, Kim Jongkook]
He got picked over Sooro hyung!
Good!
[Game rivals(?) Jaesuk vs Jongkook]
We'll see how it goes, Jongkook!
Hyung, I won't get wet easily
Oh yea? What about...
[Digging his own grave again...]
[Lost again...]
[Game Devil Sooro too?]
That's not fair!
[Junki's team, Kim Sooro]
It's ok, whatever
Oppa! Don't you dare pick me!
[Can't compare Jaesuk's team vs Junki's team (Sooro, Jongkook)]
At this rate, no one will want to be on my team!
[The uneasy Hyori and Yejin go over to Junki's side]
It doesn't matter, some of you will have to end up here anyways
[Junki's team, Lee Hyori]
There's no more room on Junki's team anymore!
[All alone...]
My turn to pick?
[Just picking however!]
You guys should be nice to me!
Yejin! Come here now
I don't want to! He's so crazy
[Tantrum]
Alright, next... who shall it be...?
Why aren't you guys smiling?! Huh?! No one is meeting my gaze!
Me?! No!
Alright Daesung, come here
Aww, why?!
[Now left are Jongshin and Chunhee]
Chunhee! Where are you?!
[The hiding Chunhee]
Chunhee! Get over here!
[Clumsy Chunhee, can't be helped]
[The game hasn't even started]
[A sight to behold...]
Hey! You can't fall in before the game even starts!
[Will they be able to play like this...]
Your pants are going to rip!
[The Elder hasn't been picked yet]
Even though my team is small, I still like this
But still, since my team is strong...
[The Elder kicked off?]
[Jongshin, Jaesuk, Chunhee, Yejin, Daesung] vs [Sooro, Jongkook, Hyori, Junki]
When you knock out the girl from the opposing team, you win
How come none of you look intimidating at all standing there?
How can you guys look so scary just standing there?
[Best of the best in strength team]
[Best of the best in weakness team]
Get ready...
Hold on, hold on!
This isn't fair! This has got to be a violation!
[Pose]
How do we stand a chance against that?!
[Jaesuk's team only looked at their posture and are frightened]
[How are their body postures against the rules...]
Oppa, just do it like them then
How do we block that?!
[On top of that, wetting their gloves with water]
Oppa, you should be worried about Junki too. We don't know what he's capable of.
He knows martial arts and stuff, so watch out!
[Iljimae's Dark horse, Junki is also here!]
He knows martial arts?
You're lying!
Really? Then this team is totally unfair!
Me and Junki against each other? That makes no sense then!
I only ask that at the start of the game, to push the floats together!
No, no, no! This game is totally unfair!
[I'm worried... for my team...]
[Strength team vs Weakness team]
[Ready to attack]
[Not sure if they'll be able to play defense well]
[The floats slowly coming together]
[The outcome is pretty obvious]
[And so]
[They meet!]
[Crossing enemy lines]
[In an instant]
[Annihilated]
[By just Sooro and Jongkook]
[Junki's team wins this round]
What is this?!
What happened?!
[I can't live like this]
[Now they ask if Yejin is okay...]
Fine! Ok! We got a taste of the game!
[Where does he get this confidence from...]
[Confused]
Why did you wear skinny jeans to the ocean?
[When they're wet it's hard to move...]
How are you going to play like that?
[Only helping up the men...]
How come you guys aren't helping her?!
I don't want to be on that team...
You don't have any faith in us?!
You didn't even help her up, and you're questioning her?!
How come we're not moving?
[So heartbreaking...]
I really don't want to...
[Poor Yejin...]
Junki, you'll be ok?
Yupp
They're coming, they're coming!
[Carefree]
[Nervous]
[Will they be able to protect Yejin well this time...]
[Junki, trying to pull Chunhee over]
[Swift]
[As expected from Iljimae's Junki]
[Such a Jaesuk style of attack...]
[The frustrated Yejin pushing Chunhee forward]
Don't push me! Don't push me!
[During this crazy situation]
[Iljimae's Junki makes a move!]
[Of all things... by Clumsy Chunhee]
[A proper dunking of Iljimae]
[Still gasping for air]
Pull us apart! Pull us apart!
[Yejin keeps pushing Chunhee]
Stop it! Don't push me!
[Unexpectedly pushed harder~]
[Trying to push the floats apart]
Just throw him!
[Thrown away...]
[Coming back together]
[Grabbed by the ankles...]
[Daesung kicking away the float]
Throw him! Throw him!
[Thrown away]
[But I'm the team captain...]
You're going to throw me away?!
Be gone!
[The cold hearted world of games]
[Dominating again]
[Sooro slips~!]
[The Elder taking advantage!]
[The Elder should have just stayed still...]
[Tragic]
Daesung, we haven't lost yet!
Yejin! It's all up to you!
[Jaesuk's team's sole survivor, Yejin]
[Everyone puts all their hope on Yejin]
[And so they meet at the sea!]
[The sisters fighting to the death]
[The savage and strong little sis Yejin!]
[Or competitive big sis Hyori!]
[A fight that can't be missed]
[It's either you or me!]
[The undependable men only chattering away...]
[The sole survivor, Lady Yejin]
[While they can only watch]
[Hanging on the edge]
[Big sis close to victory]
[But]
[If I'm going down you're coming with me!]
[Together]
Hyori wins!
Let us switch one player!
One of us goes over there...
-I'll go! I'll go!
[Everyone wanting to go to Junki's team...]
[Dumbfounded...]
Ok, I'll give you Jongshin hyung
Give us Jongkook hyung
No, Jongkook and I are rivals...
Sooro hyung, you come
Hey Kim Kookjong, you better watch out now!
Junki! I'm playing for real now!
[The Game Devil now on Jaesuk's team]
[With Muscular Jongkook on Junki's team]
[Now it's an even match!]
[The Game Devil pushing Chunhee forward]
[Jongkook only going after Jaesuk]
[But]
[Practically the whole team in an instance...]
[Iljimae's Junki, also caught in the scramble~]
[But, if that's the case]
[Jaesuk, caught(?) by Jongkook]
[Running your mouth... tsk tsk...]
[All they have to do is push the women over to win]
You just have to push Hyori over!
Hyori... pbbbt
[Jaesuk and Yejin completely dominated]
Jaesuk, just push Hyori over!
[Jaesuk's only goal]
[Attacking the face]
[He was talking so much smack...]
[But now, completely dominated]
[Yejin... I can't save you]
[Oppa... I wasn't counting on it...]
Yejin! I'm sorry!
[At this moment]
[Muscular Jongkook losing his center of gravity...]
[And like that, dunked!]
[The Weak Grasshopper dunked the Muscular Kookjong!]
[Even Jaesuk thinks it's a miracle!]
[Jongkook has been outwitted...]
[His moment has arrived!]
[Grasshopper, Hooray~]
[In disbelief...]
[But, this game isn't over yet]
[Jaesuk and Yejin vs Hyori]
[Hyori, avenge me]
But I beat Jongkook...
[With one kick!]
[But, at this moment]
[Hyori gets dunked too]
[Last survivor, Yejin! Jaesuk's team wins!]
We won!
[Because Jaesuk won over Jongkook...]
[Excited]
[Confused]
We got a taste of the game!
One more round! One more round!
Junki's a lot weaker than I thought
Jaesuk! Junki's one of us!
[Feeble middle aged?]
-You said you did martial arts!
Junki! Send them flying with your kicks
[Jaesuk] Junki-ah, show us some martial arts!
I'll... I'll show you later...
Let's start!
This time forget the girls, just whoever's the last one left wins
This round is going to be so amazing!
I have so much confidence right now!
I beat Kim Kookjong!
Did you see that Daesung? Hyung! Did you see?
[Getting more cocky]
[Getting angry]
-Don't worry guys, I'll get rid of Kim Kookjong! You just take care of the rest!
[Final round]
[Riled up from their previous win]
[If Junki doesn't want to be part of the middle aged men he has to win this last round!]
[Grabbing Daesung by the hair(?)...]
[Mommy~]
-Hey! You can't grab by the hair! That's against the rules!
[Foul play a rite of passage(?) in Family]
-Says who?!
[Everyone uneasy about the first attack in the last round]
[Feeling anxious Junki]
[Chunhee grabs him first]
[But Clumsy Chunhee is caught by Jongkook]
[The little brother about to fall]
[But big bro Game Devil arrives]
[But]
[The 3 fall in]
[But Junki's supposed to be a big time action star...]
[In Family... He has no proof of that...]
We have another rival on our hands
[Identified as part of the Middle Aged gang]
Junki's totally one of us!
This is a lot harder than I thought it would be
[Is this part of her plan?!]
[Jongkook, trying to save Hyori]
[Hyori not letting go of Daesung]
[Daesung stuck in the crack]
[Both teams fighting over Daesung]
[But the floats come apart...]
[Surrounded]
[Trying to rescue Daesung!]
[Mobilizing]
[Daesung, your hyung is here!]
[Easily falling over]
[Jaesuk, talking big but in the end...]
[The Edler, going after Yejin!]
[The useless(?) feeble middle ager...]
[You mean I'm like that...]
[Daesung, trying to escape]
[But these two won't let him leave]
-My stomach is cold!
[Yejin can't stand by any longer!]
[Going after Hyori, who's torturing Daesung]
[Splash]
[Daesung and Yejin vs Jongkook]
[Daesung, with Yejin now has a chance!]
You two fight...
[Enraged]
[Caught between Daesung and Yejin!]
[Muscular Jongkook, caught by hand and foot]
[If that's the case...]
[Jongkook vs Yejin the only two left...]
If you go easy on her now, then this is a real scandal!
[From a fake to a Real Scandal?!]
[Now the process is more interesting than the outcome...]
[Jongkook makes his way over,]
[Yejin runs away...]
[It's not like they're playing house...]
[Secretly~] [Secretly~]
[Female Ye Jin is the competitor.]
[Neither this nor that can do.]
Push, push!
[Unavoidable drifting apart.]
Newlywed couple!
What are you doing?
[Flustered]
What's this for?
[Maligned] Isn't this a game?!
Oppa, do you want to do this so that only one remains?
[Jong Kook is going crazy soon.]
This isn't a game!
[Spectators lapping it up.]
HR: How this progresses is going to be interesting.
Very interesting! This television drama is interesting.
Rewind, rewind!
[Ye Jin, suddenly attacking.]
All: Oh, oh, oh! They're hugging, they're hugging! We saw everything!
[Fiercely]
[One page Scandal!]
[Outpour of cries.]
[Anxious. Lost for words.]
[Jong Kook <3 Ye Jin, what will their ending be?]
[Jong Kook, grabbing Ye Jin into his arms.]
Wow, this is indeed a beautiful romance. Beautiful!
[Like a couple on a deserted island honeymoon...]
[Utter chaos.]
[The spectators who can't bear it anymore...]
[Blissfully going into the water.]
[Beautiful happy ending. It's a tie!]
[Even on a deserted island, an unavoidable scandal in the making.]
No matter what, we have to come to a conclusion. Jun Ki is our type!
[Jun Ki, Elder class member, guaranteed.]
No way~
[Now we see some action...]
We are all still the King's men!
[Mortified]
Let's quickly go.
[The hastily-formed King's men group...But now a big test awaits...]
[Act 2 Family Treasure Island]
Jun Ki is here today. We must let him leave with some memories.
[Want to help Jun Ki create special memories.]
SR: It must be meaningful memories.
He already has very meaningful ones!
Earlier on, honestly speaking, we were shocked by Jun Ki.
[Jun Ki's Discovery]
About him being like us!
[Elder qualities revealed!]
From now on, we actually need to begin making dinner. But for today, we need to prepare to find treasures.
[Deserted island special task. Finding the ingredient treasures.]
The ingredients are hidden right?
There are many locations here in which the ingredients have been hidden.
If you can't find them, we don't have the ingredients necessary for dinner. What's this?
[Must look in every corner of the island for the hidden ingredients!]
[The village head's weird-looking map.]
Two trees.
Isn't this here?
We need to break into groups...but it's very cold now.
PD: The time limit is 40 minutes.
We have to film ourselves?
What's this?
They're letting us film ourselves?
When we're back, all we have to do is film Jun Ki.
It's a good day to film.
We'll work hard, fighting!
[Family's first attempt.]
[Treasure-hunting!]
[On the island are 9 hidden treasures.]
[There are treasure secrets to be found, one by one.]
Chun Hee, run, run! Chun Hee!
[Family broken up into 4 groups.]
[Within the time limit of 40 minutes, they have to find the treasure.]
We have to film even when we're moving around.
There? There?
[Whatever it is, if they can't find the treasure, dinner's going to be in trouble!]
Let's go, let's go.
[Huge joy and risks.]
[On this treasure island, it begins.]
[Chun Hee and Hyori team treasure clue.]
Based on this picture, the treasure is...in the hill.
[First looking at the map to ascertain the location.]
What we're looking for is here.
How are we going to head up? From here?
[Following what the clue writes, heading first for the forest...]
You're filming this well, right?
Yeah, I'm doing fine.
Careful.
We're following the map's instructions and climbing up.
[When the camera's on her, Hyori brightens up.]
[Still the careless Chun Hee...]
Stick to me.
[Working hard to trek through the forest.]
We're going through the forest.
I'll film you for a while.
[What will be at the top of the hill?]
[Empty~]
[Confused.]
The bluebird's nest right?
This kind of place...how can there be a house?
[Where could the bluebird's house be?]
But if you look at the map, it should be here.
[The treasure's position on the map is at the end of the hill.]
These two sides?
It should be here.
[Unknowingly nearing the treasure location.]
Is this it?
No, no, it isn't. Doesn't seem like this is the place.
[Eventually going back the route they came from...]
[Wandering...]
[And wandering...]
[Uneasy...]
Possibly, could that be the bluebird's house? You go in and take a look.
[Suspecting that it could be the treasure spot...startling discovery!]
[Could this be the bluebird's house?]
Go in and take a look, push aside the branches.
Seems like it's here!
[The treasure is here?]
[For now it seems like it...]
[Chun Hee & Hyori team finally finding the first treasure?]
I should go in too.
It looks like there's something buried here, doesn't it?
[Fresh evidence.]
Try digging it. Yeah, it looks like there's something.
[Hyori working hard at digging.]
Hey, can't I film and you dig?
The scene now is pretty.
[Once hearing it's pretty, she obediently...]
Looks like there's none... I can't see it.
[Because of this, digging and digging...]
[Dug a great deal...]
[Nothing!]
Why can't I seem to find it...
[Treasure spot.] [Current location.]
[Searching similarly like vines...the two of them...]
[Probably embarassed.]
It seemed like it was here.
[Treasure...is behind. But...]
[Chun Hee spotted it?]
[The two slowly nearing the treasure...]
[Suddenly this looks like a bird's place too.]
[This time Chun Hee goes first...]
There's a certain feeling...
Ah!
Where?
[Found it?!]
Oh, it looks like it's been dug before. There's something!
[First treasure found!]
Bingo! Take it out for a look!
This is how they do it in show when they find a treasure...
What is it? Open and take a look.
[Full of anticipation.]
[After going through the forest to look for the blue house, their treasure is?]
It's the treasure. We've found the lark's nest.
Bluebird's nest, we've found it.
Is this kimchi?
[An essential to Koreans, Kimchi]
We found the kimchi, this is a must-have.
We've got the prize!
[Veins popping out.]
No one's replying...
[No witnesses, but finding the first treasure...success!]
[On this side, off to the small island, the King's men...]
Let's go!
[Clue: From the Leaning Tower of Pisa, you'll be able to find your treasure.]
Where's this Pisa's Tower?
That's it. Talking about the tower...it must be related to some kind of slanted object.
[Leaning Tower of Pisa = What slanted object?]
[The King's men were troubled for a moment.]
Looks like this one. The island isn't very big, if we look around, we should find it right?
[Full of confidence. Investigating without planning.]
Let's take a stroll around then.
[The treasure is right in front of their eyes...]
[This side, the Sooro & Daesung team?]
[Following the map, the old secret house is here.]
Open it and see.
[Two doors...Can it be the secret house's door?]
Oh, there's one in front.
Isn't this a bit too easy? It can't be so easy right?
[The suspicious couple.]
It can't be so easy huh?
DS: I was thinking...If you read 'mun' (door) doesn't it also sound like the moon?
Refering to two moons.
[Dumber Daesung's shocking analytical ability?]
The 'mun' here refers to the moon.
Ah~
Is it something you'll know only after a night?
Doesn't that mean we can't find it?
That means this vacation is going to be 4 days and 3 nights.
That means we can't have dinner!
[Thanks to Daesung's absurd logic.]
[The two who are getting farther away from the treasure.]
Maybe this isn't it?
Do you think they figured that we'd think like this and it actually is simply that back there?
[Dumber, who is cranking his brain a lot today]
Really simply... There must be staff that knew that we'd doubt that and are a step above us.
[Pondering]
This is too difficult
From here...
[The two doors must definitely be the plastic greenhouse?]
From what I can guess, the two doors is this.
[The treasure is in the clam grave!] [The two doors]
That does actually look like a grave...
There is no grave in the ocean...
Of course, that's right.
Why don't we simple-mindedly just go there?
[Fortunately thinking about going back to the plastic greenhouse...]
Over there...
Yeah, over there.  We'll find out after we pass through the two doors.
[When things cannot be solved, solve it physically with your body]
Yes, if we pass through the two doors, we'll know.
Okay.  One!
[Passing through the first door]
Okay, we've passed through one door!  We've passed through one door.
[The second one as well...]
Then we should see a grave.
This is a grave?!
[But...]
This is what...?
[Ocean...?]
The ocean is a grave?
[What'll they do...
They passed through the two doors in the opposite direction!]
Ah is it this?
[A clam dune that is piled on one side]
This is too small to be considered a grave...
[The two who are looking in the wrong place]
It has to look like there is something here at least...
It's too natural...
Then is it the two doors backwards?
If we passed through the two doors...
But since we came from there to here...
[Oh~  Genius Dumber?!]
Maybe we should go from here to there.
That one looks more like a grave, doesn't it?
[Turning around after listening to Daesung...]
[It really looks like a grave]
Door one!
[Going the opposite direction through the two doors]
This is door one, door one.
This is the first door.
And this is door two.
This looks like a grave.
[Finally, arriving in front of a grave]
This side is more of a grave
Good!
The criminal is... you!
[Definitely Dumber]
[As soon as they start to cautiously clean through the shells...]
But in here...  Oh!  What's this?
[The treasure box that is slowly revealing itself]
Oh!!  What's this?
[Ecstatic]
[Second treasure, found!]
Here, the criminal is... you!
[Knew where it why it was hidden from the start]
[Dumber and Stepmother's good spirits~]
We found it!
We found it!!!  We found it!!
[The treasure in the big box is?]
[Eh?]
[What's with the scuba diving gear?]
It is a treasure, but it's not edible...
This is...
You can't mean that we should wear this and dive for it...
[Bingo...]
That's impossible!
[Stepmother Kim who is quick to catch on]
[Pretending not to have found it and re-burying it...?!]
It's not right for us to be going into the ocean...
[The treasure that they sought for so long is worthless like bubbles?]
Chun Hee has a license!
That's right.
We can make Chun Hee go dive for it.
Ah, we could do that.
[I will make you wear the scuba diving gear...]
[And I will send you out into the ocean!]
[These three men are...]
[They had thought it would be easy...]
[They've only circled the island many times!!]
This is a palm sized island... Why can't we find it?
(Only saying it~)  Oh~  It's getting a bit exciting?!
That's right.
Yeah!
[Just then]
Hey, but why is this here?
[Found, Leaning Tower of Pisa (?)!]
Hey, it's seven steps from here.
[Then, what does it mean to flap seven times?]
This is Pisa?
Yes!
It's seven steps of flapping your arms...
He's definitely one of us.
[As soon as he started flapping...]
He's one of us.
[Junki, most definitely in the 'last year' group!]
[The Fabricated Scandal Team that came to the other side of the ocean]
I think the ocean one is near this side.
It should be somewhere here.
[Following the map's dinosaur's footprints (?)]
The fact that it goes in like that...
It kind of looks like it.
[These are the dinosaur's footprints?]
[The cautious hand that One Man offers for the dangerous rock road.]
Why are you doing this?
[This is embarassing...]
Because it's dangerous...
The road is...
[Again, the dangerous road is...]
Will you be okay?
-You can't do this...
-Okay, I understand.
Just because it might be dangerous...
Oh, why are you like this?
I... Wha...
[Lady Ye Jin, having fun ever since the game...]
Yes, because the road is dangerous...
Ah, this is really...  Wait a moment.
[Really steep cliff]
This really...
This is really dangerous.
[What'll I do...?]
[A difficult road for even Jong Kook to go by himself]
Will you be really okay?
[Ye Jin, will she this time...?]
Hold my hand.
-I'm just holding onto it this once.
-Yes, just hold it once because it is dangerous.
[Pretending that she is unable to win, grasping Jong Kook's hand]
But you come down a lot easier than I thought you would.
[The dinosaur footsteps that they have been following have disappeared]
It seems to have ended, so it must be somewhere here...
[Then the treasure is somewhere here?]
This seems like a very special place.
This place is... yes.
[Ye Jin:  It's a special place where the wind suddenly does not blow]
The sunlight that is glinting off here is so unordinarily glittering
[Jong Kook:  The sunlight is unordinary]
-It must be glittering because there is a treasure...
-That's right!
-If we follow the dinosaur's...
-The dinosaur's footprints...
[Anyway, it must mean that it is here...]
Put your hand in the place where it fills with water.
[The two who are getting further and further away]
The place that fills with water...
should be somewhere here...
[From reading that it's a place that fills with water, they only look next to the water...]
[They even look carefully into a crack between the boulders]
[Of course, it's a bit difficult for her alone...]
What did you just do?
It feels like a picnic...  Hey... Wait!
[Finally found?]
There's something, there's something.
There's something, there's something.  Ah...
[The treasure that is hidden within a hole in a boulder]
[As soon as he clears away the twigs that are hiding it]
[Third treasure found!]
They even hid it with twigs...
Ah, it's a treasure.
[This treasure is....?]
Vegetables
They're vegetables?
[Obtained various vegetables!]
There are a lot of vegetables.
I'm hungry.
-I wish it were something we could have just eaten right here.
-Exactly.
[So like Lady Ye Jin...]
Well, at least we found one.
We don't have that much time.  We only have eight minutes left.
[At this time, the Stepmother & Dumber Team is...]
[Found another treasure - fermented soybean paste found!]
[And still the 'last year' team that is digging (?)]
From here, I think all we have to do is find the right direction to go seven steps.
[Still trying to figure out "lofty flapping of arms"]
Let's make this the path...
[Keeping the Leaning Tower of Pisa (?) the center]
Let's all try to run in this manner
[Running seven steps in three directions]
[Somewhat looking pathetic...]
[Will there be a treasure?]
There's nothing.
Ah, I found something!
[Fourth treasure found!]
[After circling around the island so many times]
[The hard found treasure box]
It was right ahead of it
Look into the box.
[All expectant]
[The second they open the box!]
[Surprise]
[Empty!]
[How could this be!?]
What?
[This unbelievable situation]
It's empty!
Ah, why are they like that...
[It was such a hard found treasure box, too...]
What were they thinking?
What were they thinking?  Our...
[Stupified]
It's empty, but the formal writing is more annoying.
How happy Junki must have been...
[Blank]
[In the end, going in the wrong direction again]
There are only trees this way.
Let's try to search the sheep's head area.
I think there's something this way because in the picture...
[Jong Kook * Ye Jin Team is also searching for their other treasure]
There's one in the middle of the return path from the treasure we found.
[Trying to figure out the location by looking at the map]
I think we need to find it there.
[Then it must mean that it is somewhere here...]
Then it must be here...
It's a place where water comes in and disappears.
Then it must be one of these kinds of places...
[However!]
[It has been swept away by the waves]
It was swept away?
What?!
Go in quick!
-Excuse me?
-Go quick!
[Lady Ye Jin is obstinate in front of a treasure]
I'll film you nicely.
What's in the box?  The contents?
The marinating sauce...
What'll we do...
It was the marinade, the marinade!
[Why did the most important marinating sauce box go...]
It's so funny how you're freaking out over the marinade.
But the marinade!
If there's no marinade...
[Watching the marinade floating away...]
[My marinade...]
[Junki, dangerously going after the container]
[Treasure acquired!]
[Gathering together]
Jaesuk oppa!
[Only the Middle Agers left!]
[Time's Up]
[Treasure Hunt over!]
Jaesuk!
[Family found kimchi, vegetables, soybean paste, rice, scuba diving gear]
They're ringing the siren.
Time's up! We have to go.
[5 out of 9 treasures found (marinade exempt)]
They really hid all these well.
I applaud you guys. I can't find it.
[The Middle Agers give up]
Junki, forget about it.
[Strong desire to win Junki]
You really like to win. That's where we differ.
[The one difference between him and the Middle Agers]
They made this way too hard.
[The hiding spots were too hard?]
[Behind them...]
[The last treasure, the fishing net]
[Ch. 3]
[Find the lost marinade...]
They're here!
[Gathering together the treasures they found on the island...]
[kimchi]
[rice]
[vegetables]
[scuba diving gear]
[All found with a lot of effort]
Then the scuba...
You can't just go scuba diving carelessly.
[Can't be...]
Do you have a certificate?
Do you?
No.
JS: Do you?
JK: No.
Do you?
I don't.
Junki, do you?
We all don't.
Do you have one?
You do!
Let's just hurry and make dinner.
Yeah, before it gets dark or else it'll be too cold.
Junki can pick someone to go fishing with.
Yeah, and on the way back look for the marinade.
Junki, just take one person with you.
[Pick Jongkook...]
[Still carrying on their rivalry from the game...]
Hyung, you have to come too then.
Fine, I will!
Yeah you will!
Ok!
He loves me...
I'll hit him...
I won't hit him...
[Can't be...]
I'll hit him.
Just go, hurry hurry hurry!
I'll get hit...
I won't get hit!
Ok, so the people going fishing...
Jongkook and
Daesung
Junki
And me. The four of us will go.
[And this melancholy man]
JS: Alright, let's go.
HR: What about Chunhee?
Chunhee goes by himself.
He has to suffer by himself, it's not like he can talk down there.
Yeah, I'll be underwater.
Alright, let's get all this ready then.
Do you think you'll be able to do this well, Junki?
I think so, I mean I grew up by the ocean.
Oh, that's right.
Junki, you've never worn this before huh?
I haven't.
He grew up in Busan and this is his first time.
[Anyways...]
[Putting the familiar outfit on at the island...]
[Looking good...]
[The rest...]
[The 3 men not caring about fashion and more about utility]
[Finally setting off!!]
Junki, you seem to look like you want to go home.
[His face rapidly sinking]
Your face getting on the boat to now is so different.
[Before arriving on the island]
[Going out into the wide ocean...]
Junki, take a look.
[The bright sun making the ocean sparkle]
[The ocean shining like gold]
So we just pick this up?
[Arriving at the fish trap]
[Place the trap and then just take the fish caught inside after a week]
[Although his first time, Junki handles it expertly]
[But will they catch anything?]
[Empty...]
Heave ho!
[After 1 year, the Family have totally become boatsmen...]
[But still they keep bringing up empty traps...]
We picked such a great island...
Hey, a gunnel fish!
However, it has only one small fish...
[One startled fish]
[One sea cucumber]
You guys, all our hopes rest on Chunhee then...
[The situation at this point...]
[Can only hope on Chunhee!]
Here's one!
Oh, a crab!
[Junki got pinched but they're the ones freaking out]
[Huh?]
It's a fur coat!
Hey chatterbox! Back up, will you?!
[In the end Junki takes care of the fur coat too...]
Hey, I'm doing all the pulling!
Junki is doing all the catching!
What the heck are you doing?!
[Jongkook is... only talking...]
Why is this back?!
Let's make a soup with that!
Or we can give a fur coat to the grandmother.
Wow! This one's big!
[Big crab]
Daesung
Since Junki's been doing all the work, you get it out.
[Unreasonable scolding]
[Gathering his courage and putting in his hand...]
[Attack]
[About to faint]
Wow, did you see that?!
It was like this and then AH!
[In the end, Junki again...]
Will you guys help Junki already~
[Jongkook still chattering away~]
[The magnificent crab claws]
It's Kim Jongkook.
[The unfailing muscles of Kim Jongkook]
[Another big crab]
You have to grab it from the back so you won't get bit.
[Chatter...]
If you knew that, then you do it!
This one is dangerous!
Then what are your muscles good for?! Pull this at least!
Man, I'm tired.
When did Kim Kookjong get so freaking talkative?!
Hey, be careful. You're going to get in trouble!
[Even now still chattering away...]
Junki's getting irritated now.
You guys! Help Junki!
[Lee Junki, Suffering Generation]
Junki's going through such a hard time right now.
Those four birds over there are like us.
Those birds over there.
[They really are exactly the same...]
They're just chattering away like us.
[The four birds in the sky...]
[The four men at sea...]
Junki, you've suffered a lot.
I don't know what we would have done without you.
DS: They're fighting!
[Crab fight!]
[Between the big crab and little crab!]
[Yoo Jaesuk?]
[Kim Kookjong?]
See! I won't lose easily!
[Jongkook Crab extraordinary strength]
[While Jaesuk crab...]
[Firmly holding on to one leg]
[With the crab fight over, Jongkook back to work...]
[But only empty traps...]
The moment you took over all the traps become empty!
Fine, the ace will take over! Jongkook, get out!
[You'll get hit acting like that...]
[Talking Big Jaesuk's traps then?]
How come there isn't anything?
[Fishes!]
The moment we switched they come!
I knew this even before you beat Jongkook hyung.
Just go sit in that corner over there.
[Only a matter of time before he starts hitting(?)]
[Jaesuk boasting over the fish traps]
See! I'm here and another crab comes up!
[The gunnel trying to escape]
Catch it quickly!
[The fish being suppressed by Junki]
[While Daesung wrestles with the crab]
Hey, you got him cornered now. You can do it!
[Suppressing the crab isn't easy]
Did you get bit? Did you?
Huh?
[Using the pail]
Good job, Junki!
[Dealt with in no time]
[Getting frustrated as time goes by]
I can catch crabs even with my eyes closed!
Catching all this is a breeze!
I think this amount is enough
[Recovering the fish traps finished!]
Let's go find the marinade Unlucky Jongkook lost
Who are you calling unlucky?!
Let me pull it!!
See, there's nothing
[Empty again]
Tell us where the marinade is
[Kim Kookjong is very unlucky today]
Over there
[Departing to find the lost marinade!]
[Can they find it in the big sea?]
[Chun Hee, on the other side]
I want to just sit here and sell this off
Swim fins! Who wants swim fins?!
[Going against his will]
[Everyone just leaving him by himself]
[We received permission to film at the fishing spot]
I'm stuck! I'm stuck! I don't think this is the right size...
[How can it be so difficult from the start...]
You look so cold
What do you guys want to eat?
You have a hard life
We don't have anything right now
What if there isn't anything in the water?
While Chunhee is diving, we don't even have any wood
So, we'll gather the wood and use rocks to surround the fire like a barbeque pit
What if you do all that and I can't catch anything?
Then...
Just bring back everything you see
Chun Hee, we believe in you
[The Family's lives resting in Chunhee's hands]
Chun Hee, come back fast since it's cold
Do some stretching before you go in!
Ok, thank you!
-Thanks for caring about me!
-Get in already!
[It may look like a heartwarming family from the outside]
Don't come back if you can't find anything. Don't come back!
[Being dragged to the water]
-Please have the fire lit when I come back
-Alright
[Come back alive~]
Can you test the water for me?
[Stepmother Kim indulging him]
[SHOCKED]
It's uh~ warm!!
[Even though it's May it's still probably cold]
-Hyung, please make sure there's a fire lit
-Yea yea, don't worry about it
You think he can do this?
[Can I just not do it?]
Lee Chun Hee is a remarkable kid!
[At Stepmother Kim's remark...]
[He goes in...]
[The spring ocean still cold...]
[If you ask me what wrong I have done...]
[It is to possess a diving license...]
Should we light a fire? It's cold.
PD: We'll provide the clean water and cooking equipment
-Yes please
-Thank you
Lets light the fire now
The kids are tired, we have to show them a fighting spirit
[Big rocks being moved one at a time]
I'm doing down into the water now~
[We thought you already went]
Chunhee, fighting!
Hey Chunhee! Go really deep!
It's cold!
Sooro hyung!
Just go with some dignity!
We already said goodbye!
[Slowly getting irritated]
[Just like that, Chunhee was forced into the water]
Good bye!
[Diving into the cold sea for the sake of the Family...]
[Worried]
[Sad]
The water is really warm~
Alright, alright, just go in already!
Hey Chunhee! You're annoying! Stop talking to us!
I'll see you later...!
[Just like that, Chun Hee]
[Goes into the sea]
[Lady Yejin is carrying the rock easily]
[What is wrong with him]
[In the end doing it with Sooro]
[And still only made it a few steps]
Do it yourself
Sooro, come
[Stepmother Kim suffering alone because of the Elder's weak strength]
[A big pile in no time]
Oppa, why are you just throwing rocks instead of lighting the fire? Are you going to build a tower?
[Even straightening the gathered rocks is too much for him]
Next year I'll probably...
Not even be able to pick a rock up...?
[The new life of an Elder]
[Making dinner on a deserted island isn't easy]
I did a good job!
Oppa, light the fire quickly
[A decent looking bbq pit in a blink of an eye]
I think we can even survive on an deserted island now
We can light a fire anywhere
I heard we have to get camping permits to camp here
[Received approval from the village chief beforehand]
We had to get permission to light a fire
That's right, there's usually designated areas to light fires
So this area, it's okay
It'd be fun to have a trip at places like this, when the weather is nice
[While they were enjoying the warmth of the fire]
[What about Chunhee underwater...?]
[Home to amazing underwater creatures]
[Chunderella's outing there!]
[Worried that he wouldn't find anything]
[One crab...]
[Coming eye to eye with Chunhee]
[Diving into deeper waters]
[Finding the conch that Hyori wanted!]
[Pleased]
[Huh?]
[Came up just to boast]
Hey Hyori!
I got it!
You caught one?
[Anticipating]
What have you caught?
A conch... I can't find any abalone~
-Hyori: Tell him he can't come back until...
-Sooro: Stay there until you find abalone!
[Why did you tell them you didn't have any...]
You better catch enough for 9 people!
[In the end... going down again...]
[How long will it take for 9 people...]
[Another conch...!!]
[Found the 2nd conch!]
[And]
[What did Chunhee get in his sightline...]
[Large pen clam]
[Filling it up in no time]
[Resurfacing again to boast about the pen clam]
Clam~ Pen clam~
[Proud of himself]
I caught a clam!
[Concentrating]
Clam? Clam? Wow!
I caught a clam!
Good job!
[Can Chunhee come out of the water now?]
Chunhee, good job!
Now get 9 clams!
But I got a couple of conch, too...
9 clams!
How long do I have to do this?
[But then rescue comes in the vast open sea...]
[The team that went to find the marinade]
[Chancing upon Chunhee!!]
-Hey Chunhee!
-It's Chunhee!
I caught a conch!
-I caught conch!
-He caught a conch?!
Caught a conch?  Woah~
We have a basket full of conch here
There's a bunch of conch here!
Did you catch a lot?
When Jongkook was catching there was nothing at all, but when I tried, I caught all the big ones..
What's it got to do with me?!
Of course it concerns you
Sooro hyung said not to go back if I did not catch any abalone, but can I go up there?
What have you caught?
Conch and...
There's a lot there! Woah!
-Look at Chunhee's face!
-Chunhee get up here
I can come up?
[Face looks like he's about to collapse]
Poor thing
Here Chunhee!
[Family's diver, Lee Chun Hee!]
Woah there's more clams!
[Ignoring Chunhee and only paying attention to the clams]
-Hyung, do you want to play ping pong?
-Yea
Wanna play?
Chunhee is really no joke
[Chunhee has been rescued(?) too]
Let's quickly find the marinade!
[Setting off again to look for the lost marinade]
Look at this it's really huge!
[Thanks to Chunhee there are lots of ingredients now]
Chunhee is really great!
You are our treasure, really
[In such a cold weather, still giving his all for family's sake]
[Back to the topic, where can the marinade be found...]
Isn't the waves a bit too big?
[The waves that are getting bigger and bigger]
Where's the marinade, Jongkook?!
We'll probably end up in the Pacific Ocean looking for it...
How far do we have to go to find it?!
It's somewhere around here
There it is!
[Found it?]
[Off in the distance...]
There's something there!
[Extreme excitement]
Is this really happening?
We seriously were able to find it?!
[Oh? A buoy?]
Oh, there it is!
There it is! There it is!
Chunhee, go in!
-Go in!
-In there?!
[He just came up from the water..]
Swim over and bring that back!
[It really is the marinade...]
Pass that to me. I'll do it!
[Slowly nearing...]
We found it!
[Retrieved it!]
[Actually found the marinade that floated into the sea]
What do you guys know about marinade?!
I thought we lost this for sure
Look at the setting sun! It's like it's congratulating us!
You know what the sun said?
'You're just playing around' (word play with 'setting sun' and 'play')
Let's go back!
[The other side on the island]
[Water]
[Rice]
Oppa, I saw that you guys had a lot of fun at karaoke. Dripping sweat and everything.
It's because I haven't gone for so long
Back? They are back.
[The savior who came at the right time!!]
Hey! Yejin and Hyori! We found the marinade!
[Happiness]
HR: Oppa where did you guys find it?
We even reached the Pacific Ocean!
[Exaggerating a lot...]
What's this? Crab?
[Excited over the freshly caught ingredients...]
What what what?
Crab! We have crab!
There's even fishes
Well done Well done!
[Abundant]
Ah, this smell is really a work of art
[Cooking the clam in no time...]
We can put more sauce on here, right?
[As expected, only when it comes to food, everything is in order]
[Excellent]
[Having a clam bake on the island thanks to Chunhee...]
Looks so good
Woah look at that!
Chunhee caught all this, but where did he go?
He went to change his clothes
If Chunhee hyung wasn't here, we'd be in trouble
[New family Junki got the honour of trying it first]
-I can eat this first?
-You're the guest
The elders should get it first...
I'm the elder!
[Everyone having a taste...]
Oppa, it's a masterpiece!
Good, isn't it?
Where's Chunhee hyung?
Chunhee hyung!
[Back]
[One for Chunhee...]
The ones you caught are so good!
So good! So good!
[How good if it's like that too normally..]
[Junki starts to prepare to cook the crab]
SR: Are we making crab soup?
Good job, Junki!
Junki's the best!
Junki, use this to wash
[Everyone's calling Junki's name]
[Jongkook keeps on nagging by the side]
[Just like that the handling of the crab is done]
[Goes straight over the fire]
[Rice seems a little uncooked]
Cooking a meal here is really not easy
[Cooking rice in a pot is a bit hard anyways...]
It's cooked through inside, it's okay
[1. Put the crab and soybean paste in the boiling water]
[2. Put in kimchi for a little spice]
[3. Put in the cut vegetables]
[There's also another dish today]
[Hyori's speciality, panfried vegetables]
Junki's pretty good at cooking
He must have cooked a lot before
I think the rice is ready
[The starving Lady Yejin eating plain rice...]
Let's clean while we cook. It's so messy
[Jaesuk suddenly wants to clean?]
Let's clean up the place
Sir, please get out of the way.
[Where did he find the box...]
I just want to clean a little...
We're going to eat, why are you cleaning?!
[Why does he want to clean before dinner...]
You better not litter! Throw it away... hereee!
Were you just talking informally?
Ple..ase... plea..se...
This island... you won't get out alive...
[Sounds familiar...]
[The Grannies are creating unforgettable memories...]
Let's prepare the dinner table
Scoop the rice and get the table ready
[Because it's a uninhabited island, there's no table..]
Just grab a bowl and take it buffet style
[All in a rush to eat]
[But if you look carefully..]
The vegetables are really yummy!
[The lights keep turning on... and off...]
So, the sun has already set...
[Staff Emergency]
Our lighting is weird because the power supply is unstable
Because it's an uninhabited island
We're trying to light the set...
There's no electricity
Yes, we cant seem to switch it on
[These people are too busy eating..]
This is more important than eating...!
[One mouthful]
The viewers won't be able to see us!
[Didn't you say it's more important than eating...]
[Lights off...]
[Lights back on...]
[No one cares...]
The soup is so tasty!
It's really refreshing
[Forgetting about the show... Just enjoying the blissful dinner...]
[But.. their life on the uninhabited island has yet to end...]
[The person who can make me open my mouth]
[Can then escape from this island]
[Mission: To use the charcoal to make the shell open up]
[To escape this desolated island, they desperately struggle]
[They want it to open]
[but they want to stay closed]
[The family who is more excited than any other time]
[But...]
[No matter how hard he shakes]
[The man with the stubborn clam]
[Second day, Family that came to the bamboo forest]
[A big hit for 2009]
[Family's "SA" Dance!]
[The "SA" Dance that shook the bamboo forest]
Translators: suebee, rahrah, angelyrique, aloha91, byakucii
Timers: prince08, jocelyne03, yoochunism, swtsrwlove, celestial_nurse07
Editors: swtsrwlove, melijay, suebee
Typesetter: suebee
Encoder: melijay
Uploader: melijay