PREVIOUSLY ON "MOONLIGHT"...
(Mick) I WANNA HELP PEOPLE.     IT'S WHY I BECAME A P.I.
I HEARD WHAT YOU SAID.  THAT I'M A VAMPIRE.
(Mick) AFTER LAST TIME,  WHAT WITH THE INCINERATING...    UGH!
AND THE STAKES IN THE HEART,  I WASN'T SURE
IF I WAS   GONNA SEE YOU AGAIN. IT WAS A LOT TO PROCESS.
SOME PEOPLE JUST AREN'T MEANT     TO BE TOGETHER.
BETH HAS A VERY REAL BOYFRIEND,  AND AFTER MY EX-WIFE CORALINE,
IT'S HARD FOR ME     TO TRUST SOMEONE AGAIN.
I KNOW WE DIDN'T EXACTLY GET OFF   ON THE RIGHT FOOT,
BUT I'VE HEARD GOOD THINGS FROM BETH.   I'M GLAD THE BUZZ IS GOOD.
(Josh) SHE ALSO SAID  IT'S NEVER BORING AROUND YOU.
VAMPIRES     CAN BE IN THE DAYLIGHT,
BUT TOO MUCH OF IT  WILL KILL US,
AND OUR SURVIVAL INSTINCTS   ARE SIMPLE.
IF YOU'RE DYING,     YOU NEED BLOOD.
NO,NOT YOURS!   NOT LIKE THIS!
AT SOME POINT,    YOU HAVE TO STOP ME.
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
THERE. IF DR. ROSIN   SAYS IT'S OKAY,IT'S OKAY.
FEEL BETTER NOW?
I FELT FINE BEFORE.
WELL,I FEEL BETTER.
THAT IS ONE WEIRD CUT.   I MEAN,TWO.
IT WAS PRETTY CRAZY OUT THERE  IN THE DESERT,WASN'T IT?
YEAH,A LITTLE.
IT'S STRANGE THAT MICK    HASN'T EVEN STOPPED BY SINCE,
AT LEAST  TO SEE HOW YOU ARE.
I'M FINE.  IT'S JUST,FOR A WHILE, IT WAS LIKE HE WAS THERE
EVERY TIME WE OPENED THE DOOR,  AND NOW HE SORT OF DISAPPEARED.
IT WASN'T SOMETHING I SAID,    WAS IT?
SORRY. WHAT?
IF I'VE LEARNED ANYTHING   IN 89 YEARS,
IT'S THAT WHAT YOU WANT...
(woman) WATCH IT.   (baby cries)
DOESN'T ALWAYS MATTER.   SORRY.
YOU CAN WANT TO GET   FROM HERE TO THERE.
YOU CAN WANT TO BE ON TIME.
YOU CAN WANT TO AVOID SOMEONE    FOR THEIR OWN GOOD
BECAUSE SAY,YOU DRANK  THEIR BLOOD OUT IN THE DESERT.
BUT IF THE UNIVERSE   WANTS SOMETHING DIFFERENT...
(elevator bell dings)    WELL,YOU CAN RUN,    BUT YOU CAN'T HIDE.
MICK.
HI.
WE WERE JUST TALKING  ABOUT YOU.  YEAH,WE WERE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE? SO WHAT ARE YOU DOING--
OH. WE'RE,UH, HERE FOR A BLOOD TEST. A BLOOD TEST?   ARE--ARE YOU TWO--
GETTING MARRIED? NO,NO.  UH,FOR THIS.
JOSH THOUGHT I MIGHT    HAVE TETANUS.
YOU KNOW, FROM THE CHAIN-LINK FENCE?  AH.
SO WHAT ARE YOU   DOING HERE?
SAME. BLOOD... WORK.
I-I-I HAVE TO GET    SOME BLOOD WORK DONE.
YOU KNOW, I LEFT YOU A MESSAGE.
ACTUALLY,SHE LEFT FOUR. I MUST HAVE MISSED THAT SOMEHOW.
WELL,YOU KNOW NOW, SO CALL WHEN YOU GET A CHANCE.
YEAH.  OR BETTER YET, COME BY TOMORROW NIGHT.
WE'RE HAVING   A FEW FRIENDS OVER
TO CELEBRATE    ONE YEAR TOGETHER.  OH,I DON'T THINK-- MICK DOESN'T WANNA...
NO I WOULD,WANT TO,UH,   BUT I CAN'T.  (elevator bell dings)
I'M SORRY.
BUT CONGRATULATIONS.  THAT'S,YOU KNOW,ONE YEAR,
THAT'S,UH, THAT'S REALLY SOMETHING.
THANKS.
SEE YA.
THERE'S WHAT WE WANT...  THEN THERE ARE
THE MILLION COINCIDENCES     WE HAVE NO CONTROL OVER.
THE EVENTS THAT PUT US
IN A CERTAIN PLACE    AT A CERTAIN TIME
AND CHANGE OUR LIVES FOREVER.
(The Bravery) * COMING BACK *
* WE DO HAVE TIME LIKE PENNIES *
WHO CONTROLS   THESE COINCIDENCES?
* ...SAVING FOR? *
* WHAT ARE WE SAVING FOR? *
ALL I KNOW...
IT'S NOT US.
* FEAR THAT'S REEKING    FROM OUR SKINS *
* AND THE DRINKING NEVER STOPS *
* BECAUSE THE DRINKS   ABSOLVE OUR SINS *
* WE SIT AND GROW OUR ROOTS INTO THE FLOOR *  (beep)
* BUT WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR? *
* WHAT ARE WE WAITING FOR? * (knock on door)
* SO GIVE ME SOMETHING   TO BELIEVE * (knock on door)
* 'CAUSE I AM LIVING    JUST TO BREATHE *
* AND I NEED SOMETHING *
OH,NO,HONEY. I JUST CAN'T.
NOT WITH YOU.
SO RUN ALONG, AND WE'LL CALL IT EVEN.
YOU KNOW,YOUR PICTURE WAS A LOT PRETTIER.
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：
校对：
时间轴: 守护天使
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
《血色月光》 第一季第5集
HEY,WAKE UP,GIRL.  WE G A LIVE ONE.
RECIPES?
OH,JOSH AND I ARE HAVING SOME FRIENDS OVER TONIGHT.
MM.
"COQ IN A REDUCTION SAUCE"?
IT'S FRENCH FOR "CHICKEN."
STILL.
YOU SAID YOU HAD A LIVE ONE?
OH. DEAD,ACTUALLY.  YOU'RE GONNA LIKE THIS.
AN ESCORT?
MM-HMM. JUICY STUFF,TOO.
MY SOURCE SAID,    "A VERY DISTINCTIVE M.O."
YOU THINK THIS IS...  LIKE THE SAN FRANCISCO GUY, YEAH.
THE WAY THIS HAS BEEN IN THE NEWS
BRINGS OUT ALL THE PERVERTS.   LOOK FOR A COPYCAT ANGLE.
I'M ALL OVER IT. YOU KNOW,THE DEGREE YOU LIKE THIS STUFF
ALMOST MAKES ME UNCOMFORTABLE.
(woman) SHE CAME OUT HERE    TO BE AN ACTRESS.
SHE WAS IN "OUR TOWN"   IN TENTH GRADE.
SHE WAS THE MAIN ONE.
YOU KNOW,THE ONE   THAT DOES ALL THE TALKING.
SUDDENLY  WE COULDN'T REACH HER.
ALL HER LETTERS CAME BACK,  AND HER PHONE WAS DISCONNECTED.
I'D HEARD THE SAME STORY   FOR DECADES.
SMALL-TOWN BEAUTY LEAVES HOME  LOOKING FOR EXCITEMENT
AND GETS IT.
USED TO BE IT ENDED WITH  HER DANCING IN A CAGE ON SUNSET
OR IF SHE WAS LUCKY,     LIVING IN SOME APARTMENT
PAID FOR BY A GENTLEMAN   THREE TIMES HER AGE,
BUT LATELY,I'D BEEN HEARING     SOMETHING ELSE.
PEOPLE ALL OVER TOWN KNEW, BUT...
NOBODY TOLD US.
(man) WE WERE THE LAST ONES TO KNOW.
THAT SHE WAS ON THE INTERNET    AS AN ESCORT?
WE TRIED THAT NUMBER,
BUT SHE NEVER  CALLED US BACK.
AND THEY REVIEW THEM    ON THE INTERNET,
LIKE SOWS AT AUCTION.
I'M GONNA FIND HER FOR YOU.
I PROMISE.
THANKS.
(Carl) HEY,EVERYONE,BACK.
HEY,NO PICTURES.
CAMERAS OFF.
(Carl) COME ON,GUYS. COME ON.    HEY. KEEP EVERYBODY BACK
????
HEY,I SAID EVERYONE BACK.
BETH,COME ON. YOU KNOW THE DRILL.
WHO ARE THOSE GUYS IN SUITS?   OH,THEY HEARD THE APARTMENT'S AVAILABLE.
THOUGHT THEY MIGHT TAKE IT. ARE THEY F.B.I.?
NO COMMENT. CAN I QUOTE YOU ON THAT?
LOOK,WE'RE DEALING WITH A SERIOUS SITUATION HERE.
I NEED YOU TO BACK OFF,OKAY?   PLEASE. FOR ONCE.
IS IT LIKE SAN FRANCISCO--   THE ESCORT KILLER THERE?
A COPYCAT  OR DID HE COME TO L.A.?
(man) ALL RIGHT,EVERYONE BACK.   COMING OUT.
IS THAT WHY THE F.B.I.'s HERE?    HE'S COME TO L.A.?
BETH,YOU KNOW WHAT YOU NEED?   YOU NEED AN "OFF" SWITCH.
(Josef) SO YOUR REPORTER FRIEND.  UH,WHAT'S HER NAME?
YOU KNOW HER NAME.
SO HOW'S IT GOING SINCE,UH,HAPPY HOUR?
FINE.
OH,KNOWING YOU, IT MEANS YOU'RE AVOIDING HER.
YOU'RE A ROMANTIC IN THE ABSTRACT,MY FRIEND,
BUT THE REALITY OF FANG ON FLESH...
LOOK,YOU SAID YOU COULD HELP ME FIND THE MISSING GIRL.
DID I? YES.
HMM. WHAT DO YOU THINK   RIDER'S HERE FOR?
YOUR NEW VALET?
NO,MAESTRO OF ALL THINGS TELEPHONIC--
RIDER ENGLAND.
MICK ST. JOHN.
I HEAR YOU'RE LOOKING FOR SOMEONE.
RIGHT.
(Josef) HMM.
"A PERFECT 10."
WHAT'D SHE DO? SHE BREAK YOUR HEART?
NO,HER PARENTS'.
WELL, SHE REQUIRES REFERENCES.
YOU KNOW THAT.
YEAH,I'M NOT LOOKING TO HOOK UP.
I-I JUST NEED    THE ADDRESS.
NO PROBLEM.
YOU HEAR THAT? NO PROBLEM.
BOY,A LOT'S CHANGED    IN 400 YEARS.
YEAH,THERE'S    NO REGULAR CATHOUSES ANYMORE.
YEAH,ANOTHER CASUALTY  OF THE DIGITAL AGE.
NOW IT'S CATEGORIES.
BLONDES,ASIANS, BUSTY,MATURE.
(Josef) EQUESTRIAN.
HMM.
CHOICE,CHOICE,CHOICE.
IT'S VERY EFFICIENT,   VERY AMERICAN.
YOU SOUND ALMOST NOSTALGIC.   WHATEVER HAPPENED TO THE GOOD OLD DAYS
OF FOUR GIRLS ON A STREET CORNER    UNDERCUTTING EACH OTHER?
OKAY. HERE WE GO.
WILSHIRE CORRIDOR.
GOD,THESE PROS DO LOVE    THEIR HIGH-RISES.
THANK YOU,GENTLEMEN.  YEAH.
ALL RIGHT,LISTEN UP.
TOOU BOTH,    TOGETHER A YEAR NOW.
(Josh) CHEERS. CHEERS.
HEY,WAIT. I'M NOT THROUGH.    IS ANYONE ELSE DYING OF THIRST HERE?
TO YOU AND TO THAT MOMENT YOU FIRST MET.
OKAY,DON'T EVEN--    THE ONLY TWO CARS
IN A PARKING LOT THE SIZE    OF RHODE ISLAND COLLIDE.
YOU SAID LET AN INSURANCE    ADJUSTER CALL IT AN ACCIDENT.
I CALL IT FATE.  SO... TO,UM...
INSURANCE ADJUSTERS.
FATE.
TO FATE.
CHEERS.
(cell phone rings)  OH,I'M SORRY.
I'M KIND OF EXPECTING    A CALL RIGHT NOW.  (ring)
HEY.
YEAH,I'M GOOD.
UH,YEAH.   I C--I CAN TONIGHT.
UM,MAYBE IN,LIKE,   TWO OR THREE HOURS?
RIGHT NOW? NO,I-I'M--I'M KIND OF IN THE MIDDLE OF SOMETHING.
NO,NO,I WANT TO.  OKAY.
I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT. I'VE GOT  THIS WEIRD CASE I'M WORKING ON.
I'VE GOT A WINDOW  TO GET INTO THE MORGUE TONIGHT.
YOU'D RATHER BE AT THE MORGUE?
NO,NOT "RATHER."  IT'S JUST...
YOU KNOW,I CAN--I CAN PROBABLY GET IN TOMORROW MORNING.
NO,IT'S OKAY.
IF YOU HAVE TO,YOU HAVE TO.
THANK YOU FOR BEING SO UNDERSTANDING.
YEAH,    I'M SO UNDERSTANDING.
OKAY,YOU'RE MAD.
I'M NOT MAD.
WELL,YOU'RE SOMETHING.
LOOK,YOU HAVE TO ADMIT,    IT'S PRETTY RUDE.
THOSE ARE YOUR FRIENDS   IN THERE.
NOW YOU INVITE THEM HERE, AND THEN HE CALLS,AND YOU BAIL.
WHO CALLS?
MICK ST. JOHN.   THAT WASN'T MICK ST. JOHN.
THAT WAS A CONTACT    I HAVE AT THE MORGUE.
WELL,WHAT WOULD YOU    HAVE THOUGHT?
I SAW THE WAY YOU TWO LOOKED AT EACH OTHER
WHEN WE BUMPED INTO HIM.  OH,FOR GOODNESS SAKES.
HONESTLY, I COULDN'T MISS IT.
NOW IS NOT THE RIGHT TIME   TO HAVE THIS CONVERSATION.
NOT THE RIGHT TIME? IT'S OUR ANNIVERSARY.
ONE YEAR TOGETHER,
AND I COOKED THE CHICKEN FOR YOU. YOUR FRIENDS ARE HERE.
I SAID I'LL BE BACK   AS SOON AS I CAN.
(scoffs) YOU KNOW WHAT? TAKE YOUR TIME.
NORMALLY,VAMPIRES DON'T HAVE  TO FREQUENT WOMEN IN THE TRADE.
BETWEEN WILLING FRESHIES   AND YOUR BASIC VAMP APPEAL,
THERE'S JUST NO NEED,
BUT THIS WAS DIFFERENT.
A VAMPIRE HAD BEEN HERE.
EVEN THROUGH THE DOOR,    I ULD SMELL IT.
STRUGGLE,RESISTANCE
AND ULTIMATELY,DEFEAT.
AAH!
AND IT WASN'T JUST THE VICTIM.
IT WAS THE VAMPIRE    WHO DID IT TO HER.
YOU GOTTA HURRY. MY BOSS WILL BE BACK ANY MINUTE.
IT WON'T TAKE LONG.
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
I'LL KNOW WHEN I SEE IT.
WHY HAVEN'T THEY IDENTIFIED HER?
MM. THEY HAVE,KIND OF.   NOT ACCORDING TO THIS.
WELL,SHE HAD ONE OF THOSE STRIPPER NAMES,YOU KNOW.
WE GIVE HER "JANE DOE" UNTIL WE FIND OUT WHO SHE REALLY IS.
OH,MY GOD. HE DID THIS?
YOU THINK IT'S FUNNY? HEY,YOU PAY ME 50 BUCKS TO SEE A DEAD GIRL NAKED.
I ASSUME YOU'RE UP   FOR ANYTHING.
YOU'RE SICK.    DO YOU KNOW THAT?
(elevator bell dings) (whispers) SHH. IT'S MY BOSS.
????
YOU SURE YOU WANT    TO DO THIS?
WE HAVE TO KNOW.
OKAY.
I'M SORRY.
(voice breaks)  IT'S NOT HER.
IT'S NOT HER.
EVERYBODY'S GONE NOW. YOU CAN GET UP.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO ASK YOU    THE SAME THING.  NO,THE PERSON HIDING AROUND THE CORNER
IN THE OTHER ROOM GETS TO GO FIRST.
THERE IS A SEXUAL PREDATOR  ON THE LOOSE.
I DON'T KNOW IF "SEXUAL"   IS THE RIGHT WORD,
BUT THERE WAS RUMORS   ABOUT AN ODD M.O. A BITER?
THAT'S AN UNDERSTATEMENT. I DON'T MEAN TO CAST ASPERSIONS,
BUT I THINK IT MIGHT BE A,UH...
IT'S A VAMPIRE-- AN EXTREMELY FRUSTRATED
AND DANGEROUS ONE.
SO YOUR TURN.
WHAT? WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
YOU TRACKING THE SAME GUY?   NO,I'M LOOKING FOR A MISSING GIRL--
THE DAUGHTER OF THAT COUPLE I WAS WITH.
SHE'S WORKING AS AN ESCORT. NOT THIS ESCORT?
NO. THEY SAID THAT THIS IS THE GIRL
THAT THEIR DAUGHTER CAME TO L.A. WITH AFTER HIGH SCHOOL.
THEY WERE ROOMMATES,   I GUESS.    SO WAIT A SECOND. YOU BROUGHT  THOSE PEOPLE HERE,
THINKING THEY WERE GONNA SEE THEIR DEAD DAUGHTER? FIRST,I WENT TO A CONDO, THINKING I'D FIND
THEIR LIVE DAUGHTER,BUT THAT HAPPENED TO BE A CRIME SCENE.   WHICH CRIME SCENE?
WILSHIRE CORRIDOR,87--  18?
YEAH.  THAT'S HOW I ENDED UP HERE,  TOO.
I'M FREEZING.   LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
OKAY,   I'M JUST GONNA SAY IT.
DON'T YOU THINK IT'S A LITTLE WEIRD,
US RUNNING    INTO EACH OTHER HERE? NOT REALLY. WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I MEAN, YOU'VE BEEN AVOIDING ME.
NO,I HAVEN'T.
YES,YOU HAVE.    EVER SINCE...
YOU KNOW,THE DESERT,
YOU'VE BEEN DODGING MY CALLS,    AVOIDING ME,
AND THEN WE RUN   INTO EACH OTHER TWICE,
FIRST DOWNTOWN AND NOW HERE.   FOLLOWING
TWO COMPLETELY DIFFERENT PATHS,   WE END UP IN THE SAME PLACE.
DON'T YOU THINK THAT'S A LITTLE STRANGE? YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M NOT BIG ON CATEGORIZING THINGS INTO STRANGE AND NOT.
(whispering) WOW. VAMPIRES    MAKE REALLY BAD LIARS.
GO ON. ADMIT IT.
I JUST DON'T THINK WE NEED TO MAKE THIS INTO A BIG DEAL.
IT IS A BIG DEAL.   I FED YOU.
YOU WERE DYING OUT THERE,
AND I BROUGHT YOU BACK TO LIFE  WITH MY BLOOD.
WITH MY BLOOD.
MICK,NOW WE'RE HERE,  TOGETHER.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO SAY?
HUH? WHAT--WHAT DO YOU    WANT ME TO SAY?
I WANT YOU TO ADMIT THAT  SOMETHING HAPPENED BETWEEN US.
OKAY.
(whispering) OKAY,SOMETHING HAPPENED.
IF YOU'RE GONNA SAY IT   LIKE THAT...
SO WHAT IF I CALLED YOU BACK,    HUH? WHAT THEN?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?   YOU UNDERSTAND THAT I'M A VAMPIRE,RIGHT?
YEAH. AND DON'T YOU HAVE SOME DINNER  THAT YOU'RE GIVING?
ALL I'M SAYING IS THAT    I'M HERE,AND SO ARE YOU,
AND THERE MUST BE A REASON.
HELP ME TRACK THE KILLER,AND I    THINK YOU'LL FIND THE GIRL.
YEAH?
(man) Hi,Cherish.
WHO IS THIS?
I'M A FRIEND OF YOUR OLD ROOMMATE.
Huh. How is she?
GOOD. NEVER BETTER.
SHE SAYS HI.
Really?
'CAUSE WE KINDA HAD A FALLING OUT
AFTER SHE SWIPED MY OLD WEB SITE.
YEAH, SHE'S SORRY ABOUT THAT.
SHE SAID I SHOULD GIVE YOU A CALL.
LOOK,I'M PRIVATE NOW.
NOT REALLY INTO EXPANDING  MY CIRCLE OF FRIENDS.
I COULD OFFER A SUBSTANTIAL DONATION.
500 ROSES?
OKAY.
Per hour?
FINE.
AND YOU'RE SURE NATALIE WON'T GET ALL SKEEZY ABOUT THIS?
I PROMISE YOU, SHE WON'T SAY ANYTHING.
YOU'D THINK BY NOW YOU'D KNOW  HOW TO SPELL "PREDATOR."
MARISSA.
SO WAS THE MORGUE    EXCITING?
I'M SORRY I HAD TO BAIL.
DON'T APOLOGIZE TO ME. APOLOGIZE TO THE MAN WHO BURNED THE COQ.
IS HE MAD?
NO,NOT REALLY.
THAT'S KIND OF THE POINT.
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH YOU TWO,ANYWAY?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU'VE BEEN TOGETHER FOR A YEAR,
AND YET YOU'RE NOT EVEN    LIVING TOGETHER.
WE HAVE SLEEPOVERS.
EXACTLY. DON'T YOU THINK IT'S TIME TO GET SERIOUS?    I AM SERIOUS.
ABOUT STIFFS IN THE MORGUE.
IS THERE SOMEONE ELSE?  NO.
REALLY?    NO.
NO. WHERE--WHERE IS THIS    COMING FROM ANYWAY?
I THOUGHT YOU SAID  JOSH AND I WERE FATED.
FATE'S FINE, BUT AT SOME POINT,
THE HUMAN'S GOTTA STEP IN    AND MAKE IT HAPPEN.
FATE'S NOT GONNA GET THE EXTRA KEYS MADE
AND MOVE YOUR STUFF INTO HIS APARTMENT.
I MEAN, IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT.
THE UNIVERSE SENDS YOU A SIGN,    AND YOU JUST...    (cell phone rings)
YOU SEE? THAT'S A SIGN,
BUT YOU GOTTA ANSWER  THE CALL.   (ring)
IT'S NOT JOSH.
(Rider) THE DEAD ESCORT'S NAME    WAS NATALIE HALL.
PROFESSIONAL NAME JAZZMYN,   TWO Z's AND A "Y."
VOTED "MOST LIKELY TO SUCCEED"    BY HER HIGH SCHOOL CLASS.
NOT SURE HOW THE OTHERS FARED,
BUT THAT'S SEEMING UNLIKELY AT THIS POINT.
FAVORITE QUOTE--
"HAVE FUN IN THE SUN, GET LAID IN THE SHADE."
CAREFUL WHAT YOU WISH FOR,  RIGHT?
JOSEF,RIDER,    MEET BETH TURNER.
BETH TURNER,"BuzzWire."
OH,SUCH BEAUTIFUL WOMEN    ON THE INTERNET.
THANK YOU...
I GUESS.
SO ARE YOU GONNA TELL ME  WHAT I'M DOING HERE?
MICK SAID YOU HAD A GREAT VOICE.
RIDER HERE HAS GOT A LIST  OF ALL OF THE INCOMING CALLS
TO THE DEAD ESCORT'S WEB SITE
DURING THE LAST 24 HOURS  OF HER LIF
ONE OF THEM IS PROBABLY THE KILLER.
SO YOU WANT ME    TO CALL THE NUMBERS?
QUICK STUDY.
AND WHAT,TALK TO HIM?
IF WE'RE LUCKY,YEAH.   WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO SAY?
I'VE NEVER SPOKEN   TO A SERIAL KILLER BEFORE.
OH,YOU KNOW,BE POLITE. YOU KNOW,"PLEASE," "THANK YOU."
JUST DO WHATEVER-- WHATEVER ESCORTS DO?
YEAH.
OKAY.
(sultry voice)  WHATEVER YOU WANT.
(man) Hello?  (sultry voice) HEY.
Who is this?
IT'S ME--JAZZMYN.
Oh,you.
SO,UH,I WAS THINKING...
What? Wh were you thinking?
YOU KNOW.
No,I don't know, you idiot whorebag.
I told you never to call me here. (click)
I MESSED UP. NO,YOU DIDN'T.
I RUINED IT.  YOU DIDN'T. IT'S FINE.  IT'S NOT HIM.
(Mick) HE THINKS SHE'S ALIVE.
HE'S NOT WHO WE'RE LOOKING FOR,  REALLY. YOU WERE,UH,
I MEAN,SHE WAS... VERY IMPRESSIVE.
(Rider) HOT. VERY,VERY HOT.
NEXT?
UH-HUH.
(man) HELLO?
(Beth) Hey.
CHERISH?
(whispers) CHERISH?
Is that--is that you?    Are you there?
YEAH,I'M HERE.   WHERE ELSE WOULD I BE?
STILL ON FOR TODAY,RIGHT? Can't wait.
THAT'S WHY I'M CALLING YOU. Good.
I'M REALLY GLAD.
YOU SEEM REALLY NICE.
We're gonna have a blast.
So...
YEAH?
SEE YOU AT GREENIES.
WAIT. W--HE HUNG UP.
THAT'S WEIRD.
KIND OF REMINDED ME    OF HIGH SCHOOL.
SOUNDS LIKE HE WANTS  A GIRLFRIEND,NOT A HOOKER.
DOES ANYONE KNOW WHERE GREENIES IS? I'VE NEVER HEARD OF IT.
I'LL POKE AROUND.
MEANWHILE,CALL WAS TRACED TO A LANDLINE.
1730 LOS FELIZ.
IF THE PLAN IS FOR TODAY, YOU MIGHT WANNA HURRY.
LET'S GO.
SO YOUR FRIENDS-- ARE THEY,UM...
WHAT?
YOU KNOW.
VAMPIRES?
CAN'T TELL,CAN YOU?
SCARY.
IT DOESN'T SOUND LIKE--
SHH.
(woman) GET YOUR HANDS UP!    TURN AROUND. TURN AROUND.
LET THEM GO!    PUT YOUR HANDS ON YOUR HEAD.
NOW!
ALL RIGHT,ALL RIGHT.
(man) * SHE'S PARANOID   WITH A BODY DIZZY *
* HER EYEBROWS MELTED     INTO HER FACE *
CHERISH?
* GOT TO GET ME   OUT OF THIS PLACE *
SURE. WHY NOT?
FINALLY,IT'S YOU.
I SAW YOUR PICTURE.
JUST SIT DOWN,OKAY?
UH,YOU KNOW WHAT?
CAN YOU GET ME A DOUBLE?
MICK ST. JOHN.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW CLOSE  YOU CAME TO GETTING SHOT?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA    HOW CLOSE YOU CAME
TO GETTING  YOUR FACE RIPPED OFF?
I NEVER UNDERSTOOD WHAT IT IS    ABOUT HUMANS AND YELLING.
NOT THAT I DON'T APPRECIATE
THAT FLUSHED,  BLOOD-IN-THE-FACE LOOK
MORE THAN I USED TO,  BACK BEFORE I BECAME A VAMPIRE.
IT'S JUST THAT WHATEVER RELIEF
????
CAUSES YOU TO MISS THINGS--    IMPORTANT THINGS.
(Carl) WHAT'S THAT?
I DON'T KNOW. LOOKS LIKE SOME OLD PHOTO.
LOOKS LIKE OLD HOOKERS  OR SOMETHING.
COULD WE JUST STICK   TO THE CASE HERE,
NOT WASTE TIME ON SOME STUPID-ASS PICTURE?
THE FEDS    HAVE THIS GUY NAILED.
HE'S A LONER,  38 TO 45 YEARS OLD,
TORTURED ANIMALS AS A CHILD,    WET HIS BED.
THAT FREEZER?
IT'S A PLACE TO KEEP TROPHIES   OF HIS VICTIMS.
????38,HUH?
IT'S 38 TO 45.
PROFILING'S    NOT AN EXACT SCIENCE.
I'LL SAY.
THEY SAID WE CAN GO.
HE'S A KID,  MAYBE 16 YEARS OLD.
16?
WELL,GOING ON 200.   I SAW A PICTURE.
UGH,AWKWARD AGE.
YOU'RE NOT KIDDING.
YOU KNOW,BOYS THAT AGE THINK    ABOUT SEX 20 TIMES A MINUTE,
AND THAT'S  A SCIENTIFIC FACT?
TIMES TWO CENTURIES,    THAT'S GOTTA TAKE A TOLL. SHOULDN'T WE TELL THE POLICE?
WELL,HE'S A VAMPIRE.
IT'S PROBABLY HEALTHIER  ALL AROUND IF WE DON'T.
OH,MY GOD. NATALIE HALL.
THIS BELONGED  TO THE DEAD ESCORT.
JUST KEEP IT HIDDE UNTIL WE'RE IN THE CAR.
THEY'RE STILL WATCHING US.
LOOK.
THAT'S HER.
THAT'S THE GIRL I'M LOOKING FOR.
YOU THINK HE'S WITH HER?   THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE.
GREENIE'S? THERE'S A NUMBER ON THE BACK.
CALL IT.
SO WHAT'S THE DEAL?    YOU A VIRGIN?
DEPENDS ON WHAT YOU MEAN.
I MEAN, WOULD I BE YOUR FIRST?
MY FIRST?
NOT REALLY.
HOW OLD ARE YOU?
I SAID.
21,SURE.
I MEAN,REALLY.
REALLY?
197 1/2.
LOOK, YOU SEEM LIKE A NICE KID.
ARE YOU SURE THAT...
HEY. DON'T ANSWER IT.
OKAY,OKAY. JUST...
UGH. IT WENT TO VOICE MAIL.
IT'S A PUBLIC PLACE  AT A CROWDED PIER.
SHE SHOULD BE OKAY  UNTIL WE GET THERE.
HOW FAR IS IT ANYWAY?
IT'S JUST AT THE BEACH.    WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
SO WE CAN GO    ON THE RIDES,
PLAY SOME GAMES.
RIDES?
YEAH,THE ROLLER COASTER'S KILLER. YOU'LL LOVE IT.
I DON'T HAVE TIME   FOR ALL THAT.
COME HERE.
YOU CAN WAIT.
I WANT YOU CLOSER.
SO HOW DOES IT WORK,   ANYWAY?
WHAT?
JUST,YOU KNOW, THE SEX THING.
YOUR PARENTS  NEVER TOLD YOU?
THEY SOMEHOW SKIPPED THE PART  INVOLVING VAMPIRES.
OH.
VAMPIRES AND HUMANS,   I MEAN.
OH,I'M TALKING TOTALLY HYPOTHETICALLY,BELIEVE ME.
KISS ME.
LIKE YOU MEAN IT.
YOU WANNA KNOW    HOW IT WORKS?
IT DOESN'T,OKAY?    IT DOESN'T WORK.
SO IT'S IMPOSSIBLE?
IT'S NOT IMPOSSIBLE.   IT'S INADVISABLE.
IT NEVER ENDS WELL.
NEVER?
WE'RE ALMOST THERE. YOU SHOULD CHECK THAT NUMBER AGAIN.
OKAY.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD JUST CALM DOWN.
YOU KNOW WHAT? MAYBE YOU SHOULD   JUST DO WHAT YOU'RE PAID FOR.    (cell phone rings)
(scoffs) I'M OUT OF HERE.  DO NOT ANSWER THAT.
YEAH? UGH! (grunts)
????
DO YOU HAVE HER?
I CAN'T TELL. LISTEN.
(whispers)  NOW GIVE ME THE PHONE.
????
(Mick) I know what you are.  I know why you're doing this.
THE BORDELLO. IS THAT IT?
WHO TURNED YOU?
What did they do?  Are you there?
LET HER GO. I KNOW YOU WANT TO.   Who are you?
WHO ARE YOU?
My name is Mick St. John.
I know you're a vampire...
WHERE DID YOU GET THIS NUMBER?
????
Like me.
OH,LIKE YOU,HUH?
I KNOW WHAT  YOU'RE GOING THROUGH. Oh,you know?
IS THAT RIGHT?   I know that you feel cursed,
like fate has played  a cruel trick on you,
li you're gonna wake up   one day and realize
THIS WAS ALL A MISTAKE, BUT YOU DON'T WAKE UP,
not as the years roll by,  the decades--
CENTURIES,MICK.   200 YEARS.
I didn't choose any of this.  It was done to me.   YOU CAN ALWAYS CHOOSE.
(scoffs) SURE.
LET GO OF ME.
LET ME GO!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS.
????
WAIT,WAIT,WAIT,WAIT.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
(crying)  THAT GUY WAS GONNA KILL ME.
(Mick) IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE THIS WAY.
I KNOW   WHAT YOU'RE GOING THROUGH.
????
you???
YOU THINK SO?
YOU THINK YOU KNOW?
COULDN'T POSSIBLY.
I MEAN,YOU WERE TURNED  AT WHAT,30?
I'M STUCK.
ALL I'VE EVER WANTED IS  TO GROW OUT OF THIS,
AND I WON'T... EVER.
SOMEONE BETRAYED YOU.
OH,YOU THINK?
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE.
HAVE YOU EVER LOVED SOMEONE   COMPLETELY?
SO THAT SHE WAS    YOUR WHOLE WORLD?
YOU'D DO ANYTHING SHE ASKED,    ANYTHING AT ALL.
HAVE YOU EVER LOVED SOMEONE    THAT WAY?
SO YOU FORGOT ABOUT YOURSELF
AND ALL YOU THOUGHT ABOUT    WAS HER?
(The Used's "The Bird and the Worm" playing)
* HE WEARS HIS HEART SAFETY PINNED TO HIS BACKPACK *
I LOVE YOU FOREVER.
FOREVER.
* THE HEART AND DEVOUR *
YES.
* ALL ALONE *
SEE,I NEVER HAVE.
* WHILE HOLDING HIS BREATH HALF TO DEATH *
* TERRIFIED OF WHAT'S INSIDE *
* TO SAVE HIS LIFE *
* HE CRAWLS LIKE A WORM  FROM A BIRD *
* CRAWLS    LIKE A WORM FROM A BIRD *
(men whispering indistinctly)
* OUT OF HIS MIND AWAY,    PUSHES HIM,WHISPERING *
* MUST HAVE BEEN    OUT OF HIS MIND *
* MIDDAY DELUSIONS OF PUSHING THIS OUT OF HIS HEAD *
* MAYBE OUT OF HIS MIND *
* OUT OF HIS MIND *
* ALL ALONE,HE TURNS TO STONE *
* WHILE HOLDING HIS BREATH, HALF TDEATH *
* TERRIFIED OF WHAT'S INSIDE *
* TO SAVE HIS LIFE *
* HE CRAWLS LIKE A WORM *   * CRAWLS LIKE A WORM *
* CRAWLS LIKE A WORM  FROM A BIRD *    * ALL ALONE *
* CRAWLS LIKE A WORM *
* CRAWLS LIKE A WORM  FROM A BIRD *
IF I'VE LEARNED ANYTHING   IN 89 YEARS,
IT'S THAT WHAT WE WANT  DOESN'T ALWAYS MATTER.
YOU CAN WANT TO GET   FROM HERE TO THERE.
YOU CAN WANT TO SURVIVE,
BUT IF THE UNIVERSE    WANTS SOMETHING DIFFERENT,
YOU CAN RUN,   BUT YOU CAN'T HIDE.
* ALL HE KNOWS *
* IF HE CAN'T RELIEVE IT,   IT GROWS *
* AND SO IT GOES *   * AND SO IT GOES *
* HE CRAWLS LIKE A WORM *
* CRAWLS LIKE A WORM  FROM A BIRD *
HI.
WHERE ARE THE CAMERAS?  YOU'RE MISSING THE MOMENT.   (lowered voice) THEY DON'T WANT THIS PUBLIC.
"BEAUTIFUL ESCORT NEARLY KILLED,    REUNITED WITH PARENTS"--
THAT'S JUST ABOUT THE JUICIEST    STORY WE'VE EVER HAD.
SHE DOESN'T WANT TO BE ON THE INTERNET.  SINCE WHEN?
I GOTTA GO.  UH...
MAYBE IT'S THE SUM    OF A MILLION COINCIDENCES
WE DON'T QUITE CONTROL  THAT BRINGS US
TO A PARTICULAR PLACE  AT A PARTICULAR TIME.
OR MAYBE    IT'S THE CHOICES WE MAKE,
THE ACTIONS WE TAKE.
IF THERE'S ONE THING    I'VE LEARNED IN 89 YEARS,
IT'S THAT WHAT WE WANT--    IT DOESN'T ALWAYS MATTER.
YOU JUST TOOK OFF. OH,UH,YOU WERE KIND OF TIED UP WITH YOUR EDITOR.
YOU COULD AT LEAST  HAVE SAID GOOD-BYE.
GOOD...
BYE.
WHAT WE WANT  DOESN'T ALWAYS MATTER.
BUT THEN AGAIN...
SOMETIMES IT'S ALL THAT DOES.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入