Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
AL DI Là DELLE NUVOLE (1995)
Excuse me.
Can you suggest a hotel?
A good one
or a simple one?
You choose.
I'll trust you.
There's onejust back there.
Thanks.
I need a room, please.
A single?
Room 4. Any luggage?
I'll be right back.
We met earlier,
but you didn't even look at me.
The beautiful thing is
that I came here by chance.
Why beautiful?
I was supposed to go
somewhere else.
At one point
I let the car drive me.
Me, I'm stuck here
in the fog.
I'm a teacher. I can't escape
except when school is out.
Where do you go?
The city.
I just escaped from there.
Have you noticed
nobody watches sunsets anymore?
Maybe it happens in towns too...
but when myjob brings me
out to the country...
I'm always enchanted
by the sunsets.
I'm a drainage pump technician.
There are lots around here.
My name is Carmen.
I'm Silvano.
Voices never become part ofyou
like other sounds.
The sea, for instance.
You end up not hearing it.
But a voice
you can't help listening to.
It's strange.
We always want to live
in someone's imagination.
Maybe that's the secret
of being in love.
I like your eyes.
They're so empty
ofeverything...
except sweetness.
Which is your room?
The one on the right.
Good night.
Night.
Has the girl in Room 8
already left?
Ofcourse.
She's always up early
for work.
Where can I buy flowers here?
Flowers don't grow
in the lagoon.
Can you send those
to her room?
I'll get some fresh ones.
Did you like it?
It's a miracle
meeting you again!
Nothing happens by chance.
- This is Sara.
- Pleased to meet you.
- I have to go. I'm running late.
- Did I scare you off?
No, I must get to the shops
before they close.
Bye, Carmen.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
I've wondered for two years
why you left that morning...
without even saying good-bye.
I waited all night foryou.
I've been wondering lately...
why I have such a need
to hear words.
Nobody talks anymore.
Eyes are in fashion.
True words are shut up inside.
Bring some out.
All right.
There's a kind ofenslavement
that we can desire...
when we're under a spell.
For example, now...
I'm enslaved by your silence.
Do you live here?
Yes, this is my home.
You must be very rich!
It's beautiful.
Another world.
Who else lives here?
A family from Naples
lives upstairs.
Are you with somebody?
Not at the moment.
There's always something
left behind.
Like dregs in a coffee cup.
My grandma used to read
coffee cups.
She knew all about everyone
who drank coffee with her.
I lived with a man
for a year.
Ten days ago,
he wrote me a letter.
I know it by heart.
It's about scents.
Some scents cling
to your skin forever.
"l can still smell the scent
ofyour skin and your words.
A few nights ago,
I went back to the river...
where we stopped last time.
I stayed there...
feeling you close to me."
Words do us good,
even in writing.
A woman expects them.
She always does.
Can I help you?
Excuse me.
Sorry to botheryou.
May l?
Thankyou.
I read a strange thing
in my magazine.
I want to talk to someone
about it.
And you picked me?
You're not French,
are you?
No, I'm from New York,
but I live here.
Where are you from?
Italy.
- So may l?
- Go ahead. I'm "all ears."
Isn't that what they say?
I hope so.
In Mexico...
some scientists hired porters
to take them...
to an lncan city
in the mountains.
At one point,
the porters stopped.
They refused to go on.
The scientists got angry
and tried to get them moving.
They couldn't understand
the long delay.
After several hours...
the porters set off again.
Finally, their leader decided
to explain.
What had happened?
I see you're interested.
Now, very.
He said...
they'd been walking too fast.
They'd left their souls behind.
Their souls?
It's wonderful! It's like us.
We go rushing around...
and lose our souls.
We should wait for them.
To do what?
Everything that seems
pointless.
You're still up?
I asked you
a friendly question.
Were you with her?
We met briefly.
Since that story
about souls in the cafe...
it's been three years.
Some things can't be
called off overnight.
For the last time...
it's her or me.
You're late.
Sorry.
The traffiic was bad.
Everything's against us.
Look, we've got to talk.
Go ahead...
but caress me
at the same time.
Gently.
I've forgotten it all.
Patricia.
Oh, shit.
What's up?
What are you up to?
I've been calling you
for two days.
That's a vase to me.
What's a vase to you?
Vase offlowers.
Flowers... colors.
Colors... beauty.
Beauty... Iove.
Everything seems ridiculous.
Love is ridiculous.
It has to be said.
It's an illusion. A trap.
But the trap is mysterious,
so we all fall into it.
Like stewed prunes!
You bring me your calm...
after sleeping with her?
I slept alone.
I felt bad.
I was away on a trip.
You know that.
Didn't you take her?
I didn't take anybody.
I loved making love to you.
Go fuckyourself.
You've got a new vocabulary.
Because you're talking gibberish.
Say what you like,
but last night...
I realized how much I miss
making love to you.
I'll come back
ifyou leave her.
I will. I swear.
- When?
- Today.
This morning.
Now.
Right now.
Don't leave me.
Tell me.
Do you still make love
behind my back?
I've been saying no to her
for three years.
Would she want to?
Probably, yes.
And you've always refused.
Well, yes.
And today?
Did you say yes or no?
I pitied her.
Don't you pity me?
For three years you've been
bringing her smell here!
The smell on your clothes.
The stale smell ofa cheated woman!
Thanks.
Bye.
You'ne back?
- Where are you?
- Somewhene.
What's gotten into you?
- Emptying the house.
- It's my funnitune.
- You could leave a note.
- You nevendid.
- Because of myjob!
- Leaving mestuckat home!
- Where are you?
- Don't tryto findme.
Is the lady here?
No, she went out.
I spoke to her
about renting the place.
What place?
This one, I think.
I brought the newspaper ad.
It's entirely my wife's idea.
I'm not even sure I agree.
Don't say that
or I'll go crazy.
May I explain my situation?
I prefer short stories.
I'll put it in a nutshell.
My husband has been having
an affair for three years.
I was patient.
He always said it would pass.
But in fact--
- The doorbell rang.
- I didn't hear it.
I'm expecting the furniture.
What furniture? Mine?
My husband's.
So you emptied an apartment too.
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
I guess I'll have
to go away again.
Where to?
I have commitments
outside Paris.
So you'll cope somehow.
Yes.
But this time I was planning
to stay put.
I told her so.
Maybe that's why she went
to live with him.
With whom?
The lover.
So you're in a precarious
position too.
Right.
It seems to be the thing.
This is her.
She's beautiful.
My wife.
Don't try to fii nd me.
There's a cure for everything.
That's what disturbs me.
May l?
I told you.
Don't phone me again.
I wonder why our society needs
all these copies ofthings.
Notjust paintings.
Copies ofeverything.
Even things like clothes,
suitcases, bags, watches.
Originals are very costly.
True.
But in your case,
a reproduction of Cezanne...
or a photo
ofthe landscape would do.
I believe that anyone
who copies a masterwork...
has a chance of repeating
the artist's action...
and possibly recapturing,
ifonly by chance...
the exact gesture.
A copy ofthe gesture.
Why not?
Recapturing a genius's nature...
will satisfy me more...
than any brushstroke of my own.
I can see why you laugh.
I won't sell it to you anyhow.
Don't worry.
- Please.
- I'm sorry.
Thankyou.
I'm looking
for the architect's offiice.
It's across the street.
Excuse me.
May I come with you?
I'm going to church.
Are you a Catholic?
Do you believe in God?
What is this, a test?
If I say yes, I can escort you,
and if not, I can't?
Is that the idea?
Sorry.
No, I'm not sorry.
Are you always so quiet?
Why?
I have nothing to say.
With so many things
going on around you?
Maybe I should go alone.
No, I should escort you.
Don't worry.
Nothing can happen to me.
You must read a lot.
Not even the papers?
I used to browse through them.
Not anymore.
Once I read this in a paper:
"lfonly a cherry tree
could eat its own cherries!"
You're the tree
that eats its own fruit.
I think that to be happy
we should eliminate our thoughts.
That's a thought in itself.
That's true.
That's why I prefer
to keep quiet.
That only makes it worse!
Silence fii lls our heads
with thoughts.
I mean pointless thoughts.
How do we get rid ofthose?
If I could...
I'd escape.
Where to?
Away from my body.
Why?
One ofthe body's shortcomings...
is that it needs so much.
It's never satisfiied.
Don't run down all its needs.
Some can be fun to satisfy.
Try giving up your little fun.
You'll see the peace it brings.
We already have
so many unfulfii lled dreams...
at the end ofeach day!
I think I've got it.
You're in love.
You show all the signs
ofa girl in love.
- It's true.
- I knew it!
You're detached,
like all satisfiied women.
Yes, I am satisfiied.
So peaceful!
Right now I have
life's rarest treasure: serenity.
It comes from being
with a satisfiied woman.
Satisfiied people are rare.
Excuse me.
Are you satisfiied?
Don't be ridiculous.
- See? It's rare.
- What time is it?
A quarter to 5:00.
Can we hurry?
Where are we going?
St.John of Malta's.
- Are you from here?
- No.
Will you tell me
where you're from?
I'd really rather not.
Like flowers.
That's true.
It's pretty.
This sounds like sacrilege...
but I don't like flowers.
I do, but they make me sad.
They're beautiful--
gorgeous for two days.
Then they wilt
and get thrown away.
TheJapanese don't grow flowers
so as not to see them die.
Why are you smiling?
You're scared ofdeath,
aren't you?
Scared is not the word.
I'm scared of life.
A girl your age,
scared of life? Absurd!
The life people lead.
You undervalue it.
What do you want from life?
Nothing.
What? Nothing?
Life is all we have.
It's all there is.
It's the only thing
we know exists.
Look.
Here we're alive.
There we're dead.
Here we can laugh.
There we can laugh all we like--
no one will see.
We're in the beyond.
Your opinion is
beside the point.
Please don't treat me
like this.
Your courtesy reminds me too much
that I'm a woman.
You don't like it?
I wish I were a man.
A strong man.
Almost all women say that...
but usually
for practical reasons.
Never for poetic ones.
I mean I'd like to be
as strong as a man.
An enigma--
that's what you are.
And, like all enigmas,
disconcerting.
I want to know you better.
Discoveryou.
I'd like us to be friends.
It's hard to relate to someone
who's in love...
but I'd like to try.
I'm not saying this
to please you.
You're not the type
to like compliments.
Not that kind ofcompliment.
I'd rather be told
that I pray well.
Can you be good or bad
at praying?
Oh, yes!
The way you looked in church,
you must be brilliant!
It was like you were dead.
I was dead.
A little.
Look!
Lone men at night
look like criminals.
Typical!
A criminal who lets you by
and then starts singing.
I haven't seen a man sing
in the street foryears.
Are you hurt?
- Sure you're okay?
- I'm fii ne.
You got your coat dirty.
What if I fell in love
with you?
You'd be lighting a candle
in a room full of light.
Can I see you tomorrow?
Tomorrow I enter a convent.
Download Movie Subtitles Searcher from www.OpenSubtitles.org