Times like these...
One feels
the very weight of the world upon us.
Everyone is here.
Our agenda is clear.
What's at stake
should not be underestimated.
The decisions we make today
will reverberate for years to come.
And influence whether or not
the world continues to put their trust
in the Justice League.
Please, take your seats.
We have work to do.
Season 1, episode 22
“Agendas”
Another expansion of the League
could generate another escalation
of hostilities from our enemies.
No one needs or wants
another Injustice League.
Point taken. But the option remains
to vote no one or all candidates.
So...
I nominate Icon
for League membership.
Why, because you suspect Icon
might be Kryptonian,
like you did with Captain Marvel?
You thought I was Kryptonian?
Cool!
Icon interests me also.
As does his protégé,
Rocket.
Athena knows the League
could use more female members.
- Agreed.
- Hear, hear!
Gabble, gabble!
Aw, I love Thanksgiving!
- Ow!
- Those are for dinner, Wally!
There, seasoned to perfection
and ready for the oven!
Wally, I thought
you were eating with your family!
Oh, yeah,
Dad will kill me if I'm late!
See ya!
Wally!
It's nothing.
The onions...
These are all the things
I used to cook for...
It's my first Thanksgiving
without my Dad.
At least she had a Dad.
With Superman off world,
only one thing alive
with less than four legs
can hear this frequency,
Superboy.
And that's you.
Meet me in Washington DC,
East Potomac Park.
Come alone.
I promise,
it will be worth the trip.
Conner?
Figured you don't want my help
in the kitchen.
Remember the last time?
When the...
Yeah. But...
Just walking Wolf.
No big.
Seriously?
The Atom?
How useful could he be
at that size?
It's the size
that makes him useful.
Absolutely.
Still, we could always use
more raw power.
And Earth has
a third Green Lantern.
- Guy Gardner.
- No!
- But we could really...
Superboy...
My name is Lex Luthor.
I'm the new Chairman
of the Board for Project Cadmus.
I know who you are, Luthor.
And I want nothing to do with you.
Or Cadmus.
Cadmus has created
a new super clone.
Guardian!
Fast work on the rebuilt.
Now escort me down
the easy way.
Or I escort myself down,
the hard way.
You're letting Superboy down here?
Focus on the matter at hand,
Dr. Spence.
Another genomorph has vanished.
Every disappearance
is being investigated.
Not good enough, Dubbilex.
The new super clone.
Where are you holding it?
Welcome home, Superboy.
Now, what are you talking about?
Brother, you are
the only super clone in Cadmus.
All cloning projects,
human and Kryptonian
had been shut down
since your escape.
"Since my liberation".
As you say.
But now I'm needed
back in my lab.
Sometimes I hate this job.
You... you look a lot
like Red Arrow.
Not all that surprising,
Red Arrow is my nephew.
If we're considering Blue Devil,
then I nominate Red Arrow.
Roy has more experience
and he's no kid anymore.
He's eighteen.
A legal adult.
- He's ready.
- Is he?
Red Arrow has been uncooperative
and disrespectful.
If we reward that behavior...
What message does that send
to the rest of the Team?
Here's the floor 1-1.
This is the new and improved Cadmus.
Doctor Spence and her team
are doing truly worthwhile
genetic medical research now.
The genomorphs are becoming
more independent. More educated.
Some even have names.
Hey, Benny!
And, someday...
The working done here
will save millions of lives...
Superboy...
You may trust Guardian.
He keeps no secrets.
Unlike you...
Apparently, you still keep
your psychic power a secret.
Some secrets have their place.
We were all created
to be exploited as living weapons.
You were designed...
...to replace or destroy Superman,
I know. What's your point?
That you should understand
the plight of those left behind,
after I helped free you
from Cadmus.
The League liberated all genomorphs.
Are we free to walk the surface,
as you do?
Or has our role merely changed
from weapons to minimum labor?
Look... it's complicated.
But first things first.
Guardian, could a super clone exist
without you knowing?
It's highly unlikely.
Tell me, Brother,
what would you do
if you found this super clone?
If it'd exist, I'd free it.
Just like Aqualad, Robin and Kid Flash
freed me.
Then I will question our brothers.
Nothing happens at Cadmus
without a genomorph knowing.
If a super clone exists,
we will find him.
Look, I have my own
missing genomorphs to locate.
But you got the run of the place.
I just doubt you'll find
what you're looking for.
It's OK.
You're free now.
Stop! I'm on your side!
You can fly...
Why can you fly?
I don't wanna do this!
Enough!
I'm trying to help you!
No!
Red Arrow may be eighteen,
but the rest of the Team is too young.
We're not inducting children
into the League.
That seems ironic.
I have been one
with Kid Flash and Aqualad.
Both are ready.
- And what of Zatanna?
- Absolutely not!
That sounded almost protective,
Doctor.
At least we know Zatara
is still in that helmet, somewhere.
Why is Doctor Fate a member?
You coerced Zatara
into giving up his life to you.
Or else,
lose his daughter instead.
Not cool.
Should such behavior
be condoned?
Zatara desires
Doctor Fate remain with the League.
- Oh, please...
- It is true!
Zatara's trust in Nabu is...
measured.
He desires the League
to maintain a close watch upon us.
No, no, no!
It's alright!
It's not "alright"!
You put me in a pod!
It was the fastest way
to heal your injuries!
She's another Cadmus' mad scientist,
picking up where Desmond left off!
"Project Match" is yours!
Admit it!
Believe what you want!
Superboy, please!
She was as shocked to see the security
camera footage of this "Match" as I was.
- Where is he now?
- We don't know.
He... disappeared.
What?
All cameras went offline
after your battle.
By the time we arrived...
Match was gone.
And he isn't the only genomorph
to disappear.
We need to go
to the bottom of this.
So, the truth
wasn't that hard to find, after all.
I assume you suffered no...
- ...permanent damage.
- Like you care!
Tell me what you know
about Project Match.
Very little.
I know more about you.
Kryptonian DNA is notoriously
difficult for human science to read.
When you were created,
the gaps in the sequences were bridged
with human DNA.
Robbing you
of your full Kryptonian powers.
No flight, no heat vision,
etcetera.
I'm part human!
Yes.
Obviously, your... twin
was created with pure Kryptonian DNA.
The missing sequences have...
apparently left Match unstable.
Insane.
I'd advise you to get him
back on ice as soon as possible.
Not gonna happen.
Your call.
Either way, you'll need help.
Consider this a gift.
I call them "shields".
Stick one on your arm
and it will suppress your human DNA
for about an hour.
Allowing your Kryptonian powers
to bloom.
You'll be as powerful
as Match.
As Superman.
I don't want anything from you.
Keep them, anyway.
You never know.
Plastic Man.
I don't know... The guy has
a pretty substantial criminal record.
Sorry... sorry.
The guy just cracks me up.
Maybe it's time we all talk
about the elephant in the room.
Should Captain Marvel
stay a member?
Now that we know
he's really only ten years old?
He does possess an adult body
and the wisdom of Solomon.
Wisdom does not equal maturity.
Hey, I'm sitting right here!
Then, Billy, maybe
you should leave.
Until we hash this out.
No. Captain Marvel is a member
and is entitled to participate,
until or unless he's voted out.
It's not just his age.
It's the fact that he lied about it.
I didn't lie...
...exactly.
I just left out the part
about being a kid.
A lie of omission is still a lie.
You kept an important secret from us.
No one in the League
knew the truth.
I did.
I shouldn't be surprised.
Since you indoctrinated Robin into crime
fighting at the ripe old age of nine...
Robin needed to help bring the man
who murdered his family to justice.
So he could turn out like you?
So that he wouldn't.
At least these are empty.
OK, Dubbilex, spit it all.
When I accused Spence,
I could hear your heart rate increase.
Stress.
You're hiding something.
From them, not you.
I have questioned
the oldest genomorphes.
They tell me Match is not
your younger brother.
He was Cadmus' first attempt
to clone Superman.
His Kryptonian DNA
rendered him uncontrollable,
so they froze him,
and struck again.
Who are "they"?
Desmond? Spence?
Desmond, yes.
And his superior
and Cadmus founder,
Lex Luthor.
So Luthor took Match.
Actually, Brother,
I did that.
Turn left, Brother.
Welcome, Brother,
to Genomorph City.
So you're responsible
for the missing genomorphs.
I am.
One by one,
I liberated them,
brought them here, to a new life,
where all our brothers can be free.
Of course, I have a dream that one day,
the world you live in will accept us.
But for now, no one must know
Genomorph City exists.
Which is why
I brought our brother here.
- What have you done to him?
- He is safe.
The genoms keep him docile
with their psychic abilities.
And the chains?
Should he escape,
in his current condition,
he could set back
the genomorph cause by decades.
So you hold him prisoner,
like Cadmus held me?
You might as well put him in a pod!
Our goal is rehabilitation.
We will release him
when he is ready.
That's not your call!
Be calm!
You seem to have reached consensus
that eighteen years is a suitable
minimal age for joining the League.
Yet, what of Miss Martian?
Though she is a biological adolescent
by Martian standards,
she was born 48 Earth years ago.
So what is the deciding factor?
Chronology or biology?
- Take Superboy.
- Exactly.
He's less than a year old.
Does he have to wait 17 more
to stand beside us?
My turn.
Superboy, enough!
He's down.
You won.
It has to be this way.
No other ideas?
Then here are candidates
for new, or continued membership.
We've debated origin,
gender, size, experience, age,
temperament and background.
But... What is the fundamental
criteria for membership?
When all is settling down,
the question must be,
whom do we trust?
Trust to fight beside us,
trust to have our backs,
trust to uphold the high standards
and ideals of the Justice League.
Time to vote.
There was a tracker
in that tin box you gave me.
Yes. I assume you discovered it,
with your X-ray vision?
You initiated the cloning projects!
I wanted Superman
to meet his match.
And you used both of us
to locate the missing genomorphs.
A good businessman
has to keep track of his assets.
But none of that
is what really bothers you.
Half your DNA is human.
Haven't you wondered
who the donor was?
Or have you just been afraid
to acknowledge the obvious...
Face it, son.
You have much more in common
with me than Superman.
That's a lie!
What has he given you?
Nothing.
Not even affection.
And, why?
Because Big-Boy-Blue
lives in a world of black and white.
You were created by the "bad guys".
So there must be
something wrong with you.
But we both know
life isn't that clear cut.
The real world is full of grays.
Weren't you determined
to free Match at all cost?
Yet, ultimately, you wisely agreed
to my suggestion to refreeze him,
for the greater good of all.
And though you think me a villain,
you still accepted my shields.
We're more alike
than you care to admit.
- Take them back.
- They're a gift!
From a father to his son.
I won't need them for this...
"Red Sun."
Two words,
and he shut me down...
What else can he make me do?
All those in favor
of ratifying the results...
I!
All opposed?
Then, we are adjourned.
www.tvsubtitles.net