- Explore!
- Rescue!
- Protect!
Octonauts!
CAPTAIN BARNACLES GRUNTS
We're all connected and ready to go, Cap.
Let's turn on the Octo-cam and see if it works.
Barnacles to Shellington, is the Octo-cam working?
Yes, Captain. The picture of the hermit crab
is coming in nice and clear.
No-one's explored this part of the ocean before. With this Octo-cam
- we can film the sea creatures who live here.
- Very good.
Barnacles out. Good work, Octonauts. Let's head back.
CAPTAIN BARNACLES WHISTLES
CLATTER
What's that sound?
Nothing, I guess.
BARNACLES RESUMES WHISTLING
CLATTER
HE RESUMES WHISTLING
That sound is coming from outside the GUP.
Is anybody out there?
Nobody but those tiny, skinny black fishes.
The GUP probably just needs a check up, Captain.
We'll be home soon and then you can take a look.
Have some food.
Thanks, Tunip. These fish biscuits are delicious.
- Fascinating.
- Brrrp!
How many sea stars are travelling together in this group? Let's see.
There's one, two... Huh?
I...
Come back! Captain!
- Something's wrong with the Octo-cam.
- Let me see what I can do.
It's not working.
Hm, that's strange. The Octo-cam was working perfectly when we left.
Cap, can you come down here?
There's something you've got to see to believe.
Check out these three perfectly round holes in the GUP.
What could have made those holes?
Not what, Captain - who? Look at this.
A whole set of teeth...
..Strong enough to take a bite out of the GUP.
Hm, first our GUP was damaged and now the Octo-cam isn't working.
This smells fishy. Tweak, sound the Octo-alert.
- SIREN
- Octonauts, to the launch bay!
There's something wrong with the Octo-cam.
We've got to get back there.
I'll have those holes in the GUP-A fixed faster than you can say,
"bunch of munchy-crunchy carrots!"
Thanks. See if you can work out whose teeth these are
- while we check on the Octo-cam.
- All right.
What kind of animal would leave their teeth behind like that?
Don't worry, I'll get to the tooth - I mean truth!
CHUCKLES
This is a mystery and we've got to solve it.
Kwazii, Peso, into the GUP with me.
It's not working all right.
Not beeping or whirring or nothing.
And here's why - three holes in the rubber cable.
just like the holes in the GUP.
Three more holes here.
And here.
- Who's biting our equipment?
- Hm.
Captain, Kwazii, I've found another set of teeth.
Where?
Argh! They were here just a second ago.
Look!
It's gone.
There's nothing around but those skinny little fish.
It's like someone's playing tricks on us and then disappearing.
Who would do that?
I know, but I wish I didn't.
It is none other than the tri-toothed terror!
Who-toothed-what-er!
The tri-toothed terror - a giant sea monster
with three huge sharp teeth. He sneaks up on pirate ships,
bites them with his enormous teeth, then disappears into thin air!
You think the tri-toothed terror could be around here, following us?
I don't think we're dealing with the tri-toothed terror.
If it isn't the tri-toothed terror that made these holes, what was it?
Hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Where's that coming from?
It's a blue whale.
Maybe he's seen something that could help us work this out.
Hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
- Excuse me, but...
- Hoo-hoo-ha-ha!
What's so funny? Is my eye patch crooked?
Something's tickling my blubber, but I can't tell what.
wish it would stop now. Hoo-hoo-hoo!
Can you help me? It's down by my tail.
Ah, we've seen these marks before.
It's under my chin now!
- Hmm!
- That scurvy tri-toothed terror must be nearby, but where?
Hoo-hoo! I've got to get out of here!
- Hold on to me!
- OTHERS: Whoa!
Ha-ha-ha!
Ooh!
Whoa! That was a wild ride!
- I wish I knew who was tickling me.
- I think the creature who gave you the giggles
is the same one giving us trouble.
It left more of them tiny round marks in your blubber.
Don't worry. the Octonauts will find the troublemaker and stop him.
Ah. No, too big. Too small. Too thin. No, no, no. Wait a minute!
There, that's it.
'Captain, I know whose teeth these are.'
- Great work.
- 'They're called cookiecutter sharks.
'They dig their teeth into a whale's blubber and leave round holes,
'the way a cookiecutter leaves a shape in dough or pastry.'
They went after the blue whale as they wanted a bite of his blubber.
Why did the wee sharks attack the Octo-cam cables?
'They get confused and mistake soft material like rubber for blubber.'
- Rubber...
- ..For blubber!
We've got to ask them to stop biting our equipment.
First we need to catch these rubber, blubber lovers
and I have an idea.
Barnacles to Tweak. We're going to need your help.
FISH SCREECH
Hey, Cap, you ordered a big rubber whale balloon?
Thanks, Tweak. Let's set it up near the Octo-cam - then everybody hide.
- KWAZII SNORES
- Eh?
FAINT SQUEAKING
POP!
SHARKS: Hey-ho. Go!
Stop right there, you nasty nibblers!
SHARKS: Whoa!
We've got you now.
Caught us! I'm innocent! I wasn't even there!
You took bites out of our equipment and broke it.
Oh, that. Look, we're cookiecutter sharks.
We thought your equipment was food so we took a nibble. Sorry.
- Yes, sorry!
- Sorry about that. Sorry!
PESO: But how did you keep hiding from us?
Uh... Oh...
Yeow! Clamming up, are you?
OK, OK, we'll show you how we do it.
Your bellies glow, so when we're looking at them from below
they blend in with the sunlight.
And all you see are those black marks
that make them look like skinny fish.
So that's why nobody can see you from below.
- We can't fool you anymore.
- No, absolutely no fooling you at all!
Why did you leave your teeth in our GUP? Don't you need them?
Our teeth come out in whole rows like that...
..And grow back really quickly.
PESO: What about the teeth that disappeared?
I put them down and they were gone.
- The teeth disappeared because I ate them.
- You ate your own teeth?
That doesn't sound healthy.
It is if you're a cookiecutter shark.
Our teeth have lots of vitamins in them.
So the mystery is solved,
but could you please stop nibbling on our equipment?
OK, OK, but we'd really like a snack about now.
Oh, yes. We're really hungry.
I've got an idea for that.
Brrp!
CHOMP
This fish biscuit is way better than rubber!
Absolutely!
He's not wrong!
CHOMP CHOMP
See, Tunip, nobody can resist a bite of your fish biscuits.
GIGGLES
I'm a bit partial meself!
You're not the only one!
Brrrp!
ALL LAUGH
Have you got another?
Subtitles by Shaun Hadnett Red Bee Media Ltd
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk