We came as soon
as we got your message.
- What's the problem?
- There's something you both need to see.
Almost had me that time, Conner.
You deserve a reward.
Season 1, episode 21
“Image”
- Dinah!
- Freeze playback!
That never happened!
You need to keep watching.
Play!
Freeze playback.
Don't you laugh!
She and...
He and...
Oliver, this is not funny!
No... no,
of course not.
Please, understand.
On Mars,
this is a common game.
My people, all shape-shift.
But also read minds.
So, no one is ever mislead.
And I am certain Conner knew
he was with M'gann from the very first.
We are not on Mars,
J'onn!
No...
But my niece does not understand
things are different on Earth.
Then I'll make her understand.
Hello, Megan!
M'gann!
Just a sec!
Uh... OK.
Come in!
So, you can see that,
among humans,
that game could be
very hurtful.
I'm sorry...
I'm really sorry!
I'm not upset...
...anymore!
But please, M'gann,
from now on,
just be yourself.
This IS myself!
This IS who I am.
Robin, Kid Flash,
Superboy, Miss Martian.
Report for mission briefing.
Rumaan Harjavti is the democratically
elected President of Qurac.
Harjavti has been praised
as a fair, wise leader.
A humanitarian.
Sure, any friend of Bruce Wayne's...
But five days ago...
Harjavti allied himself with the dictator
of the neighboring nation of Bialya.
Queen Bee.
- Not a fan.
- Few are.
But Harjavti suddenly backs
Queen Bee's baseless claim
that Qurac and Bialya
were one nation in ancient times.
And has announced
the countries will reunify
in two days
at a ceremony in Qurac.
After the ceremony,
I will step down as President
so that our rightful monarch,
Queen Bee, may rule.
I laud president Harjavti
for unifying our peoples
and I will gladly come to Qurac
to be crowned
sole leader of our nation.
And the Quracies are OK with this?
Hardly.
They're well aware of the brutality
of Queen Bee's regime
But Harjavti has censored the press,
silenced all legitimate protesting
and invited the Bialyan military
into his country,
to enforce Martial Law.
Queen Bee
has to be controlling Harjavti.
Doesn't she have the power
to enthrall most men?
And some women.
But not long distanced.
And we have confirmation
she hasn't left Bialya.
Something else is at work here.
Find out what.
Robin, you're team leader.
Promotion! Sweet!
Me?
What about Aqualad?
Busy helping Aquaman.
You're the next logical choice.
- Great...
- Dude! You totally left me hanging!
We're right above
the Quraci-Bialyan border.
A border the Bialyans
are in the process of ignoring.
No opposition.
I guess Harjavti really is in bed with Bialya.
I wouldn't expect opposition here.
It's an animal sanctuary.
The Logan Animal Sanctuary?
You've heard of it?
Guys...
Tanks have caused a stampede.
The civilians in herd's way!
I see them.
A woman and a small boy.
- We have to help them!
- We're way off mission here!
Deploy.
But stealth mode!
If the Bialyans know we've hit them,
this becomes an international incident.
Oryx!
- Wow!
- Are you both alright?
Mom.
Mom! Mom!
We were just saved by Robin.
And Kid Flash!
Course, Superboy and Miss Martian
helped too!
Oryx!
We diverted the Bialyans
around the sanctuary.
You should be safe now.
Uh... yeah!
Coast has cleared, Miss M.!
You can decamo now.
H-hi!
You may have made things worse.
Bialyan border-crossings
are a way of life here.
Usually, they wreck a few fences
and move on.
Engaging them
might have made us a target.
Mom...
Uncool!
I'm sorry...
I should thank you.
This is my son, Garfield.
- I'm...
- Marie Logan!
I can't believe I'm actually
meeting you in person!
I've... I've admired your stands
on animal rights for years.
You've only been on Earth
six months!
The oryx is sick.
And I think you injured this wildebeest.
Uh... sorry?
I suppose it was unavoidable.
But both need to go
to our clinic.
The boys can do that!
You and I can...
- Fix your fences!
- That's not exactly our...
- Robin...
- Please, Mom!
- Fine.
- Yes!
Hey, get it off!
It's OK...
Meet Monkey!
Good name!
But I hate monkeys.
Looks like Monkey hates Superboys.
Dude, be glad
he only threw a proteine bar.
So... Pretty weird about
Miss Martian and my mom, huh?
- What do you mean?
- I mean she looks exactly like Marie.
- You know, except greener.
- She does?
Well, duh!
Especially back when Mom was a TV star
in "Hello, Megan!"
Wait...
"Hello, Megan!" is a TV show?
I just thought it was
something she says all the time.
Yeah...
On the TV show!
Way before we were born.
Only one season!
You can't even find it online.
I know Mom has a tape somewhere...
Well, you're certainly a time-saver.
How was it?
Being Megan?
"Being Megan"?
I don't know, I was young.
It was fun.
Remember that time when you were
supposed to make cookies for the big sale
only you thought it would be faster
to make one giant cookie and...
Listen!
"Hello, Megan!" was a job.
The person you saw on TV
isn't who I am.
"Hello, Megan!"
The pilot episode.
Wow!
You still have VHS!
Where is your 8-track?
Wait!
Aircraft!
Headed this way.
Gar!
Stay put.
What is it?
- Where is my son?
- I ordered him to stay inside.
He's eight!
He doesn't do "orders"!
Mom!
It's OK,
I got the animals out!
Garfield!
I told you
there'd be consequences!
Always!
Let's get him inside.
He's in shock.
He needs a blood transfusion,
now.
Is either of you O negative?
No, I'm sorry.
Neither am I.
It's the hardest to match.
I've kept a supply in the clinic...
I can run into the nearest hospital...
The nearest hospital with
this type of blood supply,
half an hour away,
at your top speed.
Longer, by Bio-Ship!
He doesn't have that much time!
What's Superboy's blood type?
He's Kryptonian.
- And Miss Martian...
- Might be able to help.
My shape-shifting occurs
at the cellular level.
I think I can modify blood
to match his.
Please, try!
I'll need to concentrate.
No distractions.
Out!
All of you, out!
I'm ready.
And on top of all this,
Harjavti steps down tomorrow.
Subjecting all of Qurac to this danger.
KF, can you find a news station?
Sure.
Which remote is it?
~Hello, Megan!~
~School and boys and parents too,~
~A whole lot to juggle
from Miss You-Know-Who~
~Hello, Megan~
~Hello, Megan!~
~This cheerleader knows the score,~
~Center of attention
and so much more,~
~Hello, Megan,~
~Hello, Megan...~
~A little bit distractable,
but never too ***~
~She's really quite attractable,
OK, a lot distractable,~
~Eventually, she'll get a ***~
~Hello, Megan!~
~The girl for me,
The girl for you...~
~Hello, Megan,~
~Hello, Megan!~
~The girl for me,
The girl for you,~
Maybe it's a coincidence.
~Hello, Megan!~
Mom, I'm going to the library,
to study!
But didn't you invite a certain someone
"to study"...?
...Here?
Hello, Megan!
Conner!
I thought
you'd never get here!
Oh, yeah,
"pure coincidence"...
It's done.
All we can do now is wait.
My fellow Quracians,
Is that Harjavti?
Queen Bee's rule
is a gift to Qurac
Hey, that guy in back!
I know him!
It's Psimon! The psychic we fought
last time we were in Bialya!
He was working
for Queen Bee then,
he must be controlling Harjavti
for her now!
I still remember the headache
from when he brain-blasted us.
We have to get Harjavti
away from him.
I think it worked.
Garfield is stable.
Good.
Because, we have our mission.
Harjavti is alone.
Where's my daughter?
- Where is Psimon?
- Forget him.
Let's get you out of here.
Well, well...
American heroes...
Here, to assasinate the President.
Such a shame
we arrived too late to stop them...
Those are Apokoliptian weapons.
Which they'll use to kill Harjavti,
we get cleaned
and Queen Bee gets to rule Qurac!
Full roundup around the President!
I found Psimon!
- Wait!
- I'll get her!
No!
The mission is Harjavti.
Indeed, it is...
Am I the only one to learn anything
from our previous encounter?
You didn't think that,
maybe,
if you could sense me,
I could sense you too?
Or that this time I'll be ready
to use your greatest fear against you?
"Psimon says..."
Show me who...
or rather what you really are...
No, no, no!
This IS who I am!
Thank you for saving my father.
We will take care of him now.
M'gann, we're coming!
"Psimon says",
smartly done!
Brain-blasting your own team...
I had no idea
you'd go to such lengths
to hide your true self
from your good friends.
Oh, actually, I did.
But you needn't have bothered.
It's been recorded for posterity.
No...!
Uh-ah-ah!
I didn't say,
"Psimon says!"
Come, now...
We both know
that's not who you really are...
Must you even lie to yourself,
whithin your own mind?
It's not a lie!
This IS who I am!
Wow...
And they say I'm pathological...
Off our game, are we ?
Let's take it a little deeper,
find out what we're really afraid of.
Keep back!
Well, of course...
Friends and teammates
shrink from you in fear.
You should have told us
the truth.
I don't see
how we could trust you now.
Then you're kept off the pep squad.
I am sorry, M'gann.
But there is no place for you
on Earth now.
Oh, there is none on Mars too!
And even that's not the worst,
is it?
No, please...
stop!
"Love you"?
I can't even look at you!
Oh, what you wouldn't do
to prevent that, now right?
That's right...
Now, now, my pretty...
I know you don't want to do
anything you'll regret...
You don't know me at all!
Conner?
Are you OK?
And there's the headache...
Psimon...?
He brain-blasted you.
I stopped him.
What do you mean,
"The President won't see me"?
He invited me!
Not of my free will!
No!
But now, that I am free,
of your minion's thrall,
the Quraci people
will never suffer
your tyrannical rule!
Mark me, Harjavti!
You will suffer for this!
Qurac will be mine!
Sorry you had to lie everyone
like that.
But I couldn't think of any other way
to convince the public
Queen Bee was behind this.
Dude...
Saving a country...
Pretty big way for your first turn
as "leader"...
Yeah...
Thanks.
And, I assure you,
The Wayne Foundation is here
to do whatever it can
to help you and your people
rebuild Qurac.
Gee,
Bruce Wayne surely got here fast.
Almost like he knew...
Don't you have a souvenir to collect,
or something?
"Hello, Megan!"
Something you'd like to tell us?
Growing up on Mars was...
Not a happy time for me.
But I started watching the broadcast
my uncle sent from Earth...
To teach us about our sister planet...
When I saw "Hello, Megan!"...
Something just...clicked.
Maybe it was
the similaties in our names...
Maybe it was the way all Megan's
problems could be solved in 22 minutes.
All I know for sure is...
That Megan helped me smile
through a lonely childhood.
So, when I came to Earth...
And had to adopt a human form...
I chose you.
Well...
Megan.
Which begs the question...
What do you really look like?
Bald M'gann...
Still hot!
You know, you don't have to
put on the mask for me.
I do it for me.
This is who I am.
Inside.
Please, don't be mad.
Mad?
I'm honored.
M'gann, you saved my son.
He says he's you blood-brother now.
And I agree.
You're family!
Thank you!
You can't know what that means to me.
Garfield?
Shh! It would be a shame
to wake him.
I might have to order
my little thrall here
to damage himself.
Uh-uh! He already has orders
to do just that
if anything happens to me.
Now...
Your performance...
A bit over the top,
I think,
but then,
you haven't practised me
the way you've perfected
the role of "Megan".
That's right...
Poor Psimon
is not the only one
who knows your true from.
And, if you don't cooperate,
I'll make sure
everyone knows
what you really are.
www.tvsubtitles.net