[DFC Guangzhou]
[Campaign For A Better Environment]
[Four Steps of DFC]
[Social problems we care about]
[Situations we wanna change]
[Wishes we wanna fulfill]
[...]
[How we can make it?]
[We have 7 days to act]
[Share our story with those around us]
Going into our community
Discovering the problems around us
Too much trash and not enough trash cans
Tree branches grew into people's balconies
Discussing the problems with the directors
Finding the problems we wanna solve the most
"Why do you want to solve it?"
"Who are bothered by these problems?"
"How to deal with the excessive amount of trash?"
"Recycling is a good solution."
"How to raise public awareness?"
"Putting posters on trash cans would work."
"And we can use bigger posters elsewhere."
"How about through board games like poker?"
Designing a computer game
"environmentalists' battle"
Making promotional cards
Designing poker games for promotion
Finding promotional materials from the recycling centers
[Campaign Day]
Preparing for our campaign
Putting up posters
Pingpong waste sorting game
Promotional cards we made
Poster for "environmentalists' battle"
Ready to start the game
Lots of kids came to play our games
Trash should be properly sorted
And then put into different baskets
We have presents for all participating children
Handing out promotional poker cards
Teaching foreigners to read out the words
Sharing what we've learned in our campaign
Children sharing after the campaign
"We all need to protect our environment."
"We'll keep spreading the message."
[DFC Guangzhou]