Deep fried shrimp,
and lobster.
I never had lobster.
What? They boil 'em
or grill 'em?
Which one's better?
Ah, just get 'em both.
And I know I need
a strawberry malt.
And then there's those chocolate
donuts, they come in a box?
(warden)
We'll do our best
to accommodate.
Tomorrow you'll be moved
to a holding cell.
That's where you'll get
your last meal.
You also have the
Constitutional right
to a spiritual advisor
of your choice.
No, I don't need
none of that.
One last thing
to think about.
(warden)
After I read
the execution warrant,
you'll be given an opportunity
to make a statement.
Might wanna take some time
and think about what you wanna
say as your final words.
(prisoner)
Yo, Clarence?
You hear that?
A spiritual advisor
of my choice?
Don't matter.
You're going to hell anyway.
You think I'll get
another stay?
You should.
Supreme Court says it ain't
right to kill retards.
(guard)
Cut the chatter.
Exercise time.
Be back in an hour.
(guard)
Enjoy.
Why did you hit me
so many times, Clarence?
You know why.
You could've stopped.
You stabbed me
in the back, man.
I never...
You couldn't fight fair?
Like you did!
I had a wife
and three kids.
You are a sick bastard!
Open the door!
Open the door.
Hey!
What did I ever
do to you, man?
(man)
How old are you, son?
I was just minding
my own business.
How could you do me
like that?
I'm your brother.
I never did you.
You can't go in there.
Who are you?
And why are you wearing a tie?
I'm Dr. Cuddy's new assistant.
Can I tell her
what it's regarding?
Yes, I would like to know
why she gets a secretary
and I don't.
I'm her assistant,
not her secretary.
I graduated
from Rutgers.
Hmm, I didn't know
they had a secretarial school.
Well, I hope you
took some classes
in Sexual Harassment Law.
Does the word ka-ching,
mean anything to you?
I'm going in now.
Dr. House, we are in
the middle of a meeting.
What's with hiring
a male secretary?
JDate not working out?
He is cute.
Be careful.
She's not like you.
She can't just walk
into a bar
and pick up her soul mate
in 20 minutes.
I met Mark at a fund-raiser
that happened to be held at--
You met me
at a strip club.
You are the worst
two dollars I ever spent.
We'll catch up later.
Stacy, it's House.
I know you can handle it.
Nothing to handle.
He obviously
wants to talk to you alone.
If you have a problem working
with Stacy,
you should've said so.
What was I supposed to do?
Ask her to leave?
That's just rude.
Death-row guy.
I want the case.
How do you even
know about him?
You don't have access
to the hospital's main frame.
No, but "PartyPants" does.
You stole my password?
Hardly counts as stealing.
Pretty obvious choice.
Well, I have already assigned
"death-row guy" to Dr. Nolo.
Nolo?
Well, I--
I don't wanna say anything bad
about another doctor.
Especially a useless drunk.
You are addicted to pain pills.
But I'm not useless.
Tell Nolo I'm taking over.
Dr. Nolo is a board
certified cardiologist.
Well, good, I'm sure he'll
explore all the usual options
for why a guy's heart
starts beating so fast
it pumps out air
instead of blood.
Wait a second,
there are no usual options.
How badly do you want this?
I will give you two more
clinic hours this week.
Don't bend over for the soap.
Just the heart, or the patient
have any other complaints?
Patient's not talking
to anybody.
Where are we going?
You are going to the clinic
for two hours.
Me? Why?
Talk to Cuddy.
She's got me going
to Mercer State Prison,
Capital Sentences Unit.
I don't know.
Aren't there better ways
to spend our time?
Good question.
What makes a person deserving?
Is a man who cheats on his wife
more deserving than a man
who kills his wife?
Uh, yeah, actually.
He is.
What about a child molester?
Certainly not a good guy,
but he didn't kill anybody.
Maybe he can get
antibiotics, but no MRIs.
What about you?
What medical care should you be
denied for being a car thief?
Tell you what, the three
of you work on a list.
What medical treatments
a person loses
based on the crime
they committed?
I'll review it
when I get back.
Your patient shanked one inmate
his first month here.
Broke another one's neck,
nearly decapitated
one of my guards.
Relax, I got a great
bedside manner.
(Warden)
Too dangerous to house him
in the infirmary.
You don't have to worry.
We've taken every precaution.
I had my men clear
from the cell
all pens paper clips
and staplers.
(Warden)
Any supplies that might
be used as a weapon.
(Warden)
Open her up!
For your visit, we've got him
cuffed and shackled.
And yet,
you're staying out there.
Uh, you're gonna have
to give me that.
Wouldn't want anybody
to get hurt.
Hi, I'm Dr. Cameron.
Hi.
How you feeling?
A little cough.
No big deal.
Okay, then what
are you doing here?
I just got a job
at the University.
They need a health clearance.
Apparently,
I'm a little anemic,
so they made me get
some more tests.
Any family history
of anemia?
Not that I know of.
My mom died of cancer
when I was a kid.
My dad's heart gave out
a couple of years ago.
Brothers and sisters?
I'm afraid it's
a short family history.
That's it.
I had a husband once.
But it didn't stick.
My tests should be back.
Probably in that file.
Probably.
Is everything okay?
Did you redo the x-ray?
Twice.
Well, you don't need
a consult.
You know the diagnosis.
All she has is a cough.
Bluish tinge
to the fingernails, lips.
He's hypoxic.
What's that mean?
It means he's not getting
enough oxygen.
You know how people say
you can't live without love?
Well, oxygen's
even more important.
He's got fluid
in his lungs.
Breathing rate of 50.
He needs to be incubated
and put on a respirator.
Don't have a respirator.
Well, you better get one
in about an hour
or you're gonna lose him.
I'll make out a requisition.
State's already sentenced
this man to die.
I think the State was a tad more
specific about how.
This is Dr. Gregory House.
I need an ambulance to pick up
at Mercer State Prison.
Wasted call, my men
will stop them at the gate.
No way a death row inmate
leaves my prison.
At least not
through the front doors.
You work fast.
So do you.
Is that a shot?
Yeah.
It was easy.
Once I convinced the clerk
to take it to Judge Markham,
she's a sucker for
Eighth Amendment arguments.
Stop, I'm getting turned on.
House!
[as Scooby Doo]
Ruh-roh.
It was just a consult.
You expect us to shut down
an entire floor for this guy?
You do something
to your hair?
Stacy?
You said you
cleared it with her.
Come on,
you know me how long?
Still can't tell
when I'm joshing you?
(Cuddy)
Take him back to prison.
Now.
No, can't.
See, ironically, I'm bound
by this court order
that your ace attorney got.
Have to make him all better
before shipping him back
for the state to kill him.
Is it just me,
or is that weird?
Anyway, we're walking.
Somebody left this
on my chair.
It's clever 'cause it forces me
to either deal with the file,
or never sit down again.
Cindy Kramer.
I told her you'd see her.
You shouldn't have
told her that.
She's got metastatic squamous
cell lung cancer.
Six months tops.
Have you even looked
at the x-ray?
No. Just guessing.
It's a new game.
If I'm wrong,
she wins a stuffed bear.
A spot on an x-ray doesn't
necessarily mean
that she's terminal.
I love children.
So filled with hope.
It could be pneumonia.
It could be sarcoidosis.
Could be if she didn't already
have swollen hilar lymph nodes
on the other lung.
Could we at least brainstorm
for other ideas?
Thank you.
I still think pneumonia
and sarcoidosis.
But we should check
for tuberculosis
and definitely rule out
congestive heart failure.
The five stages of dying.
Exactly.
Personally, I think
it's all just new age crap,
but from your tear-filled,
puppy-dog eyes,
I think I made my point.
Now go tell Cindy
whatever-her-name-is
that she's dying.
Tachycardia, pulmonary edema.
Likely suspects?
The death-row guy?
That's who you're working on
instead of Cindy?
God, I've got to learn
not to beat around the bush.
By dying, I meant,
no matter what we do,
very, very soon
she's going to be dead.
That's still too subtle?
I took an oath
to do no harm.
Yeah, well it's not like they
make you sign it or anything.
We cure your patient,
he goes back to death row.
He goes back to death row,
they kill him.
And he stays here
and we don't treat him, he dies.
And I still don't treat
Cindy Lou Who.
Can we get on with this?
Yeah, I knew I could count
on your help for your homie.
Exactly, I'm black.
I sympathize with guys who grew
up in the inner city
kept down by the man.
Makes sense to me.
(Foreman)
It's a bunch of crap.
You can't blame society
for the fact
that you chose
to become a killer.
(Foreman)
The guy's probably
a heroin addict.
Explains the tachycardia which
caused the pulmonary edema.
How's an inmate on death row
get his hands on heroin?
[scoffs]
Are you serious?
(House)
The man knows prisons.
When we got a yachting question,
we'll come to you.
(House)
Okay, drugs it is.
Let's test his hair,
blood, urine, the works.
Thanks for
getting my back.
Thought you seminary boys
were against the death penalty.
I left the seminary.
Over their stance
on capital punishment?
I'm against the death
penalty in principle.
In practice, however,
watching a murderer die,
causes me a lot less grief
than annoying my boss.
I gotta pat you down
before you go in.
(Cameron)
Justice statistics show
it's a racially motivated
from of punishment.
Black defendants are
ten times more likely
to get a death sentence
than whites.
Doesn't mean we need
to get rid of the death penalty,
just means we need to kill
more white people.
(Foreman)
It's okay,
you're in a hospital.
We're taking care of you.
(Chase)
Stay calm, you hear me?
Push 2 milligrams Ativan!
Water.
What's the differential
for being thirsty?
He was just a little
dehydrated.
And out of his mind.
We upped his saline drip.
He's fine now.
Blood and urine tests
came back clean,
no sign of opiates
in his system.
Don't do that.
What, you have some House theory
explaining heroin use
despite the negative tests?
Nope.
Only I get to write
on the board.
So it's not drugs.
What else can cause
a heart to do wind sprints?
Got the blood work back.
Any...
...thing out of the ordinary?
His bi-carb is low.
Yeah, but which column?
Could be a result
of the tachycardia.
(House)
Could be the cause.
It's the cause.
Why, because you
want it to be?
Let's see how well that works
with your other patient.
We're just talking
semantics here.
(Cameron)
We should put him on a bi-carb
drip and send him back.
Right, buff his numbers.
Don't bother trying to figure
out the underlying cause.
(House)
I thought you cared
about patients.
(Foreman)
Our job is to make sure
he can bounce his
grandkids on his lap.
Our job is to get him
healthy enough
to go back to death row.
(House)
Our job is to diagnose him.
What?
Mommy and daddy are having
a little fight.
It doesn't mean
we've stopped loving you.
(House)
Now go outside and play.
Get daddy some smokes
and an arterial blood gas test.
Wow.
That was impressive.
Okay, what number
am I thinking of?
Are you trying
to get me fired?
If you didn't want
me working here,
why didn't you just say so?
I just don't want you working
right here, in my office.
But anywhere else
in the building is fine.
It's a really big hospital.
I'm a lawyer, you're a jerk.
There's gonna
be some overlap.
God, I hope that was
a euphemism.
Cuddy just reamed me.
I hope that one means
what I think it means.
For trusting you.
She figured when she hired me
she'd at least have someone
you couldn't walk all over.
The number was six
by the way.
I need to know,
can I trust you?
If I hadn't lied to you about
Cuddy's approval,
my patient would be dead.
Great.
Now I know.
Now we can work together.
I'm drawing some blood
from your femoral artery.
From my what?
Runs through your groin.
You think you're gonna stick me
in the jewels with that?
It's really close
to your thigh.
Technically, at this point,
it seems like your jewels are
more for display
purposes anyway.
Hold up, hold up, give me some
painkillers or something.
Tough guy like you
don't need 'em.
Forget that.
Numb me up, man.
You got some gang ink?
Let me see that.
It's a Native American symbol.
It means the force of life.
That's what you tell
all these white dudes
so they let you play doctor?
Yep, got 'em all fooled.
For real, how a brother like you
go from gang bangin'
into wearing that white coat?
How's a brother like you
go from loving a woman
to punching her skull in?
Bitch stepped out.
(Foreman)
Sorry about that.
Guess I didn't use
enough lidocaine.
Blood gas came back
with a pH of 7.28
and decreased HCO3.
Which means two things.
Most importantly,
Cameron was wrong
about the bi-carb.
And less significantly,
we have a new symptom.
Anion gap acidosis.
Who's chubby?
Come on,
pretend he loves puppies.
Pretend he's a human being.
What do ya got?
I think we should
reconsider drugs.
He already tested negative.
That's why I said
"reconsider."
Back in juvie,
I cut up oregano
and sold it as pot.
Is that how you put yourself
through med school?
What if Clarence thought
he was taking heroin,
but it was something else?
What something else could lead
to anion gap acidosis?
MUDPILES.
You don't have to ask,
just wash your hands before
you come back.
Methanol, Uremia, Diabetes...
Oh, it's a mnemonic.
That makes sense too.
Paraldehyde, INH,
Lactic acid--
Rewind.
INH?
Yahtzee.
Drugs for tuberculosis.
Nearly a quarter of the prison
population in infected with TB.
Clever entrepreneur
like Foreman here,
chops up his meds
passes it off as heroin.
INH poisoning would explain
all the symptoms.
Who wants to head over
to the prison
and find Clarence's
secret stash?
Fine. I'll do it.
Great.
Chase it is.
I assume you have a reason
beyond wanting
to make me
completely miserable?
You got a prettier mouth.
Better chance the inmates
will open up to you.
(man)
Perhaps I'll come out
looking just as monstrous.
I mean, isn't that
what I deserve?
John, it wasn't your fault.
If your father hadn't
slipped you those drugs,
you'd have never done
what you did.
I still might do.
The man's in a coma.
He didn't mind.
I asked.
You're getting crumbs
all over him.
Why do you think
they put TVs
in coma patients'
rooms anyway?
Some people think
they can still hear.
So leave 'em a radio.
His eyes are closed.
Who thinks they can see?
Do you know why people
are nice to other people?
Oh, I know this one.
Um, because people are good,
decent and caring.
Either that or
people are cowards.
If I'm mean to you,
then you'll be mean to me.
Mutually assured destruction.
Exactly.
You gonna eat these chips?
You gonna get
to your point?
You need people
to like you.
I don't care
if people like me.
Yes, but you need people
to like you
because you need people.
Unless you think you can get
the next court order yourself.
If Stacy can't trust you,
you can't use her.
And that's not even dealing
with the greater agenda
of getting her
to dump her husband
and fall in love with you
all over again.
I know you're friends with her,
but there is a code.
Bros before hoes, man.
Crap.
What is it?
Death-row guy is dying.
Bradycardia. His heart rate's
dropped to 30.
He's not gonna hold
on much longer.
You just waiting
to call time of death,
or are you gonna
give him atropine?
(Foreman)
Temporary fix.
Right.
I don't know why those diabetics
are hung up on insulin,
they're just gonna
have to take more.
Atropine's only gonna
buy you a few hours.
We don't even know
what's wrong with him.
Just get out of here.
This is Chase.
Did you beat any confessions
out of anybody?
I haven't spoken
to any inmates.
Does anybody do
their jobs anymore?
Decided Clarence's life
isn't worth risking mine for.
I appreciate your candor.
Did you even go to the prison
or are you just
out playing polo?
I'm searching
both Clarence's cells.
I figured if he's on something,
it's stashed somewhere.
Unless he finished it.
[laughs]
Yeah, that'd be a shame.
He could've shoved it anywhere.
There's envelopes
staked to the ceiling,
bottles of copier toner,
boxes of rubber bands,
tons of paper,
files, folders, the works.
Call it off.
(House)
Come on back.
[weakly]
What's going on?
You're dying.
A man deserves a last drink.
You're okay.
Thanks.
That means a lot.
All the tests
have been inconclusive?
Diagnostics is more
of an art than a science.
Should I be
worried right now?
I work for one of the top
diagnosticians in the country.
We're pouring all of our energy
into figuring this out.
I thought you convicts
knew how to drink.
You're at least three
shots behind.
Now you're four shots behind.
You better get me the next one
or I'm gonna kill you.
House?
I was just waiting
for test results--
Little busy right now.
Getting my drink on.
Unbelievable.
(Clarence)
Oof!
That's the finest piece
I've seen in ten years.
I coulda hit that.
And you didn't?
Eh.
Man, you're the one
who should be locked up.
Tell me something.
I've been trying
to figure this out.
Why does a guy
who's on death row
suddenly try to off himself?
I know you drank
that copier fluid.
It's not as visually
dramatic
as slitting your wrists
with a homemade shiv,
but it'll do the trick.
It just hit me all of a sudden.
It was like they tell me
when to eat,
when to sleep, when to walk,
when to talk,
everything.
I had to take control
of something, right?
When to die.
I figured that was
as good as anything.
And that thought
just came to you?
Just like that?
Man, I told you,
23 hours of--
[slurping]
Aaah.
Well, look,
here's the good news.
The copier fluid you drank
contains about 90% methanol,
which is very poisonous,
and you took more than enough
to kill yourself.
The bad news is,
the alcohol you just drank,
contains so much ethanol,
that it's gonna bind
that nasty formic acid
rampaging through your body.
And you're just
gonna pee it out...
harmlessly.
Man, you are drunk.
Yes, I am.
I also saved your life.
Shee-ya.
At least for now.
Morning!
Your head hurt?
No, you just have a very
grating voice.
You always were
a lightweight.
Why are you talking to me?
Can it be enough
that I want to cause you pain?
The patient is okay.
Now you're gonna
send him back.
Absolutely.
Can I trust you?
You used to.
I still think the patient is
sick and I'm keeping him here.
Now either you
can do your job
and keep the hospital informed,
or you can help me make sure
the hospital is not informed
and buy me some time.
[bell dings]
(Chase)
Have you done a C.T.?
Yeah, I have.
With contrast?
She's done everything
she needs to do
except tell her patient
that she's dying.
I told you, only I get
to play with the markers.
Our prisoner,
has a new symptom.
I'm not telling Cindy
she's dying
until the diagnosis
is confirmed.
I'm not buying that Clarence
was trying to take
control of his
life by suicide.
Healthy people don't
kill themselves.
kill other people.
The guy just filed
an appeal in a state
that hasn't actually killed
anybody in about 30 years.
What if it wasn't suicide?
(Chase)
What if it was
an escape plan?
Drink enough methanol to get
transferred to a hospital,
try to escape from here?
Excellent.
Explains everything except
the symptom that got him here.
His heart went nuts
before he got stuck
in that storage cell
and chugged a toner martini.
I think there's something
going on in his head.
Check for intracranial lesions,
brain infections,
auto-immune diseases.
Do a CT, LP,
full work up.
State's paying,
so go nuts.
(Foreman)
Where'd you
get these scars?
I got shivved
my first month in.
After I healed up,
I got mines.
You guys still think I'm sick?
Obviously.
Why do you care?
Why don't you just
let me die?
I'm different than you.
Right.
You love me like
your own momma.
That's why the nurse says
you kicked her out
when my heart nearly stopped.
Take a deep breath.
Any family history
of mental illness?
I've always heard
my pop was crazy.
I never met the man.
With my mom, it was the drugs.
Any siblings?
I got a brother, pretty much
raised him on my own.
Inspirational story.
He doing time too?
Hey.
He's a good kid.
Don't go judging
what you don't know.
How's his health?
I never heard from him
since I went inside.
Spent 16 years with him.
Changed his damn diapers.
Can you imagine your whole
life being all about
the worst thing
you ever did?
You killed four people.
And somehow, making mac
and cheese just the way he wants
kind of loses
its significance.
Oh, no.
Now you've left your
entire body in my chair.
What does that mean you want?
I need a segmental
bronchoalveolar lavage.
I take it the CT
with contrast came back.
They're not definitive.
Biopsy would be.
A biopsy would be invasive
and unnecessary.
And definitive.
But you don't
want definitive.
You wanna hang on to your
delusions as long as you can.
A lavage could prove
it's not cancer.
But you need me to approve
the procedure.
It must be a bitch.
The answer is no.
Why? Because it's me?
I['m over you.
I've jumped on the bandwagon.
I hate you, okay?
Great.
Let's treat her.
[scoffs]
What is it?
You won't help Cindy,
but you're obsessed with
this piece of dirt!
Are you just trying to prove
that who someone
is doesn't matter?
That all that matters
is your stupid puzzle?
Fine, treat them the same.
That's all I'm asking.
One test.
Wow.
That is remarkable.
According to those patchouli-oil
selling new-agers,
it's supposed to be
the terminal patient.
But you're going through
the five stages.
You just made a completely
seamless transition
from anger to bargaining.
Cover two more
of my clinic hours,
and you can have
your one procedure.
[computer beeps]
No lesions,
no aneurisms.
Ironically, the mind of a killer
looks completely normal.
If someone asked you
to describe me to them,
what's the first thing
you'd tell 'em?
Insecure.
What are you asking?
Like if you were setting
me up on a blind date.
Would you describe me
to the girl as
the black guy,
a neurologist,
the car thief?
This guy is really
getting to you, isn't he?
There's no sign of infection.
You're gonna have
to do the biopsy.
(Cuddy)
You're death-row guy
is still here.
Yeah, sorry,
just gotta get him stabilized.
Probably keep him on fluids
for a few more hours,
then off he goes.
Oh, yeah? 'Cause I'm figuring
that you still think he's sick.
Figuring requires
deductive reasoning.
I'm figuring
that you did no figuring.
Stacy just ratted
me out, right?
So much for attorney-client
privilege.
I'm the client,
you moron.
Stacy has a duty
to this hospital.
Right.
I'm sending him
back to prison.
Whoa, can't.
Court order.
Court order says
he has to be declared healthy.
Doesn't specify which doctor
needs to make that declaration.
What is it, Clarence?
My gut!
Would you describe
it as a shooting pain,
a throbbing pain,
or maybe an imaginary pain
because you don't want
to go back to prison?
Where does it hurt?
My gut, I feel like
I'm getting stabbed!
Well, he'd know.
Let me take a look.
Oh, so everybody lies
except a convicted murderer.
I don't think
he's faking this stuff.
What do you think, doctor?
I didn't have
any choice.
No, you had to tell Cuddy.
She's your boss.
I get it.
Hitler thought he was
doing the world a favor too.
Yeah, pretty much
on that same level.
Gandhi didn't march the sea
because his buddies
asked him to.
Pol Pot didn't wipe out
the teachers
because he wanted
to make friends.
You're not making
friends right now.
I trusted you.
I know.
Wilson's a fool.
I'm an idiot.
I had to do
what I thought was right.
It's the only reason
anybody does anything.
Surgery went fine.
They removed almost a foot
of necrotic bowel.
They're shackling him
and taking him into recovery.
I wonder...
I wonder why Clarence
killed that second inmate.
Fine, I'll bite.
What the hell are
you talking about?
Everything we do
is dictated by motive.
(House)
Why did he kill
his girlfriend?
Because he's a maniac.
Is that the reason he gave?
She was cheating on him.
Jealousy.
That gets him sent
to prison
where he kills
inmate number one. Why?
Guy attacked him first.
Revenge.
Who's he kill after that?
Prison guard.
He had a file full
of abuse complaints.
Probably been kicking
Clarence's ass for months.
Clarence is just
ridding the world of bad seeds.
We'll call that one
retribution.
Then he kills
inmate number two.
Anybody know why?
Uh-uh, it's not in there.
(Clarence)
All of a sudden,
I've gotta have a reason?
It's an anomaly.
Doctors love anomalies.
Dark spot on an x-ray,
bright spot on an MRI.
Killing that second inmate
was the homicidal equivalent
of blood in the urine.
It doesn't fit.
I'm getting interested
in things that don't fit.
Tell me why you did it.
Your other victims
you were almost
bragging about.
What was different
about this guy?
It happened when
I was in gen pop.
I was in the library
just reading.
And I started feeling
real nervous.
This guy was staring at me.
I could feel his eyes digging
holes in the back of my neck.
It made me feel crazy.
Sweat was pouring
down my face.
I could hear my heartbeat
racing in my ears.
I just raged out
on the dude.
So what's the differential
for raging out?
Excess testosterone.
Steroids--
Adrenaline?
Prep Clarence for surgery.
Care to share
with the class?
Oh, come on, do I have
to spell it out for you?
Pheochromocytoma.
Actually, I'm not sure
how you spell it.
But you said it
yourself, adrenaline.
Pheochromocytoma sits on top
of the adrenal gland,
randomly spits out
oodles of the stuff.
It's perfect.
It explains everything.
The tachycardia,
pulmonary edema,
the vasoconstriction
that caused the necrotic bowel.
It even explains how
he had the strength
to rip the rail off his bed.
Pheo's extremely rare.
I love rare.
Set up an MRI.
Where's Cameron?
Like I don't know.
[both talking]
Dr. Cameron?
Can I borrow you
for a consult?
Bittersweet thing about being
head of the oncology department,
I get CCd on all
the biopsy results.
Yeah, I know.
She's terminal.
Yeah, so I take it
you were in there informing her?
Well, I--I haven't exactly
gotten around to that,
but I was just--
Doing what?
Making friends?
Cindy's divorced.
She doesn't have any kids,
no siblings,
both her parents are--
It's not your job
to be her friend.
Do you understand?
And it's not worth it.
She feels better her
final few days,
and you're not the same,
maybe for years.
You don't think
it's worth it?
I know it's not worth it.
My husband--
I met him just after
he was diagnosed
with terminal brain cancer.
If I hadn't married him,
he was alone.
When a good person dies,
there should be
an impact on the world.
Somebody should notice.
Somebody should be upset.
Pheo--what?
I don't even remember.
It's just a fancy way
of saying
small, adrenaline-secreting
tumor.
Yeah, that clarified
it for you.
All you need to know is,
if I'm right, we can fix it.
Just gotta find it first.
We need an MRI.
It's completely painless
for most people.
But not for me?
I assume you got
those tattoos in prison.
Prison tats often contain
inks with heavy metals.
The MRI is basically
a giant magnet.
It'll suck those metallic inks
right out of your skin.
[machine beeps]
[Clarence screams]
[screaming continues]
Stop squirming.
(House)
Don't make us
do this again.
Big baby.
I still don't see anything.
Turn it off!
[screams]
There's Waldo.
Found it, Clarence.
(Clarence)
Turn it off!
Turn this damn thing off!
Keep him in there
until you guys see it too.
Son of a bitch.
Looks like they got
the pheo out successfully.
So what now?
Clarence goes back
to death row.
Just like that?
He's cured.
That tumor caused
random shots of adrenaline,
which obviously led to the rage
attacks that made him
become a murderer
in the first place.
My, God, you're right.
Let's call the surgeons.
We gotta save that tumor,
put it on the witness stand.
We could testify
in Clarence's appeal.
[sniffs]
You smell that?
I think that is
the stink of hypocrisy.
You wouldn't even
consider the notion
that Clarence's social
upbringing was responsible
for what he became,
but now you're
sprinting to the witness stand
to blame everything
on a little tumor.
A person's upbringing
and their biology
are completely different.
Yeah, because you only
overcame one of them.
Let's just give Clarence
a free pass, huh?
We'll probably gonna piss off
all those other pheo sufferers
who manage to control
their "rage attacks"
and become lawyers,
or race car drivers
or even doctors.
Removing that tumor
puts a stop
to those random
shots of adrenaline.
It doesn't absolve him.
You want him to be executed?
That's not what I'm saying.
Got an opinion?
Everyone's got an opinion.
I, um...
I think I'm gonna testify
at Clarence's appeal.
You'll do what
you think is right.
On your own time.
[Jeff Buckley's Hallelujah]
* I heard there was
a secret chord *
* That David played
and it pleased the Lord *
* But you don't really care
for music do you? *
* Well it goes like this *
I--It's just a cough.
* And the major lift *
* The baffled king *
* Composing hallelujah *
* Hallelujah *
* Well your faith was strong *
* But you needed proof *
* You saw her bathing
on the roof *
* Her beauty and the moonlight *
* Overthrew you *
* As she tied you to
her kitchen chair *
* As she broke your throne
and she cut your hair *
* And from your lips *
* She drew the Hallelujah *
* Hallelujah
Hallelujah *