[ Fanfare plays ]
[ Lively music plays ]
[ Tiger roaring ]
擒虎――听起来就震慑人心
Tiger hunting --what mystery.
非凡的冒险经历
What adventure.What an experience.
人类以自身微乎其微的力量
Man pitting his puny strength
对抗老虎：
against the pent-up fury
of the tiger --
最凶残、最冷血、最狡猾的重达500磅的
500 pounds of the most vicious,cruel, merciless, sly,
卑鄙的、凶暴残忍的杀手
mean, fiendish,ferocious killer
潜入深不可测的丛林，探寻神秘黑影
-- to tread the shadowy depths of the jungle.
-- [ Gulps ]
[ Whir! Zip! ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Honk! ]
Ha-yuck!
Unh-unh !
[ Roars ]
说的不是我啦！
Mnh-mnh ! Not me!
Wow!
[ Clank! ]
[ Zip! Boom ! ]
[ Up-tempo jazz music plays ]
我们在蒸蒸日上的富饶的丛林里慢慢行进着
Steadily we move toward the steaming, teeming jungle,
这里至今还未有一人安全通过过
where the hand of man has never set foot.
[ Tap! ]
[ Tap! Tap! ]
[ Tap! Tap! Tap! ]
[ Stre-e-e-e-tch ! ]
[ Whistle! Bong ! ]
[ Creak! ]
开----饭！
[ Trumpeting ] Lu-u-u-u-nch !
[ Rattling ]
[ Clink! Clank! ]
[ Thud ! ]
[ Zoo-o-o-o-o-p! ]
走到一块空地，我们停下来，准备吃些东西补充体力
Upon reaching a clearing, we pause for rest and refreshment
为我们的狩猎提供物质保障
before pursuing our hazardous quest.
[ Slow jazz music plays ]
这是老虎的领地――
Tiger country --
每一棵树的后面都有可能潜伏着未知的危险
unseen danger lurking behind every tree,
令人毛孔悚然
creeping, crawling danger
似乎在等牺牲者自掘坟墓
ready to spring upon its unsuspecting prey.
孟加拉虎登场！
The royal Bengal tiger!
[ Fanfare plays ]
丛林之王
Lord of the jungle.
[ Yawns ]
冷酷无情的猎杀者
A cruel, merciless killer.
无肉不欢
He eats nothing but meat.
无所不吃
Man -- he likes... to eat.
人类也不在话下！
A man-eater!
[ Roars, hiccups ]
[ Blows ]
尖到足以撕碎人类的爪牙
Sharp talons that can rend a man to shreds.
[ Boingggg ! ]
[ Up-tempo music plays ]
天生就有保护色，
lts natural coloration blends into the surrounding foliage
潜伏在植物中不被发现
and becomes well nigh invisible.
[ Music continues ]
吼声响震天
lts roar -- the voice of doom.
[ Note ]
-- Meow
[ Growling ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Zip! ]
[ Clattering ]
[ Zip!Knock! Knock! Knock! ]
[ Whistle! Crank! ]
我们一丝不苟地跟踪野兽的踪迹
Grimly we stalk our quarry.
[ Sniffing rhythmically ]
终于发现了野兽的藏匿点！
Suddenly, a spoor!
我们立即提高警惕
lnstantly we're on the alert.
心跳加快、预感将要有大事情降临
Pulse quickening, keenly aware to a sense of danger
杀气遍布弥漫
that pervades the atmosphere.
[ Fanfare plays ]
Aah-hooey!
[ Trumpet! ]
[ Thud ! Creak! ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Crash ! ]
Oh-aah ! Oh-aah !Oh-aah !
[ Roaring ]
[ Crash ! ]
Oh-ohh !
[ Stre-e-e-tch ! Zip! ]
-- [ Roaring ]-- Aaaaah!
[ Zip! ]
[ Gasps ] Aah !
[ Roars ]
[ Scraping ]
Aah ! Aah !
Aah ! Ohh !
[ Bong ! ]
-- Ugh !
[ Whirl ! Whirl ! Whirl ! ]
[ Bong ! Thud ! ]
[ Creak! ]
[ Boing ! ]
[ Ping ! Ping ! Ping !Ping ! Ping ! ]
[ Zip! ]
[ Thud ! ]
[ Crunch ! ]
[ Rip! ]
[ Crunch ! Crunch !Crunch ! Crunch ! ]
[ Gulps ]
Ha-yuck!
Ha-ha-ha-yuck!
Ha ha ha!
Ouch !
Ha ha ha ha!Ohh !
[ Clicking ]
[ Crackling ]
Owwwww!
[ Yowling ]
[ Roaring ]
Ugh !
[ Whip! Whip! Whip! ]
[ Boom ! ]
Aah !
[ Roars ]
[ Chug ! Chug ! Chug ! Chug ! ]
Aaah !
Whoo!
Aah !
[ Roars ]
[ Bong ! ]
Aah ! Ohh !
[ Roars ]
Ouch ! Ha-yuck！Aah !
[ Tiger roaring ,
Goofy screaming ]
[ Tiger roaring ,Goofy screaming ]
Aah ! Aah !
Aah-hoo-hoo-hooey!
[ Snap! ]
Aah!
Aah !
[ Tiger roaring ,
Goofy screaming ]
[ Tiger roaring ]
[ Goofy panting ]
[ Both panting ]
Ooh-hoo!
[ Roars ]
[ Roaring ]
Aah !
[ Thud ! ]
Aaah !
[ Roars ]
[ Trumpet! ]
[ Thud ! ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Clank! Clank! Clank! Clank! ]
Aaah !
[ Trumpet! ]
Ugh !
[ Chug ! Chug ! Chug ! Chug ! ]
[ Thud ! ]
[ Trumpet! ]
[ Screech ! ]
[ Thud ! ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Gasps ]
孟加拉虎就是这样弄丢了自己的纹路！
And that is how the tiger lost his stripes.
[ Lively music plays ]
[ Music ends ]