1
00:00:35,120 --> 00:00:38,520
泰皮来劲! 泰皮来劲! 泰皮真来劲!
Juice by Tappy! Juice by Tappy! Juice by Tappy!

2
00:00:38,560 --> 00:00:41,920
噢!泰皮真热情有劲啦!
ohhh, Tappy's got juice! Tappy's got juice!

3
00:00:41,960 --> 00:00:46,090
噢!泰皮!
Whoa, Tappy!

4
00:00:46,120 --> 00:00:49,420
来劲! 来劲! 来劲!
Juice! Juice! Juice!

5
00:00:49,520 --> 00:00:51,690
你真来劲! 你真来劲!
Juice by you! Juice by you!

6
00:00:51,720 --> 00:00:56,620
热情有劲! 谢谢!
Juice! Juice by you! Thank you, thank you..

7
00:00:56,720 --> 00:00:59,590
- 赢家出来了. - 我们有了个赢家
- We got a winner. - We got a winner.

8
00:00:59,620 --> 00:01:02,220
- 我说 我们有了个赢家. - 我们有了个赢家!
- I said, we got a winner. - We got a winner!

9
00:01:02,320 --> 00:01:04,290
我们有了个赢家!
We got a winner!

10
00:01:04,320 --> 00:01:07,420
第一名她是来自华盛顿的飞行员
She's a flight attendant from Washington, DC.

11
00:01:07,460 --> 00:01:09,890
欢迎玛丽 肯林顿
Please welcome Mary Kellington.

12
00:01:09,920 --> 00:01:13,920
玛丽热情有劲! 玛丽热情有劲! 哦…
Juice by Mary! Juice by Mary! Whoa...

13
00:01:14,420 --> 00:01:17,290
不要动电视的脑筋
Harold, please, not again the TV.

14
00:01:17,320 --> 00:01:18,924
妈! 别这样 妈!
Ma! Come on, Ma!

15
00:01:18,925 --> 00:01:21,600
你为什么要这样小题大作呢?
Why do you have to make a big deal outta this?

16
00:01:21,800 --> 00:01:22,600
你知道我们几个小时内
You know you'll get the set back

17
00:01:22,603 --> 00:01:25,020
就可以把它要回来
in a couple of hours.

18
00:01:26,920 --> 00:01:29,620
为什么要让我觉得如此愧疚呢 妈?!
Why you gotta make me feel so guilty, Ma?!

19
00:01:36,920 --> 00:01:38,990
天呀! 你在做什么?
Jesus! What are you doing?

20
00:01:39,020 --> 00:01:41,481
你想让我弄坏电视
Trying to get me to break my own mother's set?

21
00:01:41,482 --> 00:01:43,020
或天线吗?
Or radiator?

22
00:01:43,060 --> 00:01:45,290
还是炸掉整个屋子?
And maybe blow up the house?

23
00:01:45,320 --> 00:01:47,837
我是你的儿子,你的血肉耶,妈!
Im your own son!Your own flesh and blood!

24
00:01:47,838 --> 00:01:50,020
你要这样对待你的儿子吗?
Is that what you're trying to do? Your son?

25
00:01:52,520 --> 00:01:54,720
为什么老是跟我玩游戏呢?
Why you play games with my head,

26
00:01:54,721 --> 00:01:55,820
莫名其妙!
for Christ's sake?

27
00:01:55,920 --> 00:01:58,120
哈瑞 我不会这样做的
Harold, I wouldn't do that.

28
00:01:59,220 --> 00:02:03,020
那链子不是针对你的. 是防小偷用的
The chain isn't for you. It's for the robbers.

29
00:02:03,120 --> 00:02:05,120
那你怎么不出来?
Then why won't you come out?

30
00:02:10,120 --> 00:02:13,420
知道我的意思吗? 知道你让我有多不开心吗 妈?
See what I mean? See how you always upset me, Ma?

31
00:02:13,460 --> 00:02:15,120
真是的
Christ's sake.

32
00:02:28,120 --> 00:02:29,620
妈?
Ma?

33
00:02:31,520 --> 00:02:32,920
妈!
Ma!

34
00:02:35,520 --> 00:02:38,320
出来嘛. 好不好 妈?
Come on out. Please, Ma?

35
00:02:41,720 --> 00:02:44,020
随你去吧!
Ah, screw it!

36
00:02:45,120 --> 00:02:46,790
这不会再发生了
This isn't happening.

37
00:02:46,820 --> 00:02:49,605
如果还是会发生的话,
And if it should be happening,

38
00:02:49,606 --> 00:02:50,720
那也好
it would be all right.

39
00:02:50,820 --> 00:02:55,220
所以别担心 西蒙. 一切都会没事的
So don't worry, Seymour. It'll all work out.

40
00:02:55,320 --> 00:02:59,220
你已经看过了. 最后还是会没事的
You'll see already. In the end, it's all nice.

41
00:03:04,820 --> 00:03:06,570
妈的! 老兄.
Shit, man.

42
00:03:06,571 --> 00:03:07,770
这玩意开始
That motherfucker's starting

43
00:03:07,771 --> 00:03:09,320
有点零散了
to look a little seedy.

44
00:03:09,360 --> 00:03:11,420
你怎么突然挑惕起来了?
You particular all of a sudden?

45
00:03:12,520 --> 00:03:14,050
我对女朋友无所谓,
I don't care my girlfriend go hell,

46
00:03:14,051 --> 00:03:15,920
只要能得到我们的面包
just as long as we get our bread.

47
00:03:15,960 --> 00:03:18,720
来帮我吧 泰隆
Just give me a hand, Tyrone.

48
00:03:21,320 --> 00:03:23,020
你看
Look at that.

49
00:03:26,620 --> 00:03:28,920
- 哈罗. - 嗨
- Hello. - Hi.

50
00:05:33,920 --> 00:05:35,690
连桌子也干来啦!
Fuck, the table too!

51
00:05:35,720 --> 00:05:37,746
你要我怎么样呢?
What do you want for me?

52
00:05:37,747 --> 00:05:39,520
背着过来吗?
You want me to schlep it on my back?

53
00:05:39,560 --> 00:05:41,217
- 你有朋友呀.
- You got a friend.

54
00:05:41,218 --> 00:05:43,290
- 我可不是搬运工
- I ain't my leper's schlepper shit.

55
00:05:43,320 --> 00:05:44,663
这款儿子.
Such a son.

56
00:05:44,664 --> 00:05:45,600
你妈生个蛋
Your mother needs you

57
00:05:45,607 --> 00:05:47,620
还比较划算
like a moose needs a hat rack.

58
00:06:14,620 --> 00:06:16,690
靠! 老兄
Shit, man.

59
00:06:16,720 --> 00:06:19,520
真是高档货呀,宝贝
This is some boss scag, baby.

60
00:06:19,620 --> 00:06:21,446
- 我觉得 超赞的.
- I mean, dynamite.

61
00:06:21,447 --> 00:06:23,820
- 噢 老兄 真的很特别
- Oh, man, it's something else.

62
00:06:29,620 --> 00:06:31,420
你知道我门该怎么做吗?
You know what we need to do?

63
00:06:33,220 --> 00:06:35,431
我们要弄整块的
We need to get us a piece of this Brody shit,

64
00:06:35,432 --> 00:06:37,920
分散之后再卖出去!
cut it up and off it!

65
00:06:37,960 --> 00:06:39,450
我们很容易就赚双倍
We could double our money... easy.

66
00:06:39,460 --> 00:06:41,600
一些卖给别人
They maybe buy some pieces

67
00:06:41,607 --> 00:06:43,920
一些自己用
and we got some whole other never shit coming off

68
00:06:44,020 --> 00:06:45,820
这样做才对
That'd be righteous.

69
00:06:45,920 --> 00:06:47,503
我打赌很快
I'll bet in no time off

70
00:06:47,504 --> 00:06:50,248
我们会拿整磅纯货
we'd get a pound of pure

71
00:06:50,249 --> 00:06:51,620
直接通过药头
straight from Sal the Geep.

72
00:06:51,660 --> 00:06:52,890
噢!
Oooh!

73
00:06:52,920 --> 00:06:56,420
我就是这个意思, 豪无疑问
That's what I'm talking about, baby - no hassles.

74
00:06:58,620 --> 00:07:01,020
- 还好吧? - 有事吗 老哥?
- How's it goin'? - What's up, buddy?

75
00:07:01,120 --> 00:07:03,420
- 一如往常. - 嗯 那还不错
- The usual? - Yeah, sounds good.

76
00:07:39,120 --> 00:07:41,820
要点别的吗? 喂?
Anything else? Huh?

77
00:07:44,020 --> 00:07:46,870
- 还要什么吗? - 喔 不了
- Anything else? - Ah, no.

78
00:07:46,910 --> 00:07:49,720
没事.我很好
Nothing. I'm all right.

79
00:07:57,320 --> 00:07:59,740
- 午安 哥德太太.
- Good afternoon, Mrs Goldfarb.

80
00:07:59,741 --> 00:08:01,720
- 午安 拉宾先生
- Good afternoon, Mr Rabinowitz.

81
00:08:01,820 --> 00:08:04,820
不过我不确定有多好 你呢?
Although I'm not so sure how good it is. And you?

82
00:08:04,920 --> 00:08:07,058
- 我能说什么呢? 你想要回电视?
- What can I say? You want your TV?

83
00:08:07,059 --> 00:08:08,820
- 是的 如果你不介意的话
- Yes, if you don't mind.

84
00:08:10,220 --> 00:08:12,920
哥德太太 我能请教你一件事吗?
Mrs Goldfarb, can I ask you a question?

85
00:08:12,960 --> 00:08:14,820
希望你别太在意
You won't take it personal?

86
00:08:15,720 --> 00:08:18,034
我们认识几年了?
How many years we know each other?

87
00:08:18,035 --> 00:08:19,320
谁在乎呢?
Who's to count?

88
00:08:19,420 --> 00:08:21,358
你为何不报警处理呢?
Why not tell ready the police?

89
00:08:21,359 --> 00:08:23,120
也许他们会跟哈瑞谈谈
Maybe they could talk to Harry.

90
00:08:23,220 --> 00:08:26,032
- 你就再也不会有电视被偷了.
- He wouldn't be stealing no more the TV.

91
00:08:26,033 --> 00:08:27,720
- 我不能这样做
- I couldn't do that.

92
00:08:27,820 --> 00:08:31,920
哈瑞是我唯一的孩子. 他是我的一切
Harry's my only child. He's all I have.

93
00:08:32,020 --> 00:08:34,720
谢谢你,拉宾先生
Thank you, Mr Rabinowitz.

94
00:08:36,320 --> 00:08:39,820
'加入我们并创造惊奇. JUICE!'
'Join us in creating excellence. JUICE!'

95
00:08:42,020 --> 00:08:45,120
'你会有更多难以想象 生命的热情'
'You have more passion for living.'

96
00:08:45,220 --> 00:08:48,170
'兴奋! 兴奋吧!
'Be excited! Be, be excited!

97
00:08:48,210 --> 00:08:51,120
'兴奋! 兴奋起来吧!
'Be excited! Be, be excited!

98
00:08:51,520 --> 00:08:54,320
'兴奋!兴奋吧!
'Be excited! Be, be excited!

99
00:08:54,620 --> 00:08:57,420
'兴奋! 兴奋起来吧!
'Be excited! Be, be excited!'

100
00:08:57,520 --> 00:08:59,390
'他们来劲吗?'
'They got the juice?'

101
00:08:59,420 --> 00:09:02,520
- '是的 他们真来劲!' - '振奋吧.'
- 'Yeah, they got the juice!' - 'Juice it up.'

102
00:09:30,520 --> 00:09:33,820
'哈罗? 是谁呀?'
'Hello? Who is it?'

103
00:09:48,920 --> 00:09:51,920
呃 妈的. 现在呢?
Aw, shit. Now what?

104
00:10:15,220 --> 00:10:16,690
哈罗?
Hello?

105
00:10:16,720 --> 00:10:19,890
- '莎拉哥德太太吗?' - 是我,请说
- 'Mrs Sara Goldfarb?' - Me. Speaking.

106
00:10:19,920 --> 00:10:22,690
我是马林集团的罗素赖尔
This is lyle Russell from Maylin and Block.

107
00:10:22,720 --> 00:10:24,048
- 我没有兴趣.
- I'm not interested.

108
00:10:24,049 --> 00:10:26,870
- '等一下. 我不是要推销东西
- 'Wait. I'm not selling anything.

109
00:10:26,910 --> 00:10:27,920
'我只是要给你一个机会
'I just want to offer you a chance

110
00:10:27,921 --> 00:10:31,020
上电视'
to be on television.'

111
00:10:31,120 --> 00:10:32,520
上电视?
Television?

112
00:10:32,620 --> 00:10:36,070
'是的,哥德太太. 恭喜你!'
'That's right, Mrs Goldfarb. Congratulations!'

113
00:10:36,110 --> 00:10:37,530
- 不过我没有任何…
- look, I don't have any...

114
00:10:37,531 --> 00:10:39,520
- '我不是为钱,哥德太太
- 'I don't want money Mrs Goldfarb.

115
00:10:39,560 --> 00:10:42,520
'我打电话来告诉你,你赢了
'I'm calling to tell you you've already won.

116
00:10:42,620 --> 00:10:45,220
'马林集团为大部份电视节目
'Maylin and Block discovers contestants

117
00:10:45,221 --> 00:10:46,420
寻找参赛者
for TV shows.

118
00:10:46,460 --> 00:10:49,120
'你从一长串名单中被选中了-
'You've been chosen from a long list -

119
00:10:49,160 --> 00:10:51,220
'也就是说 你赢了!'
'meaning, you've already won.'

120
00:10:51,320 --> 00:10:54,290
- 噢… - '是的,哥德太太'
- Ohh... - 'Yes, Mrs Goldfarb.'

121
00:10:54,320 --> 00:10:57,820
我从没想过会上电视 我只是…
I never thought I'd be on television. I'm just...

122
00:10:57,860 --> 00:11:00,120
'没错. 你会上电视
'That's right. You, on television.

123
00:11:00,220 --> 00:11:03,270
'我们会把所有的资料寄给你
'We'll send you the necessary information.

124
00:11:03,310 --> 00:11:06,320
'再见 恭喜 请保重'
'Goodbye, congratulations and take care.'

125
00:12:12,320 --> 00:12:13,761
可是我不懂
But I don't get it.

126
00:12:13,762 --> 00:12:17,220
你为什么对你父母苛求?
Why are you so hard on your folks?

127
00:12:17,260 --> 00:12:19,590
我是说 他门给你每样东西
I mean, they give you everything.

128
00:12:19,620 --> 00:12:21,248
供你吃
They hook you up with an apartment,

129
00:12:21,249 --> 00:12:23,420
,供你住
a croaker shrink.

130
00:12:23,520 --> 00:12:27,390
那很好 你知道的. 很棒. 只是…
Which is fine, you know. It's great. It's just...

131
00:12:27,420 --> 00:12:30,270
钱从不是我真正想向他们要的东西
money is never what I really wanted from them,

132
00:12:30,271 --> 00:12:31,220
你懂吗?
you know?

133
00:12:31,260 --> 00:12:34,420
钱对他们来说太多了
That's pretty much all they have to give.

134
00:12:35,520 --> 00:12:38,220
为什么不离开他们?
Why don't you get away from 'em?

135
00:12:38,320 --> 00:12:42,220
- 我要怎么做呢? - 我不知道
- How am I gonna do that? - I don't know.

136
00:12:42,260 --> 00:12:44,320
何不利用你的衣服?
What about your clothes?

137
00:12:44,420 --> 00:12:48,020
你图画得不错. 可以开个店
Your sketches are great. Open up a store.

138
00:12:48,720 --> 00:12:51,520
- 我不行. - 为什么?
- I can't. - Why not?

139
00:12:51,620 --> 00:12:54,220
这样我怎么有时间跟你在一起?
When will I have time to hang with you?

140
00:13:07,220 --> 00:13:09,247
- 哇! 要在哪开派对?
- Well! So where's the party?

141
00:13:09,248 --> 00:13:12,120
- 我一告诉你 你会吓得跳出窗外
- When I tell you, you're gonna die.

142
00:13:17,120 --> 00:13:19,120
这里紧了点
This is a tough one.

143
00:13:23,220 --> 00:13:25,520
我有本不错的减重书
I got a great diet book.

144
00:13:28,120 --> 00:13:30,120
嘿
Hey.

145
00:13:40,220 --> 00:13:41,820
他们来了
They're coming.

146
00:14:05,820 --> 00:14:08,720
'振奋! 振奋吧!'
'Be excited! Be, be excited!'

147
00:15:17,220 --> 00:15:19,820
我想我应该晒点太阳
I thought I'd catch a little sun today.

148
00:15:19,920 --> 00:15:22,690
是吗? 我想上电视时会有打光
Really? Well, in a box you'll catch it.

149
00:15:22,720 --> 00:15:24,951
只管放松自己 想
Just relax and think how gorgeous

150
00:15:24,952 --> 00:15:28,020
想你新染的红发有多亮丽
you'll look with your new red hair.

151
00:15:28,120 --> 00:15:31,220
今天先照顾头发,明天再管阳光
Today the hair, tomorrow the sun.

152
00:15:33,020 --> 00:15:35,420
有谁想浪费时间吗?
Anybody wanna waste some time?

153
00:15:39,520 --> 00:15:41,790
'天使说现在就是最佳时机'
'Angel says this is time wish do it now.'

154
00:15:41,820 --> 00:15:45,020
'我明天会打给布迪' '布敌是谁?'
- 'she'll call Brody tomorrow.' - 'whos Brody?'

155
00:15:45,070 --> 00:15:46,300
'他是我可爱的药头,
-that's my sweet connects

156
00:15:46,500 --> 00:15:48,373
有超赞的玩意'
-'He gets unbelievable shit.'

157
00:15:48,374 --> 00:15:49,390
'正点'
- 'Righteous.'

158
00:15:49,420 --> 00:15:53,320
'玛丽,我们有个想法' '什么?'
- 'look, we got this idea.' - 'What is it?'

159
00:15:53,420 --> 00:15:54,600
'弄整块的毒品,
'Get a piece of stuff,

160
00:15:54,821 --> 00:15:57,420
分割开来倍增我们的钱'
cut it up and double our money.no problem'

161
00:15:57,460 --> 00:16:00,020
'然后搞个整磅的纯货后退休
'Then get a pound of pure and retire.

162
00:16:00,120 --> 00:16:02,720
'你知道这个意思'
'You know what that means.'

163
00:16:02,820 --> 00:16:06,420
'我们不用再辛苦了 日子就好过了'
'We get off hard knocks and on easy street.'

164
00:16:07,520 --> 00:16:09,420
到底要做什么?
What's the catch?

165
00:16:09,920 --> 00:16:12,590
那是红的. 我是说 是红的
That's a red. I mean, that's a red.

166
00:16:12,620 --> 00:16:16,720
不是纯红, 但那是红的
It's not a red red, but that's a red. It's a red.

167
00:16:16,760 --> 00:16:18,820
- 红的? - 是呀,是红的
- Red? - Yeah. It's a red.

168
00:16:18,920 --> 00:16:22,020
- 你是说这是红的? - 是的
- You're telling me that's red? - Yeah.

169
00:16:22,060 --> 00:16:23,920
那橘色是什么?
Then what's orange?

170
00:16:24,020 --> 00:16:27,220
如果这是红的, 我想知道 - 橘色是什么?
If this is a red, I want to know - what's orange?

171
00:16:30,520 --> 00:16:33,720
嗯 它也可以…
Well, it could be...

172
00:16:35,420 --> 00:16:38,420
算是有点偏橘
that it's a little orange too.

173
00:16:40,420 --> 00:16:42,920
你知道吗?
You know something?

174
00:16:49,720 --> 00:16:51,153
我总是在想
I always thought

175
00:16:51,154 --> 00:16:54,020
你是我见过最美的女孩
you were the most beautiful girl I ever seen.

176
00:16:54,620 --> 00:16:56,120
是吗?
Really?

177
00:17:00,820 --> 00:17:03,220
从我第一眼见到你
Ever since I first saw you.

178
00:17:04,320 --> 00:17:06,420
那很好呀 哈瑞
That's nice, Harry.

179
00:17:12,120 --> 00:17:15,620
我觉得很开心
That makes me feel really good.

180
00:17:18,020 --> 00:17:20,720
从前也有人对我这样说过
Other people have told me that before,

181
00:17:20,820 --> 00:17:23,320
不过都没啥意义
and it was meaningless.

182
00:17:30,820 --> 00:17:31,914
为什么?
Why?

183
00:17:31,915 --> 00:17:36,020
因为你觉得 他们在逗你开心?
Because you thought they were pulling your leg?

184
00:17:36,120 --> 00:17:39,520
不 不是这样. 我的意思是…
No, no, not like that. I mean...

185
00:17:39,620 --> 00:17:40,305
不知道.
I don't know.

186
00:17:40,306 --> 00:17:43,220
我不知道 或说我跟本不在乎是如何
I don't know or even care if they were.

187
00:17:43,320 --> 00:17:45,520
只是从他们口中说出来…
Just from them it was...

188
00:17:47,620 --> 00:17:51,220
就是毫无意义 懂吗?
just meaningless, you know?

189
00:17:52,320 --> 00:17:55,820
当你说时 我听到了
When you say it, I hear it.

190
00:17:58,020 --> 00:17:59,920
真的听到了
I really hear it.

191
00:18:05,820 --> 00:18:07,796
像你这样的女孩
Somebody like you

192
00:18:07,797 --> 00:18:10,620
能够真的带给我好运
could really make things all right for me.

193
00:18:10,720 --> 00:18:12,620
你这样想?
You think?

194
00:18:15,420 --> 00:18:17,220
这是什么?
What is it?

195
00:18:17,320 --> 00:18:20,520
记得我告诉过你开店的事吗?
Remember when I told you about the store?

196
00:18:20,560 --> 00:18:21,990
嗯
Yeah.

197
00:18:22,020 --> 00:18:24,970
我一直思考了好久…
I've been thinking about it and...

198
00:18:25,010 --> 00:18:27,920
我找了一些资料 而且…
I put together some numbers and...

199
00:18:28,020 --> 00:18:30,020
这不是不可能的事!
and it's not impossible!

200
00:18:31,120 --> 00:18:33,820
我是说 你知道吗 你可以做的
I mean, you know, you could do it.

201
00:18:33,860 --> 00:18:35,720
你应该做的!
You should do it!

202
00:18:35,820 --> 00:18:38,720
我的意思是 我们可以一起来做
I mean, we could do it together.

203
00:18:45,720 --> 00:18:47,520
你觉得呢?
What do you think?

204
00:19:51,020 --> 00:19:53,590
够了
Stop already.

205
00:19:53,620 --> 00:19:55,860
你穿红礼服会比
You'll feel better in the red dress than

206
00:19:55,861 --> 00:19:58,420
吃起司面包快乐
in the cheese Danish.

207
00:20:35,020 --> 00:20:37,720
'我做了叁件事改变了我的生活. 叁件事.'
'Three things changed my life. Three.'

208
00:20:37,760 --> 00:20:40,420
'第一! 不吃红肉!'
'Number one! No red meat!'

209
00:20:40,520 --> 00:20:43,590
'想想看. 为何有人锺情红肉?
'Think about it. What do they stick in red meat?

210
00:20:43,620 --> 00:20:45,227
'我吃红肉
'I ate red meat to the point

211
00:20:45,228 --> 00:20:48,120
到了整块生吃的地步
where I would eat it... right off, raw.

212
00:20:48,220 --> 00:20:50,520
'我喜欢肉! 但我彻底改变
'I loved my meat! I turned it around.

213
00:20:50,620 --> 00:20:52,470
'你要坚定.
'You need to be committed.

214
00:20:52,471 --> 00:20:54,320
你要有热忱
You need to be passionate.

215
00:20:54,360 --> 00:20:57,820
'叁十天不吃红肉. 不吃红肉!
'No red meat for 30 days. No red meat!

216
00:20:57,920 --> 00:21:01,108
'做了叁件事改变了我的生活
'Three things is all I did to change my life.

217
00:21:01,109 --> 00:21:02,020
叁件事'
Three things.'

218
00:21:12,320 --> 00:21:15,020
艾达告诉我们了. 真是太好了
Ada told us. It's gorgeous.

219
00:21:15,060 --> 00:21:17,720
我们明天要把颜色弄深一点
We're gonna make it darker tomorrow.

220
00:21:17,820 --> 00:21:20,020
- 为什么? - 好搭配我的红礼服
- Why? - To go with my red dress.

221
00:21:20,120 --> 00:21:21,927
- 可是现在看起来像玛丹娜.
- But it's looking like Madonna.

222
00:21:21,928 --> 00:21:23,090
- 我不是玛丹娜
- It's not Madonna.

223
00:21:23,120 --> 00:21:24,220
我也不是
And neither is this.

224
00:21:24,221 --> 00:21:26,420
不过我很快会进行节食
But soon - I'm going on a diet.

225
00:21:26,460 --> 00:21:29,090
- 怎样的节食? - 蛋跟葡萄柚
- What diet? - Eggs and grapefruit.

226
00:21:29,120 --> 00:21:32,120
- 我试过这套. 真是万幸 - 没有那么遭
- I was on that. Lots of luck. - It's not so bad.

227
00:21:32,160 --> 00:21:34,590
- 你进行节食多久了? - 整天
- How long you been on it? - All day.

228
00:21:34,620 --> 00:21:38,820
整天! 现在是下午一点!
All day! It's one o'clock!

229
00:21:38,920 --> 00:21:41,870
- 我想要瘦. - 她想要瘦
- Thinking thin. - She's thinking thin.

230
00:21:41,910 --> 00:21:44,820
我们家路易丝 就像那样甩了50磅
My louise, she lost 50lbs just like that.

231
00:21:44,920 --> 00:21:46,720
像怎样? 娘娘腔
- like what? - Poof!

232
00:21:46,820 --> 00:21:50,020
你把她放干燥箱吗?
Did you put her in a sweatbox?

233
00:21:50,120 --> 00:21:53,145
他去看医生 医生给他药
She went to a doctor. He gave her pills.

234
00:21:53,146 --> 00:21:55,070
你不会想吃的
You don't want to eat.

235
00:21:55,310 --> 00:21:57,142
所以呢? 你的意思是可以坐在这
So? You mean, I'm sitting here

236
00:21:57,350 --> 00:22:00,020
不去想面包上的熏肉吗?
not thinking about pastrami on rye?

237
00:22:00,060 --> 00:22:03,390
你不该在有人节食的时后这样说的
Don't talk like that when someone's on a diet.

238
00:22:03,420 --> 00:22:06,720
没什么啦. 我会再偷吃片葡萄柚吧
Big deal. I'll sneak another wedge of grapefruit.

239
00:22:08,820 --> 00:22:12,390
- 我是想瘦! - 噢 莎拉 邮差来了
- I'm thinking thin! - Ooh, Sara, the mailman.

240
00:22:12,420 --> 00:22:16,174
哥德莎拉? 你有哥德莎拉的信件吗?
Sara Goldfarb? You have something for me?

241
00:22:16,175 --> 00:22:17,720
我在等我的信
I'm expecting something.

242
00:22:17,760 --> 00:22:21,020
哥德 哥德. 哥德莎拉
Goldfarb, Goldfarb. Sara Goldfarb.

243
00:22:21,120 --> 00:22:23,520
- 是这封吗? - 就是这封!
- Is that it? - That's it!

244
00:22:23,620 --> 00:22:25,820
- 快点. - 等一下,我拿东西
- Come on. - I gotta get my stuff.

245
00:22:25,860 --> 00:22:28,020
- 好的. - 我可以教你
- All right. - I can tell you.

246
00:22:28,060 --> 00:22:31,220
名字. 填上你的名字
Your name. Put your name.

247
00:22:31,260 --> 00:22:34,040
S-A-R-A G-O-l-D…
S-A-R-A G-O-L-D...

248
00:22:34,070 --> 00:22:36,200
F-A-R-B!
F-A-R-B!

249
00:22:36,230 --> 00:22:38,320
吓吓叫?
Dynamite?

250
00:22:39,220 --> 00:22:40,720
吓吓叫的
It's dynamite.

251
00:22:42,020 --> 00:22:44,690
阿哈! 吓吓叫!
A-ha! Dynamite!

252
00:22:44,720 --> 00:22:47,220
没问题 我们马上过去
All right, we on our way.

253
00:22:47,320 --> 00:22:49,360
- 布迪的人说有高档货了
- Brody's man says it's fine shit.

254
00:22:49,361 --> 00:22:50,720
- 好吧 老兄
- All right, man.

255
00:22:51,820 --> 00:22:54,520
- 就是这样. - 嘿 泰?
- Here we go. - Hey, Ty?

256
00:22:56,120 --> 00:22:58,044
- 我们不能出差错 老兄
- let's do this right, man.

257
00:22:58,045 --> 00:22:59,820
- 哎呦 宝贝. 当然的
- Come on, baby. Naturally.

258
00:23:03,220 --> 00:23:05,347
- 快点 我们快点
- Hurry, hurry. Let's hurry.

259
00:23:05,348 --> 00:23:08,420
- 不知道你们有没有听到
- I wonder when you'll hear.

260
00:23:08,520 --> 00:23:11,520
- 嗨! - 我想跟你去!
- Hi! - I wanna come with you!

261
00:23:11,620 --> 00:23:13,186
也许她们会送你
Maybe they'll send you to

262
00:23:13,187 --> 00:23:16,320
到绿茵小舍 明星都会到那里去
the Tavern On The Green with the stars.

263
00:23:16,420 --> 00:23:19,790
嗯 我要在那里吃蛋跟葡萄柚
Yeah, eggs and grapefruit at Tavern On The Green.

264
00:23:19,820 --> 00:23:20,772
- 我希望他们有提供
- I hope they have that.

265
00:23:20,773 --> 00:23:22,490
- 趁邮差还没来快点
- Hurry before the mailman comes.

266
00:23:22,600 --> 00:23:25,820
- 好了 - 寄出去吧!
- Here we are. - Mail it!

267
00:23:25,920 --> 00:23:28,320
噢 莎拉!
Oh, Sara!

268
00:24:40,620 --> 00:24:43,720
- 在这里 老兄 - 阿?
- There it is, Jim. - Huh?

269
00:24:44,920 --> 00:24:48,920
- 在这里 宝贝 - 噢 靠!
- There it is, baby. - Oh, shit!

270
00:24:49,020 --> 00:24:53,220
- 要试试吗? - 等等 泰
- Shall we try it? - Wait, Ty.

271
00:24:53,320 --> 00:24:58,220
听着 这是我们发财的机会
Look, this is our chance to make it big.

272
00:24:58,320 --> 00:25:03,320
我们好好做, 可以弄到整磅的纯货
We play it right, we can get a pound of pure.

273
00:25:03,420 --> 00:25:06,190
可是如果我们浪费了…
But if we get wasted...

274
00:25:06,220 --> 00:25:09,720
- 一切就搞砸了 - 我知道
- we'll fuck it up. - Right on.

275
00:25:09,820 --> 00:25:13,420
嘿 听我说 我不是想愚弄你 老兄
Hey, look, I ain't trying to jive you, Jim.

276
00:25:13,520 --> 00:25:14,920
我不希望一辈子在接上打混
I dont wanna be running the streets my whole life

277
00:25:14,960 --> 00:25:19,090
挨冻受饿
my nose runnin' down to my chin.

278
00:25:19,120 --> 00:25:21,700
我的意思是我们先尝一下
All I'm sayin' is take a little taste

279
00:25:21,701 --> 00:25:23,420
才知道该怎么分装
so we know how much to cut.

280
00:25:23,460 --> 00:25:24,820
纯为生意
It's business.

281
00:25:27,420 --> 00:25:29,020
嗯 有道理
Yeah, fair enough.

282
00:25:35,320 --> 00:25:38,820
靠…
Shit...

283
00:25:54,920 --> 00:25:57,420
'谢谢大家! 我只做了叁件事
'Thank you! Three things is all I did.

284
00:25:57,460 --> 00:25:59,390
'只需花叁十天
'30 days is all it takes.

285
00:25:59,420 --> 00:26:02,620
'第二! 不吃精制糖!
'Number two! No refined sugar!

286
00:26:02,660 --> 00:26:05,090
'现在 糖无所不在
'Now, sugar's everywhere.

287
00:26:05,120 --> 00:26:08,320
'你知道吗? 商家在瓶装水里也放了糖
'You know they even put sugar in bottled water?

288
00:26:08,420 --> 00:26:11,420
'我曾得了嗜糖症! 那曾是我的药
'I was sick with sugar! That was my medicine.

289
00:26:11,520 --> 00:26:13,572
'它浸蚀着我的大脑
'It nurtured my spiralling brain

290
00:26:13,573 --> 00:26:15,420
让我觉得是个输家'
that felt I was a loser.'

291
00:26:15,460 --> 00:26:17,020
'振作起来!'
'Juice by you!'

292
00:26:17,120 --> 00:26:21,790
'第二条守则就是不吃精糖
'Rule two is no refined sugar.

293
00:26:21,820 --> 00:26:25,120
'汽水? 汽水连想都不要想
'Sodas? Don't even think about sodas any more.

294
00:26:25,220 --> 00:26:27,657
'不要再舔任何糖果了
'No sucking candies. None of that.

295
00:26:27,658 --> 00:26:29,120
只管远离它
Just stay away from it.

296
00:26:29,160 --> 00:26:33,420
'30天没有糖的生活'
'No refined sugar. For 30 days.'

297
00:26:33,520 --> 00:26:35,320
'我要吃得正确
'I'm gonna eat right.

298
00:26:35,420 --> 00:26:37,732
'我要提起我的精神
'I am gonna pick up my spirits

299
00:26:37,733 --> 00:26:39,120
我将放手一搏
and I am gonna try!

300
00:26:39,220 --> 00:26:41,380
'我找到了希望.
'I found hope.

301
00:26:41,381 --> 00:26:44,020
在希望中找到了方法…'
And in that hope, I found a way...'

302
00:26:52,720 --> 00:26:54,420
别再说了!
Shut up!

303
00:27:28,120 --> 00:27:29,790
'哈罗?'
'Hello?'

304
00:27:29,820 --> 00:27:31,420
- 露西? - '是'
- Rosie? - 'Yeah.'

305
00:27:31,460 --> 00:27:33,020
- 我是莎拉. - '嗯?'
- Sara. - 'Yeah?'

306
00:27:33,120 --> 00:27:35,320
我想跟你要那位医生的电话
I need the number of that doctor.

307
00:27:37,120 --> 00:27:40,490
我不了解为何你要去见他
I don't understand why you gotta see him.

308
00:27:40,520 --> 00:27:43,690
真他妈的
Cut the son of a bitch loose, for Christ's sake.

309
00:27:43,720 --> 00:27:45,920
因为我不想他跟我爸妈
Because he'll tell my parents

310
00:27:45,921 --> 00:27:48,120
提到我停止治疗的事
that I've stopped therapy.

311
00:27:48,220 --> 00:27:51,320
它们已经对我很不爽 打算跟我断绝,你知道吗?
They're already thinking of cutting me off.

312
00:27:52,420 --> 00:27:54,720
哈瑞 我不会跟他上床什么的
Harry, I'm not gonna sleep with him.

313
00:27:54,820 --> 00:27:57,920
演唱会节束我就会回来了
I'm gonna come home after the concert.

314
00:27:58,020 --> 00:28:00,320
你在吃醋!
You're jealous!

315
00:28:01,420 --> 00:28:03,720
哈瑞吃醋?
Harry - jealous?

316
00:28:05,220 --> 00:28:08,490
- 抱住我 - 不要
- Put your arms around me. - No.

317
00:28:08,520 --> 00:28:11,720
你真不听话! 抱住我
You are so stubborn! Put your arms around me.

318
00:28:14,020 --> 00:28:15,820
别玩了!
Stop that!

319
00:28:16,820 --> 00:28:19,520
- 我要把你眼球吸出来 - 嗯
- I'll suck your eyeballs out. - Mm-hm.

320
00:28:20,720 --> 00:28:22,020
唔…
Well...

321
00:28:22,120 --> 00:28:25,520
我很失望你不怎么自在
I'm disappointed that you're indisposed.

322
00:28:27,820 --> 00:28:30,120
安妮塔有出外什么的吗?
Is Anita out of town or something?

323
00:28:31,320 --> 00:28:33,090
为什么问呢?
Why do you ask?

324
00:28:33,120 --> 00:28:36,620
我只是想知道她是不是不自“在”
I was just wondering if she was "indisposed".

325
00:28:41,320 --> 00:28:42,720
没有
No.

326
00:28:42,820 --> 00:28:44,453
她很好 谢谢你
She's fine, thank you.

327
00:28:44,454 --> 00:28:47,020
事实上 她在佛罗里达
Actually, she's in Florida.

328
00:28:47,060 --> 00:28:51,220
- 我可以问一个私人问题吗,亚诺? - 当然
- Can I ask you something, Arnold? - Of course.

329
00:28:54,920 --> 00:28:56,690
任何东西. 什么?
Anything. What?

330
00:28:56,720 --> 00:28:59,520
- 你这里沾了东西 - 没有了吗?
- You just have something here. - Gone?

331
00:28:59,560 --> 00:29:02,320
下面一点 再下来一点
A little bit, a little bit lower.

332
00:29:02,420 --> 00:29:05,020
没事了. 别担心 好多了
It's OK. Don't worry. It's much better.

333
00:29:05,060 --> 00:29:06,520
亚诺!
Arnold!

334
00:29:09,320 --> 00:29:11,520
你觉得如何 哥德太太?
How are you, Mrs Goldfarb?

335
00:29:11,620 --> 00:29:15,420
我如何? 身躯庞大 所以我才会来这
How am I? Enormous. That's why I'm here.

336
00:29:15,520 --> 00:29:18,420
- 我看过情况更遭的 - 噢…谢谢
- I've seen much worse. - Oh... thank you.

337
00:29:19,520 --> 00:29:23,020
- 你的听力跟视力如何? - 我两个都有
- How's your hearing and vision? - I have both.

338
00:29:24,120 --> 00:29:26,620
医师等一下就来
The doctor will be with you shortly.

339
00:29:34,420 --> 00:29:37,320
- 你有点过重 - 有点?
- You're a little overweight. - A little?

340
00:29:37,420 --> 00:29:40,170
我想捐50磅出来
I have 50lbs I'm willing to donate.

341
00:29:40,210 --> 00:29:42,920
我们会处理的 没问题
We can take care of that. No problem.

342
00:30:33,520 --> 00:30:35,420
我们要发了 宝贝
We're on our way, baby.

343
00:30:35,460 --> 00:30:37,820
我们要发了!
We are on our way!

344
00:30:37,920 --> 00:30:39,374
天呀 在那里真棒
God, It was great out there.

345
00:30:39,375 --> 00:30:41,920
我的意思是每个人都很  渴
I mean, everybody is thirsty.

346
00:30:41,960 --> 00:30:44,890
过来
Come to me.

347
00:30:44,920 --> 00:30:48,420
哈瑞! 我好高兴
Harry! I am so glad.

348
00:30:54,120 --> 00:30:56,020
自然地
Naturally.

349
00:30:59,620 --> 00:31:01,520
自然地
Naturally.

350
00:31:06,720 --> 00:31:08,720
自然地
Naturally.

351
00:31:32,520 --> 00:31:34,620
紫色早上吃
Purple in the morning.

352
00:31:34,720 --> 00:31:36,570
蓝色是下午
Blue in the afternoon.

353
00:31:36,610 --> 00:31:38,420
晚上吃橘色的
orange in the evening.

354
00:31:39,920 --> 00:31:43,020
这是我的叁餐 神气的家伙
There's my three meals, Mr Smarty-pants.

355
00:31:44,820 --> 00:31:47,720
绿色夜里吃 就像那样
And green at night. Just like that.

356
00:31:47,760 --> 00:31:49,520
一 二  叁 四
one, two, three, four.

357
00:32:59,920 --> 00:33:01,990
怎么不回床上来? 亲爱的
Come back to bed, baby.

358
00:33:02,020 --> 00:33:05,320
等一下 艾利丝 有的是时间
Come on now, Alice. Got plenty of time for that.

359
00:33:05,420 --> 00:33:05,958
现在
Right now

360
00:33:05,959 --> 00:33:08,920
我正在装配新的活门镜子
I'm grooving with these new mirrors I got.

361
00:33:08,960 --> 00:33:11,020
呼!
Oooh!

362
00:33:29,620 --> 00:33:33,020
妈 我跟你说 我以后一定要成大事
I told ya, Mom, one day I'd make it.

363
00:33:33,120 --> 00:33:35,920
你什么都不用做 我的宝贝
You don't have to make anything, my sweet.

364
00:33:36,020 --> 00:33:38,520
你只要爱你妈妈就好,嗯
You just have to love your mama, huh?

365
00:33:38,620 --> 00:33:40,720
你在做什么 亲爱的?
What ya doin', baby?

366
00:33:40,820 --> 00:33:42,290
喔?
Huh?

367
00:33:42,320 --> 00:33:45,420
- 你在做什么 亲爱的? - 没什么
- What ya doin', baby? - Nothin'.

368
00:33:49,220 --> 00:33:51,120
只是在想你
Just thinkin' about you.

369
00:33:52,820 --> 00:33:55,820
在想我要跟你做的下流事
About the nasty things I'm about to do to ya.

370
00:33:55,860 --> 00:33:58,320
我要上你了
Bitch, get over here!

371
00:34:00,320 --> 00:34:03,020
泰 你吓到我了
Ty, you scare me to death.

372
00:34:03,120 --> 00:34:05,820
没有,我没有吓你
No, I wouldn't scare you.

373
00:34:05,821 --> 00:34:07,920
我不想吓任何人
I don't wanna scare nobody.

374
00:34:09,920 --> 00:34:11,435
我只想生命中
All I want out of life

375
00:34:11,436 --> 00:34:14,720
有点平静与快乐 ,仅此而已
is a bit of peace and happiness. That's all.

376
00:34:15,620 --> 00:34:17,420
就是现在…
Right now...

377
00:34:18,720 --> 00:34:22,820
你是我见过最漂亮的美人
you're the finest fox I ever laid my eyes on.

378
00:34:24,720 --> 00:34:27,690
- 那是我要做的事 - 咦?
- That's what I'll do. - Hmm?

379
00:34:27,720 --> 00:34:28,895
为了我妈
For my mother.

380
00:34:28,896 --> 00:34:30,158
我一直在想
I've been thinking about

381
00:34:30,159 --> 00:34:32,420
买个东西给她
getting something for her.

382
00:34:32,520 --> 00:34:34,690
像是一件礼物什么的
Like... a present or something.

383
00:34:34,720 --> 00:34:35,600
但我不知道要给她什么
But I didn't know what I was gonna get,

384
00:34:36,600 --> 00:34:38,020
直到现在
until now.

385
00:34:38,060 --> 00:34:40,820
- 所以? - 后来我问我自己
- And? - I finally asked myself, right,

386
00:34:40,860 --> 00:34:43,140
她着迷什么?
what's her fix?

387
00:34:43,170 --> 00:34:45,390
电视机 对吧?
Television, right?

388
00:34:45,420 --> 00:34:48,520
如果有谁是电视迷 那她一定是个老太太
If ever there's a TV junkie, it's the old lady.

389
00:34:48,620 --> 00:34:49,535
我想我欠她一台新电视机
I owe her a new set,

390
00:34:49,600 --> 00:34:51,320
之前老是搬来搬去
with all the wear and tear it got

391
00:34:51,520 --> 00:34:55,220
全是磨损和伤痕
being schlepped back and forth to old Abe's.

392
00:34:55,260 --> 00:34:57,420
你真的很爱她 是吧?
You really love her, don't you?

393
00:34:59,920 --> 00:35:02,420
我想是吧. 你知道吗?
I-I guess so. You know?

394
00:35:05,220 --> 00:35:08,720
我一直希望她快乐
Most of the time I just want her to be happy.

395
00:35:08,820 --> 00:35:11,670
我们现在去买一台
Let's go get it now.

396
00:35:11,710 --> 00:35:14,520
先离开吧
Let's push off first.

397
00:35:17,520 --> 00:35:19,420
现在还早 哈瑞.
It's early, Harry.

398
00:35:19,421 --> 00:35:21,320
我们晚上再出发
We shouldn't get going till tonight.

399
00:36:08,720 --> 00:36:11,320
'兴奋吧. 兴奋吧
'Be excited. Be, be excited.

400
00:36:11,520 --> 00:36:14,420
兴奋 兴奋吧!
'Be excited. Be, be excited.

401
00:36:14,520 --> 00:36:16,090
'兴奋吧
'Be excited.

402
00:36:16,120 --> 00:36:18,590
'要坚决而热忱'
'Be committed and be passionate.'

403
00:36:18,620 --> 00:36:22,506
'我是活生生的例子 瘦了65磅
'I am a living testament. 65 lbs thinner.

404
00:36:22,507 --> 00:36:24,320
感觉太好了!
I feel great!

405
00:36:32,420 --> 00:36:36,120
'第叁. 噢 第叁项!
'Number three. Ohhh, number three!

406
00:36:36,220 --> 00:36:40,820
'这个让很多发疯
'This drives most people crazy.

407
00:36:40,860 --> 00:36:45,720
'目前为止都很容易
'This is easy so far.'

408
00:37:40,620 --> 00:37:44,490
- 瘦了 - 她跟以前不一样了
- That is thin! - She's not the same person.

409
00:37:44,520 --> 00:37:46,728
我快要可以穿那件红礼服了
I can almost zip the red dress.

410
00:37:46,729 --> 00:37:49,120
差不多可以把拉  拉上了
I've almost got the zipper up.

411
00:37:49,220 --> 00:37:51,090
- 邮差来了! - 喂!
- The mailman! - Oh!

412
00:37:51,120 --> 00:37:53,420
我看到你的信的话 我会拿着到处示众
When I see it I'll wave it all over the place.

413
00:37:53,520 --> 00:37:56,190
- 你确定吗? - 是的 我确定
- Are you sure? - Yeah, I'm sure.

414
00:37:56,220 --> 00:37:57,667
- 他说什么呀?
- What did he say?

415
00:37:57,668 --> 00:37:59,920
- 别担心 莎拉 一定会来的
- Don't worry, Sara, it'll come.

416
00:38:01,020 --> 00:38:03,520
是呀 别担心 会来的
Yeah, don't worry. It'll come.

417
00:38:05,420 --> 00:38:06,870
是哈瑞!
It's Harry!

418
00:38:06,910 --> 00:38:08,320
哈瑞 噢!
Harry, oh!

419
00:38:08,420 --> 00:38:13,020
嘿 妈 轻一点 你会把我压碎的
Hey, Ma, easy. You'll crush me, for Christ sakes.

420
00:38:13,060 --> 00:38:15,190
- 进屋吧 - 哈罗
- Come inside. - Hello.

421
00:38:15,220 --> 00:38:18,720
嗨 哈瑞! 哈罗! 有客人来罗!
- Hi, Harry! Hello! - We'll have a little visit.

422
00:38:18,760 --> 00:38:21,840
过得如何呀 哈瑞? 你看起来不错
So, how are you, Harry? You look so good.

423
00:38:21,870 --> 00:38:24,890
- 想吃点什么吗? - 不了 妈
- You want something to eat? - No, Ma.

424
00:38:24,920 --> 00:38:27,196
小点心 还是蛋糕?
A little nosh, a piece of cake?

425
00:38:27,197 --> 00:38:29,220
我可以去弄点来
I could go and get something if you want.

426
00:38:29,320 --> 00:38:31,120
家里没什么东西了
I don't have anything in the house,

427
00:38:31,121 --> 00:38:32,720
不过艾达阿姨那有
but Ada would have.

428
00:38:32,820 --> 00:38:35,220
来个小蛋糕好吗? 要吃点什么吗?
A cupcake? You want something to eat?

429
00:38:35,320 --> 00:38:38,290
不 不用 妈 什么都不用 请坐下吧
No, no, Ma, nothing. Please, sit.

430
00:38:38,320 --> 00:38:41,290
你让我头昏眼花的
You're making me dizzy, for Christ's sake.

431
00:38:41,320 --> 00:38:44,920
你有发现我有啥不同吗? 注意到我变瘦了吗?
You notice anything, huh? You notice I'm slimmer?

432
00:38:45,020 --> 00:38:46,990
嗯 我想是的
Yeah, I guess you are.

433
00:38:47,020 --> 00:38:50,520
25磅 我瘦了25磅耶! 你相信吗?
25lbs, I lost. 25lbs! Can you believe it?

434
00:38:50,620 --> 00:38:51,704
- 而且这才刚开始而已
- And that's only the beginning.

435
00:38:51,995 --> 00:38:54,220
- 那很好 妈 真的很好
- That's great, Ma That's readly great.

436
00:38:54,320 --> 00:38:55,592
我真的很为你高兴
I'm really happy for you.

437
00:38:55,593 --> 00:38:57,820
但是你要不要坐下来? 拜托
But will you sit? Please.

438
00:39:00,620 --> 00:39:03,762
很抱歉我没回家好一阵子了
I'm sorry I haven't been around in a while,

439
00:39:03,763 --> 00:39:06,120
妈 但我一直很忙
Ma, but I've been busy.

440
00:39:06,220 --> 00:39:09,120
是吗? 你有好工作了? 做得好吗?
Yeah? You got a good job? You're doing well?

441
00:39:09,220 --> 00:39:12,420
- 嗯 很好 真的很好 - 什么工作呢?
- Yeah, good, real good. - What kind of business?

442
00:39:12,520 --> 00:39:15,075
嗯 我有点像批发商
Well, I'm sort of a distributor like,

443
00:39:15,076 --> 00:39:17,120
为大进口商做销售
for a big importer.

444
00:39:17,220 --> 00:39:19,448
- 哇! 我真为你高兴!
- Ohh! I'm so happy for you!

445
00:39:19,449 --> 00:39:22,020
- 妈… 轻点. 这样我会死的
- Ma... Easy. You're killin' me.

446
00:39:22,060 --> 00:39:24,820
天呀 你一直在练举重吗?
Jesus, what, you been lifting weights?

447
00:39:24,920 --> 00:39:27,690
- 我知道你办得到的 - 你是对的 妈
- I knew you could do that. - You were right.

448
00:39:27,720 --> 00:39:29,700
现在你可能跟个好女孩恋爱
Now maybe you'll meet a nice girl

449
00:39:29,701 --> 00:39:31,020
顺便生个小孩?
and have a baby?

450
00:39:32,520 --> 00:39:34,820
嗯 我已经认识一个了
Well, I already met one.

451
00:39:34,920 --> 00:39:37,490
妈 别太夸张了
Ma, don't go ape shit.

452
00:39:37,520 --> 00:39:41,220
- 她是谁? 谁家的女孩呢? - 你认识的
- Who is she? Who's her parents? - You know her.

453
00:39:41,260 --> 00:39:44,920
- 玛丽? 玛丽西尔法. 记得吗? - 噢 西尔法!
- Marion? Marion Silver. Remember? - Oh, Silver!

454
00:39:44,960 --> 00:39:47,990
当然. 曼哈顿海滩
of course. Manhattan Beach.

455
00:39:48,020 --> 00:39:51,220
他在布拉格有间房子 做服装生意的
House on the esplanade. Garment business.

456
00:39:51,320 --> 00:39:53,420
嗯. 他是女性内衣的大亨
He's big in women's undies.

457
00:39:53,520 --> 00:39:55,970
妈 被你这么一闹
Before you go bouncing all over again

458
00:39:55,971 --> 00:39:58,420
我都忘记了…
and make me forget, just...

459
00:39:59,520 --> 00:40:00,943
我想告诉你
What I wanna tell you is that

460
00:40:00,944 --> 00:40:03,220
我有件礼物要给你
I got you a present.

461
00:40:03,260 --> 00:40:06,420
我不需要礼物 只要有个小孙子
I don't need a present. Just have a baby.

462
00:40:06,520 --> 00:40:08,770
让我来告诉你好吗?
Will you let me tell you what I got ya?

463
00:40:08,771 --> 00:40:10,120
可以吗 妈?
Will ya, Ma?

464
00:40:11,220 --> 00:40:14,153
天呀 你今天真的有点反常
Christ, you are really something else today,

465
00:40:14,154 --> 00:40:15,620
你知道吗?
you know that?

466
00:40:15,660 --> 00:40:18,220
听我说 我知道…
Look, I know...

467
00:40:19,720 --> 00:40:21,120
嗯…
Well...

468
00:40:22,720 --> 00:40:25,720
很抱歉我一直不学好
I'm sorry for being such a bastard.

469
00:40:25,721 --> 00:40:27,520
我很想补偿你
I wanna make it up.

470
00:40:27,620 --> 00:40:28,514
我是说
I mean,

471
00:40:28,515 --> 00:40:31,420
我知道我不能改变发生过的事
I know I can't change anything that's happened,

472
00:40:31,460 --> 00:40:33,890
但是我希望你知道…
but I want you to know that...

473
00:40:33,920 --> 00:40:37,820
我很爱你 而且我对你很抱歉
That I love ya, and that I'm sorry.

474
00:40:37,920 --> 00:40:39,705
我希望你快乐.
And I want you to be happy.

475
00:40:39,706 --> 00:40:43,020
所以我买了台新电视机给你
So I got you a brand-new TV set.

476
00:40:43,120 --> 00:40:45,360
过几天就会送来了
It's gonna be delivered in a couple of days.

477
00:40:45,361 --> 00:40:47,320
梅西来的喔!
It's from Macy's!

478
00:40:47,420 --> 00:40:49,120
噢 哈瑞!
oh, Harry!

479
00:40:51,920 --> 00:40:53,790
你父亲会很开心的
Your father'd be so happy

480
00:40:53,820 --> 00:40:55,435
如果他看到你
if he could see what you're doing

481
00:40:55,436 --> 00:40:57,320
为妈妈所做的事
for your mother.

482
00:41:00,820 --> 00:41:02,790
看到了吗 西蒙?
See that, Seymour?

483
00:41:02,820 --> 00:41:05,990
你看到你的儿子有多棒了吧?
You see how good your son is?

484
00:41:06,020 --> 00:41:06,807
他知道
He knows

485
00:41:06,808 --> 00:41:10,220
妈妈一个人独居 是什么感觉
what it's like for his mother living all alone.

486
00:41:10,260 --> 00:41:12,420
都没人来看她
No one to visit her.

487
00:41:23,720 --> 00:41:25,620
嘿 妈
Hey, Ma.

488
00:41:25,720 --> 00:41:28,290
- 你在磨牙吗? - 什么?
- You on uppers? - What?

489
00:41:28,320 --> 00:41:29,360
你在磨牙
You're on uppers.

490
00:41:29,361 --> 00:41:32,220
你在吃减肥药 是吗?
You're on diet pills, ain't you?

491
00:41:32,320 --> 00:41:34,820
我跟你说了 我去看专科医生
I told you. I'm going to a specialist.

492
00:41:34,920 --> 00:41:38,320
我想也是! 你让体重急速下降 不是吗?
That's what I thought! You're on speed, ain't ya?

493
00:41:38,360 --> 00:41:40,690
哈瑞 你还好吧 我是去看医生耶
Harry, I'm goin' to a doctor.

494
00:41:40,720 --> 00:41:42,710
- 他给你什么 有给你药片吗?
- Does he give you pills?

495
00:41:42,711 --> 00:41:44,170
- 当然 他是医生呀
- Of course. He's a doctor.

496
00:41:44,210 --> 00:41:45,390
- 什么样的药片?
- What kind of pills?

497
00:41:45,391 --> 00:41:47,620
- 有紫的 有蓝的 还有橘色的…
- A purple, a blue, an orange...

498
00:41:47,660 --> 00:41:49,590
我的意思是 里面含有什么?
I mean, like what's in 'em?

499
00:41:49,620 --> 00:41:51,370
哈瑞 我是莎拉哥德
Oh, Harry, I'm Sara Goldfarb,

500
00:41:51,371 --> 00:41:52,595
又不是爱因斯坦
not Albert Einstein.

501
00:41:52,596 --> 00:41:54,520
怎么知道里面有什么?
How should I know?

502
00:41:54,620 --> 00:41:57,620
那些玩意是不是让你感觉很好 而且充满活力?
Does it make you feel good and give you pep?

503
00:41:57,660 --> 00:42:00,320
嗯… 是吧 有一点
Well... yeah, a little.

504
00:42:00,420 --> 00:42:03,020
妈 我从这里就可以听到你在磨牙的声音
Ma, I can hear ya grinding your teeth.

505
00:42:03,120 --> 00:42:05,520
- 晚上就不会了呀 - 晚上?
- That goes away at night. - At night?

506
00:42:05,620 --> 00:42:07,590
对呀 我吃了绿色药片
Yeah, when I take the green one.

507
00:42:07,591 --> 00:42:09,920
30分钟后就睡着了 真好用
30 minutes I'm asleep. Poof.

508
00:42:09,960 --> 00:42:13,020
妈 妈 你要甩掉这些玩意
Ma, Ma, ya gotta cut that stuff loose.

509
00:42:13,060 --> 00:42:15,190
我可以告诉你 这不是好东西
I'm tellin' ya, it's no good.

510
00:42:15,220 --> 00:42:18,220
怎么会不好呢? 我瘦了25磅耶
What do you mean it's no good? 25lbs I've lost.

511
00:42:18,260 --> 00:42:20,890
那又怎么样? 你想变成毒瘾虫吗?
So what? You wanna be a dope fiend?

512
00:42:20,920 --> 00:42:23,680
毒虫? 我有口吐白沫吗?
Dope fiend? Am I foaming at the mouth?

513
00:42:23,681 --> 00:42:25,520
人家是个好医生
He's a nice doctor.

514
00:42:25,560 --> 00:42:27,820
我告诉你 那家伙一点都不好
I am telling you, he's no good.

515
00:42:27,920 --> 00:42:29,670
你怎么会知道那么多?
How come you know so much?

516
00:42:29,671 --> 00:42:32,120
你怎么会比医生更了解药呢?
How come you know more than a doctor?

517
00:42:33,820 --> 00:42:37,820
相信我 妈 我知道的. 好吗?
Believe me, Ma, I know. All right?

518
00:42:38,820 --> 00:42:40,990
你会慢慢上瘾的
You'll get strung out for creat sick.

519
00:42:41,020 --> 00:42:44,120
噢 别这样嘛! 我快要可以穿那件红礼服了
Ah, come on! I almost fit in my red dress.

520
00:42:44,160 --> 00:42:47,220
就是去参加你高中毕业典礼那件
The one I wore to your high school graduation.

521
00:42:47,260 --> 00:42:49,520
你爸爸好喜欢那件
The one your father liked so much.

522
00:42:49,620 --> 00:42:49,893
噢,
oh,

523
00:42:49,894 --> 00:42:53,720
我记得他看我穿那件时的眼神
I remember how he looked at me in that red dress.

524
00:42:55,220 --> 00:42:58,720
妈 那件红礼服有什么大不了的吗?
Ma, what's the big deal about the red dress?

525
00:43:00,720 --> 00:43:03,120
我要穿它上…
I'm going to wear it at...

526
00:43:04,220 --> 00:43:06,290
你还不知道!
You don't know!

527
00:43:06,320 --> 00:43:08,014
我要上电视了
I'm gonna be on television.

528
00:43:08,015 --> 00:43:11,120
我接到了电话和申请书
I got a call and an application...

529
00:43:11,220 --> 00:43:14,120
噢 妈 谁在跟你开玩笑?
Come on, Ma, who's pulling your leg?

530
00:43:14,160 --> 00:43:16,090
不 不 不. 我跟你说
No, no, no. I'm tellin' ya.

531
00:43:16,120 --> 00:43:19,320
我要上电视当个参赛者
I'm gonna be a contestant on television.

532
00:43:19,420 --> 00:43:22,020
他们还没有告诉我什么时后上
They haven't told me when yet,

533
00:43:22,120 --> 00:43:23,878
不过一定会很骄傲的,
but you'll be proud

534
00:43:23,879 --> 00:43:27,220
当你看到妈妈穿上红礼服 金鞋子上电视时
when you see your mother in her red dress on TV.

535
00:43:27,320 --> 00:43:29,608
上电视有什么大不了?
What is the big deal?

536
00:43:29,609 --> 00:43:32,520
那些药在你上电视前会要你的命
Those pills will kill you before you get on.

537
00:43:32,560 --> 00:43:34,520
“没什么大不了?. ”
"Big deal? "

538
00:43:34,620 --> 00:43:36,490
坐计程车的时后
You drove up in a cab.

539
00:43:36,520 --> 00:43:39,520
你知道谁坐最好的位子吗?
Did you see who had the best seat?

540
00:43:39,560 --> 00:43:42,220
我现在是有名的人了 哈瑞
I'm somebody now, Harry.

541
00:43:42,260 --> 00:43:44,820
大家都喜欢我
Everybody likes me.

542
00:43:44,860 --> 00:43:46,590
过不久…
Soon...

543
00:43:46,620 --> 00:43:49,272
成千上万的人会看到我
millions of people will see me

544
00:43:49,273 --> 00:43:50,720
而且会喜欢我
and they'll all like me.

545
00:43:51,420 --> 00:43:53,620
我会跟他们谈到你…
I'll tell them about you...

546
00:43:53,660 --> 00:43:55,320
还有你爸爸
and your father.

547
00:43:55,920 --> 00:43:57,820
他对我们有多好
How good he was to us.

548
00:43:57,920 --> 00:43:59,620
记得吗?
Remember?

549
00:44:02,820 --> 00:44:05,420
它是早上起床的理由
It's a reason to get up in the morning.

550
00:44:06,520 --> 00:44:08,653
也是减肥的理由
It's a reason to lose weight,

551
00:44:08,654 --> 00:44:11,320
为了能穿上那件红礼服
to fit in the red dress.

552
00:44:12,920 --> 00:44:15,020
它是微笑的理由
It's a reason to smile.

553
00:44:16,920 --> 00:44:20,120
它让明天更美好
It makes tomorrow all right.

554
00:44:22,220 --> 00:44:24,920
我得到了什么 哈瑞?
What have I got, Harry?

555
00:44:25,620 --> 00:44:27,090
嗯?
Hmm?

556
00:44:27,120 --> 00:44:30,053
为什么我还要整理床
Why should I even make the bed

557
00:44:30,054 --> 00:44:31,520
洗碗盘?
or wash the dishes?

558
00:44:31,620 --> 00:44:35,120
这些我都做 但我为何要做?
I do them, but why should I?

559
00:44:36,320 --> 00:44:38,020
我很孤单
I'm alone.

560
00:44:39,120 --> 00:44:42,520
你爸爸走了 你也离家了
Your father's gone, you're gone.

561
00:44:44,920 --> 00:44:47,520
我没有人可以…
I got no one to...

562
00:44:47,560 --> 00:44:49,420
照顾
care for.

563
00:44:50,220 --> 00:44:52,420
我得到了什么 哈瑞?
What have I got, Harry?

564
00:44:57,420 --> 00:44:59,120
我很寂寞
I'm lonely.

565
00:45:01,420 --> 00:45:03,190
我老了
I'm old.

566
00:45:03,220 --> 00:45:05,620
你有朋友呀 妈
You got friends, Ma.

567
00:45:05,720 --> 00:45:08,020
那不一样的
It's not the same.

568
00:45:09,520 --> 00:45:11,320
她们不需要我
They don't need me.

569
00:45:16,520 --> 00:45:18,620
我喜欢这样的感觉
I like the way I feel.

570
00:45:20,620 --> 00:45:23,390
我喜欢想着红礼服
I like thinking about the red dress...

571
00:45:23,420 --> 00:45:27,520
想着电视 还有你跟你爸爸
and the television and you and your father.

572
00:45:29,120 --> 00:45:32,720
现在我看到阳光 都带着笑容
Now when I get the sun, I smile.

573
00:45:38,920 --> 00:45:40,720
我会回来看你的 妈
I'll come and visit, Ma.

574
00:45:41,820 --> 00:45:43,529
我现在按步就班
Now that I'm straight,

575
00:45:43,530 --> 00:45:46,520
我的生意也上轨道 我会回来的
m-my business is going good, I'll come.

576
00:45:46,560 --> 00:45:49,120
我和玛丽会回来吃晚餐
Me and Marion, we'll come for dinner.

577
00:45:49,160 --> 00:45:50,990
好呀 你带她来
Good. You bring her.

578
00:45:51,020 --> 00:45:53,820
我会做蘑菇汤跟烧烤给你们吃
I'll make you mushroom soup and a roast.

579
00:45:54,820 --> 00:45:58,020
这样不错 妈 很棒
That sounds great, Ma. That sounds great.

580
00:45:58,120 --> 00:46:02,020
- 我会先打个电话回来 好吗? - 好
- I'll call ahead, all right? - OK.

581
00:46:03,820 --> 00:46:05,390
我很高兴
I'm glad.

582
00:46:05,420 --> 00:46:07,920
我很高兴你有个不错的女朋友
I'm glad you have a nice girl

583
00:46:07,921 --> 00:46:10,420
还有自己的生意 我很高兴
and your own business. I'm glad.

584
00:46:16,920 --> 00:46:18,490
我该走了 妈
I gotta go, Ma.

585
00:46:18,520 --> 00:46:21,920
我待会儿在曼哈顿跟人有约
I got an appointment in Manhattan in a little bit

586
00:46:21,960 --> 00:46:23,820
不过我会回来的
but I'll be back.

587
00:46:23,920 --> 00:46:26,170
- 好 你…你还有家里钥匙吗?
- OK, y-you still got your key?

588
00:46:26,171 --> 00:46:27,520
- 嗯 我有 妈
- Yeah, I got it, Ma.

589
00:46:30,020 --> 00:46:31,720
再见 儿子
Bye, Son.

590
00:47:09,620 --> 00:47:12,020
布迪说你反应快
Brody says you comin' up quick.

591
00:47:12,060 --> 00:47:15,320
谢啦 老兄
oh. Thanks, man.

592
00:47:18,020 --> 00:47:19,386
他说你很聪明
He says you're smart,

593
00:47:19,387 --> 00:47:22,120
忠诚l 而且不是个毒鬼
you're loyal and you're not a junkie.

594
00:47:25,720 --> 00:47:27,620
布迪想提拔你
Brody wants to promote you.

595
00:47:27,720 --> 00:47:30,620
让你承担更多责任 有兴趣吗?
Give you more responsibility. Interested?

596
00:47:30,720 --> 00:47:32,620
有 当然!
Yeah, yeah!

597
00:47:32,720 --> 00:47:34,720
当然有 老兄
Shit, yeah, man.

598
00:47:39,020 --> 00:47:41,520
布迪说你背判他的话 他会杀了你
Brody says, you fuck him, I kill you.

599
00:47:41,560 --> 00:47:43,920
- 我知道 - 记住
- I got that. - Remember that.

600
00:47:47,620 --> 00:47:49,720
靠! 你有个白人司机!
Shit! You got a white driver!

601
00:47:56,620 --> 00:47:58,520
干!
Fuck!

602
00:48:00,720 --> 00:48:03,020
搞什么呀?
What the fuck?

603
00:48:12,320 --> 00:48:14,020
别动!
Don't move!

604
00:48:47,820 --> 00:48:50,120
我爱你 哈瑞
I love you, Harry.

605
00:48:53,320 --> 00:48:55,620
你让我觉得像个人
You make me feel like a person.

606
00:48:58,220 --> 00:49:01,020
像我自己
Like I'm me...

607
00:49:02,720 --> 00:49:04,620
让我觉得很美
and I'm beautiful.

608
00:49:06,320 --> 00:49:08,420
你本来就很美
You are beautiful.

609
00:49:12,720 --> 00:49:16,120
你是世上最美的女人
You're the most beautiful girl in the world.

610
00:49:17,720 --> 00:49:19,820
我的梦人情人
You're my dream.

611
00:49:26,020 --> 00:49:29,490
'不 哥德太太 我很确定 我已经查过了'
'No, I'm certain. I've checked again.'

612
00:49:29,520 --> 00:49:32,820
可能你们上次给我的药效较弱
But maybe you gave me a weaker one last time.

613
00:49:32,920 --> 00:49:34,153
'不可能的
'That isn't possible.

614
00:49:34,154 --> 00:49:36,620
药效都是一样的.'
They're all the same potency.'

615
00:49:36,720 --> 00:49:38,820
可是感觉不一样呀
But something isn't the same.

616
00:49:39,220 --> 00:49:41,183
'你只是渐渐习惯了
'You're becoming adjusted to them.

617
00:49:41,184 --> 00:49:44,020
没什么好担心的 好吗?'
It's nothing to worry about, OK?'

618
00:50:02,220 --> 00:50:04,690
- '我们有了优胜者!' - '有了优胜者!'
- 'We got a winner!' - 'We got a winner!'

619
00:50:04,720 --> 00:50:08,120
'她很漂亮, 极有幽默感
'She's beautiful, with a winning sense of humour

620
00:50:08,160 --> 00:50:09,720
'和魔法般的笑容
'and magical smile.

621
00:50:09,820 --> 00:50:13,420
'来自布鲁克林 布莱顿滩 让我们热烈欢迎
'From Brighton Beach, Brooklyn, let's welcome

622
00:50:13,520 --> 00:50:15,120
'哥德莎拉女士!'
'Mrs Sara Goldfarb!'

623
00:50:15,220 --> 00:50:19,820
'莎啦来劲! 莎啦来劲! 噢 莎拉!
'Juice by Sara! Juice by Sara! Ohh, Sara!

624
00:50:19,920 --> 00:50:24,920
'莎啦热情有劲! 莎啦热情有劲! 噢 莎拉!'
'Sara's got juice! Sara's got juice! Ohh, Sara!'

625
00:50:33,220 --> 00:50:36,120
嗨 泰隆
Love, Tyrone C.

626
00:50:36,220 --> 00:50:38,820
收拾一下你的东西 有人来保你了
Get your shit together. You made bail.

627
00:50:38,920 --> 00:50:40,520
多少钱?
How much?

628
00:50:40,620 --> 00:50:44,020
花了我们大部份的现金 你行情涨高了
Most of our cash. You're up for consortin'.

629
00:50:44,060 --> 00:50:45,920
噢 靠 他妈的!
oh, shit, man!

630
00:50:46,020 --> 00:50:47,125
安杰拉说
Angel says

631
00:50:47,126 --> 00:50:49,890
意大利人跟黑人在争斗
there's a war between the Italians and Blacks.

632
00:50:49,920 --> 00:50:51,831
货会留在佛罗里达
Sal the Geep is keeping the shit in Florida

633
00:50:51,832 --> 00:50:54,220
除非布迪的势力消失
until Brody's gone.

634
00:50:54,320 --> 00:50:55,290
靠
Shit.

635
00:50:55,320 --> 00:50:58,320
- 没有人可以拿到货 - 除了提姆老大
- No one's got a thing. - Except Big Tim.

636
00:50:58,360 --> 00:51:00,290
靠. 我们去找他
Shit. Let's go see him.

637
00:51:00,320 --> 00:51:03,220
他不卖的 只给娘们
He only givin' up for pussy.

638
00:51:03,320 --> 00:51:04,820
什么?
What?

639
00:51:04,920 --> 00:51:07,620
娘们. 他喜欢这一套 老兄
Pussy. He's hooked on it, man.

640
00:51:07,720 --> 00:51:09,625
我说我会满足他要的
I'd give him all he wants.

641
00:51:09,626 --> 00:51:11,320
他嫌我不够漂亮
He said I ain't cute enough.

642
00:51:23,220 --> 00:51:26,190
'来吧 第叁项!
'Come on, number three!

643
00:51:26,220 --> 00:51:30,220
'这会让很多人发疯
'This drives most people crazy.

644
00:51:30,320 --> 00:51:32,220
'他们不会喜欢的
'They're not gonna like it.

645
00:51:32,320 --> 00:51:34,034
'到现在都还算容易!
'This is easy so far!

646
00:51:34,035 --> 00:51:35,920
戒除30天 就会…'
Give it up for 30 days, it will...'

647
00:51:49,600 --> 00:51:51,500
你还好吧?
You all right?

648
00:51:54,200 --> 00:51:56,700
嗯. 只是个恶梦
Yeah. It was just a bad dream.

649
00:51:58,100 --> 00:51:59,800
要喝点水吗?
Want some water?

650
00:52:21,600 --> 00:52:23,400
也许我们现在该打一点
Maybe we should dip in now.

651
00:52:23,500 --> 00:52:26,300
好了!玛丽 我跟你说过了 好吗?
Come on! I already told you, all right?

652
00:52:28,300 --> 00:52:30,160
我们就剩这一点了
It's all we have.

653
00:52:30,200 --> 00:52:33,300
泰隆早上会再带点来的 哈瑞
Tyrone is gonna score in the morning, Harry.

654
00:52:39,000 --> 00:52:40,800
我不知道 只是…
I don't know, it's...

655
00:52:40,900 --> 00:52:42,700
只是发点劳骚
it's a bitch out there.

656
00:52:44,700 --> 00:52:46,700
没事的
It'll be OK.

657
00:52:48,700 --> 00:52:50,600
会没事的 哈瑞
It'll be OK, Harry.

658
00:52:54,800 --> 00:52:56,900
是呀…
Yeah...

659
00:52:57,000 --> 00:52:58,800
我想是吧
I guess so.

660
00:53:05,700 --> 00:53:07,900
我爱你 哈瑞
I love you, Harry.

661
00:53:46,400 --> 00:53:50,400
有什么问题吗? 体重正常
What's the problem? The weight's fine.

662
00:53:50,500 --> 00:53:52,800
体重正常 我可不
The weight's fine, I'm not.

663
00:53:53,900 --> 00:53:56,000
电冰箱…
The refrigerator...

664
00:53:57,600 --> 00:53:59,500
怎么了?
Something wrong?

665
00:54:01,700 --> 00:54:03,500
每样东西都…
Everything's...

666
00:54:07,900 --> 00:54:09,900
都混在一起了
all mixed up.

667
00:54:10,000 --> 00:54:12,600
- 好杂乱… - 没什么好担心的
- Confused... - Nothing to worry about.

668
00:54:12,700 --> 00:54:15,900
填好这张表 约下星期看诊时间
Get this filled. Make an appointment for a week.

669
00:54:25,200 --> 00:54:26,600
怎么了?
Well?

670
00:54:27,700 --> 00:54:30,000
泰还没有拿到东西
Ty ain't found nothin' yet.

671
00:54:31,900 --> 00:54:33,800
那我们怎么办?
What are we gonna do?

672
00:54:33,830 --> 00:54:35,760
我不知道
I don't know.

673
00:54:35,800 --> 00:54:38,500
好吧 你要想点办法 哈瑞
Well, you have to do something, Harry.

674
00:54:38,600 --> 00:54:41,850
都是你 我们早上才没有东西
It's your fault we don't have anything.

675
00:54:41,880 --> 00:54:45,060
- 你在说什么? - 你昨晚激动得把剩的都用完了
- What? - You were all hot last night.

676
00:54:45,100 --> 00:54:46,163
- 简直胡扯!
- That is such bullshit!

677
00:54:46,164 --> 00:54:49,050
- 你大可不用那样 我们就有东西了…
- We could've had something...

678
00:54:49,080 --> 00:54:50,924
我会想要看你受苦
Was I supposed to watch you push off

679
00:54:50,925 --> 00:54:53,000
自己置身事外吗?
and not go myself?

680
00:54:53,030 --> 00:54:55,100
别都往我身上推 好吗?
Don't put it all on me, OK?

681
00:55:06,300 --> 00:55:09,600
别担心 老兄 我们会再装满它的
Don't worry, man. We'll fill it up again.

682
00:55:10,600 --> 00:55:12,500
情况会好转的
Things'll get better,

683
00:55:12,600 --> 00:55:16,200
到时我们就能再装满它的 懂吗?
then we'll be fillin' the box back up, you know?

684
00:55:23,000 --> 00:55:26,000
想听听新的消息吗?
So, you wanna hear the news?

685
00:55:26,030 --> 00:55:27,860
什么消息?
What news?

686
00:55:27,900 --> 00:55:31,600
有好消息 也有坏消息
You got your good news, you got your bad news.

687
00:55:31,700 --> 00:55:33,360
说吧!
Shoot.

688
00:55:33,400 --> 00:55:35,260
好消息是
Good news is,

689
00:55:35,300 --> 00:55:38,300
再过几天街上就会出现高档货
there's gonna be some prime on the street.

690
00:55:39,300 --> 00:55:41,900
- 是吗? - 嗯
- Really? - Mm-hm.

691
00:55:42,000 --> 00:55:44,100
谁告诉你的?
Who told you that?

692
00:55:45,200 --> 00:55:47,300
- 安杰拉 - 是喔?
- Angel. - Yeah?

693
00:55:47,400 --> 00:55:48,600
大盘放话
Sal the Geep sent word

694
00:55:48,601 --> 00:55:51,900
在圣诞期间放点东西出来
to let a couple of keys go for Christmas,

695
00:55:51,930 --> 00:55:54,060
他是个好的基督徒
him being a good Christian and all,

696
00:55:54,100 --> 00:55:57,200
不想破坏过节的气氛
not wantin' bad feelin' during the season.

697
00:55:57,230 --> 00:55:59,800
- 你信吗? - 嗯 相信…
- You believe it? - Well, I did...

698
00:55:59,900 --> 00:56:01,900
直到我听到了坏消息
till I heard the bad news.

699
00:56:07,700 --> 00:56:09,460
什么?
Yeah?

700
00:56:09,500 --> 00:56:12,400
价格加倍 还得按重量买
Price is double. You have to cop for weight.

701
00:56:12,500 --> 00:56:15,800
- 至少一半的基本量 - 多少?
- At least a half a piece. - How much?

702
00:56:17,100 --> 00:56:19,000
- 2块 - 2块?
- Two. - Two?

703
00:56:19,100 --> 00:56:22,200
- 神经病呀! - 不然又能怎样?
- That's fuckin' insane! - What you gonna do?

704
00:56:22,300 --> 00:56:24,800
羊毛出在羊身上 这是一定的
Man ain't gonna lay no nickel bag on ya.

705
00:56:24,830 --> 00:56:26,700
我们去哪拿到2块?
Where we gonna get two?

706
00:56:26,730 --> 00:56:28,860
你是说阿诺?
You mean Arnold?

707
00:56:28,900 --> 00:56:32,900
是呀 你父母又不回你电话
Well, your parents won't even return your call.

708
00:56:34,200 --> 00:56:36,200
我几个月没见过他了
I haven't seen him in months.

709
00:56:36,300 --> 00:56:39,300
- 又如何? 他还是有打电话给你 不是吗?
- So? He's still callin', ain't he?

710
00:56:39,301 --> 00:56:40,300
- 我不知道
- I don't know.

711
00:56:41,800 --> 00:56:44,600
听着 我不知道还有什么其它办法
Look, I don't know what else to do.

712
00:56:44,700 --> 00:56:47,460
这是我们重回计划的最后机会了!
It's our last chance to get back on track!

713
00:56:47,500 --> 00:56:48,150
我们不用再每天争吵
We won't have to squabble

714
00:56:48,351 --> 00:56:51,200
然后彼此僵在那!
and make the freezing scene every day!

715
00:56:53,500 --> 00:56:55,360
我们须要钱
We need the bread.

716
00:56:55,400 --> 00:56:59,000
赚钱不是问题 哈瑞
Getting the money is not the problem, Harry.

717
00:56:59,100 --> 00:57:01,200
那到底问题是什么?
What is the problem?

718
00:57:01,300 --> 00:57:04,300
我不知道该怎么弄到钱
I don't know what I'll have to do to get it.

719
00:57:11,300 --> 00:57:12,950
听着…
Look...

720
00:57:12,980 --> 00:57:14,600
宝贝…
Baby...

721
00:57:16,300 --> 00:57:18,800
我们会很快再展开生意
we'll be back in business in no time.

722
00:57:19,900 --> 00:57:22,100
重新再动起来
We'll start movin' again,

723
00:57:22,200 --> 00:57:24,400
还会开始累积财富
and we'll start savin'.

724
00:57:26,200 --> 00:57:28,978
一且会很完美 像原本那样
It'll be perfect, just like it was.

725
00:57:28,979 --> 00:57:30,600
我保证 玛丽
I promise, Marion.

726
00:57:34,300 --> 00:57:36,000
你看着吧
You'll see.

727
00:57:44,700 --> 00:57:46,757
不 我只是 嗯…
No, I've just, uh..

728
00:57:46,758 --> 00:57:50,100
我好像 永远得染上感冒似的
. I've had this flu forever, it seems like.

729
00:57:51,600 --> 00:57:53,247
- 你忧郁吗?
- Are you depressed?

730
00:57:53,248 --> 00:57:55,100
- 不 不是那样的
- No, it's nothing like that.

731
00:57:55,130 --> 00:57:57,800
我一直 嗯… 我一直都很忙
I've been, uh... I've been really busy.

732
00:57:57,900 --> 00:58:01,600
事实上, 我一直在做设计…没停过
Actually, I've been designing... non-stop.

733
00:58:01,700 --> 00:58:05,300
太好了 很高兴知道你有所斩获
Wonderful. Glad to hear you've been productive.

734
00:58:10,100 --> 00:58:11,960
明白得说吧
To be perfectly frank,

735
00:58:12,000 --> 00:58:14,900
接到你的电话我很惊讶
I was a little surprised to hear from you.

736
00:58:18,200 --> 00:58:22,400
- 有什么问题吗? - 没有 为何这样问?
- Is there something wrong? - No. Why?

737
00:58:22,500 --> 00:58:25,200
嗯 通常是这样子的...
Well, it's usually the case...

738
00:58:25,201 --> 00:58:27,900
接到许久没消息的人电话
from someone you haven't heard from.

739
00:58:28,700 --> 00:58:30,600
一切都很好
Everything's fine.

740
00:58:34,400 --> 00:58:36,200
事实上
Actually,

741
00:58:40,100 --> 00:58:42,300
我有点事相求
I have a favour to ask.

742
00:58:48,200 --> 00:58:50,700
王八蛋!
You smug fuck!

743
00:58:50,730 --> 00:58:53,200
什么呢?
What is it?

744
00:58:58,400 --> 00:59:00,450
我需要点钱
I need some money.

745
00:59:00,480 --> 00:59:02,500
我能知道你为何需要钱吗?
May I ask what for?

746
00:59:04,300 --> 00:59:06,400
- 把灯关掉好吗?
- Could you turn the light off?

747
00:59:06,401 --> 00:59:08,500
- 为什么想关灯呢?
- Why do you want the light off?

748
00:59:08,530 --> 00:59:10,400
没有为什么
I just do.

749
00:59:11,600 --> 00:59:14,300
- 你没做过吗? - 拜托 阿诺
- You never did before. - Please, Arnold.

750
01:02:43,800 --> 01:02:46,300
- 人到哪去了? - 我不知道 老兄
- Where is everybody? - I don't know, man.

751
01:02:46,400 --> 01:02:49,600
安杰拉只说在沃德邦超市碰面
All Angel said was meet at Waldbaum's.

752
01:02:52,700 --> 01:02:54,961
- 确定是这一家吗?
- Is this the right Waldbaum's?

753
01:02:54,962 --> 01:02:56,400
- 对 我确定
- Yeah, I'm positive.

754
01:02:57,700 --> 01:03:01,200
你只要帮我留意 我也帮你留意
You just watch my back, and I'll watch yours.

755
01:03:04,800 --> 01:03:07,500
- 我们现在该怎么办? - 嘿
- What are we supposed to do now? - Hey.

756
01:03:20,200 --> 01:03:22,300
真是人山人海
Everyone and their mother.

757
01:03:24,100 --> 01:03:26,500
车子要来了 后退
The truck's gonna be here. Back up.

758
01:03:29,300 --> 01:03:30,700
往后退
Back up.

759
01:04:54,400 --> 01:04:56,200
回来!
Come back!

760
01:04:58,800 --> 01:05:01,446
去他妈的药头!
Stupid fuckin' junkie!

761
01:05:01,447 --> 01:05:03,100
我们被耍了
We're fucked! We are fucked.

762
01:05:03,200 --> 01:05:05,300
妈的 他们在佛洲坐热太阳
Sitting in that hot-ass sun

763
01:05:05,400 --> 01:05:08,800
我们却要坐在这寒冷的冰雪中
while we sit here ass deep in motherfuckin' snow.

764
01:05:12,500 --> 01:05:14,400
再回去看看不知道会怎样?
What if we went down there?

765
01:05:14,500 --> 01:05:16,850
- 你是认真的吗? - 为什么不?
- Are you serious? - Why not?

766
01:05:16,880 --> 01:05:19,200
你在鬼扯些什么?
What the fuck are you sayin'?

767
01:05:19,300 --> 01:05:23,600
你想你可以攀得上关系吗?
We ask some room clerk at some hotel for a connection?

768
01:05:23,700 --> 01:05:25,650
你不把握机会吗?
You saying you can't nose out some dope

769
01:05:25,651 --> 01:05:27,600
当货来的时候
when it's around?

770
01:05:27,700 --> 01:05:30,560
老兄 我们没什么好失去的了 现在是大好时机
Man, we got nothin' to lose. It's wide open.

771
01:05:30,600 --> 01:05:32,560
如果我们马上回去的话
And if we get there right away

772
01:05:32,561 --> 01:05:34,700
要卖多少价格就由我们来订
we can name our own price,

773
01:05:34,730 --> 01:05:37,900
还可让那群白痴为我们上街头
and have those fools cover the street for us.

774
01:05:40,200 --> 01:05:41,319
是呀 老兄
Yeah, man.

775
01:05:41,320 --> 01:05:44,900
去年夏天真他妈的开心 不是吗?
Last summer was a motherfuckin' ball, huh, Jim?

776
01:05:49,100 --> 01:05:50,720
就好像有千年那么久
Just seems like a thousand years ago

777
01:05:50,721 --> 01:05:53,300
了至去年夏天
since last summer, man.

778
01:05:53,330 --> 01:05:55,500
我们会再像那时一样的 老兄
It'll be like that again, man.

779
01:05:59,600 --> 01:06:02,000
我可以叫安杰拉给我们简短的
I could get Angel to get us a short...

780
01:06:02,100 --> 01:06:04,900
如果我们能保证给他高档海洛因
if we promise him some dynamite scag.

781
01:07:22,400 --> 01:07:24,950
感谢老天. 你去哪了?
Thank God. Where have you been?

782
01:07:24,980 --> 01:07:27,500
你以为我们去哪了?
Where the hell you think I've been?

783
01:07:28,300 --> 01:07:31,500
- 东西呢? - 我们碰到了一点麻烦
- Where's the score? - We had a bit of a problem.

784
01:07:31,600 --> 01:07:35,500
我是说 每样事情都还好,只是
I mean, everything was goin' good, and then...

785
01:07:35,530 --> 01:07:38,060
- 有些人渣药头… - 怎么了?
- some dumb-ass junkie... - Did what?

786
01:07:38,100 --> 01:07:41,500
有些人渣药头怎么了?! 你搞砸了是吗?!
Some dumb-ass junkie did what?! You fucked up?!

787
01:07:41,600 --> 01:07:43,082
- 你在发什么神经?
- What the fuck is wrong with you?

788
01:07:43,083 --> 01:07:45,900
- 你保证过不会有问题的! 记得吗?
- You promised it was gonna be OK.

789
01:07:46,000 --> 01:07:48,042
我为了你跟那个混球搞
I fucked that sleaze-bag.

790
01:07:48,043 --> 01:07:49,900
为了你我什么都做了!
I put myself through hell for you!

791
01:07:50,000 --> 01:07:51,762
- 就是没有货嘛!
- There's nothing out there!

792
01:07:51,763 --> 01:07:54,700
- 我才不管! 妈的死无赖!
- I don't give a shit! Fucking loser!

793
01:07:57,400 --> 01:07:59,800
你就是以为我们还有就对了?
You wanna be sure we have some extra?

794
01:07:59,900 --> 01:08:02,800
泰告诉我有个家伙有一些
Ty told me about a guy holding some weight.

795
01:08:02,830 --> 01:08:05,100
不过他不卖的!
But he ain't sellin' it!

796
01:08:05,130 --> 01:08:07,100
'喂?'
'Yeah?'

797
01:08:07,200 --> 01:08:09,800
- 给我那家伙的电话 - '哪个?'
- Gimme that guy's number. - 'What guy?'

798
01:08:09,830 --> 01:08:12,400
- 喜欢娘们那个! - '为什么?'
- The guy who likes broads! - 'Why?'

799
01:08:12,500 --> 01:08:14,400
告诉我就对了!
Just gimme the number!

800
01:08:14,500 --> 01:08:18,300
'好拉. 934-8777.'
'All right. 934-8777.'

801
01:08:20,000 --> 01:08:23,600
你这么烦的话, 去跟他搞在一块吧!
You worried so much, go fix yourself up with him!

802
01:08:23,700 --> 01:08:25,938
这样就不须要再等了
You won't have to fuckin' wait

803
01:08:25,939 --> 01:08:28,400
我也不用在街头上受冻了
and I won't freeze my ass off the fucking street!

804
01:08:28,430 --> 01:08:30,300
妈的
Fuck you.

805
01:09:04,500 --> 01:09:06,860
'好的 优胜者出现了'
'All right, we got a winner.'

806
01:09:06,900 --> 01:09:09,800
- '优胜者' - '优胜者出现了'
- 'We got a winner.' - 'We got a winner.'

807
01:09:09,900 --> 01:09:12,500
- '优胜者' - '优胜者出现了'
- 'We got a winner.' - 'We got a winner.'

808
01:09:12,600 --> 01:09:13,965
'她不但美丽
'She's beautiful,

809
01:09:13,966 --> 01:09:16,500
还有过人的幽默和神奇的笑容
with a winning sense of humour and smile.

810
01:09:16,530 --> 01:09:18,100
'她将赢得你们的心!
'She'll win your heart!

811
01:09:18,200 --> 01:09:20,400
'来自布鲁克林 布莱顿滩
'From Brighton Beach, Brooklyn,

812
01:09:20,500 --> 01:09:23,041
'让我们热烈欢迎
'please give a juicy welcome to

813
01:09:23,042 --> 01:09:25,900
哥德莎拉太太!'
our own Mrs Sara Goldfarb!'

814
01:09:26,000 --> 01:09:30,800
'莎拉热情有劲! 莎拉热情有劲! 噢 莎拉!'
'Juice by Sara! Juice by Sara! Ohh, Sara!'

815
01:09:32,700 --> 01:09:34,500
'噢 莎拉!'
'Ohh, Sara!'

816
01:09:34,600 --> 01:09:37,260
'真高兴到来这来'
'It's a pleasure to be here.'

817
01:09:37,300 --> 01:09:39,431
'很高兴你来参加节
'It's a pleasure to have you.

818
01:09:39,432 --> 01:09:41,800
目 你的服装真是出色
And that is one smashing dress.'

819
01:09:44,700 --> 01:09:46,272
'谢谢你. 泰皮
'Thank you. Tappy.

820
01:09:46,273 --> 01:09:49,024
如果你不介意 我想跟我先生
I would like to say hello

821
01:09:49,025 --> 01:09:50,400
西蒙打声招呼
to my husband, Seymour,

822
01:09:50,430 --> 01:09:53,500
'还有我那英俊有为的儿子…'
'and my beautiful, successful son Harold...'

823
01:09:55,600 --> 01:09:57,900
'我希望你活在爱中
'I hope you're in love.

824
01:09:58,000 --> 01:09:59,200
'请来看我,
'Please come and see me,

825
01:09:59,201 --> 01:10:01,800
顺便把玛丽带来 好吗?'
and bring Marion, won't you?'

826
01:10:01,900 --> 01:10:04,060
'我想他很快会来的
'I'm sure he'll be here soon.

827
01:10:04,100 --> 01:10:08,000
'差不多是时候了 你准备好了吗?'
'It's almost that time. Are you ready?'

828
01:10:08,030 --> 01:10:10,000
'我好了 泰皮'
'I'm ready, Tappy.'

829
01:10:12,500 --> 01:10:14,900
'别担心 别担心'
'Not to worry. Not to worry.'

830
01:10:17,900 --> 01:10:20,300
你在那做什么?
What are you doing here?

831
01:10:20,330 --> 01:10:23,660
你怎么会在这?
Why are you here?

832
01:10:23,700 --> 01:10:26,700
- 你想干嘛? - 噢 泰皮!
- What do you want? - Oh, Tappy!

833
01:10:26,800 --> 01:10:29,700
'加入我们一起创造卓越
'Join us in creating excellence.

834
01:10:29,730 --> 01:10:32,600
'噢 我以为你不会叫我'
'Oh, I thought you'd never ask.'

835
01:10:36,500 --> 01:10:39,160
你看这个
Look at this.

836
01:10:39,200 --> 01:10:42,600
- 真呕心 - 你想怎样呢?
- It's disgusting. - What do you expect?

837
01:10:42,700 --> 01:10:45,700
你能做得更好吗?
Could you do any better?

838
01:10:45,730 --> 01:10:47,600
看这个
Look at this.

839
01:10:47,700 --> 01:10:49,414
这是栋老建
It's an old building.

840
01:10:49,415 --> 01:10:51,700
有几年没粉刷过了
It hasn't been painted in years.

841
01:10:51,730 --> 01:10:54,400
我老了! 孤独一人!
I'm old! Alone!

842
01:10:54,500 --> 01:10:56,800
你不了解的
You don't understand.

843
01:10:56,830 --> 01:10:59,100
拜托 我会解释的
Please. I'll explain.

844
01:11:40,300 --> 01:11:43,150
那是什么? 不 我不要!
What is that? No, I don't want that!

845
01:11:43,180 --> 01:11:46,000
你在干什么? 离我远一点!
What are you doing? Get away from me!

846
01:11:46,030 --> 01:11:48,100
- 开始罗 哥德太太 - 什么开始了?
- Ready, Mrs Goldfarb. - Ready for What?

847
01:11:48,200 --> 01:11:50,200
叁 二…
Three, two...

848
01:11:50,300 --> 01:11:54,000
我要做什么?
What am I supposed to do?

849
01:12:32,600 --> 01:12:34,000
我!
Feed me!

850
01:12:41,800 --> 01:12:43,560
我
Feed him yourself.

851
01:12:43,600 --> 01:12:48,060
-   我 莎拉 -   我 莎拉
Feed me, Sara.

852
01:12:48,100 --> 01:12:51,100
我 莎拉!
Feed me, Sara!

853
01:12:51,200 --> 01:12:55,000
我 莎拉!   我 莎拉!
Feed me, Sara! Feed me, Sara!

854
01:13:02,600 --> 01:13:06,000
我只是想上电视! 拜托!
I just wanna be on television! Please!

855
01:13:42,700 --> 01:13:45,300
谢拉 安杰拉
Thank you, Angel.

856
01:13:45,400 --> 01:13:47,400
噢-噢!
Whoo-hoo!

857
01:13:47,500 --> 01:13:49,563
希望这样行得通
Sure hope this motherfucker works.

858
01:13:49,564 --> 01:13:52,400
我的屁股可以好好热一下
My ass could use some heat.

859
01:13:52,500 --> 01:13:54,300
- 要多久才会到?
- How long this trip's gonna take?

860
01:13:54,301 --> 01:13:56,500
- 我会在一天内到达
- We'll make it in a day.

861
01:13:56,600 --> 01:13:58,660
一天? 靠!
A day? Shit!

862
01:13:58,700 --> 01:14:01,050
加州 我们来了
California, here we come.

863
01:14:01,080 --> 01:14:03,140
是佛罗里达 泰 佛州
It's Florida, Ty. Florida.

864
01:14:03,170 --> 01:14:05,160
加州 佛州…
California, Florida...

865
01:14:05,200 --> 01:14:08,000
两个都可让白屁股晒黑是吧
Either way, your pale ass getting a tan.

866
01:14:08,100 --> 01:14:10,500
啊!
Ah!

867
01:14:11,600 --> 01:14:14,700
这辆列车有到麦迪逊大道吗?!
Does this train go to Madison Avenue?!

868
01:14:14,800 --> 01:14:16,700
你认识默林跟布洛克吗?
Do you know Maylin and Block?

869
01:14:16,800 --> 01:14:20,100
我有他们的地址. 在麦迪逊大道上
I have their address. It's on Madison Avenue.

870
01:14:20,200 --> 01:14:23,900
- 我就要上电视了 - 你累坏了!
- I'm gonna be on television. - You're whacked!

871
01:14:25,600 --> 01:14:28,400
嘿! 嘿! 哈罗?
Hey! Hey! Hello?

872
01:14:28,500 --> 01:14:32,400
你知道这辆列车有到麦迪逊大道?
Do you know if this train goes to Madison Avenue?

873
01:14:32,500 --> 01:14:35,300
我要上电视了!
I'm gonna be on television!

874
01:14:36,800 --> 01:14:39,300
我只想知道什么时候
I just have to find out when.

875
01:14:40,900 --> 01:14:42,600
佛罗里达?
Florida?

876
01:14:45,800 --> 01:14:47,900
他什么时候回来?
When is he gonna be back?

877
01:14:49,500 --> 01:14:53,800
几天后? 安杰拉 我该怎么办?
A few days? Angel, what am I supposed to do?

878
01:14:54,900 --> 01:14:57,000
你一定要帮我
Please, you gotta help me.

879
01:14:57,100 --> 01:15:00,000
噢 好啦 我可以给你钱
Oh, come on, I can get you money.

880
01:15:01,100 --> 01:15:04,315
安杰拉 无论如何一定要
Angel, there's gotta be something. Anything.

881
01:15:04,316 --> 01:15:04,900
帮我
Help me.

882
01:15:05,000 --> 01:15:07,660
你怎么不打电话给我呢?
Why aren't you calling me?

883
01:15:07,700 --> 01:15:11,300
我要知道我什么时候上电视
I have to know when I'm gonna be on television.

884
01:15:12,400 --> 01:15:15,160
我是莎拉哥德
I'm Sara Goldfarb.

885
01:15:15,200 --> 01:15:17,000
你应该告诉我
And you should tell me

886
01:15:17,001 --> 01:15:19,400
什么时候要上电视
when I'm gonna be on television.

887
01:15:19,430 --> 01:15:22,100
请稍坐一会 我会通知他们
Just sit for a moment. I'll ring them.

888
01:15:22,130 --> 01:15:24,500
我只是想知道什么时候
I just wanna know when.

889
01:15:24,600 --> 01:15:26,760
也许你弄丢了我的资料!
Maybe you lost my card!

890
01:15:26,761 --> 01:15:30,000
拜托, 请看一下 然后就可以告诉我了
Please, have a look, and you'll tell me.

891
01:15:30,030 --> 01:15:35,000
不是为了得奖 我会把奖给别人的
It's not the prizes. I'll give them away.

892
01:15:35,030 --> 01:15:37,200
我只想上节目
I just wanna be on the show.

893
01:15:37,230 --> 01:15:39,600
我等了好久
I've waited so long...

894
01:15:39,700 --> 01:15:44,400
跟我的儿子哈瑞还有我的小孙子
to be on with my Harry and my grandson.

895
01:15:44,500 --> 01:15:46,900
来 哥德太太 慢慢喝
Here, Mrs Goldfarb, sip this.

896
01:15:47,000 --> 01:15:48,446
有时要一阵子
Sometimes it takes a while

897
01:15:48,447 --> 01:15:50,375
才能通知你上电视
to get called for a show,

898
01:15:50,376 --> 01:15:51,500
哥德太太
Mrs Goldfarb.

899
01:15:51,530 --> 01:15:55,000
噢
Oh. Oooh.

900
01:15:57,100 --> 01:15:59,060
- 是她吗? - 是的
- Is this her? - Yes.

901
01:15:59,100 --> 01:16:03,400
- 你能走吗? - 我可以走台步!
- Can you walk? - I'm walkin' across the stage!

902
01:16:03,500 --> 01:16:07,100
你一定要看看我家哈瑞上电视
And you should see my Harry on television.

903
01:16:07,130 --> 01:16:09,300
我们会把奖给别人
We're giving the prizes away.

904
01:16:09,400 --> 01:16:13,300
我只是想上节目!
I just wanted to be on the show!

905
01:16:14,800 --> 01:16:19,000
- 她叫什么名字? - 应该是莎拉哥德吧
- What's her name? - We think it's Sara Goldfarb.

906
01:16:19,100 --> 01:16:22,700
跟西蒙说在美容院跟我碰面
Tell Seymour to meet me at the beauty parlour.

907
01:16:22,800 --> 01:16:23,505
我穿了
I've got the red dress that

908
01:16:23,506 --> 01:16:26,800
参加哈瑞毕业典礼的那件红礼服
I wore to Harry's graduation and gold shoes.

909
01:16:26,900 --> 01:16:29,300
好了 哥德太太. 我们走吧
oK, Mrs Goldfarb. Here we go.

910
01:16:29,400 --> 01:16:32,000
一 二 叁…
- One, two, three...

911
01:16:32,100 --> 01:16:34,500
放轻松慢慢来
Let's take it nice and easy.

912
01:16:57,900 --> 01:17:00,400
'喂?'
'Yeah?'

913
01:17:23,600 --> 01:17:25,300
'喂?'
'Yeah?'

914
01:17:27,100 --> 01:17:29,900
嗨…
Hi...

915
01:17:33,000 --> 01:17:36,500
告诉罗丝说我要上电视了
Tell Rose I'm going to be on television.

916
01:17:53,400 --> 01:17:55,300
噢
Whoo.

917
01:18:04,500 --> 01:18:06,160
噢 靠!
oh, shit!

918
01:18:06,200 --> 01:18:08,760
天呀! 你有那玩意多久了?
God damn! How long you had that?

919
01:18:08,800 --> 01:18:10,366
- 只有几天
- Just a few days.

920
01:18:10,367 --> 01:18:13,500
- 那东西看起来不太好
- That shit don't look too good.

921
01:18:13,530 --> 01:18:15,900
我也觉得不是很舒服 老兄
It don't feel too good either, man.

922
01:18:17,200 --> 01:18:20,800
不过来点海洛因就会没事了
But a little stuff will take care of that.

923
01:18:20,830 --> 01:18:23,010
嘿! 不要打在那里!
Hey! Don't shoot in there!

924
01:18:23,050 --> 01:18:25,200
不这样的话 血管会爆开
I'll blow it if I don't.

925
01:18:26,100 --> 01:18:27,700
妈的
Fuck it.

926
01:18:36,800 --> 01:18:38,400
噢…
oh...

927
01:18:40,100 --> 01:18:41,700
靠
Shit.

928
01:18:57,100 --> 01:18:59,166
- 嗨 还好吗? 听得到吗?
- Hi, how are you? Can you hear me?

929
01:18:59,167 --> 01:19:00,200
- 嗯 西蒙
- Yes, Seymour.

930
01:19:00,300 --> 01:19:01,966
- 有吃了什么吗?
- Take anything?

931
01:19:01,967 --> 01:19:03,800
- 我穿了红礼服还有…
- I took my red dress and...

932
01:19:03,900 --> 01:19:05,925
- 非紧急状况. 带她到精神科
- No emergency. Take her to psych.

933
01:19:05,926 --> 01:19:06,600
- 电视
- Television.

934
01:19:17,700 --> 01:19:19,400
进来吧
Come on in.

935
01:19:22,300 --> 01:19:23,700
谢谢
Thanks.

936
01:19:29,100 --> 01:19:30,900
你叫什么?
What's your name?

937
01:19:33,000 --> 01:19:34,600
玛丽
Marion.

938
01:19:34,700 --> 01:19:36,600
嗯 你知道吗?
Well, what do you know?

939
01:19:36,700 --> 01:19:38,600
罗宾汉里的少女玛丽
Maid Marion.

940
01:19:45,100 --> 01:19:47,300
我是小约翰
I'm little John.

941
01:19:50,200 --> 01:19:51,660
你这里景色不错
Beautiful view.

942
01:19:51,700 --> 01:19:54,400
你知道我喜欢小女生什么吗?
You know what I like about paddy chicks?

943
01:19:55,600 --> 01:19:58,300
她们口技都不错
They give good head.

944
01:19:58,400 --> 01:20:01,100
黑妞们就是不会口交
Black broads know nothin' about head.

945
01:20:01,130 --> 01:20:02,960
不知道为什么
I don't know why.

946
01:20:03,000 --> 01:20:06,700
可能是按部落传统来做的吧
Maybe it's to do with some ancient tribal custom.

947
01:20:11,700 --> 01:20:13,800
来吧
Come here.

948
01:20:26,400 --> 01:20:29,800
嗯. 最好留点体力
Mmm. Better save some of that energy.

949
01:20:46,900 --> 01:20:49,200
噢 我知道它很漂亮 宝贝
oh, I know it's pretty, baby,

950
01:20:49,230 --> 01:20:51,500
但我不放它出来亮相
but I didn't take it out for air.

951
01:21:02,100 --> 01:21:04,300
好呀
Yeah.

952
01:21:08,700 --> 01:21:12,300
我跟你说过离那只手臂远一点. 知道吗?
I told your ass, stay away from that arm. See?

953
01:21:13,900 --> 01:21:16,100
我得打电话给玛丽 老兄
I gotta call Marion, man.

954
01:21:16,200 --> 01:21:19,400
现在来说那可是长途电话罗
That's about to be a long-distance call now.

955
01:21:19,500 --> 01:21:20,987
600哩了!
That's 600 miles!

956
01:21:20,988 --> 01:21:23,750
我们接近了迈阿密600哩了
We are 600 miles closer to Miami.

957
01:21:23,780 --> 01:21:28,000
是呀 也远离纽约600哩了 泰
It's also 600 miles further away from New York.

958
01:21:33,300 --> 01:21:36,050
你知道吗 我还有真正好口味的货
I know where to get a real nice taste,

959
01:21:36,080 --> 01:21:38,760
虽然有点竞赛的味道 星期天晚上t?
though it's more like play. Sunday night?

960
01:21:38,800 --> 01:21:41,112
我们发起了一个聚会
We're throwing a little gathering.

961
01:21:41,113 --> 01:21:42,500
大家人都很好
All good people.

962
01:21:42,530 --> 01:21:44,600
不行 我没空
I can't, I'm busy.

963
01:21:44,700 --> 01:21:46,960
反正我的瘾不是很重
Anyway, I'm not really hooked.

964
01:21:47,000 --> 01:21:50,200
噢 我知道 但是口味真的不错
Oh, I know, but it's a real nice taste.

965
01:21:56,700 --> 01:21:59,000
星期天见了 少女玛丽
I'll see you Sunday, Maid Marion.

966
01:22:00,600 --> 01:22:03,260
好了 哥德太太 试着回答我的问题
OK, just try and answer my questions.

967
01:22:03,300 --> 01:22:06,392
- 你什么时候开始服用药片?
- When did you start taking pills?

968
01:22:06,393 --> 01:22:08,160
- 噢 夏天时
- Oh, the summer.

969
01:22:08,200 --> 01:22:10,103
- 你从去年夏天开始服用?
- You started last summer?

970
01:22:10,104 --> 01:22:12,300
- 我得到做日光浴最棒的位子
- I got the best place in the sun.

971
01:22:12,330 --> 01:22:14,513
- 艾达帮我整理头发
- Ada fixed my hair.

972
01:22:14,514 --> 01:22:16,300
- 一切都会很好的
- Everything is gonna be all right.

973
01:22:16,330 --> 01:22:18,800
我们很快就会帮你整修
We'll get you fixed up in no time.

974
01:22:40,200 --> 01:22:43,100
- 撑着点 老兄 - 我真的撑不下去了
- Hold tight, man. - I can't fucking cut it.

975
01:22:43,200 --> 01:22:45,300
我得为我的手臂想点办法
I gotta do something about my arm.

976
01:22:45,330 --> 01:22:47,400
让我看看怎么了
Let me see what it looks like.

977
01:22:54,500 --> 01:22:56,900
噢 天呀 靠!
oh, damn, Jim!

978
01:22:58,100 --> 01:22:59,500
噢
oh, man.

979
01:22:59,600 --> 01:23:02,260
我没看过这么呕心的东西
That's one ugly motherfucker.

980
01:23:02,300 --> 01:23:04,950
- 我要打给玛丽 - 真他妈的
- I gotta call Marion. - Fuck that.

981
01:23:04,980 --> 01:23:07,600
你非上医院不可了 老兄
We gotta get you to a hospital, man.

982
01:23:12,700 --> 01:23:14,460
那是什么?
What is that?

983
01:23:14,500 --> 01:23:18,200
我不要 我不要!
I don't want that. I don't want that!

984
01:23:18,230 --> 01:23:20,500
啊! 呃…
Ah! Oh...

985
01:23:56,600 --> 01:23:58,660
什么问题?
What's the problem?

986
01:23:58,700 --> 01:24:01,373
- 我的手臂 我的手臂痛得要命
- It's my arm. My arm is killin' me.

987
01:24:01,374 --> 01:24:02,800
- 我来看一下
- let's have a look at it.

988
01:24:07,000 --> 01:24:08,500
好吧
All right.

989
01:24:12,800 --> 01:24:14,700
我等一下就回来
I'll be back in a minute.

990
01:24:41,400 --> 01:24:43,600
我想通宵玩二十一点
I wanna play blackjack all night long.

991
01:24:43,700 --> 01:24:45,207
所以我就来排班.
So I make up this routine.

992
01:24:45,208 --> 01:24:48,600
我说 “尽管去吧. 我不是很舒服”
I say, "you go ahead. I don't feel good."

993
01:24:48,630 --> 01:24:50,860
很显然的 他们离开了…
Sure enough, they leave...

994
01:24:50,900 --> 01:24:53,100
好了吗? 一 二 叁
Ready? One, two and three.

995
01:24:54,800 --> 01:24:56,960
他们一离开
As soon as they leave,

996
01:24:57,000 --> 01:24:58,647
我马上跑回赌场
I go running back to the casino,

997
01:24:58,648 --> 01:25:00,500
坐在二十一点台桌上
sit at my blackjack table.

998
01:25:00,600 --> 01:25:02,600
我整晚都泡在那里
I am there for the whole night.

999
01:25:02,700 --> 01:25:04,752
最后 我赢了不少
Finally, I get up so big,

1000
01:25:04,753 --> 01:25:08,600
我口袋里有五个一百的黑色筹码
I got five $100 black chips in my pocket.

1001
01:25:08,700 --> 01:25:11,300
我发誓 时间过得真快
I swear to God. The hours are going by.

1002
01:25:11,400 --> 01:25:14,325
我回来时 跟一个十七岁辣妹搭讪
I'm laying back, hittin' on hard 17 s.

1003
01:25:14,326 --> 01:25:15,300
真是漂亮
It was beautiful.

1004
01:25:15,400 --> 01:25:17,600
接着我所知道的
Next thing I know,

1005
01:25:17,700 --> 01:25:19,757
那是一位安全人员
this security guard

1006
01:25:19,758 --> 01:25:22,500
坐在一旁 叫我非离开不可
is sitting there telling me I have to leave.

1007
01:25:22,600 --> 01:25:25,900
我说 “你为什么说我要离开?”
I'm like, "Why you telling me I have to leave?"

1008
01:25:26,000 --> 01:25:28,400
他说, “你要离开是因为…”
He says, "You have to leave because..."

1009
01:25:34,200 --> 01:25:35,800
吞下
Swallow.

1010
01:25:39,400 --> 01:25:42,200
吞下去
Swallow.

1011
01:26:11,700 --> 01:26:13,676
哥德太太 你非吃点东西不可
You have to eat.

1012
01:26:13,677 --> 01:26:15,500
你要吃东西才能维持健康
If we're gonna get you healthy you have to eat.

1013
01:26:15,600 --> 01:26:18,225
跟护理人员配合一下 好吗?
Work with the attendants.

1014
01:26:18,226 --> 01:26:20,100
我会试一些新的药看看
I'm gonna try some new medications.

1015
01:27:22,600 --> 01:27:24,800
- 哈罗 - '玛丽'
- Hello. - 'Marion.'

1016
01:27:26,400 --> 01:27:28,100
哈瑞?
Harry?

1017
01:27:28,700 --> 01:27:33,200
'玛丽 我一直都好想你
'Marion, I've been thinking about you so much.

1018
01:27:33,300 --> 01:27:35,200
'你好吗?'
'Are you OK?'

1019
01:27:38,100 --> 01:27:42,000
- 你什么时候回家? - 快了
- When you comin' home? - Soon.

1020
01:27:42,100 --> 01:27:43,600
什么时候?
When?

1021
01:27:45,100 --> 01:27:46,600
就快了
Soon.

1022
01:27:47,700 --> 01:27:51,200
- '你坚持一下好吗?' - 哈瑞?
- 'You holdin' out all right?' - Harry?

1023
01:27:53,100 --> 01:27:55,500
你今天能回来吗?
Can you come today?

1024
01:27:59,200 --> 01:28:01,700
嗯
Yeah.

1025
01:28:08,100 --> 01:28:10,000
我会回去
I'll come.

1026
01:28:10,100 --> 01:28:13,400
'我今天会回去'
'I'll come today.'

1027
01:28:18,100 --> 01:28:21,200
只管等着我 好吗?
You just wait for me, all right?

1028
01:28:24,400 --> 01:28:27,900
- 好 哈瑞 - '我就回去了 玛丽'
- OK, Harry. - 'I'm coming back, Marion.'

1029
01:28:27,930 --> 01:28:29,800
- 嗯 - '玛丽?'
- Yeah. - 'Marion?'

1030
01:28:29,830 --> 01:28:31,300
怎了?
Yeah?

1031
01:28:32,400 --> 01:28:35,100
我真的很抱歉 玛丽
I'm really sorry, Marion.

1032
01:28:35,130 --> 01:28:37,000
我了解
I know.

1033
01:28:46,100 --> 01:28:48,100
哥德太太?
Mrs Goldfarb?

1034
01:28:50,100 --> 01:28:51,900
你还好吗?
You all right?

1035
01:28:53,500 --> 01:28:56,112
嗯 是这样的 哥德太太
Um, so, Mrs Goldfarb,

1036
01:28:56,113 --> 01:28:59,200
我们已经试过多种药物治疗
we've tried several medications,

1037
01:28:59,230 --> 01:29:01,660
不过好像都没什么效果
and you don't seem to be responding.

1038
01:29:01,700 --> 01:29:03,066
我想我们会
I believe we might want to

1039
01:29:03,067 --> 01:29:05,800
试着采用非常态性治疗
try some alternative methods.

1040
01:29:05,830 --> 01:29:09,800
我们的脑电汤治疗在过去有不错的结果
We've had excellent results with ECT in the past.

1041
01:29:09,830 --> 01:29:12,100
嗯… 只要你可以…
Um... So if I can just...

1042
01:29:12,200 --> 01:29:14,800
填好保险的表单…
get your John Hancock...

1043
01:29:16,200 --> 01:29:17,900
我们就可以进行了
we'll get underway.

1044
01:29:18,000 --> 01:29:19,500
太好了. 谢谢
Great. Thanks.

1045
01:29:20,700 --> 01:29:23,450
噢 天呀!
Oh, Jesus Christ!

1046
01:29:23,480 --> 01:29:26,200
我需要医生 老兄
I need a doctor, man.

1047
01:29:26,300 --> 01:29:29,500
我的朋友病了 帮他一下 拜托
My friend is sick. Give him some help, please.

1048
01:29:29,600 --> 01:29:33,200
我受不了了 老兄! 我的手臂! 我他妈的手臂!
I can't take it, man! My arm! My fuckin' arm!

1049
01:29:34,700 --> 01:29:36,600
救我!
Help me!

1050
01:29:36,700 --> 01:29:41,100
帮帮我们! 来个人帮帮忙吧 拜托!
Help us! Somebody fuckin' help us, please!

1051
01:30:01,400 --> 01:30:04,560
少女玛丽. 欢迎
Maid Marion. Welcome.

1052
01:30:04,600 --> 01:30:06,700
听得到? 看得到吗?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?

1053
01:30:06,800 --> 01:30:08,460
- 是的 长官 - 好的 可以工作
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.

1054
01:30:08,500 --> 01:30:10,600
听得到? 看得到吗?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?

1055
01:30:10,700 --> 01:30:13,060
- 是的 长官 - 好的 可以工作
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.

1056
01:30:13,100 --> 01:30:15,200
听得到? 看得到吗?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?

1057
01:30:15,300 --> 01:30:17,360
- 是的 长官 - 好的 可以工作
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.

1058
01:30:17,400 --> 01:30:19,200
听得到? 看得到吗?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?

1059
01:30:19,230 --> 01:30:21,460
- 是的 长官 - 好的 可以工作
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.

1060
01:30:21,500 --> 01:30:23,400
听得到? 看得到吗?
- Can you hear me? Can you see me?

1061
01:30:23,500 --> 01:30:25,300
- 是的 长官 - 好的 可以工作
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.

1062
01:30:25,400 --> 01:30:29,460
伙伴们 认识一下玛丽吧
Fellas, meet Marion.

1063
01:30:29,500 --> 01:30:31,960
听得到? 看得到吗?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?

1064
01:30:32,000 --> 01:30:34,260
- 是的 长官 - 好的 可以工作
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.

1065
01:30:34,300 --> 01:30:36,600
听得到? 看得到吗?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?

1066
01:30:36,700 --> 01:30:38,700
- 是的 长官 - 好的 可以工作
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.

1067
01:30:38,800 --> 01:30:40,800
好戏上场了
Show time.

1068
01:30:41,700 --> 01:30:44,900
好的 可以工作 听得到? 看得到吗?
OK for work. Can you hear me? Can you see me?

1069
01:30:45,000 --> 01:30:46,800
是 呃!
Yes. Oof!

1070
01:30:46,900 --> 01:30:50,700
说 “长官”. 妈的纽约毒瘾黑鬼
Say, "sir". Goddam New York dope fiend niggers.

1071
01:30:50,800 --> 01:30:52,800
学点礼貌
Learn some manners.

1072
01:30:52,900 --> 01:30:55,100
听得到? 看得到吗?
Can you hear me? Can you see me?

1073
01:30:55,130 --> 01:30:57,960
- 是的 长官 - 好的 可以工作
- Yes, sir. - OK for work.

1074
01:30:58,000 --> 01:30:59,320
- 戴上护齿套
- Got a mouthpiece.

1075
01:30:59,321 --> 01:31:01,300
- 听得到? 看得到吗?
- Can you hear me? Can you see me?

1076
01:31:01,330 --> 01:31:04,200
听说他的手臂有点问题
Says something's wrong with his arm.

1077
01:31:05,700 --> 01:31:08,500
我想他没有办法再打药在那里了
He won't be puttin' any more dope in that.

1078
01:31:08,530 --> 01:31:10,960
- 闻起来比他还糟 - 试机
- Smells worse than he do. - Test.

1079
01:31:11,000 --> 01:31:14,000
先把他带到医院去
Get him over to hospital.

1080
01:31:14,100 --> 01:31:17,000
好了吗? 来…一
Ready? And... one.

1081
01:31:40,900 --> 01:31:43,700
那是你们这些毒虫的通病
That's the trouble with you dope fiends.

1082
01:31:43,730 --> 01:31:46,100
你们态度很差. 知道吗?
You got a rotten attitude. You know that man?

1083
01:31:46,900 --> 01:31:50,300
- 现在我们要做什么? - 屁眼对屁眼
- So what are we gonna do now? - Ass to ass.

1084
01:31:50,400 --> 01:31:54,100
屁眼对屁眼!
Ass to ass!

1085
01:32:02,800 --> 01:32:06,600
把你那玩意放进自己的屁眼吧! 来吧!
Put your spineless back into it! Come on!

1086
01:32:08,600 --> 01:32:11,400
好了吗? 来…二!
Ready? And... two!

1087
01:32:15,400 --> 01:32:17,400
屁眼对屁眼!
Ass to ass!

1088
01:32:20,700 --> 01:32:24,600
- 放进去! - 就是这样
- Put it in there! - That's it.

1089
01:32:24,700 --> 01:32:27,700
放轻松慢慢来
Nice and easy.

1090
01:32:27,800 --> 01:32:30,960
马玲薯泥!
Mashed potatoes!

1091
01:32:31,000 --> 01:32:33,800
接近了 给我一斤吧. 对了
Here's the close. I need one gram. Bingo.

1092
01:32:35,200 --> 01:32:37,052
别放弃 别放弃
Don't give up. Don't give up.

1093
01:32:37,053 --> 01:32:39,700
加油 加油 加油!
Move it, move it, move it!

1094
01:32:40,800 --> 01:32:42,460
好了
OK.

1095
01:32:42,500 --> 01:32:45,100
好了吗? 来…叁!
Ready? And... three!

1096
01:32:50,200 --> 01:32:53,000
射吧! 射吧! 射吧! 射吧!
Cum! Cum! Cum! Cum!

1097
01:32:55,300 --> 01:32:58,400
我们得从肩膀以下切除才行
We're gonna take it off at the shoulder.

1098
01:32:58,430 --> 01:33:01,300
射吧! 射吧! 射吧! 射吧!
Cum! Cum! Cum! Cum!

1099
01:33:06,900 --> 01:33:08,300
锯子
Saw.

1100
01:33:48,700 --> 01:33:50,900
玛丽!
Marion!

1101
01:33:53,600 --> 01:33:54,371
没事了
It's all right.

1102
01:33:54,372 --> 01:33:57,200
别担心. 你在医院里
Don't worry. You're in a hospital.

1103
01:33:57,230 --> 01:33:59,500
- 玛丽? - 谁?
- Marion? - Who's that?

1104
01:33:59,600 --> 01:34:01,900
我们会通知她 她会来的
She'll be sent for. She'll come.

1105
01:34:04,400 --> 01:34:07,400
- 不. - 不要?
- No. - No?

1106
01:34:09,600 --> 01:34:11,550
不 她不会来
No, she won't.

1107
01:34:11,580 --> 01:34:13,500
她会来的
She'll come.

1108
01:36:17,700 --> 01:36:21,260
优胜者出来了 优胜者出来了
- We got a winner. - We got a winner.

1109
01:36:21,300 --> 01:36:24,800
优胜者来了! 优胜者出来了
- Got a winner! - We got a winner.

1110
01:36:24,900 --> 01:36:28,300
我们的新优胜者 就是有着人见人爱的性格
Our next winner is that delightful personality,

1111
01:36:28,330 --> 01:36:30,560
来自布鲁克林 布莱顿滩
from Brighton Beach, Brooklyn.

1112
01:36:30,600 --> 01:36:32,433
请热烈欢迎
Please, give a juicy welcome

1113
01:36:32,434 --> 01:36:35,000
哥德莎拉太太!
to Mrs Sara Goldfarb!

1114
01:36:37,200 --> 01:36:39,042
很高兴告诉你
I'm delighted to tell you

1115
01:36:39,043 --> 01:36:41,500
你赢得了首奖!
that you have won the grand prize!

1116
01:36:41,530 --> 01:36:45,260
- 噢 不会吧! - 让我告诉你赢得了些什么
- Oh, no! - let me tell you what you've won.

1117
01:36:45,300 --> 01:36:48,960
他有迷人的笑容 跟自己的事业
He has a sweet smile and his own business.

1118
01:36:49,000 --> 01:36:50,000
他刚订完婚
He just got engaged,

1119
01:36:50,001 --> 01:36:53,000
而且将在今年夏天完成终身大事
and is about to get married this summer.

1120
01:36:53,030 --> 01:36:54,965
让我们热情地欢迎
Please give a warm and juicy welcome.

1121
01:36:54,966 --> 01:36:56,900
哥德哈瑞先生!
Harry Goldfarb!

1122
01:36:56,930 --> 01:36:59,800
哈瑞热情有劲! 哈瑞热情有劲!
Juice by Harry! Juice by Harry!

1123
01:36:59,900 --> 01:37:03,300
噢 哈瑞真来劲! 哈瑞真来劲!
ohh, Harry's got juice! Harry's got juice!

1124
01:37:03,400 --> 01:37:05,700
噢 哈瑞!
ohh, Harry!

1125
01:37:05,800 --> 01:37:08,875
- 我爱你 哈瑞 - 我也爱你 妈
- I love you, Harry. - I love you too, Ma.

