Barnacles!
Kwazii!
Peso!
- Explore!
- Rescue!
- Protect!
Octonauts!
Ach, this spyglass is no good.
It's supposed to see things far away but I can't make out that shape.
We're so far down, it's dark as night.
Good thing the octoscope can see in the dark.
- Can you give us a better picture of what's out there?
- Aye-aye, Captain.
- It looks like a ship of some kind.
- Oh, shiver me whiskers!
Unless I miss me guess, that's the pirate shipwreck of Calico Jack!
TOGETHER: Calico who?!
Calico Jack. He was my grandfather
and the finest cat pirate ever to roam the seven seas.
He had a golden spyglass.
The spyglass was passed down from one member of me family to the next.
Before it could pass down to me,
Calico Jack's ship sank in the North Atlantic Ocean.
That golden spyglass sank with it.
The North Atlantic Ocean? But...that's where we are now.
Kwazii, do you really think
that could be the pirate ship of Calico Jack out there?
- Aye-aye, Captain.
- Then, let's go and investigate.
Kwazii, sound the octo-alert.
- Yow!
- SIREN WAILS
Octonauts, to the launch bay.
Octonauts, there's a mysterious ship out there
that may have belonged to Kwazii's grandfather, Calico Jack.
Our mission is to explore the shipwreck
and help Kwazii find his grandfather's spyglass.
Peso, Dashi, Kwazii, let's go.
- Tweak, open the octo-hatch.
- Right away, Captain.
Can't you go any faster, Captain?
Kwazii, that shipwreck has been down there for years.
It'll still be there in a few minutes.
Oh!
Look, everyone.
There it is.
Well, Kwazii, do you think it's Calico Jack's ship?
That's got to be a carving of your grandfather. He even looks like you.
Let's go inside! Yow!
Eh?
- Hold on, Kwazii.
- Hey?
- This may have been a pirate ship once,
but now she's home to hundreds of plants and animals.
Octonauts, be extra careful. We don't want to disturb anything.
- TOGETHER: Aye-aye, Captain.
- Have you got that, Kwazii?
Kwazii?
I wonder where that spyglass might be.
Yow! Spiky sea urchins!
Yow!
Ye-hah!
Huh?
A little seaweed isn't going to keep me from that spyglass.
Hah!
Oh!
Ah!
Shiver me whiskers!
Me grandfather's treasure chest!
I just know that spyglass is inside.
The spyglass!
HISS!
Aggh!
Agggh! Ugh!
Kwazii, what happened?
I got slimed before I could grab the spyglass.
HE SNIFFS Who goes there?
We can't see, but we can still smell you and hear you, dagnabbit!
Uh-oh, looks like this is slime eel territory.
Get off our property or I'll slime you again!
- Sorry, Kwazii, we've got to go.
- One!
- But what about the spyglass?
- Just leave it, Kwazii.
Two!
No! It was me grandfather's, and it should be mine!
- But, Kwazii... - Three! OK, boys, let them have it!
HISS-S-S! HISS!
ALL: Agh!
Ppt!
- Ugh!
- Agh!
Ughhh...
Agh, huh...
Ppt!
Give me two seconds and I promise I'll be...
SPLAT! SPLAT! SPLAT!
Miaow...
..And then we ran in and Kwazii was covered in this disgusting slime!
Fascinating.
A single slime eel can produce a bucket of slime in no time.
Tell me about it...
That's the slime eel's way of protecting itself and its home -
especially since it can't see.
There certainly were a lot of slime eels protecting that spyglass.
- Not to mention spiky sea urchins...
- And tangly seaweed.
Sorry, Kwazii, it's too dangerous to go back.
What would a slime eel want with a spyglass anyway?
Ohh, I'm going to bed.
..Calico Jack...spyglass...
It's mine...mine...MINE!
THE SPYGLASS IS MINE!
DOOR OPENS, ENGINE STARTS >
Oh! Kwazii.
This time I'm not leaving without that spyglass.
Oh!
ALL SNORE
Um...
Me grandfather's spyglass!
At last!
- Huh!
- >
ALL SNORE
- Haha! I made it!
- DOINK!
CREEAAAK! THUNK!
DOING!
Hey, what's all the ruckus?
Ugggh!
Oh, great(!) You again.
So, you're back for some more, eh?
- Kwazii!
I finally had me grandfather's spyglass,
till this beam fell down and trapped me.
Agh!
I can't move it without bringing the whole ship down.
Didn't we warn you to clear out of here and never come back?
Ah, you caught me, slime eel.
I suppose you're going to slime me again. Go ahead!
That's it! You're right!
Ahem!
Go ahead! Slime him! I dare you.
- What?! But...
- My pleasure!
SPLAT!
You call THAT sliming someone? Ha, you missed him!
- Ah, well, I can't see, remember?
- Captain?
Slime makes Kwazii's tail slippery and we can pull him loose.
Ohhh... Try a little lower next time.
Peso, what are you saying?
SPLAT!
Just a little lower...
You asked for it!
SPLAT! SPLAT!
Great work! Let's pull!
I'm free!
Thanks, matey!
And thanks, slime eel!
At last! Me grandfather's spyglass!
And it's all mine!
Huh?
There's all kinds of plants and animals in there.
Looks like this spyglass has become home to many different creatures.
Aye.
Back for more, eh?
Wait! Just a minute.
This spyglass has always been passed down in my family.
But now, I'm passing it on to you and these little creatures.
- Ah, that's mighty kind of you.
- Take good care of it.
Oh, we will! And, um, sorry about the slime.
No, go on! Get out of here.
And after all this time, I finally had the spyglass in me own paws.
But when I saw those creatures, I had to put it back.
Miaow...
Kwazii, you did the right thing.
You can tell everyone you discovered Calico Jack's shipwreck.
Besides, it's not like you didn't get any souvenirs.
Huh?
Here!
ALL LAUGH
Yargh!
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk