AHHH!
AFTER 10,000 YEARS, I'M FREE!
ITS TIME TO CONQUER EARTH!
ALPHA, RITA'S ESCAPED!
RECRUIT A TEAM OF
TEENAGERS WITH ATTITUDE!
# GO, GO, POWER RANGERS #
# MIGHTY MORPHIN POWER RANGERS #
# POWER RANGERS #
# GO, GO, POWER RANGERS #
# YOU MIGHTY MORPHIN
POWER RANGERS #
Woman: EVERYBODY TAKE
THEIR PLACES, PLEASE.
IT'S A VIDEO PROJECT--
BULK, THE WORLD'S GREATEST GUY.
TAKE 32.
I HAVE ALWAYS ENJOYED
THIS NOTABLE CLASS.
TAKE YOUR SEATS NOW, PLEASE.
THAT WAS MISS APPLEBY
WHO CAN'T WAIT FOR ME
TO SIT DOWN.
SHE REALLY IS A LOVELY TEACHER.
( chuckling )
LIGHT'S NO GOOD.
COULD YOU? LEFT...
NO, MY LEFT.
GO TO YOUR LEFT.
BACK, BACK IT UP.
RIGHT... RIGHT THERE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, BULK.
I'LL... EDIT IT OUT LATER.
IT'S TIME FOR OUR FIRST
VIDEO PROJECT TODAY.
TRINI.
MY VIDEO PROJECT IS CALLED
POLLUTION PROBLEMS
IN ANGEL GROVE.
Trini: Pollution... It exists
even here in beautiful Angel Grove.
Despite all of the attention
focused on the environment
in the past few years, we still
have a problem with trash
dirty air, and polluted water.
Heavy industry
a major source of contaminants
has made progress recently
but there is still a lot
that needs to be done.
We must take care not to destroy
nature's delicate balance
for the sake of the animals
and for our very world
because
if the animals disappear...
ultimately, so will we.
The time to act is now.
VERY NICE JOB, TRINI.
POLLUTION IS A SERIOUS CONCERN
TO OUR SOCIETY.
Billy:
I COULDN'T AGREE MORE.
I'M DEEPLY CONCERNED ABOUT
THE ECOLOGICAL RAMIFICATIONS
OF OZONE DEPLETION,
ACID RAIN
DEFORESTATION,
AND THE LOSS OF OUR TOPSOILS.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
SO WHAT CAN WE DO
TO HELP BEAUTIFY OUR CITY?
I WANT TO START
A CLEAN-UP CLUB.
ONE DAY A WEEK,
WE CAN DO SOME RECYCLING
CLEAN UP MAJOR TRAILS, OR EVEN
COUNT ENDANGERED ANIMALS.
- YEAH.
- COUNT ME IN.
SOUNDS COOL.
TOTALLY.
Rita:
A CLEAN-UP CLUB, EH?
WE'LL GIVE THEM SOMETHING
TO CLEAN.
CALL FINSTER'S POLLUTICORN.
THE POLLUTICORN WILL MAKE
SUCH A MESS OF THEIR PLANET
THEY'LL NEVER GET IT CLEANED UP!
SCORPINA! GOLDAR!
MAKE SURE THIS WORKS. NOW GO!
YES, MY QUEEN.
YES!
( exaggerated karate yell )
THAT WAS VERY GOOD...
BUT WATCH THIS.
( exaggerated karate yell )
NOT VERY PRACTICAL,
BUT BIG-TIME POINTS FOR STYLE.
HOW'S IT GOING, HUH?
GOOD. TWO MORE,
AND WE'RE DONE.
GOOD.
VERY GOOD, BILLY.
THANKS. I'M USING
A SPECIAL MIXTURE
OF TOTALLY ORGANIC PAINT
PIGMENTED WITH VARIOUS
NATURAL SUBSTANCES.
A LITTLE TO THE LEFT.
BACK A LITTLE BIT TO THE RIGHT.
PERFECT.
I WANT TO THANK
YOU GUYS
FOR REALLY HELPING ME OUT
WITH THIS RECYCLING STUFF.
THAT'S WHAT
THE CLEAN-UP CLUB IS FOR.
NOW, LET'S GET OVER
TO THAT FIELD NEAR THE PARK
AND PICK UP TRASH,
SHALL WE?
TAKE CARE, GUYS.
BULK, THE WORLD'S
GREATEST GUY,
SCENE 42.
WORKING OUT.
THIS IS WHERE I TRAIN.
PUMPING UP
IS IMPORTANT TO ME.
HEY, BULK?
YOU PROMISED I COULD
DO THE SCENE WITH YOU.
WHO'S GOING TO RUN
THE CAMERA, STUPID?
HEY, ERNIE, YOU WANT
TO FILM US WORKING OUT?
YOU TWO?
WORKING OUT?
JUST RUN THE CAMERA,
OKAY?
OH, THIS OUGHT TO BE FUN.
GUYS, THIS IS REALLY SAD.
LOOK AT THIS MESS.
THIS IS TERRIBLE.
I CANNOT BELIEVE
PEOPLE WOULD RUIN
SUCH A BEAUTIFUL PLACE.
LET ME TAKE A SOIL SAMPLE.
COMPLETELY POLLUTED.
THIS KIND OF
WANTON DISREGARD
IS SO DESTRUCTIVE
TO SUCH A FRAGILE ECOSYSTEM.
AND IT STINKS.
TIME TO GET BUSY.
LOOKS LIKE OUR CLUB
REALLY CLEANED UP.
IT LOOKS TOTALLY FAR OUT
AND FUNKY DOWN THE DRAIN.
VERY SUCCESSFUL VENTURE.
IT WAS FUN TOO.
LET'S DO THAT SECTION THERE
AND THEN WE'LL HEAD DOWN
TO THE RECYCLING CENTER.
ALL RIGHT.
IT'S ALMOST TIME.
( evil laughter )
ANOTHER BRILLIANT PLAN,
MY QUEEN.
NOW I SHALL SEND PUTTIES
TO SOFTEN THEM UP
FOR THE POLLUTICORN.
THIS IS GOING
TO MAKE ME LOOK GOOD.
THANKS FOR ALL YOUR HELP,
GOODY-GOODS.
( chuckling )
BULK, THE WORLD'S GREATEST GUY
TAKE 53.
I PICKED UP
ALL THIS TRASH MYSELF.
BEAUTIFUL, BABE, BUT THIS WAY.
RIGHT.
THE OTHER RIGHT.
OKAY, TO MY RIGHT.
( yelling )
GET ME OUT OF HERE!
WHAT KIND OF PEOPLE
JUST DUMP THEIR TRASH LIKE THIS?
POLLUTANTS, LIKE THAT!
Trini:
OH, NO! PUTTIES!
NOW WE GOT SOMETHING ELSE
TO CLEAN UP.
Tommy:
LET'S BAG THEM!
SO MUCH FOR THEM.
YEAH.
( roaring )
YO, MONSTER HORSE
SKY HIGH.
FLYING IN FAST.
THAT'S ONE
REAL NIGHTMARE.
IT'S MORPHIN TIME!
MASTODON!
PTERODACTYL!
TRICERATOPS!
SABER-TOOTHED TIGER!
TYRANNOSAURUS!
POWER RANGERS!
POWER WINDS BLOW!
( all yelling )
YOU GUYS OKAY?
WE'VE GOT TO STOP HIM
BEFORE HE POLLUTES
EVERYTHING IN SIGHT.
OH, MAN, WHAT NOW?
OKAY.
NO. I WILL TAKE CARE
OF THESE IRRITANTS.
IT DOESN'T EVEN FEEL
OUR ATTACKS.
I LIKE HIS STYLE.
I'M GOING TO DESTROY YOU
AND YOUR MISERABLE PLANET.
Rita:
THAT'S THE WAY, POLLUTICORN.
I'M SO DEVIOUS, IT'S DELICIOUS.
THAT HORSE-THING'S
TOO MUCH.
THIS MONSTER MAY PROVE DIFFICULT
FOR YOU TO DEFEAT, RANGERS.
BILLY, HELP ALPHA
WITH A SITUATION ANALYSIS.
YES, SIR.
DATA PRINTOUT
COMING UP.
WHAT'S UP
WITH THIS MONSTER?
IT'S ALL PART
OF RITA'S LATEST PLAN
TO DESTROY THE EARTH.
OBSERVE THE VIEWING GLOBE.
RITA HAS CREATED THIS MONSTER
TO COVER THE EARTH
WITH POLLUTION.
WE CAN'T LET
THAT HAPPEN.
THERE'S GOT TO BE A WAY
TO STOP THAT THING.
YEAH, BUT HOW?
AY-YI-YI-YI-YI!
WHOA!
ALPHA.
OH, ALPHA,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
ARE YOU OKAY?
MY ANALYSIS SHOWS
THAT THE POLLUTICORN
DERIVES ITS POWERS
FROM ITS HORN.
GOOD WORK, BILLY.
I WILL BRING IT UP
ON THE VIEWING GLOBE.
THE POLLUTICORN
IS ATTACKING
THE ANGEL GROVE RECYCLING PLANT.
I can pollute
your whole pathetic planet
faster than you can clean it up.
WE CAN'T LET HIM
WRECK THAT FACTORY.
IT'S MORPHIN TIME.
MASTODON.
PTERODACTYL.
TRICERATOPS.
SABER-TOOTHED TIGER.
TYRANNOSAURUS.
( yelling )
YOU GUYS GET THEM.
I'LL TAKE OUT
HORN-HEAD.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO IT!
GOT TO FIND A WAY
TO CHOP OFF THAT HORN.
FACE IT
I'M TOO POWERFUL FOR YOU.
BESIDES,
YOUR FRIENDS ARE FINISHED.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I'VE GOT TO FINISH DESTROYING
THIS RECYCLING PLANT FIRST.
AW, SO MUCH TO POLLUTE
SO LITTLE TIME.
YOUR POLLUTING DAYS
ARE OVER, HORSEFACE.
I'M SENDING YOU
BACK TO THE BARN.
ALL RIGHT, SMOG-BREATH,
MY FRIENDS NEED HELP.
I SUMMON THE POWER
OF THE DRAGON SHIELD.
( crying )
I'LL GET YOU FOR THAT!
SEE THE UNICORN GROW!
( growling )
WE NEED DINOSAUR POWER NOW!
TOXIC WINDS BLOW!
( laughing )
CLEAN THAT.
WE'RE GETTING WRECKED, GUYS.
WE NEED THE POWER SWORD!
# GO, GO, POWER RANGERS #
HUH?
UH-OH.
LET'S FINISH HIM!
# GO, GO, POWER RANGERS #
# YOU MIGHTY
MORPHIN POWER RANGERS. #
OH, SUCH A HEADACHE.
NEVER FEAR, SOMEDAY WE'LL
MAKE THOSE POWER RANGERS PAY.
Man:
This bulletin just in.
We've just gotten word
that once again
the amazing Power Rangers
have saved our town
and the world
from one of Rita Repulsa's
lethal monsters.
After a lengthy battle,
the Power Rangers
and their Zords
defeated the beast
just before it attacked
Angel Grove.
No people
were reported injured.
How long will we be safe
from Rita Repulsa
and her notorious monsters?
No one knows for sure
but thank you, Power Rangers,
whoever you are.
HEY, MORE RECYCLING, GANG.
IT'S TIME TO GO TO WORK.
OKAY, ERNIE.
THAT MAKES OVER 500.
SOMEDAY SOON,
THIS PLASTIC WILL MAKE
A LOT OF CREDIT CARDS.
OH, YEAH?
WELL, CHECK OUT
THIS PILE OF PAPERS.
MAN, WE JUST SAVED A REDWOOD.
Skull:
REMEMBER, YOU WANT TO HELP.
ACT REAL HELPFUL.
TELL THEM
YOU'RE HERE TO HELP.
I KNOW MY LINE.
ALL RIGHT.
SCENE 78.
I ALWAYS HELP OUT
WITH THE RECYCLING DRIVE.
WHAT A DORK.
I'M GOING TO POUND YOU.
BULK, BULK, BULK, BULK.
I'M TAPING.
OH. OH, YEAH.
I THINK, WHENEVER POSSIBLE,
EVERYTHING SHOULD BE RECYCLED.
TODAY, WE WILL BE SEEING
BULK AND SKULL'S VIDEO,
WON'T WE?
UM... WELL...
JUST FINISHED EDITING IT.
THIS WILL BE
VERY INTERESTING.
Bulk:
I'M SURE IT WILL BE
AN AWARD-WINNING PROJECT.
HOW'S IT LOOK?
THERE ARE
A FEW GLITCHES
BUT NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
I have
no
class.
Take your seats now.
That Miss Appleby
can't, can't
teach.
( stammering )
Pumping up is important to me.
I'M GOING TO...
I-I-I-I...
THOUGHT I CUT
THAT PART OUT.
I pick
trash myself.
I think I should be recycled.
I'M GOING TO POUND YOU,
CAMERAMAN!
I CAN FIX IT.
Captioned by Grant Brown