Ahhh!
After 10,000 years, I'm free!
Its time to conquer earth!
Alpha, rita's escaped!
Recruit a team of
teenagers with attitude!
# Go, go, Power Rangers #
# Mighty Morphin Power Rangers #
# Power Rangers #
# Go, go, Power Rangers #
# You Mighty Morphin
Power Rangers #
You okay, man?
Yeah.
Good move.
Hey, you weren't too bad yourself.
So, what's up with the dance?
I haven't asked her.
What?
I guess I'm nervous.
Aw, bro, I'm telling you.
Kimberly's going to say yes,
but you have to ask her first.
You think I should ask her today?
Don't put it off, man.
It's time to make your move.
You're right.
( Rita laughing )
The time has finally come!
Gather 'round, fools.
I have the perfect plan
to conquer that pathetic
little planet Earth.
Yes, it's so devious, even for me.
What's the plan, your Evilness?
With the green candle
formed from magic wax.
When it burns down
it will steal
the Green Ranger's powers.
First, we kidnap him
then the Earth shall shake.
You'll have the Green Ranger's power
as well as your own.
Ooh! Whisper softly.
Let it out.
Find Green Ranger.
Point him out!
Hey, it works!
It found him!
Oh, what a great day!
You lost
your focus.
'Cause you've got me
thinking about Kim.
The sooner you ask kim
to the dance
the sooner your mind
will be at ease.
Trust me.
Okay, if you're such a pro
let's see you in action.
Child's play, my friend.
First, you have to catch her eye
with your walk.
Then you have to impress her
with some smooth spins.
Finally, you just have
to bust a move.
Zack...
get a life.
( chuckling )
Real impressive, bud.
Yeah.
Real impressive.
If you're trying to get a date
with a carnival geek.
( giggling )
What's the matter?
Guys can't get a date?
If you're such experts,
you teach us.
Roses are red.
Violets are blue.
No girl in the world's
going to go out with you.
Hey, I'm stuck.
I'm stuck.
Get me out of here!
I can't breathe.
I can't breathe!
Hold still.
I'm trying.
Yo, ladies, check this out.
Roses are red.
Violets are blue.
BOTH:
We can learn something from you.
- Not!
Candle green with fire's flower.
Ba she sha ba!
Take Green Ranger's power!
It will be done.
The Putties will find Green Ranger
and take his coin!
( laughing )
And then...
And then we'll have him!
So what did you want
to talk to me about?
You sounded so serious
over the phone.
Yeah, um.
Well, I wanted to know if...
Yes?
If maybe you'd like to, uh...
Like to what, Tommy?
Kim, I just don't know
how to ask you this.
Come on, Tommy.
You can ask me anything.
Really?
Yes.
All right.
Here it goes.
Um... Kim, I was wondering
if maybe you'd like to go to the...
Look out!
Putties!
Tommy, my Morpher!
I can't reach mine!
It's Goldar!
What do you want, metalhead?
Now take him!
( screaming )
( sinister laughing )
Tommy!
Say goodbye to Green Ranger
forever.
Just like old times,
isn't it, Green Ranger?
What's this all about, Goldar?
Ah, yes. His Morpher!
Leave him to me.
Get comfortable, Green Ranger.
Rita has big plans for you.
Never!
( laughing )
Jason. Alpha.
Forget it.
Your telecommunications devices
don't work in this dimension.
Why am I here?
It's simple.
If you serve Rita,
you can keep your powers.
If not, you'll lose them
when the candle burns out.
What candle?
The green candle.
( laughing )
It's made of very special wax.
When it burns out
Rita will have stolen your powers!
( laughing )
Do you have my monster ready?
'Cause, Finster, I need it.
Coming right up, your Evilness.
He's the worst
in the best of ways, of course.
He's able to change
into any shape at will.
Ooh, this I want to see!
He looks great.
( laughing )
Here's looking at you!
Boy, he makes me look good
doesn't he?
Uh-huh.
Yes, yes.
Meet the Cyclops.
The Earth is mine at last!
Yes!
I won't let you
get away with this, Goldar.
Like to stop
the candle from burning?
Be my guest.
( laughing )
You are doomed!
Another one of Rita's wicked plans.
She's going to try
and regain control of Tommy.
I just know it.
I can't get a lock on him.
Rita must be holding him
in her dimensional prison.
Billy, you come up with anything?
Not yet.
I'm still trying to tune
into the frequency
on Tommy's Morpher.
( alarm wailing )
Ay-yi-yi.
The alarm!
The Viewing Globe.
JASON:
Dragonzord.
TRINI:
Attacking Angel Grove.
That means one thing.
Rita has regained control
of the Dragonzord.
( alarm wailing )
We got to stop it.
What about Tommy?
We'll have to take him down too.
ZORDON:
Wait. My sensors indicate
the Dragonzord we see
is an impostor.
One of Rita's creations?
She's trying to lure us into a trap.
It's got to be stopped.
Be careful, Power Rangers.
It's Morphin Time!
Mastodon!
Pterodactyl!
Triceratops!
Saber-toothed Tiger!
Tyrannosaurus!
Go!
Make them pay, Goldar!
I am called to battle.
Hey, don't get any foolish ideas,
Ranger.
The candle will be safe while I'm away.
See?
( laughing )
( grunting )
( kiais )
Waste them!
Where's Tommy, Goldar?!
You will never see your friend again!
It's destroying the city!
We've got to do something,
and fast!
Oh, man!
We need Dinozord power now!
Log on!
Mastodon-- ready to rock!
Triceratops-- online!
Saber-toothed Tiger-- set!
Pterodactyl-- powered up!
Power up your Crystal.
Two, one, power up.
Okay, Power Rangers,
let's do it!
Let's show them
some Megazord power!
Megazord sequence
has been initiated.
Megazord Activated.
( yelling )
It's just as powerful
as the real Dragonzord.
What if we can't defeat him?
We've got to.
But how?
We could do it with Tommy's help.
We've got to pull together
until he's here.
Hey!
I'm back, and happy to report
your miserable friends
are losing the battle.
You won't defeat them, Goldar.
Once she has your power
Rita will be able
to defeat everyone.
She'll never have it.
Oh, she will!
See how it burns?
Like to try stopping it again?
Face it, Green Ranger,
you're trapped.
I saw how you got me here, Goldar.
Now let's see if it works in reverse.
Hey! No!
No!
See you later, gold guy!
Dragonzord!
Well, you may have escaped
but your powers won't last,
for your candle burns low.
Huh? Oh, no!
Rangers, I'm here.
Goldar had me trapped!
All right!
It's time for some real
Dragonzord power!
( horn playing )
Huh?
My powers are weakening already.
Hey,
here comes the real Dragonzord.
Look!
Huh? Yes!
We must have hurt him.
He can't hold his shape anymore.
Way to go!
Way to go, Tommy!
Glad you're back.
I'm a Power Ranger till the end.
RITA: Yes, and your end
will come soon, Green Ranger.
Very soon.
( laughs )
What is Alpha doing?
He's scanning Tommy
for internal damage
due to crossing dimensions.
You're all clear.
Thanks, Alpha.
You are welcome.
I'm just glad
I could get out of there.
Rita's secret dimension
is one bad place.
The important thing
is that you're okay.
Am I?
According to Rita
my power's going to be gone soon.
She's just bluffing, Tommy.
How would she be able
to take away your power?
ZORDON:
I'm afraid
it is possible, Rangers.
Zordon,
then you found out something
about the green candle
I told you about.
Yes. Rita has a special wax
from the gamma-tri system.
Once touched, it retains
a person's body energy.
I never touched anything.
You did when you worked for Rita.
KIM: No way!
And she's been saving the wax
all this time?
Yes.
And now she has made a candle
and cast a spell over it
connecting
the Green Ranger's power
with its flame.
Then Rita wasn't bluffing.
Once the candle burns out,
I'm history.
The Green Ranger's... finished.
( Rita laughing )
Captioned by Grant Brown