Ahhh!
After 10,000 years, I'm free!
Its time to conquer earth!
Alpha, Rita's escaped!
Recruit a team of
teenagers with attitude!
# Go, go, Power Rangers #
# Mighty Morphin Power Rangers #
# Power Rangers #
# Go, go, Power Rangers #
# You Mighty Morphin
Power Rangers #
This is going to be fun.
You're going to have a good time.
Wish you were coming with us.
Yeah, there's plenty of room.
Well, barely.
Thanks, but I want
to spend some time
With my Cousin Jeremy
while he's in town.
Won't be the same without you.
Sorry I'm late, guys.
I baked these in
my gourmet cooking class
to take along on our trip.
Ugh. What is in these?
TRINI:
It's an exotic recipe.
Very popular in France right now.
They call it Torte A La Escargot.
Escargot?
Tasty.
In other words, snail.
( coughing )
Ah...
all ready to take on our trip.
Come on, guys.
Oh, goody,
they're going away.
This is just what her nastiness
has been waiting for.
So what's the plan,
your Evilness?
To find the Mirror of Destruction.
The one that can
destroy Super Putties?
Yes, into a million pieces.
That mirror's power
will destroy anything
reflected in it.
Just one look at it
and those Rangers are history.
We have to find it first.
We'll start today.
It's hidden on Earth.
( mumbling )
# Bum-bum-bum-bum-bum #
You see, Skull
the beauty of
the Sloppy Joe Pizza
is that you can
make a huge funnel
and thereby jam more
pizza down your throat.
( bubbling sound )
# Bum-bum-bum-bum-bum #
Oh, look.
It's Jason Schmason.
( laughing )
Hey, Jase.
Who's the pipsqueak?
Isn't this the famous bully
you were talking about?
Hey, Bulk, you're famous.
JASON:
Hey, Bulk.
Nice shirt.
Does that come with extra cheese?
You know...
I don't like your attitude.
Come on.
I think it's time
for me to teach you
a little lesson.
( martial arts cries )
Jase, watch out for that.
Gee, Bulk. That look is you.
That was awesome
how you tricked him
into beating himself.
Just remember that
it's brains before brawn.
Right, brains before brawn.
You're getting better.
The cool thing about Martial Arts
is it teaches you self-discipline
and confidence.
Hey, Jase,
teach me a cool move.
Okay.
Back leg, front kick.
Good. All right. All right.
Now, this one's a little harder
but I want you to try it.
Okay. All right.
Now, try it again, but focus.
Hey, I did it.
When I was your age,
I was really insecure
but Martial Arts
built my self-confidence.
Wow!
Now you're the coolest.
All you have to do is practice.
I hope I can be as cool
as the Power Rangers.
Power Rangers?
Yeah. That's what I want
to be when I grow up.
All right.
RITA:
What's Jason doing there?
SQUATT:
Martial Arts?
He's there after you said
the Rangers were gone.
Finding the mirror
will have to wait
till my Putties take care of him
and that will happen
right now!
Putties.
Oh, man.
What are we going to do?
Stay behind me.
Watch your back.
Stay back!
Good job, Jeremy.
Wow! I'd always heard
about Rita and the Putties
but I never thought
I'd actually see them.
Let's hope you don't
see them again.
Hey, hey, I got something.
A bottle.
Weird!
I wonder what's inside.
Looks like a map.
Open it.
- Whoa!
What's going on?
Get down! Get down!
Wait here!
( rumbling )
Coast is clear.
Zordon, come in.
Jason, my sensors
are picking up
something unusual
in the Morphing Grid.
Take Jeremy to a safe place.
Right.
TRINI: Oh, my gosh.
It's an earthquake.
BILLY:
Everybody hold on.
Jeremy, are you okay?
Okay?
Man, this is totally cool.
What a way to start a vacation.
And check out this map.
RITA: It leads to the
Mirror of Destruction.
( laughing )
And once I've got
my hands on it
you'll suffer the same
fate as all the others.
It will zap them so hard,
they won't know what hit them.
We need that map.
Right.
Go and get it, Scorpina.
Yeah.
( chuckling )
SCORPINA:
Over there.
SCORPINA: The Rockstar
will take care of him in no time.
Get the map from the kid.
Jeremy, run!
- But...
- I'll find you later.
Don't let anything
happen to that map.
Gotcha!
Jason, now you'll get
what's coming to you.
Attack!
Now, Rockstar!
( roaring )
You won't get away
with this, Scorpina!
That Rockstar is
one tough monster.
Jason doesn't stand a chance
pinned down like that.
He's a sitting duck.
What will we do?
Alpha, we must contact
the other Power Rangers.
They are the only ones
who can save him.
( beeping )
Zordon, I read you.
Teleport to the beach
immediately.
We're on our way.
Here!
Jason!
Don't worry, Jason.
We'll free you.
Are you all right?
( grunting )
Thanks.
That was a close one.
We got to find Jeremy.
He's got the map that
Scorpina's looking for.
Let's go.
Where's Jason?
I hope he's okay.
- JASON: Jeremy!
- KIMBERLY: Jeremy!
- BILLY: Jeremy!
- ZACK: Jeremy!
Jeremy!
( beeping )
Zordon, we read you.
You must fight Scorpina
and her Rockstar monster
at the beach club.
What about Jeremy?
Don't worry, Jason.
I'll find him.
You must go immediately.
It's Morphin Time!
Mastodon!
Pterodactyl!
Triceratops!
Sabretooth Tiger!
Tyrannosaurus!
All right! Let's do it!
ALL:
Power Rangers!
Attack!
( grunts and groans )
Zack, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Not for long, Power Rangers.
You lose.
I win.
( groaning )
( evil laughter )
( groans )
Scorpina, you've got to find
that kid with the map.
Hurry and finish them!
( growling )
Hey, you guys okay?
Yeah.
Get us out!
( panting )
Attack!
Here they are.
Get them!
( yelling )
- Ooh, yeah.
- Uh, see ya.
( evil laughter )
Yes!
Brains before brawn.
Let me see.
This is where I am now.
It says I should take
six giant steps forward.
Should I finish them off,
Scorpina?
- A good idea.
- Right!
- What are you waiting for?
- Yeah!
( both groaning )
( yelling )
( evil laughter )
Wow! This must be it.
Huh?
Whoa!
Huh? No!
Cool.
Uh-oh.
( grunting )
Yikes!
( anguished cry )
This is too hot to handle.
Okay, you've had it.
- ( grunting )
- Come on.
Hey, look what I found.
Yeah, now I've got it.
Let's finally get rid of
those Power Rangers.
Now, Scorpina, grow!
( evil laughter )
( growling )
Now you're mine.
We need Dinozord Power!
ALL:
Now!
( roaring )
Let's do it!
( all yelling )
Way cool.
Power Rangers to the rescue.
Power up the Megazord.
( roaring )
All systems are go.
Let's do it!
ALL:
Right!
- Morphin.
Megazord Battle Mode now!
Megazord Sequence
has been initiated.
Megazord activated.
( growling )
( high-pitched hum )
Hide your eyes!
( grunting )
( growling )
Yoo-hoo!
Over here.
Sucker! ( growling )
We can't break lose!
Nothing can save you now.
Behold,
the Mirror of Destruction!
Don't move.
Here's our chance!
Powerzord!
- Yeah!
- All right!
You'll pay for this,
Power Rangers.
Count on it.
ZORDON:
Another job well done, Rangers.
Thanks, Zordon.
( beeping )
Wow,
you guys were awesome.
You were pretty brave yourself.
We're real proud of you--
how you kept outsmarting
those Putties.
You know what they say--
brains before brawn.
An exemplary motto.
I can't believe I finally
got to meet you guys.
I can't wait till
I tell my Cousin Jason.
By the way, where is Jason?
I hope he's okay.
- Uh...     - Yeah...
- Yeah...
I'm sure he's just fine.
...and then I kicked
the Putty like this.
But then, just when
he was about to nail me,
this magical mirror blew him up
into a zillion pieces.
Bang!
To think we were stuck
at that boring field trip.
But the Power Rangers--
they were the coolest.
Man,
you should have been them.
Oh, you've met
the Power Rangers?
Sure did. There was also
the scorpion lady
called the Rockstar.
Idiosyncratic.
He spit out these rocks
as big as a house.
- Really?
- Really.
Yeah,
and he hit the yellow one.
The black one
kicked him into the pool.
And then later
the pink one flew through the air
with her bow and arrow.
She was just awesome.
Tell us more about
the black one.
And the scorpion lady
turned into this huge monster
and the Power Rangers
jumped into this huge robot.
- Wow.
Sounds like you had
a pretty wild time.
I got to go.
You should have seen
the red one
battle it out with
the scorpion lady.
- He was the greatest.
- Yeah?
Continue.
He did the coolest
flying spin kick.
( yelling )
Hey, Jase
I meant to ask you.
Where were you
all that time?
I have a Martial Arts class
that I need to teach.
Come on, Jeremy.
Captioned by Grant Brown