- SIREN WAILS
- 'Octonauts, to your stations!'
Barnacles!
Kwazii!
Peso!
- Explore!
- Rescue!
- Protect!
Octonauts!
Hm, you sound a lot better.
And your temperature is back to normal, too.
In a few days, you'll be feeling fine again.
Wait and see... Cucumber.
Get it? See, Cucumber?
Because you're a sea cucumber!
HE CHUCKLES
OK, let's get you back to your home.
Tweak! Are you there?
Sure, Cap. What's up?
We have an emergency, up here in the HQ.
The hot chocolate machine has gone haywire
and we can't turn it off!
THEY SQUEAL
Oh, GUP-E's battery is almost out of power.
I was just going to replace it.
But it can wait. Be there in a minute!
Ah, looks like the GUP-E is ready to go.
There we are, nice and comfy.
Hm, I wonder where Tweak is.
BEEPING
Whoa, it certainly is dark down here.
Oh, that's better!
OK, little sea cucumber. This is where I found you.
Off you go!
Thank you!
Flappety flippers!
Whoa!
Oh!
CRASHING
I think I'm trapped down here in this trench.
But you'll figure a way out of this, Peso.
Oh! Everything is going to be fine.
POWER SPLUTTERS AND CUTS OUT
OK, it's just a little dark down here.
That's all, nothing to be afraid of.
I'll just radio the Octopod for help.
Hello?
Peso to Octopod. Can anyone hear me?
Come in, Octopod!
Hello?
No radio!
The battery is out of power.
Ah! Here we go, Cap.
All fixed up!
Ah!
Next time, remember to put the marshmallows into the chocolate
AFTER it comes out of the machine.
Um, thank you, Tweak.
OK, let's clean up this mess and get ready to launch the Octopod.
- Righty-o, Captain.
- Aye-aye, sir.
RUMBLING
Steady as she goes.
- Dashi, call the roll.
- Kwazii?
- Aye.
- Tweak?
- Aye!
- Shellington?
- Present.
- Professor Inkling?
Why, yes!
Tunip and the vegimals?
THEY RESPOND
We'll take that as a yes.
Captain Barnacles?
Um, Dashi, I'm standing right next to you.
Just doing my job, sir. Peso?
Peso?
'Peso, come in!'
Stop the ship!
Ah! Where in the seven seas is Peso?
This Octo glow stick will help me see a little better.
At least while I work out what to do.
- Ah!
- Boo!
PESO SHRIEKS
Peso?
Peso? Where are you?
Yoo-hoo, Peso!
Peso? Are you in here?
Huh?!
Where did the GUP-E go?
Better check the GUP finder.
Oh, no!
Cap, Peso must be in the GUP-E.
And it's trapped way down deep in an ocean trench!
Peso, come in. Hello?
Hello, Peso?
- His radio isn't working!
- GUP-E's battery must have run out.
Dashi, sound the Octo alert!
- ALERT SOUNDS
- Octonauts, to the launch bay!
Octonauts, there is no time to waste.
We've got to rescue Peso.
Kwazii, Tweak - into the GUP-C.
Who are you?
Boo!
Ah!
You...scared me!
I'm sorry. You asked who I am.
Yes, I did.
So, who are you?
- Boo!
- Ah!
Will you please stop doing that?
Stop what?
- Scaring me!
- I didn't mean to scare you.
- I'm sorry.
- Well, OK.
So what's you're name?
- Boo! Boo! Boo!
- PESO SHRIEKS WITH FRIGHT
My name is Boo!
I'm a spook fish.
A what?
A spook fish! Everyone thinks we're all spooky and stuff cos we have
these clear see-through heads. And we can do this...
with our eyes.
Ha, see?
Wow! That IS spooky, Boo.
Ha, told ya!
According to the GUP finder, the GUP-E is stuck around here,
inside that trench.
Cap, our GUP won't fit in there.
- She's right.
- Tweak, you wait here.
We may need that tow line.
Kwazii and I are going in.
Hey, want to play a game?
Now?
Oh, why not!
It's called I Spy With My Little Eye.
One of us looks around and says the first letter of what we see
and the other one has to guess what it is!
It is kind of dark down here.
But, OK.
I spy with my little eye something beginning with...
P.
Is it...
a penguin?
No.
- Plankton?
- No.
Er... Oh, I give up. What is it?
A polar bear!
Oh, OK. My turn.
I spy with my little... A polar bear?!
That polar bear is Captain Barnacles and Kwazii!
They've come to rescue me!
Peso, are you OK?
Aye, Captain. I got stuck down here when the GUP-E's battery died.
But I'm fine.
And who's that wee little GUP-E with you?
Oh. This is my new friend.
- Boo!
- Ah!
Shiver me whiskers! What manner of wild ocean beastie is this?
I'm not a beastie.
My name is Boo! I'm a spook fish.
We can see right up through our heads.
Aye-aye.
Tweak, we're going to need that tow line.
You've got it, Cap.
Let's hook it to the GUP and pull her out of here.
OK. Lift her up.
Steady, Tweak.
Careful!
PESO GASPS
Captain, look out!
What happened down there? You guys all right?
We're OK, Tweak.
But rocks fell over the GUP and now we can't move it.
Captain, what are we going to do?
Kwazii and I will just have to try to push that huge rock
out of the way.
Peso, Tweak will pull you up.
You steer away from the rocks.
But how will I see where I'm going?
If the ship's upside down I won't be able to see up.
Ah! We know someone who CAN see up.
We do?
Of course we do! Boo!
Sure, I'll help Peso steer.
Octonauts, let's do this!
On the count of three, Kwazii. One, two, three...
- Push!
- THEY GROAN
Now, pull, Tweak!
Now steer to the left, just a little.
OK. Steady.
Turn to the right.
That's it! Now steer left, just a bit!
That's good, Peso!
Now keep going straight.
- Ah!
- Way to go!
- We did it! Yay!
Well done, crew.
And you, too, Boo.
Boo?!
Me! Boo!
Oh! Ha-ha!
THEY ALL LAUGH
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
Email: subtitling@bbc.co.uk