Previously on Grimm...
- Can I buy you dinner?
- Sure,sounds great.
So how are things going
with our Detective?
He's not interested in me.
You know how to make
yourself irresistible.
- I do.
- ****
- Well,the sooner,the better.
- Blood of the deceived.
I was doing some baking.
Now,don't go giving those
away. I made them just for you.
Cookie.
************
- You got the Burroughs report?
- Gave it to me.
- And the autopsy on Clyde Harrington?
- It's not coming till Monday.
- What about ballistics?
- Nick. Go.
The wheels of justice will keep
turning,at least for one weekend.
Right.
- Okay,I'm going.
- Good.
You're not leaving.
What if she says no?
She's not going to say
no to a romantic weekend.
Oh,man. This is it. You're bringing it.
I can't believe it.
You're finally taking the
big leap in front of the bus.
Yeah,I'm thinking,uh...Yeah,maybe
dinner tomorrow night,
someplace quiet,romantic...
Look,take it from me.
The where doesn't matter
as much as the who.
- Well,if you need me...
- I won't.
I wrote down the number of the
place I'm staying right there.
"Whispering pines: For
the rest of your life."
Will you get the hell out of here?
Yes,I'm going,okay?
Good-bye,you're gonna miss me.
Au revoir,auf wiedersehen, arrivederci.
****
********
- Hey,Robin.
- Where are you?
- I'm sorry,my just car broke down.
- I can't stay here any longer.
I'm waiting for a tow.We'll
have to do it tomorrow.
Tomorrow? I... I was barely
able to get out today.
- If... if he finds out...
- I know. I'm doing everything I can.
Okay,tomorrow,but please
promise me you'll be here,okay?
- I don't have much time left.
- I will do my best.
Any big plans for tonight?
Um,no. You?
You bet. Gonna curl up on
that couch with my cat Samson,
watch tapprentice marathon,
and have a bite to eat.
Another badass Portland Friday night.
You got it.
Robin.
You know it's not safe
for you to be outside.
I... I just wanted some air.
It's time to eat.
No.
No,please.
Come on,you know how important it is for
you to get your vitamins in your condition.
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=- proudly presents
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync:
YTET- ¶¬ÃßµÄÖí
Grimm
Season 1 Episode 16
You sure you know where we're going?
We're looking for pine meadows drive.
The house has a name.
It's called "owl's nest."
This is where we're staying?
- No.
- Good.Then why are we here?
Oh,this is where I stop
to ask where we're staying.
Be right back.
- Hey. Can I help you?
- Uh,yeah.
I'm Nick Burkhardt.
Uh,sorry to bother you.
I'm staying at a house called
"the owl's nest."It's on,uh,pine...
Pine meadow drive. Yeah,you've arrived.
Sorry,it was,uh,a drunk driver
knocked down the sign last weekend.
Robin?
Uh,sorry,in middle of cooking.
Uh,the house is just up the road there.
Okay.
- Yeah,thanks.
- It's not a problem.
Damn it,Robin.You know what
we're gonna have to do now.
It's just up the road.And
for the record,I was not lost.
Drunk driver hit the post.
Hey,you okay?
I get a creepy feeling from that place.
Well...Fortunately,we're
not staying there.
Oh,my God,look at this place!
Wow. It's a lot of wood.
- You don't like it.
- No,I love it.
I would love an igloo with you.
Hi,this is Adalind.Sorry,I'm
not here to take your call.
Please leave a message
and I'll call you back.
Well put.
- Gonna get some glasses.
- Okay.
Robin!
Get inside!
Nick?
you got to do something.
- What's wrong?
- Down at the house,they're having a huge fight,
and he just grabbed her
and dragged her inside.
- Oh,wait,wait.How do you know?
- I just saw it.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
All right.I'm gonna
call the local police.
If there's trouble down there,they might already
know about it,and if they don't,they should.
Yeah,this is Nick Burkhardt,I want to report a
domestic disturbance at 1800 pine meadows drive.
Thank you.
Hey.Sheriff's on his way.
No. No,please.No more.
Sorry,baby...But it's got to be done.
Can I help you?
- You can help yourself.
- What?
You can get in the car, you can drive
away,and you can never come back.
All right. Hey,pal,I don't know...
I'm a cop.
And I do not repeat myself.
We received an emergency call about
a domestic dispute at this residence.
May I come inside?
It looks like the
sheriff's got it from here.
I was so excited to be
getting out of Portland,
but somehow... I don't know.Does it
feel like trouble is following us?
Well,I don't know. Maybe.
Yeah.Trouble again.
Maybe we should talk about this.
Talk about what?
The stuff that's been happening lately.
Run!
Who comes for her?
- Yeah,it's... Been a lot.
- Yeah.
And we haven't talked
about it. Not really.
Listen,Juliette,listen to me.
All that stuff is gonna calm down.
- I don't believe it.
- What?
Why isn't he arresting that animal?
If there's no obvious
signs of assault...
So what,this sheriff's just going to ignore the
whole thing,and pretend like it never happened?
If the wife doesn't press
charges,there's nothing we can do.
Maybe she'll press charges next time.
Maybe next time she'll be dead.
Hey. Look. I know it's a lousy answer.
I wish I had better one,but I don't.
We did everything we could.
It doesn't feel like it was enough.
- How'd it go?
- He threatened me.
If I stayed longer,I don't
know what he would have done.
Then it's going well.
- Is there anything else I can do,sir?
- I'll let you know.
Thank you for giving
me this opportunity.
You're welcome. Good night.
- Hello?
- Hey,Monroe. It's Nick.
Nick... It's 2:30.
Yeah,I know. I'm sorry.
I have a Bikram class at 6:00 a.m.,and hot yoga
on too-little sleep is how groin pulls happen.
- Aren't you supposed to be on vacation?
- Yeah. I am.
But you need my help.
Well,I can't exactly
bring the trailer with me.
All right. I get it.What do you got?
All right,I got a cat.
It's not a lion or a tiger,
but it's not a house cat either.
It's something in-between.
- Like an alley cat?
- Yeah.
Klaustreich. Total jerks.
Women love them, but it never ends well.
- Isn't that always the way?
- I don't know.
This could be a,uh, spousal situation.
No surprise there.
Molly,my girlfriend from high
school,left me for a Klaustreich,
so I might be a wee
bit biled up about them.
He told her he loved
her. He got her pregnant.
She ended up delivering
his litter at prom.
Her parents were not thrilled.
Um,hate to say it,but getting pregnant
in high school isn't exactly unheard of.
Well,maybe not that part,
but when she told her folks who the
father was,they went to the cops.
He paid her a little visit
before he skipped town.
As a good-bye,he slashed her face.
I hope they caught him.
Well,they didn't,but...
Somebody did.
All right,well, sorry
for calling so late.
Hey,don't worry about it.Especially
if it's about a Klaustreich.
Sleep with one eye open.
Now,I have the whole day planned.
Tell me.
Well,it starts with a trip into
beautiful downtown whispering pines...
- Okay.
- Where,uh,
you can drag me through as many
antique shops as you want to
until I pass out or
beg for you for mercy.
- Really,you want to do that?
- Well,not really.
But...I need to pick up some
groceries for our special dinner.
Ooh,sounds intriguing.
You have no idea.
6:00. Bring the money.
Can we do it later? It'll be hard for me
to get out after what happened yesterday.
Look,Robin, I'm taking a real chance here.The
sooner we get out, the further you'll get.
Excuse me.
Hi. I'm Juliette. I'm actually staying
at the house up on the hill behind yours.
I'm Robin.
You're lucky you live
in such a beautiful town.
We don't get away from
Portland that much.
I'm a vet,so weekends are bad, and Nick's
a cop,so he's busy pretty much all the time.
Your husband's a police officer?
Detective actually,
and he's not my husband.
Not yet,anyway.
Excuse me.
It's okay. I got it.It's
okay. Happens all the time.
Robin...I'm sure this
is none of my business,
but if you're in some kind of
trouble,or you need help of any kind...
Robin.
It's time to go.
Look,I really appreciate you
helping me out with all this.
Well,you never know when I
might need a discount on...
Tincture of prickle poppy?
Yeah,that's for,um, romantic stamina.
Oh. Well...
No wonder I didn't know what it was.
Found something.
Oh,maybe it's money.
It's not money.Passports
from Brazil,Canada.
And Germany. Wonder who they belong to.
Isn't that your brother?
- In all of them?
- Yeah,with different names.
What was he,a spy or something?
I have no idea.
Hey,Nick,I thought a vacation
for you kind of meant,you know...
Vacation for me too.
Look,I'm sorry.You know,this wasn't
part of my weekend plans either.
Hey,how was hot yoga? You
pull a groin or anything?
My groin is fine. Thank you.
All right,I'll make this
fast,but it is a weird one.
Some kind of bird-like creature.
Big golden eyes,uh,golden plumage...
- Is this a joke?
- No joke.
That sounds like a Seltenvogel,if
they weren't extinct.
- A Seltenvogel?
- Sounds like it.
- Are you with someone?
- Yeah,I'm with Rosalee.
I'm helping her out in the shop,but
let's get back to the Seltenvogel.
In ancient times, they
were highly-valued,
usually kept prisoner,you
know,like a concubine or a parakeet.
Well,what made them so valuable?
Once in their life,a
Seltenvogel produces this kind of
large,glandular thing.
I think it's called an "Unbezahlbar."
Easy for you to say. She
thinks it's called an...
"Unbezahlbar."
- "Unbezahlbar."
- My brother has a book.
Hang on,we're looking.
Here it is.
- Oh,here.
- Okay.
Uh,it is a dense mineral deposit
which grows in the throat sack.
It develops something like an egg.
Anyway,um,yeah,if the stone gets
too big, it needs to be delivered,
and the trick is getting it out intact,
because if it's damaged,
it's,you know,worthless.
Okay,but what made them so valuable?
Well,it's unbelievably
rare,for one thing,
but it's also supposed to be mostly
gold,if you believe in that kind of thing.
What,and I'm guessing a
Klaustreich would know this too?
Oh,man,this is the woman
who's with the Klaustreich?
- Yeah.
- Listen.
If he's anything like the guy
I went to high school with,
as soon as he gets what he wants,she
is going to be in big trouble,man.
And when I say big trouble, I
mean she's gonna get plucked.Okay?
- Big time.
- Thanks.
You scared me.
That's a compliment,coming from you.
What are you doing here?
It appears Detective Griffin
is...Taking favorably to your cookies.
He's left a dozen voicemail
messages as of this morning,
if you call that a response.
And he threatened your
visitor last night too.
I wish he'd done more than threaten him.
Do you realize that Peter suggested that we
sleep together to ensure our authenticity?
He's lucky I let him leave in one piece.
The next time Griffin
calls, I want you to answer.
It's time to move this up a notch.
I hope you realize how
dangerous this is...For me.
You can handle it.
Let's hope so.
Just be... Who you aren't.
I can't believe you remember
what we had on our first date.
How could I forget that?That was the most
expensive date I've ever had in my life.
Not if you add in what
happened afterward.
Ooh. Yeah,or after that.
- She has your card, she knows she can call us.
- Right.
We did everything we could do.
You're right.We did,now back to us.
You should try the tea. It's new.
I'm not so thirsty.
Hey.
What,right now?
Uh,no.Okay,no.I'll,uh...
I'll be right over.
- Who was that?
- It was Kevin. He needs a hand.
He,uh... he hit a deer.
His car's in a ditch.
He's waiting for,uh,a
tow, and needs a ride home.
Got no idea how long this is gonna take.
Okay.
You do the crabs, I'll finish chopping.
Ooh,thanks.
- Hey.
- What?
- Gotta melt the butter.
- Right.
- That's weird.
- Glad you said it first.
- She didn't call.
- Maybe she couldn't.
- What about the crab?
- It can wait.
Okay. I'll,uh, just check
to see if she's okay.
- You want me to go with you?
- No,no.
If it's something serious,
it's better you stay here.
I know. Go.
- Hello?
- Adalind.
- Yes?
- Uh,it's Hank.
I guess I just expected to
get your voicemail again.
I've been completely off the radar.
Work's been crazy.
18-hour days. I'm so sorry.
I was just actually just
about to call you back.
That's okay. Really.
It's just good to hear your voice.
It's good to hear your voice too.
I was thinking,uh, maybe
we can see each other.
I mean,whenever is good for you.
I'm free for dinner tomorrow night.
Tomorrow. Perfect.
Um,I'll pick a place and call you back.
- How's 7:00 sound?
- Sounds lucky,can't wait.
Robin?
Hey,hurry up,we got to go.
Hi.
He was on time, but
you're a little too late.
- You killed him.
- No.
You killed him.You should have
never involved him in our business.
*****
- Sheriff Munson.
- Sheriff.
Detective Burkhardt,Portland pd.
I'm the one who called 911
about the Steinkellners.
What's the problem?
There's been a homicide.
Homicide? Are you kidding me?
No. Victim's name is Gary Cardero.
At least,I think that's
him, he's torn up pretty bad.
Where are you?
I'm on what looks to be a
forest service road about
a mile or a half-mile behind
the Steinkellner's house.
I'm coming out.
Hey! Get out!
Get... Robin! Get
out!This is your fault!
- Yeah?
- Where are you?
I just saw him driving
her up to the house.
I'm on my way back.Just stay
in the house until I get there.
Get inside!
Timothy,please. I can't.We've
already done this once today.
Once is never enough when
you're expecting,sweetie.
Open up.
Okay. Okay,let's put a little...
A little weight on that baby.
Open.
Turn it off.
Yeah,you're a Klaustreich.
Now,turn it off.
It's gonna be okay.It's gonna
be okay.You're gonna be okay.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Oh,my God,you poor
thing.What did he do to you?
He told me he loved me.
Let me get you a glass of water.
- You're a Grimm.
- Um,yeah.
Why are you helping me?
Uh, can we talk about this later?
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Look,I called the
sheriff, he's on his way.
What?
Yeah,he's pulling up
to the house right now.
The sheriff is Tim's cousin. He... he
knows all about this.He's part of it.
- Where is she?
- The guy from up the hill took her.
He was here. He had a gun.
- He's a cop.
- He's a Grimm.
- He wants her for himself.
- That's not gonna happen.
All right,we need to
get you out of here.
No,you don't understand.There's
only one road and they'll be on it.
They're coming.
Go after her.
- But what about you?
- I'll sneak outside and call state police.
- You've gotta help her,Nick.
- Oh,Juliette.
I know,but this is why you bought
it for me in the first place. Now,go.
Car's still here!
They gotta be around here somewhere.
Not gonna get far with
her in her condition.
Robin!
Oh,man.
Robin...We gotta get you out of here.
It's time.
Oh. I don't know how to do this.
You have to...Take it out.
Okay.
- Hello?
- Rosalee?
Hey,Nick Burkhardt
here. I need your help.
- What's wrong?
- Well,I'm with...
Robin, the Seltenvogel.
Nick,you need to get that stone out
of her before it cuts off her airway.
- Yeah,I know,but how?
- Is that Nick?
He called you? You called her?
Can you guys do this
later? That girl needs help.
She says I need to take it out.
You grab the book. No,you... no,you need
to cut it out of her. Do you have a knife?
Uh,yeah,I do.
Okay,right here. Oh,boy.
Okay,the cut should be made vertically
along the widest point of the Unbezahlbar.
The... the skin should be pretty tight,
so you just need to press the knife through the
flesh until you feel the hard surface of the stone.
Okay.
- Nick? Update.
- Uh,a little busy here.
Oh,it says be really careful
not to cut the jugular.
Uh,not helping.
You want to get close,
but not too close.
- How will I know if I'm too close?
- Dude,you'll know. Tons of blood.
Trust me,it's not
pretty. I've been there.
Okay. Okay,okay. I
think I'm,uh... I'm done.
All right,now slip
your hands into the cut
and gently detach the Unbezahlbar from
the Faserig membrane holding it in place.
You should feel a slight
pop when it separates.
Okay.Okay,it popped.
Okay,that's great. Just,um...Just
simply lift it up and out.
Oh,God.
How is she?
She...Seems to be
breathing a lot better.
- I think she's gonna be okay.
- Nice goin',dude.
Hey,call me later,will you,when
this all calms down,okay?
I think this is yours.
I don't want it.
I never did.
Real nice job you did there.
Yeah,saved us a lot of trouble.
From what I understand,
if this thing breaks...
- It's worthless.
- Okay,and so are you,if you're dead.
All we want is the stone.
Yeah? How about a little catch?
No,no,n... Now,take it easy.
Look,we're not greedy,
we can cut you in.
Do you have any idea how
much that is worth to us?
Oh,really?
Are you insane?
Well,I'm in the woods, I just cut a golden
egg out of a girl's neck.You tell me.
Hey,sheriff.
Juliette.
Keep the gun on him.
Well,you know what they say,Tim.
In order to make an omelet,
you got to break a few eggs.
Okay,look,I know that this weekend
didn't turn out the way I planned.
And,uh,I think the thing of it is,
you kind of have to make
your own perfect moments.
So...
Juliette,will you be my wife?
I can't.
I love you so much.
And I really,really want
to marry you someday.
But I can't right now.
- Because of what? I'm a cop? Is that...
- It's not because of your job.
It's... you.
I feel like you've been
keeping things from me.
You've been so closed off.
I know how hard Aunt
Marie's death was for you.
But until you can let
me back in again...
I can't say yes.
********
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=- proudly presents
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync:
YTET- ¶¬ÃßµÄÖí
Grimm
Season 1 Episode 16