*********
Do you think she's prettier than me?
I do.
That may just be a family bias.
We owned this in the 17th century,
then lost it along Wita lot
of heads during the revolution.
So how are things going
with our Detective?
They're not.He's not interested in me.
Maybe we need to try a little
harder.He did save your life.
Apparently,he doesn't feel
right taking advantage of that.
You know how to make
yourself irresistible.
I do,but it's gonna
require a little effort.
Well,the sooner the better.
Lucky for you,he had
a physical recently.
Why is this so important to you?
It's important to you too.
A Grimm on the other side
isn't good for either one of us.
So why am I not going after him?
Because the way to a man's
soul is through his friends.
Now go fall in love.
I think she's fat.
Nick,I wanna ask you something.
- That sounds important.
- Well,it sort of is.
I think it's time...
Look,Juliette.If you have
something to say,just say it.
But I know it's been
a little tough lately...
No,no,I wanna learn to shoot.
- W... a gun?
- No,a bow and arrow.Yes,a gun.
Oh,I thought you didn't like guns.
I don't,but you know
what I like even less?
Feeling unsafe in my own home.
- Are you expecting anyone?
- No.You?
I thought I told you
never to come back here.
No,please don't take this
wrong.Don't jump to any conclusions.
It's just that I feel so bad...
We all felt so bad about what happened here
at your house you share with your not-wife,
who is lovely,by the
way.Oh,and here she is.
- Hello,ma'am.
- Hi.
We made you both a little something.
If you ever decide to get
married and have a family...
Uh,or not.Uh,well,here it is.
Oh,and by the way,we're making
sure no one else bothers you again.
One more thing,I noticed that
you door needs a little work.
- Maybe you hadn't noticed.
- Well,I've been a little busy.
Right,right,of course you
have.Well,anyway,I didn't mean to interrupt.
Thanks again so much for everything.Uh,enjoy...
go back to whatever... uh,bye.
The refrigerator repairman is
gonna keep people from bothering us?
I don't understand.
Yeah,uh,remember that license plate you
wrote down?Those people who were watching us?
- Yeah.
- Well,I went to their house and he was there.
- The refrigerator repairman?
- Yeah.
And I told them to stop bothering us.
Well,did they say anything?Did they
explain why they were watching our house?
Well,apparently they had had
some trouble with some guy
and they thought I was that guy and
they just wanted to see if I was.
Well,who was the guy
they thought you were?
You know what,I didn't actually
get the details on that.
But I guess they felt really
bad about their mistake.
Why don't we open this up?
Oh,it's really beautiful.
Yeah,it is.
They must have felt really bad.
- This is gonna be a big score for us.
- Yeah,big.
I'm feeling good.
I'm real good.
Let's do this.
Come on.Come on!Come on!
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=- proudly presents
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync:
YTET- ¶¬ÃßµÄÖí
Grimm
Season 1 Episode 15
Hi.Remember me?
Of course.Wh... what can I do for you?
I made a list.
Coeur diable,rot inguen,essigblasse.
Hmm,let me get it for you.
- Freddy.
- Yes?
- Fresh.
- Yes,ma'am.
Absolutely.
Let's do this.
Come on.
- How much do I owe you?-
Nothing,I-it's on the house.
That is so sweet.Thank you,Freddy.
Anytime.
- Can I help you?
- Where's the "j"?
*******
Idiot,where is it?
And I want the pharmaceutical-grade
stuff,not the crap you've got on the shelf.
In the basement.
Let's go.
- Where is it?
- It's gotta be here somewhere.
Got some.I got some!
Mother lode.Come on.
We gotta get out of here.Forget
about it.The cops are gonna be here.
- There's boxes over here.
- Let's go!
- Thanks for the "j," man!
- Later.
Come on!We gotta get
out of here!Let's go!
Clint,come on!
- Let's go.
- Oh,my leg!
- Let's go.We gotta move.
- He bit my leg.
Well,he was shot at close range.There's
some powder burns on his clothing.
- Got some blood in his mouth.
- Internal bleeding,maybe.
Looks kinda human.
He took a bite out of his killer?
- Looks like it.
- Makes for some good DNA.
Why kill the owner of
a tea and spice shop?
How much money could there
be in a place like this?
Maybe he was dealing under the table.
I've checked this guy out once before.
- Fuchsbau,right?
- Oh,my God.
There's a basement.
Awful lot of herbs and spices.
Yeah,who knows what all this stuff is?
We'd better get it all tested.
We've gotta check phone
records and find next of kin.
I got a Rosalee Calvert,victim's
sister.Listed as beneficiary,lives in Seattle.
- You want me to make the call?
- No,it's my turn.
- Hello?
- Is this Rosalee Calvert?
Yes.
This is Detective Burkhardt from
the Portland police department.
Uh,you have a brother,Frederick Calvert?
Yes.
********
Okay,let's see.
Time for blood of the deceived.
And... Blood of the deceiver.
Detectives Burkhardt,Griffin,this
is Rosalee Calvert.
I'm sorry you had to come down
here under these circumstances.
Please,sit down.
- Who killed him?
- We don't know yet.
- What do you know?
- He was killed in an apparent robbery.
Since no money was taken,we assume
they were after something in the shop.
He was able to set off the emergency alarm,so
we don't know if they got what they were after.
What do you know about
your brother's business?
He sold tea,spices,and
herbs.Not very complicated.
My brother didn't have any enemies that
I know of.Is that your next question?
Do you know if your brother
was dealing in anything illegal?
No,I saw him once a year and I
spoke to him mostly on the phone.
I want to bury him.
I want to close up his shop
and and I wanna go home.
So what do I have to
do to get that done?
Lab reports are in.
I'd like to go to the
shop.Can I do that?
Well,we are done with our investigation,
but one of us will have to go with
you until we know forensics are done.
We don't know if that's
all your brother's blood.
All right,he might have taken
a bite out of the killer.
I didn't hurt your
brother.I'm not gonna hurt you.
Do you know anything about Gallenblase?
- Human gallbladder.
- I know what it is.
Did you know your brother was dealing?
No.
- He was being supplied by Geiers.
- Is that who killed him?
That was my first thought.
But I think whoever killed
him was after something else.
- What?
- I was hoping you could tell me.
I have no idea what he has in here.
But I'll look.
- Yeah?
- Went over the lab reports.
We've got a big fat nothing.
Just like the sign says...
Herbs,spices,and teas.
A few are poisonous,but
none are illegal.
- You get anything?
- Not yet.
I think the sister's
clean.I'm coming back.
If you can think of anything...
Or if you need
anything,just... Just call me.
You're not at all what I expected.
Yeah.
- If you find out anything...
- I'll call you.
Doesn't it hurt?
What do you think?
- Well,you shouldn't have shot him!
- He wasn't chomping on your leg.
Ah,police are gonna be
all over this thing now.
We're going back.
- What?
- We left a fortune in there.
Cops don't know what we're after and
they'll be done going over the place by now.
Give me the needle.Give it to me.
Hey,how you doing?
Hi.This is embarrassing.I just
stopped by to leave you some cookies.
Yeah?
I was doing some baking and I thought
I wouldn't be here if it wasn't for you,
so here I am.
You know,you already bought me dinner.
I know I didn't have to do this.
But you saved my life,and believe
it or not,that meant something to me.
It's hard to know how to repay that.This
is more for me than it is for you.
You might not even like
chocolate chip cookies.
Well,in fact,I do.
And that was very nice of you.
Maybe I should have a bite.
Maybe you should wait till I'm
gone in case you don't like them.
I'm a brave soul.
Do we have a verdict?
We do.They're incredible.
Don't go giving those away.I
made them just for you.
Uh,nothing in the
spice shop was illegal.
It's really a shame.He was a nice guy.
Is there anything in these reports
that someone would kill for?
I'm sure there is.
But I don't know what
any of these words mean.
Beramethyl silacybanate?
Hornisolic fullmanoxin?
I mean,what the heck is
this stuff?I have no idea.
- Could you tell by looking at it?
- Maybe.
********
Another partner?
Sort of.
This is Monroe.Monroe,this
is Rosalee Calvert.
I knew your brother.I'm sorry.
We need to get into the basement.
- Do you need me to go with you?
- No,just a little follow up.
Okay.
Hey,this box was opened and it looks
like some of the vials were taken.
I can't be certain,but it
looks a little bit like "j".
- "J"?
- It's derived from Jansene.It's a kind of mold.
It's lethal to most of humanity,but
it has an opiate-like effect on... us.
Used correctly,it's an
incredible painkiller,
but if it's used for recreational purposes,it's
like meth mixed with rat poison and helium.
It's highly addictive.
It's terrible for your liver and it's
not so good for your brain either.
Of course,if you had a brain,you wouldn't
be using the stuff in the first place.
- Did you find something?
- Do you know of a drug called "j"?
- Yes.
- Do you know if your brother was selling it?
Even if he was,it's... it's not illegal.
She's right.That's why you... you
know,the cop you... Has never heard of it.
I need to know everything in this
basement that a Wesen would kill for.
Will it help you find the
men who killed my brother?
- I hope so.
- Then I'll do it now.
Okay.I'll call you later.
You said you knew my brother?
Yes.
I just wanted to make sure.
So they don't know,do they?
- Who?
- The cops you work with.They don't know who you are.
No.
Does it matter?
I'm just trying to...
Understand how... How this works.
It's,um... It's a little complicated.
Yeah,I can see that.Just find
the men who killed my brother.
- Oh,my gosh,you scared me.
- Sorry.
- What are you doing?
- Oh,the door.
When I was here before,I
noticed that it needed work,
and well,Nick is so busy and I thought maybe
I'd come over and help out a little bit.
I'm really good at this stuff.I
can fix just about anything.
Oh,before I forget...
My wife baked you folks
a little something.
Uh,hope you like cherry.
That's really nice,but
you do not have to...
No,really,we want to.My wife insisted.
She makes incredible pies,believe me.
So,uh,your door should
be fine now.So,uh,enjoy.
- What about your basket?
- Oh,that's for you too.
My kids made it.
Come on.Let's go.
- Lights are on.
- Why are the lights on?
Because somebody
forgot to turn them off.
Let's just get the stuff
and get the hell out of here.
These are open.Why are they open?
Must be yours.
No.Mine's in the car.
- She cut me.
- Shut up and help me.
Don't you think it's
going a little overboard?
Maybe they're just
generous people,you know?
Did he really fix the door?
And he did a good job.
- Yeah,Burkhardt.
- It's Rosalee.
I was at the shop and two men
broke in while I was there.
- Are you okay?
- Yes,I'm f... I'm fine.
I'm scared,but I'm fine.I got
away.I'm at my brother's house.
- Are you safe there?
- I think so.
Okay,can you identify
the men who broke in?
If I saw them again,yes.
Now give me your address.I'm
sending officers to pick you up.
- You sure?
- Positive.
How do you do this?
Well,we start with the
last known addresses,
- see if we can find them or somebody who knows them...
- I mean you,as a cop.
And the people you
work with have no idea?
Well,I do what I can do.
I don't envy you.
It's not easy living two lives.
Suppose you checked into mine.
Next of kin are usually
the first suspects.
You were arrested a couple
times for breaking and entering?
A long time ago.
- You wanna talk about it?
- Not really.I cleaned up my act.
So what am I supposed to do now?
Be careful.
I'm gonna have some officers take you back
to your brother's house and stay outside.
What about your partner?
- Hank?
- No,the other one.
I want someone that I have
something in common with.
Hi,um,Nick called.
He... he thought it would be a good idea
if I came over and,you know,kept an eye...
- Thanks for coming.
- Yeah.
Can't be too careful.
That's why I wanted a
Blutbad instead of a cop.
The guys who came to the
shop were Skalengecks.
- Great.
- You'll be able to smell them a mile away.
There's food in the
fridge.You get the couch.
- Good night.
Take it easy.
- It's just me.
- Yeah,sorry,I can see that now.
I really appreciate what you
did.I'm gonna go to the shop.
Excuse me?You think that's a good idea?
I have no intention of staying
here any longer than I have to.
- I've got a lot to take care of.
- Okay,can we just slow down a second?
Why would these guys kill a shopkeeper for
some herbs and spices that aren't even illegal?
It just doesn't make any sense.
Well,there are plenty of legal
substances that'll still fry your brain.
- Burkhardt.
- Rosalee says she's going to the shop.
- Where are you?
- I'm still at her brother's place.
- What do you want me to do?
- Cookie.
- Did you bring enough for everyone?
- No.
My mother made the best
cookies on the block.
She shared them with everyone
and they loved her for it.
Well,do you think you
can talk her out of it?
All right,I'll go cookie-less.
Just stay with her.I'll
send someone over there.
- See ya.
- Hang on.Hang on.
What have we got?
Looks like we got a vehicle I.D.
For Clint Vickers,one of our perps.
We got a patrol car on the street
watching the car.So far,no sightings.
Okay,I need you to go back to the
spice shop,keep an eye on things.
- We'll check out the car.
- Yeah.You got it.
Okay,that's the car and I'm
guessing they're in that building.
- Any contact?
- No movement.
All right,you go around
back.We'll take the front.
*****
***************
Hank.
Hank?
- Hey.Hank.
- I saw someone.
Who?
I don't know.
It's gonna be sad to
see this place close.
There's not that many
places we can go anymore.
- It's not an easy business.
- You were in it?
My parents were.They were apothecaries.
I gave it a shot.
- And what happened?
- Hey.
I'm supposed to,uh... Uh,come down
here and,uh,make sure everything is...
You don't look so
good.Are you all right?
Yeah.Yeah.Never better.
Oh,my God.
Oh,God.
What the hell is this?
My guess is they use it to
smoke whatever they wanna smoke.
They got away.You mind
telling me what happened?
They made us when we got here,captain.
We lost them.
- Captain,it was my fault.
- How?
I thought I saw somebody.I
didn't want them to get hurt.
I got distracted and... They got away.
- Yeah?
- This cop you sent down here is in really bad shape.
I mean,he just walked in and collapsed.
And his whole face looks like a
volcano that's about to explode.
Rosalee says there's only one way to
deal with this and it is definitely not,
you know,standard medical practice,so
you gotta get down here.Fast.
Uh,I sent Sergeant Wu to the spice
shop and I think he has something.
So if you cover
this,I'll see what he has?
Go.
We all make mistakes,Hank.Luckily,no
one got hurt.
I can't find the... The keim
extract.Are you sure it's here?
Top shelf,corner right.I
saw some yesterday.
Got it.
- All of it?
- He'll need it.
- We need to get him to a hospital.
- They won't know what to do.
They'll read it as one of those mystery
infections they can't identify and he'll die.
I've seen this before.
Hold him down!Hold... Hold him down.
Hold him down.Hold him down.
Here we go.Here we go... okay.
- Hurry up.This is not going well.
- Open his mouth.
- Wait.You want him to drink it?
- Yeah,he better.
- Come on.
- Get his mouth.
Hello?
- Adalind?
- Yes?
It's me,Hank.I've been calling
and you haven't been picking up.
- I got worried.
- About what?
Just wanted to make sure you're okay.
That's very sweet,but I'm fine.
Good.
Is everything okay with you?
Yeah.Just a lot going on.
Listen,I was thinking maybe we
should get together for dinner.
Oh,I'm really busy this week.
But why don't you give me a call at
the end of the week and we'll see.Okay?
- Sure.
- Bye,Hank.
How much longer?
His pulse has calmed down.
We might as well have a look.
I think it worked.
He's gonna sleep for quite a while.Is
there some place we can take him?
I think it would be best if he
woke up in familiar surroundings.
- His apartment's not far.
- I'll get his feet.
- You said you've seen this before?
- Yeah,at my parents' shop.
I was probably 17.
A friend of my father's came
in with the same symptoms.
My father said he had ingested a
Zaubertrank meant for somebody else.
Zaubertrank?They can be nasty.
Does somebody wanna tell
me what a Zaubertrank is?
Primitive,antediluvian,pseudo-psychological
concoctions meant to mess with your head.
It causes obsessive behaviors.
If the right person takes it,it
creates a deep emotional response,
but if the wrong person
takes it,this happens.
I think we caught it in time.
- Can we leave him alone?
- Yeah,he should be... Good for a few hours.
All right.We almost caught the
man who killed your brother.
But they got away.
In their apartment,we found the boxes
of "j" that they stole from the shop,
and we also found this pipe.It
kind of looked like a horn.
- A Saugendampf.
- Oh,man.
Addicts.And you got their stash?
They will be needing more,and I am telling
you,addicts with guns is a bad combo.
- Where would they go for more?
- Don't look at me.
I'm not.
I have a feeling you know.
Yeah.
I was hooked for seven years.
My brother finally helped me to get
clean.That's why I went to Seattle.
If they're looking to score,it'll
be an island of dreams.
- A Trauminsel?Here?
- They're everywhere.
Are we talking about some
kind of Wesen crack house?
- Yeah.
- Well,how do we find it?
We find a dealer.They'll know.
You're kidding me.Rosalee?
- You're looking good.
- Thanks.
Thought you went straight,baby.
- What you doing around these parts again?
- You know why I'm here.
That's a shame.How much
Trauminsel time you want?
Enough for two.
****
Sweet dreams.
It's my brother,I should
be the one that goes in.
You've done enough.
Let me handle this,okay?Just
don't act like a cop.
We're just a couple of Blutbaden
out on the town,having a good time.
What up,bro?
I can't smell anyone in
here,man.This is brutal.
You take those,but be careful.
- Whoa,bro!
- Hey!
This dude's shootin' people!
Run!
I got him,Nick!I got him!
- Now you're sure you're okay?
- Yeah,yeah.
Don't remember much.I went
to that shop like you wanted.
Then woke up here.
Had some weird-ass dreams.
Clearly,I'm gonna need a facial.
Now I'm just kinda... kinda hungry.
- You got something to eat here?
- Oh,yeah,yeah,I'm good.
I'm good.
Listen,you take it easy for the next couple
of days and if you need anything,you call me.
Yes,will do.Thanks.
All right.
- Oh,hey.
- Hi.
Now,I know it's not...
Equal trade for my life,
but I just wanted to say,I'm glad you
know how to clock a dude with a brick.
Nobody's given me
flowers for a long time.
So,what's going on?I
thought you were packing up.
Sort of changed my mind and...
Had to stick around for the trial,so I thought
I'd keep the shop open till I had to sell it.
And I'd forgotten,Portland's
a pretty nice place.
- Yeah,kinda grows on you.
- Yeah.
Well,I got the rest of the day
off if,you know,you need any help.
Sure.
I'll put these in water.
Are you sure you've
never done this before?
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=- proudly presents
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync:
YTET- ¶¬ÃßµÄÖí
Grimm
Season 1 Episode 15