- Does everybody hate these shoes?
- Yeah.
But don't worry. Nobody's gonna focus
on that if you wear that towel-dress.
Tell him.
It's her first day at this new job.
You're not supposed to start with her.
All right, I suppose I can wait a day.
- What are you doing Friday?
- Why?
I need you at a bachelor party
for my weird cousin, Albert.
You know, he's the botanist?
Oh, God!
Botanists are such geeks.
Is that a dinosaur tie?
Morning!
Rach, I'm here with the purses!
It must take you forever
to find your keys.
Thank you, Pheebs.
You're welcome. Please want
the one with the turtles.
No, turtles scare me.
I don't need that today.
Honey, just relax.
It's gonna be fine.
Why don't I come down there,
and I'll take you to lunch?
Honey, thank you!
But Mark's taking me out.
Mark? Is that the same Mark
that helped you get the job?
Yeah, it's kind of like a "good luck
on your first day" sort of thing.
Is this a lunch box?
No, it's a purse.
And there's a thermos in it.
- So can you make it on Friday?
- What?
Yeah, I think so.
Why am I invited to this again?
Apparently, Albert has no friends.
He's very excited about
the bachelor party.
I think, actually, he's only getting
married so he can see a stripper.
A stripper at a bachelor party.
That is so cliche.
Why don't you guys get a magician?
Well, if a magician can open my beer
with his butt cheeks, then all right.
The One With All the Jealousy
She's having lunch with him?
Lunch with him?
You should've seen the hug he gave her
when she got the job!
And he's really good-looking.
- What am I gonna do?
- You don't do anything.
Keep it inside.
Learn how to hide your feelings.
Don't cry out loud.
Guess who has an audition
for a Broadway musical?
I wanna say you, but it seems like
such an easy answer.
It is me! It's a musical version
of A Tale of Two Cities.
So I think I'm gonna sing
"New York, New York"...
...and "I Left My Heart
in San Francisco."
Joey, I don't think
you get to pick the cities.
- What?
- Mr. Dickens gets to pick them.
Who?
I'll get you the Cliff Notes.
- The what?
- The abridgment.
Okay.
The what?
Then the style number...
...the invoice number
and the shipping date.
Good. Any questions so far?
What kind of discount do we get?
- Twenty percent.
- I love this job!
- My first call!
- Here, let me.
Rachel Greene's line.
How may I help you?
Hi, is Rachel there?
- And who may I say is calling?
- This is Ross.
Ross of?
Of Ross and Rachel.
Hi, it's Mark.
- Hey, Mark.
- Hey.
Hold on a second.
It's Ross.
- Hi, honey.
- Hi.
What's Mark doing
answering your phone?
Oh, he's just goofing around.
Oh, that's funny.
Why isn't he goofing around
in his own office?
This is his office too. I told you,
we're Joanna's two assistants.
Why does Joanna need two assistants?
How lazy is she?
Oh, my God! What did I just do?
I think I just shipped 3000 bras
to Personnel!
Honey, I gotta go!
Mark, I need you!
Okay! Bye-bye!
Ross!
I'm sorry, sweetie.
I was just trying to...
I was dialing another number.
All right, I just got changed in 30
seconds so you could be alone with him.
You better go for it.
Please. I'm not going for anything.
Well, if you don't, I will.
Would you please go?
'Night, Mon.
'Night, Julio.
Julio, someone left their book here.
Actually, that is mine.
What are you reading?
Flowers of Evil, by Baudelaire.
Have you read it?
Have I read it?
No. Are you enjoying it?
I thought that I would,
but the translation's no good.
You're a poet,
and you don't know it.
Actually, I...
I am a poet.
So you do know it.
So, what kind of things
do you write about?
Things that move me:
The shadow of a tree...
...a child laughing...
...or this lip.
Mine?
Right here?
I could write an epic poem
about this lip.
How would that go?
Well, it didn't rhyme...
...but I liked it.
Lovely.
Just lovely.
Really? Thanks.
Listen, Joey. We definitely want
to see you for the callback on Saturday.
Excellent!
- I'll be there.
- Okay.
And listen, don't forget to bring
your jazz shoes for the dance audition.
My agent said that
it wasn't a dancing part.
Joey, all the roles gotta dance a little.
Believe me, with your dance background,
it'll be a piece of cake.
"Three years of modern dance
with Twyla Tharp"?
"Five years with
the American Ballet Theatre"?
Hey, everybody lies
on their resume, okay?
I wasn't one of
the Zoom kids either.
Well, can you, like, dance at all?
Yeah, I can dance.
You know...
Oh, no, no, no, no.
What is that?
Sure, it looks stupid now.
There's no music playing.
I have to get that.
But, no, no.
Hello. Hi.
Yeah, listen, I'm in need of a stripper,
and I was told that you do that.
Let me ask you this. What do you do
for the extra hundred?
So would I have to provide the grapes?
Hi.
How was last night
with Julio, senorita?
It so was amazing. He's so sexy and
smart, which makes him even sexier.
I gotta tell you this. Last night,
we were fooling around...
...and all of a sudden he stops
to write a poem.
Get out! I couldn't stop
if a meteor hit me.
Okay, we have our stripper,
a Miss Crystal Chandelier.
Sure, you name a kid that, what do you
expect them to grow up to be?
Anyway, when he left, he forgot
to take the poem with him.
Now, I am totally dense about poetry,
but I think this is pretty good.
Check it out. Read it.
"The Empty Vase."
Translucent beauty...
To yourself.
You know what? That's pretty good.
Good. I think so too.
Phoebe?
Yeah.
Great! I'm so glad you guys like it!
- All right, I gotta go to work.
- Hold on. I'm not done.
All right, give it back when
you're through.
- See you guys.
- Bye-bye.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Poor Monica!
What? What? What?
What? He was with her
when he wrote this poem!
Look! My vessel so lovely,
with nothing inside?
Now that I've touched you,
you seem emptier still?
He thinks Monica's empty.
She's the empty vase!
- Vase, vase?
- Monica's not an empty vase.
You think vase?
- You really think that's what he meant?
- Totally.
Oh, God!
And she seems so happy too.
Done.
What happened?
Joey, what do you think
this poem means?
Monica's the vase, right?
You are such a mystery to me.
Do you have the Ralph Lauren file?
Oh, yeah, sure! It's right...
What's that?
It's from Ross. It's a Love Bug.
Somebody wants people to know
you have a boyfriend.
No, that's not what he's doing.
He's just really romantic.
- Excuse me. Are you Rachel Greene?
- Yes.
One, two, three.
Congratulations on your first week
At your brand-new job
It won't be long
Before you're the boss
And you know who will be there
To support you
Your one and only boyfriend
It's nice to have a boyfriend!
Your loyal, loving boyfriend, Ross!
I'm hurt!
I'm actually hurt...
...that you'd think I'd send you any of
those things out of anything but love.
Hurt! Hurt!
All right, Ross. I get it. You're hurt!
Can't a guy send
a barbershop quartet...
...to his girlfriend's office anymore?
Oh, please!
Ross, it was so obvious.
It was like you were
marking your territory.
You might as well have just come in
and peed all around my desk!
I would never do that.
Look, I know what's going
on here, okay?
Mark explained it all to me.
He said this is what you guys do.
Yeah, well, if Mark said that,
then Mark's an idiot.
Mark's a genius.
Why? How?
How is he a genius?
Don't you see what's happening here?
Instead of hitting on her right away,
he's becoming her confidante.
Now he's gonna be the guy she goes to,
to complain about you.
You okay over there?
I tried taking a dance class today
to get ready for this callback tomorrow.
- How'd it go?
- Knocked over a girl.
Good work. Can we get back to the
Mark thing? What am I gonna do?
Why don't you send her a musical bug?
No, you already did that.
All right, you're gonna have
to go there yourself now.
- Make a few surprise visits.
- I don't know, you guys.
Fine, don't do anything.
Just sit and talk to us.
Meanwhile, she is talking
to him about you.
And he's being Mr. Joe Sensitive.
She starts thinking, "Maybe this is the
guy for me because he understands me."
And before you know it,
she's with him.
And you'll be all, "Oh, man!"
And he'll be all, "Yes!"
And us, we'll be like, "Oh, dude!"
And pretty soon you'll be like:
"Hi."
And, "Well, I can't go.
Rachel and Mark might be there."
And we'll be like, "Man, get over it!
It's been four years!"
He paints quite a picture, doesn't he?
Here's the Shelley Segal stuff
for December.
Wait, I've got something for you.
- Mark.
- It's okay. Rachel knows.
Yeah, but even so.
I can't help it.
I'm just crazy about you.
Oh, that is so sweet!
I know I'm Mr. Inappropriate today,
but it's just so tough.
I mean, I see you walking around,
and I want to touch you and hold you.
Come on, no one's around.
Just kiss me.
All right, that's it!
Get off of her!
What is going on?
What's going on?
I'll tell you what's going on!
Ross!
I have been down in your store
for 20 minutes, trying to get a tie.
What do I have to do
to get some service?
Hi, Rach.
Joey? Joey Tribbiani?
Joey, I've got a problem.
I just got a call
from my dance captain.
He's having a relationship crisis
and can't get out of Long Island.
So does that mean the audition's off?
Listen, Joey. Seeing as you've got
the most experience...
...I want you to take these dancers
and teach them the combination.
What?
Joey, come on. It's easy.
You know, it's hand, hand...
...head, head...
...up, pas de bourree, pas de bourree,
big turn here, rond de jambe.
Slide, step, step...
...and jazz hands!
It's steppity-step and jazz hands.
Have fun.
Bye.
- Hey.
What are you wrapping?
Look what I got Julio.
Yeah, it's a vase.
Yeah, just like the one in the poem.
Not exactly like
the one in the poem.
What do you mean?
Remember how you said you were
really dense about poetry?
So I'm just an empty vase?
What?
So, I don't read as many
important books as you do.
And I don't write trick poems
that aren't actually what they seem.
And you know what?
I get excited about stupid stuff...
...like when my People magazine
comes on Saturday...
...and the new
Hold Everything catalog.
But that doesn't mean I'm empty. I care
about things, like friends and family.
You have no right to make that kind of
judgment! You don't even know me!
The poem is not about you.
- What?
- "The Empty Vase" is not about you.
My baby preciosa, you make me so sad
that you would think this.
I'm sorry. It's...
My friend Phoebe said...
No, it's...
It's about all women.
Well, all American women.
You feel better now?
All right, let's do it.
What was that?
I know. It's the best
I could get out of them.
Well, people!
People, people, people!
Let's try it again. And this time,
let's everybody watch Joey.
Show them how it's done.
Count it off, Mack.
Did you have fun at
the bachelor party last night?
Yeah, look what I got!
See, she's fully dressed, right?
And then you click it,
and she's naked!
And then you click it again,
and she's dressed.
She's a business woman,
walking down the street.
She's window shopping,
and she's naked!
Hi.
Hello.
You know what? I'm gonna spend
some alone time with the pen.
I'm sorry. I was an idiot.
A big idiot.
It's just you have to realize this whole
Mark thing is really hard for me.
Honey, why is it hard? We've
been together for almost a year now.
Well, I was with Carol
for, like, eight years.
And I lost her.
And now, if it's possible,
I think I love you even more.
So it's hard for me
to believe I'm not gonna...
...well, that someone else isn't
gonna take you away.
Let it be me. Let it be me!
Honey, that's very sweet.
It just seems to me, though,
that if two people love each other...
...and trust each other, like we do...
...there's no reason to be jealous.
I gotta get going.
Bye, Chandler.
Okay, Ross, this pen's getting kind of
boring. Can you pick me up some porn?
Where you going?
I've gotta go pick up Ben.
We got a play-date this afternoon.
With who?
Just this woman I met
last night at the party.
There was a woman at...?
The stripper?
- Yeah.
- You have a play-date with a stripper?
Man, I gotta get a kid!
Yeah, we started talking
after she did her thing...
...and it turns out she's got a boy
about Ben's age.
So we're gonna take the kids
to a Gymboree class.
- Is that okay?
- Sure. Is she married?
No.
Are you jealous?
No, I just don't see why she has
to play with you. That's all.
I mean, doesn't she, you know, have any
other stripper-mom friends of her own?
You are totally jealous!
I'm not jealous, all right.
This is about...
...people feeling certain things...
...you know, about...
...strippers. And, you know...
I love you too.
Bye.
Wait, wait, wait!
What?
Well, there's a kiss he won't forget
for a few hours.
Either that or you just turned him on
and sent him to a stripper.
All right, I'm jealous.
I'm jealous!
"Oh, no. Chandler, please don't.
No, I beg of you to not..."
Is there a Julio here?
I am Julio.
Mr. Pretentious
You think there's no one finer
Your poems are unpublished
And you work in a diner
You're no God's gift to women
That's all in your head
- You are just a butt-munch
- No one likes a butt-munch!
And you're also bad in bed
denanet for torrents.ru