Previously on Castle...
Tell me what I don't know
about my mom's murder, Detective Raglan.
19 years ago, I... I made a bad mistake,
and that started the dominoes falling,
and one of 'em was your mom.
You woke the dragon,
and this is so much
bigger than you realize.
We gotta find that shooter.
Our shooter is Hal Lockwood.
I need to know exactly
what you know about me
and my employer.
I will be back here week after week
to ask you who hired you.
Hey, guys, I could use a hand.
Thank you. Thanks. That's very funny.
Just for that, you will not be
getting an autographed copy
of my new graphic novel.
You wrote a graphic novel?
Not technically, but it is based on
one of the greatest
characters I ever created.
You see, Wolverine,
Batman, Betty, Veronica...
Sure, they were fine for their day.
But there is a new sheriff
on the spinner rack,
and his name is...
Derrick Storm.
Advance art for "A Deadly Storm,"
the new graphic novel.
Wow.
It's pretty cool.
It's epic cool is what it is.
Where's Beckett? I want to show her this.
Making her weekly pilgrimage
out to the prison to interview Lockwood.
Oh.
Right.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Welcome back, Detective Beckett.
Officer Ryker.
Our special today is serial arsonist.
No, thank you.
Perhaps I can interest
you in an armed robber
covered in gang tats and
protesting his innocence?
Uh, you know, I think I'll
just take the usual...
Hal Lockwood.
That's an excellent choice, madam.
I'll have someone bring him down.
Thank you.
It's Ryker.
I've got a visitor for Lockwood.
Ad-seg 3-4-6-1-7.
Yeah.
What do you mean?
Lockwood's no longer in
administrative segregation.
Where is he?
He was transferred to general population
about an hour ago.
What?
He was in ad-seg for a reason.
You gotta get him outta there. Now.
Why? What's the big deal?
Lockwood! Lockwood! Lockwood!
There is a prisoner
in the general population...
Gary McCallister.
Lockwood is going to kill him
the first chance he gets.
Lockwood! Lockwood!
Lockwood! Lockwood! Lockwood!
You know, I was wondering when
he was gonna get around to me.
It's okay if you want a minute.
Move! Move! Get out of the way!
Don't make a mess of it, okay?
I never do.
Go.
How did he even get into
the general population?
Esposito's running it down now,
but I'm guessing it wasn't an accident.
I'm sorry.
For what?
Well, Lockwood kills Raglan,
then he shanks McCallister,
both of them ex-cops
who had something to do
with your mother's murder.
He's cutting off all avenues
of your investigation.
Castle, he's not cutting them off.
He's giving me new ones.
I've been going to that prison
every week for the last four months
to have a staring contest with the devil,
and the devil just blinked.
This is exactly what I've been looking for.
Hey, Department of Corrections
says the signature used on the
transfer order was forged.
And the only people with access
to those documents at the prison
are correctional officers and
authorized clerical staff.
Which means bribe or blackmail.
I want a full financial
workup of every employee
in that prison, sworn and civilian.
I want to know who was
late on their mortgage,
who was behind on their child support.
Somebody took a hell of a risk
cutting Lockwood this transfer,
and they had to have been pretty desperate.
You got it.
See? Now we got a trail.
So where are we going?
To Lockwood's arraignment.
I want to see if we can rattle his cage.
Lockwood doesn't seem
like the rattling type.
Not Lockwood. Whoever's holding his leash.
First Raglan and now McCallister.
What are you doing,
collecting the whole set?
You're a real badass, Lockwood,
shanking an old man in his bunk.
I don't know what you
think you accomplished,
but this doesn't change a thing.
You hear me?
Whoever hired you...
He can't hide from me.
No, sweetheart.
You got it ass backwards.
You can't hide from him.
Please take your seat, ma'am.
All rise.
The court's in session.
Be seated.
Matter number 27 on the list...
The people of the state of New York
vs. John Doe, A.K.A. Harold Lockwood.
The matter is on for arraignment.
Counsel, for the record and
who you represent, please.
Avery Zussman for Harold
Lockwood, your honor.
On the matter of
the people of the state of New York...
What is it?
Indictment number 2-0-1-1-4-6-0,
the charge is premeditated murder...
I don't know.
With a special circumstances allegation.
Mr. Lockwood, do you waive a formal reading
of this indictment?
I do.
They're wearing chrome collar pins.
NYPD's are brass.
And how do you plead?
Now.
Castle, down!
Are you okay?!
Yeah, yeah.
Where? Where?
Downstairs.
Come on. Keep moving.
Come on. Let's go. Go.
How's she doing?
Lockwood's in the wind.
Everything about her mom's case
just went to hell in a handbasket.
How ya think?
Where are we on Lockwood's
known associates?
Courthouse security personnel were so used
to seeing cops come and go,
nobody gave 'em a second look.
He didn't care about anybody
seeing their faces.
Did FBI run 'em through facial recognition?
No hits. Guys are ghosts.
What about the chopper?
F.A.A. says that they flew below
the 1,000-foot radar ceiling.
They had to know NYPD would have
helicopters searching for 'em,
so they'd want to ditch their chopper
as soon as they could.
We got locals on the ground
checking every small airfield
in the Tristate area.
I got nothing so far.
Hey, Beckett. We got something.
Check your in-box.
So phone calls from the
prison are recorded,
and every inmate has to make collect calls.
Apparently, Lockwood made weekly
calls to the same number,
but week after week, the
person at the end of the call
refused to accept the charges,
until four days ago.
Okay, here it is.
How's the family? Same.
How are Charlie and Mike?
Good.
Anything on the phone number?
Burner cell, untraceable.
All right, check known
associates named Charlie
or Mike.
They're not talking about people.
That's the phonetic
alphabet, military jargon.
"Charlie and Mike" means continue mission.
Well, we know the mission
wasn't McCallister.
He was just a means to escape.
They could've paid off anyone
in the general population
to kill McCallister, but it
had to be Lockwood because
they needed to get him out.
Which means Lockwood was after somebody else.
Who's left?
Me.
Lockwood could've killed you in the courtroom.
You're not a threat.
You don't know anything.
I think I know who he's after.
We know that your mom was killed
because she was working to free a mobster
who was wrongfully convicted of the murder
of an undercover federal
officer...Bob Armen.
We know that the real
killers were renegade cops
who were practicing their
own form of street justice
by kidnapping mobsters for ransom.
These guys were also working for somebody...
Somebody big, somebody
who will stop at nothing
to keep his identity a secret.
Which means there's still
one loose thread out there.
The third cop.
The man that Joe Pulgatti saw
in the alley with John Raglan
and Gary McCallister the night
that Bob Armen was killed.
Whoever this guy is, if he's still around,
he knows who's behind this whole thing.
Which makes him Lockwood's next target.
But we looked through the reports.
There's no mention of any third cop.
Just because he's not mentioned in it
doesn't mean he wasn't there.
Excuse me.
Beckett. Put a detail on her.
She's not gonna like that.
You don't have to tell her.
If Lockwood's going after this
third cop, he's still in town.
You both know what he's capable of.
If you get a chance to put
him down, do not hesitate.
That son of a bitch doesn't need
to see the inside of another courtroom.
You read me?
Loud and clear.
That was the Jersey State Police.
They found the chopper.
Yours?
Yeah.
That smell... is that, uh...
Bleach in the cabin.
They were destroying D.N.A.
Evidence.
Mechanic says
the chopper must have
been stolen and returned
before anyone knew it was missing.
He says he wouldn't even have
known anybody had used it
if it weren't for the bullet holes.
Who does the helicopter belong to?
Hedge fund manager from Upstate.
Where is he now?
Sailing in the Caribbean with his family.
All right, check his
background and the mechanic's,
and anybody else who works here.
Right.
Why now?
Lockwood was in prison for months.
Why would he make a move now?
Well, they had him transferred,
and then they broke him out of a courtroom.
That takes time, planning, resources.
What if it was something else?
What if there's another reason?
Like what?
You know, um...
I think I saw a surveillance
camera outside the building.
We pull the surveillance,
look for a vehicle, maybe get an A.P.B.
You okay?
Yeah.
Beckett's mom?
I can't imagine what it
must be like for her...
Solving murders
and bringing closure to all those families,
but never to herself.
It's easier in my books.
The just are rewarded,
the wicked are punished.
Unfortunately, real life isn't that easy.
Can I help you?
I hope so. I'm Jim Beckett, Kate's father.
I feel like I already know you, Rick.
I've heard a lot of great things about you
from Katie.
Really?
Really.
So... how's she holding up?
Well, it's kind of tough to
tell with her, you know?
She doesn't flinch.
I know. She wouldn't accept a night-light
when she was a little girl.
Not that she wasn't afraid of the dark,
but I think she just felt
it was a point of pride to,
you know, stare it down.
This... man she's chasing.
How dangerous is he?
He's a trained killer.
What happens when she finds him?
I've already lost my wife over this.
I've already lost...
Now look, i... it took me years,
but I've made my peace with that.
But Katie?
She won't listen to me
and she won't back down.
Not unless someone can convince her
that her life is worth more
than her mother's death.
Look, she cares about you, Rick.
And unless you're a lot
dumber than you look,
I know you care about her.
Don't let her throw her life away.
How'd you sleep?
I didn't.
Yeah. Me neither.
Thank you.
Listen, I was wondering...
So we ran financials on everyone
associated with the prison...
guards, civilian employees,
medical staff.
Found a guard named Ryker.
He's underwater in his mortgage,
he maxed out his credit cards,
and he was about to lose his condo.
Ryker? I know Ryker.
You only thought you knew Ryker.
The day before Lockwood
was transferred to general population,
Ryker received a $50,000 wire transfer.
And guess who didn't
show up for work today.
NYPD! NYPD!
NYPD! Do not move!
Show us your hands, Ryker!
Let's go! Let me see your hands!
Let's see those hands!
Go.
The bullet entered through
the back of the head,
exited through the front,
and landed in the cabinet.
I'm making the time of death
around 9:00 last night.
Ryker made four phone calls
to the same burner cell that
Lockwood called from prison.
He was negotiating prices.
Ryker had no idea who he was dealing with.
That was the D.O.J.
The $50,000 wire transfer
bounced through the United Arab Emirates
before it ended up in Ryker's account.
It came from the Dubai
branch of a Swiss Bank.
Who the hell are these guys?
Well, whoever they are,
they've been two steps ahead
of us this whole time.
You don't go through this kind
of trouble to cover up a couple
of rogue cops kidnapping
mobsters in some back alley.
No, this is about something
else, something bigger.
If we want to catch these sons of bitches,
we're gonna have to bring
the fight to them.
Notify Ryker's next of kin.
Let's talk to his neighbors again,
anybody else that knew him at the prison.
I want to see if he made
any new friends lately.
How long did you know
Ryker, officer Haskell?
Since he came to the prison... almost, uh,
almost ten years, I guess.
Was he having trouble with
anyone at the prison?
Ryker was stainless.
All the other corrections officers
liked him, and even the
worst cons respected him,
'cause Ryker treated them with respect.
Was there anyone new in his
life, maybe a girlfriend?
Uh, no one.
In fact, he'd been working
up the nerve for weeks
to ask you out, Detective.
Uh, did you know, uh, Ryker was
having financial problems?
No. He never said a word to me.
And I was probably closer
to him than anyone.
We're getting the same thing
from everyone we talk to.
Ryker was a stand-up guy.
None of his friends even knew
he had financial trouble.
And other than calls to that burner phone,
there's nothing in his phone records
to indicate any new contacts in his life.
We just got word on the security
footage from the airport.
Cameras did pick up a
blue late-model Malibu
leaving the area, but its
license plate was blacked out.
So basically, we've got
nothing still, right?
Just a bunch of dead ends.
Everywhere I look, it's
just a bunch of dead ends.
You know, whoever planned
this escape for Lockwood
knew they would need someone on the inside.
If Ryker was such a straight arrow,
why would they approach him?
He was a soft target because
of his financial troubles.
How would they know that?
They found him the same way we did...
financial records.
They ran financials on
everybody in that prison.
Who would have that kind of authority?
A cop or someone who was a cop.
So this third cop wasn't Lockwood's target.
This third cop was the one who
was holding Lockwood's leash.
He's the one who's behind this whole thing.
Okay, I want us to pull reports
with Raglan and McCallister's name on it.
We did all that already.
Months ago. There's nothing.
No, no, no, I'm not talking
about arrest reports.
I'm talking about performance
evaluations...
We went through everything.
We looked at every cop we could find
who could've worked with them.
None of 'em are our third guy.
Well, then check it again.
And when you're done with
that, check it again.
Beckett, we want him as bad as you.
The hell you do.
Nobody wants him as bad as I do, okay?
Nobody. So check it again.
Find anything?
Hell, I bet there wasn't even a third cop.
I mean, seriously, Dubai,
paramilitary extraction...
How does a cop even begin to
mount an operation like this?
These guys were kidnapping
mobsters for months,
maybe even years before
things went sideways.
They could've made millions in ransom.
That would mean this third cop
would have plenty of cash
to hire professionals like
Dick Coonan and Hal Lockwood
to clean up his mess.
Keep checking.
Sir.
Uh... I know we're still
officially on duty, but...
Authorized.
It's lunch.
Nice work.
Ooh, those are cold. Yeah.
Those are really cold.
Yeah, we keep 'em in evidence...
refrigerated storage.
Isn't that where you keep the...
Don't worry about it.
How is she?
She hasn't returned my calls.
She just grabbed those case
files and ran outta here.
She's getting lost.
She's an inch away from the rabbit hole.
She'll be fine. She always is.
What if we come up empty?
Who's Napolitano?
Oh, he worked with Raglan on a
couple of drug busts,
but he was at his daughter's wedding
the night Bob Armen was shot,
so he's not our third cop.
Where is he now?
He died of heart failure back in 1993.
Why are you asking about Napolitano?
Uh, he and Raglan are listed
as the arresting officers on this report,
but this has been altered.
What? How can you tell?
Because I know typewriters.
Older typewriters use cloth ribbon.
If you look closely, you can see
the striations in the typeface.
Newer typewriters used film ribbon.
Somebody whited out...
The assisting officer's
name on this report,
photocopied it, and then
typed in Napolitano's name.
It's a cover-up, literally.
I'll be damned.
What are you doing?
Well, documents have a way of
disappearing in this case.
This way, we all have it.
Let's show cap.
Son of a bitch went through
a lot of trouble to cover his tracks.
We found two other reports where
Napolitano's name was added on.
We figure whoever did them
had to have done so after Armen's murder.
But before we went digital.
That's over ten years.
You're talking about
thousands of officers walking in
and out of the records room.
Yeah, but whoever took
their name off those
reports would've had to go
physically get them from the records room.
Find out who was Manning
the records desk during that time.
- Maybe that someone remembers
looking the other way. - Right.
What?
Continue mission?
If Lockwood isn't going
after the third cop,
then who's the mission?
I put a protective detail
on her...plainclothes.
These guys are good.
Good enough to stop Lockwood?
Look, she's not gonna stop, and
the next time he sees her,
one of them is gonna die.
Take her off the case.
Castle, did Beckett ever
tell you how we met?
No.
I was working late one night
and went down to archives
to locate some old reports.
And there she was, with a flashlight
and a bankers box open on her lap,
studying this unsolved.
She was a patrol cop then.
She wasn't even authorized
to be down there.
When I asked her what
the hell she was doing,
she told me, this was her mother's case
and she'd found some
things that didn't add up.
Now I could've written her up right then.
Why didn't you?
Because I knew it wouldn't stop her.
It was there in her eyes,
man, and I thought...
With this kid's tenacity and some training,
I mean, she'd make a hell of a homicide.
That tenacity is gonna get her killed.
I cannot...
Make Beckett stand down, Castle.
I never could,
and the way I figure,
the only one who can...
is you.
Can I come in?
Yeah.
So we went over
all of Raglan and McCallister's
old arrest records,
and you were right.
There was a third cop that was with them
on a lot of those arrests.
But then someone went
back into those reports
and removed their name, so Ryan
and Esposito are right now
looking into who was running
the records room back then.
Castle, you couldn't have just called me
and told me this over the phone?
Well, yeah, I... I thought that...
Castle, if you got something
to say, just please say it.
Beckett, everyone associated
with this case is dead.
Everyone.
First your mom and her colleagues,
then Raglan, then McCallister.
You know they're coming for you next.
Captain Montgomery's got a
protective detail on me.
It wasn't that hard to spot.
That's not gonna be enough
to stop Lockwood. You know that.
Think about what they're up against...
Professional killers?
I-I've been working with you
for three years. You know me.
I am the guy who says we can
move that rubber tree plant.
But you know what, Beckett?
I don't think we're gonna win this.
Castle, they killed my mother.
What do you want me to do here?
Walk away.
They're gonna kill you, Kate.
And if you don't care about that...
At least think about how
that's gonna affect
the people that love you.
You really want to put
your dad through that?
And what about Josh?
And what about you, Rick?
Well, of course I don't want
anything to happen to you.
I'm your partner. I'm your friend.
Is that what we are?
Oh, you know what?
I don't know what we are.
We kiss and then we never talk about it.
We nearly die frozen in each other's arms,
but we never talk about it,
so no, I got no clue what we are.
I know I don't want to see
you throw your life away.
Yeah, well, last time I
checked, it was my life,
not your personal jungle gym.
And for the past three years,
I have been running around with
the school's funniest kid.
And it's not funny enough.
You know what? This isn't about
your mother's case anymore.
This is about you needing a place to hide,
because you've been chasing
this thing so long,
you're afraid to find out who
you are without it.
You don't know me, Castle.
You think you do, but you don't.
I know you crawled inside
your mother's murder
and didn't come out.
I know you hide there
the same way you hide in
these nowhere relationships
with men you don't love.
You could be happy, Kate.
You deserve to be happy.
But you're afraid.
You know what we are, Castle?
We are over.
Now get out.
Oh, my God! What the hell's going on here?
Nothing. I'm sorry. Go back to bed.
There's only one person on the planet
that can get you this pissed off.
She's going to get herself killed.
She's a grown woman.
She's a homicide detective, for God sakes.
It's her job. It's her life.
If anything happens to her...
Go on.
Oh, Richard, Richard.
For a man who makes his living with words,
you sure have a hell of a time
finding them when it counts.
Darling...
Let me give you a word
of advice, all right,
from someone who's better than
halfway through the movie.
Don't waste another minute of it.
Roy, I am over it. I mean it.
I want him gone.
Okay. He's gone.
What?
You want Castle gone?
He's gone.
W...I...what... what about the Mayor?
This is my house, Kate.
The Mayor doesn't call
the shots here. I do.
You ought to know that by now.
But I-I th... I could've kicked
Castle to the curb years ago...
Anytime I wanted to.
Only reason I kept him around this long
was because I saw how good he was for you.
Kate...
You're the best that I've ever trained,
maybe the best I've ever seen.
But you weren't having any
fun before he came along.
We speak for the dead.
That's the job.
We are all they've got
once the wicked rob them of their voices.
We owe them that.
But we don't owe 'em our lives.
He said that we can't win this.
He's right.
I've spent most of my life
walking behind this badge,
and I can tell you this for a fact...
There are no victories.
There's only the battle.
And the best that you could hope for
is that you find someplace
where you can make your stand.
If this is your spot...
I will stand with you.
I really don't think a
badge is behind all this.
No one on the job has this kind of juice.
If he worked with McCallister and Raglan,
he's probably long retired by now.
I mean, he could be in private
security, politics, business.
Man, I can't believe I
gotta call these guys.
You know how pension guys love to talk.
I bet I'm gonna be on the phone for hours
listening to stories about the glory days.
Hey, listen to this...
Mike Yanavich, sergeant,
assigned to the records
room from '02 to '05.
It says he ran it right
up until he retired,
and Yanavich graduated from the academy
in the same class as Gary McCallister
and John Raglan.
Well, maybe he's our third cop. Where is he?
Looks like Yanavich relocated to
Miami Beach after he retired.
Contact Miami-Dade P.D. in the morning.
See if they can verify his address.
We'll fly down to Miami
to get him if we have to.
Hello, Roy.
You're not that fast.
Besides, they're all upstairs asleep,
safe and sound.
And they're not on tonight's menu.
But if you wake 'em up, well,
then I gotta order off the menu.
What do you want?
He's very disappointed, Roy.
We all are.
I mean, d-did you not understand
the conditions of the agreement?
Beckett stays alive as long
as you keep her on a leash.
That's the deal that you made with him.
But you're not holding up your end.
And that's unfortunate,
because she really is a lovely girl.
But now we've reached a... critical stage,
and I have to cap the well.
So here's the news...
Tomorrow night, you're gonna
call off that protective detail
that you have on her,
and then you're gonna get her
to meet you at the hangar
where we stashed the bird.
I don't care how you do it,
just get her there,
and we'll handle the rest.
Go to hell.
Well, then you have a decision to make.
You can have Beckett...
Or you can have your family.
But you can't have both.
Look at it this way...
If you and Raglan and McCallister
hadn't sinned so spectacularly,
then God wouldn't have
sent a punishment like me.
We're gonna be late.
Come on.
Where are my girls?
Come and give your old man a kiss.
Mwah. Look at you.
Hey, get off that phone and give me a kiss.
You know, I'm so proud of both of you.
Dad.
Come on. In the car, you two.
Come on. Let's go.
Bye, dad.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
What's that for?
I love you.
I know.
That was Miami-Dade.
Apparently Yanavich didn't care
too much for the sun and sand.
He was only there for a
year, and then he moved
back to Brooklyn, bought
that cop bar out on Fulton.
How does Yanavich afford a
bar on a cop's pension?
Why don't we ask him?
We better handle this, bro.
Let's see what we got before
we bring her in on this.
Sir.
Beckett, I think we have a lead.
What'd you find?
Meet me at the hangar where
we found the stolen chopper,
and I'll explain everything there.
Okay. I'm on my way.
...Maybe in the Hall of Fame, who knows?
Mike Yanavich?
That's me.
Detective Esposito, and
this is Detective Ryan.
Can we talk to you for a minute?
Sure. Want a drink?
You own this place?
Free and clear.
How do you manage that on a cop's pension
if you don't mind me asking?
You get shot on the job,
start drawing a disability
pension after you retire.
You worked the records
room at the 12th, right?
Decade ago. So what?
Some records went missing on your watch,
and some got altered.
Yeah, well, I don't doubt it.
I mean, uh, it wasn't like it is today.
We didn't make a federal case
out of everything back then.
You graduated from the Police Academy
with John Raglan and Gary McCallister.
Mm-hmm, and 40 other guys.
Listen, I read the papers.
I know Raglan and McCallister road dirty,
but I didn't have any part of it.
I mean, I knew 'em to say
hi, talk some baseball,
maybe bitch about the A.C.L.U.
They used to drink here
before I bought the place.
Do you know if Raglan or McCallister
were tight with anybody else?
Yeah. Some black kid used to
follow 'em around, a rookie.
I got a picture of 'em somewhere up here.
Yeah. That's him.
The hell was his name?
Ah. Montgomery.
Yeah, McCallister and
Raglan trained that kid.
Montgomery said he didn't
know either of these guys.
Hey! What the hell's the matter with you?
Hey!
You know it's him.
Montgomery's our third cop.
He's the one who altered those records.
How can you even say that?
How could you even think that?!
Montgomery brought us in to Homicide.
What do we got, a picture?!
Think about it.
Why else did he want us
to take Lockwood out?
Because Lockwood leads us to him.
He's been lying to us.
He's been lying to us the whole time.
No.
Hey! Get off me!
Ah.
Aah!
Go ahead! Go ahead!
Beckett.
Captain?
Over here.
Put the gun away, Roy.
Kate, I'm not going to jail for this.
I can't put my family through that.
Why?
I was a rookie when it happened, Kate.
McCallister and Raglan were heroes to me.
I believed in what we were doing.
We were just gonna snatch
Pulgatti that night.
Bob Armen wasn't even supposed to be there.
Armen reached for my gun.
That's when I heard the shot.
I didn't even know it was
my gun that went off
until Armen went down.
Then McCallister pulled me into the van.
I remember him saying,
"It's okay, kid. It's not your fault.
Happens in this town every day."
McCallister and Raglan tried to drown it,
but not me.
I put it all into the job, Kate.
I became the best cop I could be.
And then when you walked into the 12th...
I felt the hand of God.
I knew he was giving me another chance,
and I thought,
if I could protect you the way
I should've protected her...
Did you kill my mother?
No, that was years later,
but she died because of
what we did that night.
Then who killed her?
I don't know how,
but somehow, he figured
out what we had done,
and he could've turned us all in.
Instead, he demanded the ransom money.
He took that money to become what he is,
and God forgive me, but that
may be my greatest sin.
Give me a name.
You owe me that, Roy.
No, Kate.
I give you a name, I know you.
You'll run straight at him.
I might as well shoot you where you stand.
That's why you brought me
here, isn't it, to kill me?
No, I brought you here to lure them.
You baited them?
And now they're coming.
I need you to leave.
They are coming to kill you,
and I'm not gonna let 'em.
I'm gonna end this.
I'm not going anywhere, sir.
Yes, you are.
Castle, get her outta here.
Captain, I...
Don't argue. That's why I called you.
Get her outta here. Now.
Captain, please.
Just listen to me.
You don't have to do this.
Kate... no, please.
No, sir...I forgive you.
I forgive you.
This is my spot, Kate.
This is where I stand.
No.
Castle.
No, no, sir, please,
listen to me. You don't have to do this.
Castle, get her outta here now!
You don't have to...
Sir, please.
Kate. Kate.
No.
God, Castle, let me go!
No!
Let me go. Please!
Please. Please.
Shh. Shh. Oh...
Shh. Shh. I'm sorry. Shh. Shh.
Where is she, Roy?
You can't have her.
I told you, it's her or your family.
Don't be stupid.
You can't hide her from us,
from me.
You got that ass backwards, boy.
You can't hide from me.
Oh!
And that was what, your last stand?
That's just sad, Roy.
I'm just gonna kill her anyway.
No...
You're not...
And he's not.
I saw to that.
You're done, Lockwood.
We both are.
No one...
No one outside of this immediate family
ever needs to know about this.
As far as the world is concerned,
Roy Montgomery died a hero.
We owe it to him...
All of us.
Roy Montgomery taught me
what it meant to be a cop
he taught me that we are
found by our choices
that we are more than mistakes
Captain Montgomery once said to me
that for us, there is no victory.
There are only battles.
And in the end, the best you can hope for
is to find a place to make your stand.
And if you're very lucky...
You find someone willing to stand with you.
Our captain would want us
to carry on the fight.
And even if there is no victory,
he would want us to stand together.
Kate!
Down! Everybody, down!
Where'd the shot come from?
Lanie, get down!
No, no, no, Kate.
Find that shooter!
Shh.
Kate, please.
Stay with me, Kate.
Don't leave me. Please.
Stay with me, okay?
Kate...
I love you.
I love you, Kate.
Sync by YYeTs.net
Corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com