(Tale of The Nine Tailed)
(The List)
(Name: Nam Ji A, Date of Birth: March 3, 1991)
(Date of Death: Today)
(Chapter 14: Dead End)
Yeon.
Yes, it's me.
I'm sorry.
As I was entering the room,
I could feel myself losing control of my body.
It's all right. You did good.
I can still feel...
how it swarmed inside my head.
Let's hurry.
At least so I can be myself...
right before it all ends.
I want to be there beside you.
Let's end this.
Let's put an end...
to this exhausting fight.
Are you okay?
Drive.
Why?
- Why are you doing this? - What?
Is it fun to bring chaos to the world?
Is that what motivates you?
No.
Truth be told, I actually prefer reading books.
Then why are you doing this?
Because I want Lee Yeon dead.
And you think he'll easily cave in?
That's why I'm doing this.
He won't stop his fight against me.
He keeps trying to defy destiny.
There's no turning back now.
We've both crossed the line, you see.
Mr. Lee!
Did you get hurt?
Not really.
Well, you're about to.
How dare you fool me.
- This was the only way. - Shut it.
It was pretty obvious...
when he gathered us all for the meeting.
As if you knew.
He wouldn't have blabbed about the Sin Slayer...
had he found the real one.
He would've bulldozed over and slayed her.
What?
I'm saying that he's a man of action,
not words.
So were you able to get your answer?
I guess.
And what would that be?
- A key. - A key to what?
The one Imoogi needs to jump from body to body.
Do we have a way to drag it out of Ms. Nam then?
I can't be satisfied with that.
What?
My plan is to keep it buried forever...
so that it never resurfaces.
Stop right there.
You heard me!
The moment you step past those doors,
you'll lose everything.
I'll make sure of it!
And what is it do I have to lose?
The Gatekeeper of Samdo River,
powers that nearly match an Almighty,
and an immortal life. I gave you all of that!
What I want though aren't those.
It's my wife and son.
Honey, but living with you forever now...
is my biggest punishment of all.
Stop right there.
I told you to stop!
("Unveiling Urban Legends")
- Mr. Choi. - What?
Did anything happen in our absence?
Are you all right?
What did Mr. Choi say?
A police officer passed away.
- Cause of death? - He says it was a heart attack,
but Mr. Choi noticed odd spots on his body while performing CPR.
Also, he spit out an egg.
An egg?
Are they still with your boss?
Where are you right now?
So much for peace and quiet in my latter years.
Never did I think I'd see a man...
- die before my eyes. - Mr. Choi...
Guys, get away from him right now.
Got it.
Mr. Choi was at the police station?
Yes, he performed CPR on the victim.
Nothing happened though, right?
Not yet, it hasn't.
Check this out.
("Victims Covered in Spots Found Mysteriously Dead in City")
There's a rapid increase in the number of victim's dying.
I need to get going.
Where are you headed?
Head home first.
Don't go there alone and let them take you.
You must hurry, Yeon.
My wife will soon alter Ji A's date of death on the list.
What's wrong?
It's just like he warned me.
What do you mean?
He told me he'll spread a virus...
and kill everyone that's precious to me.
Wait. My parents.
I'll go check up on them. You should go and wait for Mr. Lee.
- But... - Don't worry.
Mr. Lee Rang, please take her home.
Ask me politely to take you home.
I'd rather die than do that.
Then just die.
I won't be there to help you when Imoogi comes for you.
To me, you're no different from him.
Doesn't that apply to you?
You're the female Imoogi.
- Let's just go our own ways. - As you wish.
She's so stubborn.
I really don't get what Yeon likes about her.
What? What's wrong with this?
Wait. You dropped...
Mr. Hyeonuiong?
Fortunately,
I got here on time.
Are you sure you didn't get hurt?
I'm okay.
The gatekeeper of Samdo River is involved in this?
Thank goodness.
It looks like something big is about to happen soon.
- Granny. - Choose your words wisely.
I'm in a very bad mood just as much as you are.
You messed with the list?
You turned your back on me...
and did something you won't even be able to forgive yourself for?
You really chose to do that?
No matter what you say, I won't withdraw what I wrote.
That is...
my choice.
Why not just kill the guy who spread the plague? Why Ji A?
You already know you can't kill him with a sword.
I see the blade won't kill you.
The problem is what lives inside the girl's body.
We need to destroy that in order to destroy the other one.
And to do that,
she needs to die.
I'm only going to say this once.
Return things...
back to how they were.
This is how it should be.
That's the only way it'll end.
No.
I won't let anyone...
take Ji A away.
And that includes you.
It's out of your hands now.
Go ahead.
Are you saying accidents like earlier...
will keep happening until I die?
I'm glad I got to see my parents one last time.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
You saved my life.
I tried my best to stop this.
But this is all I can do.
What about Yeon?
He went to settle things with my wife.
- Will he be okay? - I don't know.
Once my wife is convinced that she is right,
she never changes her mind.
And Yeon knows that.
Then could he get hurt...
because of me?
He's probably willing to risk everything he has right now.
You can use this to take my life.
Just give me three more days.
If I don't catch him within three days,
then just kill me with this.
I can't do that.
He's already out of control.
- I have his scale. - It's too late.
I can catch him! I can catch Imoogi!
How many more lives do you think he'll take within those three days?
Their lives are just as important as the life you wish to save.
Please don't do this.
Please don't kill Ji A.
I'll do anything.
- I'll do anything you ask. - Just fight me instead.
Cut the nonsense and just fight me like you'd normally do.
Please.
Get up.
I wouldn't have started this if I was going to change my mind.
How could you do this to me?
I've already lost my child and husband, so I can do much worse.
Even if that means I'll end up losing you.
You'll regret this,
Granny.
Where did it all go wrong?
If it weren't for me, Yeon would still be...
living as a mountain spirit.
No.
I never should've been born.
Listen. It's not your fault.
Don't hate yourself...
and deny the connection you have with him.
I feel like it's all my fault.
We may be immortal, but we're just like humans.
Our happy and precious memories are what keeps us going.
For me, it's the memory of my son.
For the Snail Bride, it's the memory of her sweet husband.
And Yeon managed to keep living thanks to you.
Imoogi told me...
that I'll eventually end up killing Yeon...
with my own two hands.
That's why...
both you and Yeon are trying so hard...
to protect each other.
I'm surrounded by dead ends.
Darn it. It won't light.
I thought you were quitting.
I've tried all sorts of things to quit.
I chewed on mints, stuck on patches, tried gums,
and even prescription medicine.
I tried all of that, but I still couldn't quit.
What are you talking about?
What if, no matter how hard you try,
the ending will stay the same?
If only one of you can survive, either you or the girl.
The ending...
won't change. I see.
Want me to blow on it?
- Are you kidding me? - Or do you want my car?
Why do I bother?
And hey, kid. Do something about your runny nose when you're with me.
I have a weak stomach.
How long have you been wearing that? Did you even wash it?
Buy some clothes at a department store.
I'm very sensitive regarding hygiene.
I'm going to the bathroom.
What are all these stickers?
You're dead when I come out!
What a nice day.
It's gorgeous out.
Your coffee.
This tree grew a lot.
It did. It grew nicely.
What are you thinking about?
Where were we...
while this much time passed?
Right? They say we were missing for years.
It feels strange, doesn't it?
All I know is that we were asleep the whole time.
It's odd that we don't have any pressure ulcers on our bodies.
And it's odd how nervous Ji A is too.
It reminds me of "Io Island".
"Io Island"?
You know, a fisherman accidentally ends up on a fantasy island,
and when he leaves, he realizes 100 years had passed.
Ji A grew really well, just like that tree,
so I'm grateful.
Is this all we're eating?
It's good.
I want naengmyeon.
Yu Ri.
When is she coming?
I'm wondering...
when would be good.
Why are you only thinking?
Because once I finish thinking,
Yeon will lose something.
It has been over 600 years.
I plan to end this fight once and for all.
What if you fail?
Rang.
That's why I need you.
If by chance something happens to me,
I'd like you to finish this yourself.
I'd like you to be my final weapon.
I refuse.
Whether Imoogi destroys the world...
or kills your woman, I don't care.
We want to protect different things.
- Rang. - You protect her.
I'll free Yu Ri...
and save you.
Why are you smiling?
I feel like being a good boy really isn't my thing.
Later.
Watch the apartment, Geomdoong.
Why am I Geomdoong?
Shi Young.
Oh, my. Hello.
What brings you here at this hour?
Well... I wanted to have a bowl of samgyetang.
But... You're not sick or anything, right?
Of course, not.
I do 200 squats a day.
Do you want to see?
Goodness.
- Have a seat. - Okay.
Serve him.
Seven cops were taken to the hospital this morning.
What about Mr. Choi?
You saw him. He was fine.
I told him to see a doctor anyway, but he won't listen.
If he's okay, we should be okay too, right?
Let's worry about editing. Walk faster.
You must be busy prepping for the day.
I felt a weird taste in my mouth. I feel so much better now.
What's wrong?
You don't look well.
Do I have a fever?
Not at all. You're so cold.
Give me your hand. Your hand's cold too.
How could your body temperature drop this much?
It's a snake egg.
He's sleeping again. Wake up.
Excuse me. Wake up.
Sir?
What happened?
He... He's dead.
Hey. Call an ambulance. I'll go get help.
What?
They died?
Everyone on our floor?
Hold on.
Breaking news. People are dying from unknown causes...
in masses.
The first of such deaths occurred only two days ago.
It is presumed to be a highly lethal,
highly contagious disease.
All of the victims had red spots...
all over their bodies.
According to the autopsy report of the first victim,
his organs showed signs of fatal injuries...
as if attacked by a wild animal.
Kim, a man in his 30s,
had no underlying illness...
- How is it? - It's lame.
It's not my style.
So it's normal.
Where are you going now?
I want to get some free tea.
I'll grant you a visit to commemorate.
- A visit? - With your boyfriend.
Go see him.
Yu... Yu Ri. Are you okay?
Let's meet up right now.
Right now?
Where?
I'll come to you.
Come out.
I know you're hiding inside of me.
Come out!
Show yourself by the count of three, or...
I'll kill myself.
One, two,
three.
Crazy wench.
You dare to summon me when you're merely a shell?
A shell?
That's rich coming from a squatter...
who's staying rent-free.
Well, your body will completely be mine soon.
I'll give it a day or so.
Soon, I'll be in full control of your body.
That's slower than I thought.
Why?
It's been a while since I lost the fox bead.
Call it the aftermath.
I've been bound by it for too long.
Anyway, say your goodbyes when you can.
Once I take control of your body,
you'll be the one who falls asleep in it...
forever.
In other words, you're not in a stable state...
until that happens.
Darn. What can you possibly do about it though?
What if I die before you take control?
You'll never be able to.
You see,
people can do just about anything to save those they love...
like going absolutely crazy.
Help!
- What's wrong with him? - Sir!
Please help. What's happening?
My gosh.
Somebody help. Call an ambulance!
Can anybody help me?
You psycho.
That'll be all.
You can go back to sleep now.
That's all I wanted to confirm.
Listen, you woman. Lee Yeon will perish because of you.
For he won't be able to give up on you.
Rather than worrying about my love life,
I advise you to worry more about your partner.
Being rejected must've hit him hard...
because he's planning to take us both with him to the Underworld.
That's absurd.
My date of death has been altered.
Do you really believe he had no idea...
that Taluipa would go to such lengths...
to stop him from slaughtering innocent lives?
Are you in here?
Yes, I'll be right out.
Yu Ri!
Are you hurt? Let me see.
I'm fine.
I'm glad.
I was worried sick about you.
How are you here though? Did you manage to escape?
Why didn't you tell me that Imoogi was behind this?
- And Mr. Lee? - He's alive and well.
He never expresses it, but he's worried sick about you too.
I'm glad.
Let's go. He'll be thrilled to know...
- that you're back... - I can't.
What?
I can't go.
I can't and you can't either.
What are you talking about?
I'm keeping you here so that you can't go.
What on earth...
No.
Let me go.
I said we both can't go.
I'll grant you a visit to commemorate.
With your boyfriend. Go see him.
Why must I do as you say?
Because if I lay my eyes on Shin Ju today,
he'll die.
- Hey, Dad. - My daughter.
- Where are you? - Out, of course.
- Why do you ask? - A friend of yours came by.
A friend? Who?
I told you not to open the door for anyone.
Well, it was a face we recognized.
Who can you possibly know?
- Yeon? - No.
That young man with a fair complexion.
The carnation.
What?
I told you that I won't be as nice to you anymore.
You'll pay if you lay a finger on them...
Don't defy your destiny.
I can shatter everything you cherish.
Who are you? You're not Ji A's friend, are you?
No, Mom. Don't!
"I wish to hang myself."
No!
You can't leave.
No, I must go.
My mom and dad are in danger. Please...
Oh, no.
Sleep.
How did you know I was here?
I'm coming back from Samdo River.
The old lady with the Clairvoyance?
She changed the date of Ji A's death...
thanks to you spreading the plague.
But she's still alive.
I just talked to her on the phone.
Hyeonuiong's protecting her in my absence.
Although, I doubt he'll be able to last.
You said you're coming from Samdo River.
Why didn't you beg the old lady for mercy?
That I already did.
So it didn't work.
If Ji A dies, the other half of you will perish too.
So?
What is it that you truly want?
Take a guess.
You exist to lack love.
Even as a human and even now.
The Almighty created a being...
that gets the short straw on everything.
That's you, Imoogi.
Is a war what you want?
No, the opposite, actually.
- What? - What if there was something...
other than your obsession with me and Ji A...
that can satisfy you?
What if you were given a chance to obtain a position not allowed...
to even lower-class mountain spirit?
Enough with the cryptic talk.
The highest of all spirits.
No way.
The gatekeeper of Samdo River.
Let's join hands and kill the gatekeeper of Samdo River.
How interesting. This is quite unexpected.
I had no idea you'd think of betraying that old woman.
I'll do anything to save Ji A.
So...
you're going to hold hands with me?
Of course. Even if that means I need to get my hands dirty with you.
And what's the condition?
Let Ji A go.
Get rid of your other half from her body once and for all.
And don't ever look for us again.
That's all I want.
If you were in my shoes, would you not think that it could be a trap?
No, I wouldn't.
What?
Then try and guess...
what my answer is going to be.
You'd probably love to say no.
But you'll eventually accept my offer.
Where does that confidence come from?
Because we're both at a dead end.
If you reject my offer, you'll lose your other half.
And I'll lose Ji A.
In the end, we'll fight like crazy and end up in the Underworld.
That's what I've been waiting for after I had my last date with her.
Let me know if you change your mind.
You have until the sun rises tomorrow morning.
You knew Imoogi went there to kill them,
but you still kept me here? Why?
Did he threaten you?
Or is he manipulating you just like how he made you stab Mr. Lee Rang?
- It's neither. - Then why?
Why did you do that?
Who cares what happens to those useless humans?
"Useless humans"?
I thought you came to see me.
I was worried about you like crazy!
But...
you just used me as bait.
You used my feelings for you.
- Shin Ju. - Stop.
If you say one more word,
I might actually regret liking you, Yu Ri.
I bet you were really worried. They're both okay.
I erased their memories.
Your parents won't remember meeting Imoogi.
Thank you, Yeon.
It's my fault. I shouldn't have left them alone.
It wasn't your fault.
I know you're always there to protect them.
Thank you for saving Ji A while I was gone.
What's your plan?
I'm going to join hands with Imoogi.
- What? - What do you mean?
Is it because of my wife?
Yes.
I guess my wife...
decided to give up on you.
She gave me a chance to fight one more time.
Be more specific.
I got myself two more days.
And you'll be fine.
Does that mean I'll be...
Yes, of course. I won't let you die.
Not on my watch.
Then what about joining hands with Imoogi?
It's obviously a trap.
I knew it.
What did my wife ask in return?
Nothing. She just asked me to catch him no matter what.
- Yeon. - Next time.
I'll tell you the details next time.
I want to go eat with Ji A.
I'll go get changed.
What if, no matter how hard you try,
the ending will stay the same?
If only one of you can survive, either you or the girl.
The ending...
won't change. I see.
Then there's nothing more to worry about.
What do you plan to do?
I'll eat this.
I'll have the Imoogi inside Ji A enter my body instead.
And along with the other half, I'll jump...
into Samdo River.
So that he won't ever be able to resurrect again.
- If you jump into Samdo River... - Yes, I know.
I'll never get a chance to be reborn again.
I also know...
that I won't ever be able to go back to Ji A.
I'm sorry for troubling you.
You could've taken me to a hospital.
It's useless to go there.
This isn't a normal kind of illness, you see.
It's cold.
Hang in there.
This nasty fight...
will soon end.
Make sure you hang in there until then.
I guess I was right. You're not...
an ordinary woman, are you?
My goodness, Hyeonuiong.
I was wondering why you weren't at the restaurant.
I'm sorry...
My goodness.
Come see me outside.
Do you even know who he is?
What are you talking about?
He's your husband.
- What? - He's the husband...
from your past life, the man you missed so dearly.
Is anyone there? Hey!
Someone's dying in here!
Darn it!
Are you okay? You have spots all over your body.
Detective, please take me to a hospital.
It'll be useless.
The fatality rate is 100 percent.
The only difference is how long it takes.
How did this happen?
Since when did a police officer wear shoes...
that are spotless like that?
Darn it. Their stupid dress code.
Who sent you?
Yeon? Or...
Why does that matter now? You're dying anyway.
I'm sure you didn't come to watch me die.
I love watching death.
See? I even brought popcorn.
I go to funeral homes on purpose too.
What do you want? Tell me.
How dare you try to make a deal? You're terminal anyway.
Are you still reminiscing about being powerful through Imoogi?
If Imoogi dies, this disease will disappear too, right?
Probably.
Get me out of here.
- Why? - I've served Imoogi...
for much longer than you think.
No one knows as much about him as I do.
So? You'll earn your freedom purely by flapping your gums?
And fix your disease for free?
I don't like that.
I stink at fighting.
I hate getting scars.
I get it.
So that's why you're here. To keep your hands clean.
(Holding Cell 2)
He got away.
Who did?
The serial killer suspect.
Who let him out?
Well... From what I saw in the surveillance video...
What? Why won't you finish talking?
It was you, Detective Baek.
What?
(Gopbuni's Tripe)
I'll take your order.
We'll take an assortment combo and a bottle of soju.
- Extra cheese, please. - Okay.
(Gopbuni's Tripe)
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
There's so much cheese.
- What? - You're so pretty.
Promise me.
What?
Let's come back here during the first snowfall.
Okay.
Spend Christmas with me.
We'll go back to that beach we went to.
- Okay. - And on New Year's Day,
come over and have tteokguk with my parents.
And on my birthday...
What do you want?
Okay, I'll get it for you.
What must you do in order to keep all of these promises?
I have to live a long life.
Cheers.
What is this? It feels like I asked for it.
You should've told me it was your birthday.
Who celebrates their lunar birthday these days?
Only the moms remember.
It smells nice.
I live alone in my apartment...
with two tropical fish.
Do they have names?
Dukbae and Choonsam.
They're both Kims.
I promised to buy them a large aquarium with this paycheck.
Will you adopt them?
Here. Make a wish.
Please let me get a cake from Jae Hwan next year on my birthday.
That's the last of it.
This may be the last soju we ever drink...
together.
I'm going to savor it.
Why would you say that?
The thing inside of me said earlier...
that I have at most two days.
That afterward, I'll be nothing...
but an empty shell.
That won't happen.
Won't it all be better if I disappear?
If I die, Imoogi will disappear.
Then everyone I love, my family, my friends,
and you...
won't get hurt.
Don't think that ever again.
But then again,
how will you live,
left all alone, if that happens?
Then...
I'd blame myself for a very long time...
for failing to protect you again.
I'd feel the same way.
I don't think I can live a proper life without you anymore.
So, we must protect each other.
Let's not give Imoogi what he wants.
Hi, Jae Hwan.
What?
I told you not to come.
Why did you come?
Why are you here like this?
Why?
Don't touch me. You'll catch it.
Let's never meet again. We don't like each other anyway.
Who knew my last moment with you would end this way?
I know. You should've died by my hands.
Given what it is, do your best to survive.
It looked like you finally made up with your brother.
Can you handle the consequences?
No. Yeon won't forgive me.
I may never see him again.
But it's better than him dying.
Give it a rest.
Melodramatic ones like you never meet a pretty end.
The ground cherries are gone now.
All I have left is this one human life.
Don't jinx me.
I'm going to spend everything I have before I die.
Bye.
You protect her.
I'll free Yu Ri and save you.
How could I not have recognized him?
You have no idea...
how harsh I've been to him.
And you missing him dearly...
must've led him here.
But where does that get me?
I finally found him but look at what's happening.
Unbelievable.
Is this all a coincidence though?
Sorry?
Every fate entwined...
with Yeon and Ji A's...
is gathering in one place.
The lover of his past life, her family, their friends,
and their enemy.
I'm scared.
I'm worried that...
an event too devastating to bear is coming our way.
You'll stay here with me for the time being.
Get him to leave.
You shouldn't be here. It's too dangerous.
I would be sick by now if it were contagious.
Or maybe I'm just in the pre-symptomatic stage.
Will you just listen?
There's no chance I'm leaving. I'll be here instead.
You need someone to care for you.
I'm going outside to talk.
Look after her for me.
What about Mr. Choi?
He threw up an egg but still hasn't gotten any better.
What on earth is that egg?
It holds a baby snake.
Apparently, it eats people from within.
I can't watch her die like this.
Never.
It'll all be over soon.
Once he takes the bait,
I'll...
So until then,
stay patient for me.
Let's join hands and kill the gatekeeper of Samdo River.
Let me know if you change your mind.
You have until the sun rises tomorrow morning.
Take one more bite for me.
I'm doomed.
Sae Rom.
- Sae Rom? - Sae Rom!
Oh, no...
I'm in. Together, we'll attack...
the gatekeeper of Samdo River.
Yeon and Imoogi?
You're joking, right?
This can't be.
Sorry?
This is a suicide mission.
Yeon's going to kill Imoogi and sacrifice his own life too.
Yeon, you'll end up being caught...
in the trap you set up yourself.
And just like this, we will step on the same stage.
A stage where one can never step down from...
until the other dies.
What are you doing here?
You must die for me to live.
I'll end this all myself.
Don't do this. If you do...
Farewell.
The forecast never mentioned any rain.
When did you get here?
As soon as it started to rain which no one expected.
Are you here to walk me home?
It's best not to walk in the rain.
What about work? Did you finish your daily task?
I only needed to edit a few frames which I did at the speed of light.
Who's this jerk that kept you from reuniting with your family?
- Mr. Choi! - And me.
- What? - I didn't bring my car today.
So it seems. Did you walk here?
It's only a 20-minute walk to your house.
Now that your parents are here, we'll have less time to go out.
Buy me ramyeon and I'll let you go free.
Fine.
One doesn't seem like enough.
It isn't. It really isn't!
I said we should buy two.
Two things make ramyeon taste better.
Do you know what they are?
One's kimchi, so what's the other?
The jerk who steals a bite!
I'll make it even tastier then.
I'm glad you're enjoying it.
I should hold off on the broth.
Why?
I don't want to crave soju.
How smart of you.
When untangled, ramyeon noodles are at least 40m long.
That's the height of a 13-story building.
Since when did this turn into Trivia Night?
I don't want even half of a noodle getting in between us.
Who confesses their feelings with ramyeon noodles?
Must you be so cute all the time?
I've been known for that since my days as a mountain spirit.
I haven't seen you this happy in a while.
I am.
My parents are waiting for me at home...
and you're here by my side.
My childhood dream has come true,
so I wonder who can help make that happen for you too.
I wonder how it feels to be human.
I don't care if you're human or a nine-tailed fox.
What matters is that we're together right now.
(Tale of The Nine Tailed)
If I don't stop this, she'll sacrifice herself...
to protect me just like last time.
Don't do it.
You need to understand me.
I'm going to wait for you...
just like how you waited for me.
This is the Underworld.
The place where I'm standing right now.
Do you even know what that means?
If I fail, I want you to kill him instead.
What if something happens to Yeon?
- How could you... - Was this your plan all along?
No. I can't do it.
No!