Ready to shoot
Run
Hurry
This way
Tomorrow noon 12 o' clock, get out of the city and surrender
Or on life will remain when we broke the city
Not even chicken or dogs
Surrender
Retreat
Open the gate and give in
Or we will all die
Right
Surrender
As the guard of Hongchuan City
I won't allow anyone
stepping into our home
making our civilians slaves
even if I have to pay my life
Who are you?
The Xiuli Army
you command was the betrayers of Yan
How can we believe you?
Yeah. Right
Three years ago
the Xiuli Army was deceived by the evil Wei
to open the gate
Hongchuan was filled with blood
Their own family and friends died
as well
All these years
they cannot even return to their home
They are not any less painful than
any of you
To return to our hometown
we gathered up together
experienced numerous battles
so that we could rush out of Chang'an
I trust them
And I plead you to
give them a chance as well
I promise you
If we can't defeat their attack tomorrow
the whole Xiuli Army and I
are willing to be tied by you
You can use us to surrender to Wei
I will keep my words
I won't make any resistance by then
Hongchuang is a old city
No updated equipment
When Cheng Yuan and Jiang Teng
escaped from here
they took everything
Miss
what can we use to be our weapon now?
I have some
drafts of weapons in my hands now
We can use what we have here
and make weapons right now
Hope we can finish in time
We will defend here
as long as we can
Our goal in the battle
is not killing the enemies
But
using the small-scale attack
to interrupt their steps to attack us
Holding down their spirit
Delaying their time on us
Time and patience
are the only weapon we own
As long as we can hang up for seven days
I believe
the reinforcements of the prince will arrive
Guys
The war is coming
No time to hesitate
Our country is in danger
Time to show our loyalty
As a soldier
the duty of protecting our land and people is
lying on our shoulder
No matter how this will end
we have no guilt to the land of Yan
to our own consciousness
to the vexillum
standing over us
To live or to die
We'll know after the battle
Guys
Please take care
Take care, Miss
Ge Qi?
General
You are not on duty today
Why don't you rest?
I can't sleep
Why?
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking
I've left home for so many years
Don't know my little wife
gave birth to a boy or a girl
Did she marry another man?
Don't know how's
my mom and dad now?
How about last time?
Last time
I did not enter their door at all
because I am still
under the title of traitors
I understand
I really hope
I can survive this war
And the prince will
remove our title as betrayers
I can go home
with honor
Don't worry, buddy
I believe
we will make it
Get out
Who are you?
You are so young
Why don't you leave with those people?
We know each other
Last time before the drug store
one of your brother
help me pay the medicine
You are not sending me away?
Your choice to live or die
is none of my business
I am pretty busy everyday
Things of you little kid is not my work
Little kid?
I... I
I am fifteen this year
I can go on the battlefield to kill enemies
I...
Look at me
How strong I am
Why didn't you leave
with them?
My mother is sick. She can't move
Don't send us away
I can guard the city with you
Help you kill the evil
Tell me, what's your name?
I'm Puppy Du
A good boy as you
Why they call you like this?
My grandmother gave me this name
She said one with humble name is easier to raise
If fact
I feel this name doesn't
sound good too
How about you think of a new one for me?
But my surname must be Du
How about Pingan?