Episode Forty-five
There is someone inside.
Why didn’t you tell me earlier?
So she is the beautiful slave
Mister Tian prepared for me.
Inside the closet,
there is a beautiful woman.
In bed,
there is an ugly shrew.
Any man will feel
it is such a pity.
So you are a man?
Why did I heard
the Guards of Yue outside
saying that you haven’t touched women for years
and are going to be a monk?
If you insult me with words again,
I shall show you
whether I am a real man.
Rascal.
Where are you going?
I am leaving.
No way.
Let go of me.
Your Young Master.
Young Master, are you still awake?
Mister Tian, it’s late.
Where are you here?
His Young Master Wei Shuye is here.
He wants to meet you.
How about this.
You entertain him for me.
I am a little
tired now.
Yes, sir.
I got it.
Rest assure.
I shall take
good care of him.
Young Master,
enjoy your lovely night.
I shall excuse myself now.
After Her Highness went back to Chang’an,
she ordered to arrest you.
She wants to kill you.
You knew
Wei Shuye has fancies Her Highness since he was a child.
Why did he come here
out of the blue?
He is here to catch you.
Why didn’t you escape
and still sit here, enjoying the food?
Didn’t you say that
Wei Shuye is outside
to catch me?
If I escape now,
I will definitely be caught.
I have a question for you.
Why did you
come here so suddenly?
I don’t have any money. I wanted to steal some.
Looks like you are going to need a lot of money.
Yanbei is
very poor.
If you don’t steal enough money,
you may starve to death.
Your Young Master Wei.
He is still asleep?
I don’t know whether
His Young Master is up or not.
I heard he
catches a cold.
I happen to have some medicine.
Your Young Master Wei. Please wait.
I heard that
he went inside to take a rest
before sunset.
It’s noon right now.
He should be up by now.
Since when Yuwen Yue becomes
so lazy?
It’s not just
my Young Master inside.
I am curious that
what kind of woman
can make him fall in love
so deeply.
Please wait here, Your Young Master Wei.
Your Young Master.
Brother Wei came here so late last night,
but you got up this early.
You really are a hard working person.
I am following the imperial decreed. I need to be cautious.
Good for you.
Mister Tian is going to give me
a banquet later.
Are you coming?
Of course.
Right.
I heard you got a
beautiful woman last night.
You two got along very well.
Why don’t you bring her with you
to the banquet?
让我好好开开眼
OK.
It’s easier to escape at night.
I shall leave after sunset.
You can’t leave.
Wei Shuye probably already knew
you are here.
Even if he is not certain,
he is suspicious.
If you escape now,
you will definitely get caught.
Is he really capable
of catching me?
How can you be so confident?
Do you know
how many people are there
wanting to catch you
in exchange for money?
Your portraits
are distributed everywhere.
Not only local officials,
but also the imperial guards
and some killers who specialise in
catching wanted people
are looking for you.
Besides,
it is too far away from Yanbei.
How can you fight against
so many people alone?
Are you insane?
I know what I am doing.
Ever since I decided to go back
to Yanbei with Yan Xun,
I have known
I am up against
the entire world.
However, it doesn’t scare me.
Yanbei is Yan Xun’s hometown.
So is mine.
Even if I will die,
I need to go to Yanbei.
Fine.
You may go.
I don’t care if you get caught,
get hurt
even get killed.
Just don’t let me know.
You may get killed somewhere
I can’t help you.
I can’t stand it.
You always wear black or white.
Are you going to a funeral?
This one is better.
At least it makes you feminine.
Dress up and
come to the banquet with me.
After the banquet, I shall escort you leave.
You look more feminine
after dressing up.
Just shut
your mouth.
Let’s go.
You look nice.
Wait
This one is good
No one will recognize you
after wearing it
Pretty good
Were you playing me?
I cannot even see the road
after wearing it
Follow me if you can't see
Sense the direction by the sound
A good chance to review it
I won't do the make-up
if I know I'm wearing it
Hold my hand
Give me your hand, hurry
Master
Slow down
Brother Yue
I heard you just got a
beauty
You stayed in the room with her
for a whole day. Never came out
I thought they were lying
at first
Now I know they are telling the truth
Come on, brother Yue
You must have worked hard
Need to take in more nutrition
How's your mission going?
Lots of wealthy businessmen in Xianyang
are now transferring their fortune property
The majesty has been aware of this
I came here at night to
check all the things out
Brother Yue, anyway
I cannot compare with you
Be luck to get leisure
I was wonder why yesterday
you refused to
meet with me
Turns out you have somewhere joyful to go for
When Minister Tian told me yesterday
about this
I could not believe it
Since you know
I am busy with her
You shouldn't pull me out from the bed
We have known for so many years
I thought
except for
the little maid besides you
You won't fall for
anyone else
Seems like that may not be true
I really want to know
how beautiful she is
You can be obsessed
with her like that
Seems like master Yue
found his true love
Master Wei
Let's not offend him
right now
Come on
Let us have a taste of
the good wine of Wupeng
Come on
Okay
Report
Minister, the product is arrived
Take him here
Yes
Let me go
Let me out
Behave
The criminal is here
Let me go
- Open it - Let me out
Let me out
Who are you?
Who give you the right to arrest me?
Shut up
He is the trusted follower of the leader of
the Xianyang Business Chamber
He owns many secrets of
the Xianyang Chamber
而且贤阳商会里
那本最重要的账册
就在他身上
这些日子
I'd ran thoroughly in all those places just to
find him out
Master Wei
We really find a treasure
this time
Someone here
Take him into custody for committing felony
Watch him carefully