[TICKING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
CARL AZUZ: This is CNN
10, your daily explanation
of world news in 10 minutes,
and I'm your host, Carl Azuz.
Hope your day is going well.
Yesterday did not go well for
international stock markets.
After drops in other
exchanges around the world,
the US stock markets set a
record, and not a good one.
The Dow Jones Industrial
Average is an index
of 30 significant stocks.
It includes companies like
Disney and McDonald's,
and its one major indicator
of how the market as a whole
is doing.
The Dow dropped so
far, so fast yesterday
that a circuit breaker kicked
in, a temporary stop to trading
to give investors a chance
to catch their breaths.
It lasted 15 minutes.
And when everything
was said and done
with at the end of
the day, the Dow
had lost more than 2000
points, its worst point drop
than on any other
day in history.
What's more important to
investors than points though,
are percentages.
The Dow lost 7.8% of its value.
That's not its biggest
percentage drop ever,
but it was its worst day
since October of 2008
when the great
recession was dragging
down the world economy.
Why did this happen?
Two main reasons.
One of them was oil prices.
They collapsed on Monday
after a disagreement
over oil production between
Saudi Arabia and Russia.
They are two major
producers of oil.
And though lower oil prices can
translate to lower gas prices,
which many drivers
see as a good thing,
investors don't like
falling oil prices
because they often
correspond with a weakening
global economy.
So this was a big reason why
there was a sell off in the US
stock market yesterday, and that
triggered the circuit breaker.
RICHARD QUEST: It doesn't
matter whether the circuit
breaker's on an electrical
box or in the stock market.
The concept remains the same.
If there's too much
power, too much
force coming down the pipe,
the circuit breaker kicks in
and everything stops.
In 1987 with Black Monday,
the Dow Jones Industrials
fell more than 500 points.
It was a loss of 22.6%.
It is still the largest
percentage daily fall
in the Dow's history.
There was a feeling at the
time of financial Armageddon.
The world was coming to an end.
The market decided to put in
place various circuit breakers
so that trading would be slowed.
Those who are in favor
of circuit breakers
say that when properly used
with proper parameters,
the circuit breaker merely
allows time for thought.
CARL AZUZ: But there was another
reason for the market dive
yesterday.
And if you've been watching,
you know what I'm about to say,
coronavirus.
According to information put
together by Johns Hopkins
University, more than
113,000 cases have been
confirmed around the world.
Almost 4,000 people who've
caught the virus have died.
That's about 3.5%
of total cases.
In more than 62,000 people,
almost 1/2 the total cases
have recovered from the virus.
But the fear of this
disease spreading
has led to school closures
for hundreds of millions
of students around the world.
The nation of Italy, which
has seen the largest outbreak
in Europe, is under lockdown
with schools, movie theaters,
and nightclubs closed.
Ireland has called off its
St. Patrick's Day parades.
Theme parks and museums
have been closed.
Sports events and some
religious gatherings
have been called off.
The coronavirus outbreak
started in China in December.
And though its spread there
has slowed down in recent days,
it has affected daily
life in Shanghai,
China's most populated city.
DAVID CULVER: In the US
when you're stocking up
for a hurricane, a blizzard,
or a viral outbreak,
you tend to buy in bulk.
Many Shanghai residents flocking
to China's only Costco location
to do that, and we joined them
for some shopping of our own.
All right, so this is the long
line that's moving, actually,
at a pretty good pace.
We've heard several
announcements
as we've been standing here.
And essentially,
they're telling people,
keep your distance from
the person in front of you.
The store only allows 1000
customers in at a time.
The wait outside?
About 10 minutes.
All right.
We're going in.
So they just told us
to come into this one
line that's clearly going to
take our temperature here.
Carts sanitized one by
one, but some shoppers
adding a layer just to be safe.
All employees, customers
and their little ones
wearing face masks.
Plastic used to protect the
apples from germs and plastic
even used to shield kids.
I can hear there's
a loudspeaker.
Essentially, they're
telling people to keep one
meter apart from each other.
But as you look around,
folks are definitely
getting a lot closer than that.
- [SPEAKING CHINESE]
DAVID CULVER: And if you
did not catch that warning,
this guy will keep you in line.
But there are other
options for folks looking
to avoid stores altogether.
One company launched
this mobile grocery van
before the outbreak.
Since, it's gained
a loyal following,
a mostly older crowd.
You can see the
folks lined up here.
They get, essentially, a menu of
items that they can pick from.
And the idea is, they're
not going into a store.
They're not congregating
with other masses.
Instead, they hand off the paper
with what they want, and folks
who are inside do
the preparation
and then pass out their food.
You can check it out.
I mean, it seems to be
pretty popular here.
The company behind it
says, over the course
of a week, the mobile grocery
visits 20 neighborhoods,
serving more than 40,000
Shanghai residents.
The project manager says
they get fresh produce daily
and they make sure it's
all fully sanitized.
But a van can only hold so much.
For shoppers looking for a
taste of normalcy and plenty
of options, like pallets of hand
sanitizer, it's back to Costco.
But a warning.
If you decide on a cooked meal
here, or a beverage like I did,
it's now it to go purchase only.
They said you would have to eat
and drink everything you buy
in there outside of this store.
Keep your mask on at all times.
They're also telling
folks to get in
and out as quickly as possible.
You don't hear
many stores telling
their customers to rush,
but they're doing that here.
An effort to minimize
exposure and to maximize
what you can stock up on.
David Culver, CNN, Shanghai.
CARL AZUZ: 10 second trivia.
The Columbus Panhandles,
Muncie Flyers,
and Rochester Jeffersons
were all teams in what sports
league?
NHL, MLB, NBA, or NFL?
In 1922, when the National
Football League was named,
these were three of its teams.
75 years later, the
Tampa Bay Buccaneers
drafted a Florida State running
back named Warrick Dunn.
And that same year,
it was 1997, Dunn
founded Homes for the
Holidays, a charity he uses
to fulfill his mother's dream.
She'd always wanted
a home of her own.
And when Warrick used
her life insurance
to buy one after she died, he
says his family found hope.
- Just show me that.
WARRICK DUNN: Everyone
deserves a home.
Home is where the heart is.
I just remember sitting in a
locker room with Coach Dungy,
and just listening to him just
talk to all the rookies about,
you guys want to get
involved, and give back,
and those things?
Then it just came up, my mom.
She was working off duty
when guys ambushed her,
and they just opened
fire on a police car.
My mom lost her life.
I just knew from
that moment that I
couldn't worry about myself.
I needed to worry about
my brothers and sisters.
She was never able to realize
her dream of homeownership.
I just saw the way that she
just cared about people,
and how she wanted her
community to be better.
Homes for the Holidays
is where we go and we
assist a single parent
family who's becoming
a first time homeowner.
So far over the last 21 years,
177 single parent families,
we given $5,000 down
payment, and we fully
furnish their homes with
food, furniture, linens,
[INAUDIBLE] TVs, computers, all
the way down to the toothbrush.
First, we were just focused
on really just helping
families get into homes.
The more I really
learned, we wanted
to get in the business of
giving people potential to break
their cycle of poverty.
And with that is financial
literacy, health and wellness,
education attainment,
and workforce development
and entrepreneurship.
KIA SAVAGE LEWIS: It
set the foundation.
For me, up until
that point, survival
was my thinking process.
WARRICK DUNN: But the goal is, I
hope we can go out of business.
And when I say that, it's,
no one else needs housing.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
CARL AZUZ: We can't say
if the meals offered
by this food truck
are human grade,
but that's kind of the point.
It's a food truck for dogs.
Woof Bowl rolls
around the Virginia
area serving hamburgers,
tacos, donuts,
and drinks, again, for dogs.
The human couple
that runs it say
they wanted to give
fresher, healthier
options to animals than
some dog food and treats
typically provide.
And like other food trucks,
they sometimes sell out.
There are Dober-many options,
you could say, poodles of them,
for specialty dog chow chow.
Breakfast could be a
Great Dane-ish, a bagel,
or an English muffin mastiff.
For lunch, an Aussie
shepherd meat pie with a bowl
of Yorkshire pudding.
And dinner, try the Char-pei
or Kipper key with the side
of Bichon fries.
Maltese milk and Earl gray
hounds are drink options,
and dessert can include a
Boston cream pie terrier
with Labra-snicker doodles.
I'm Carl Azuz.
It's funny that we
ended on dog food,
because it's the Bobcats
of Taylorsville, Utah
who made it on today's show.
Bennion Junior High School has
been subscribing and commenting
on our YouTube channel.
Follow their example today.
We may say your school tomorrow.