"In 1836, Chen Xieng from Xinhui
of Guangdong Province,"
"he wrote a text book in order to facilitate him
to teach martial arts,"
"In order to memorize three of his masters,"
"Cai Foo, Li Yau-shan and Chen Yuan-hu,"
"He thus named the book
'Choyleefut Boxing Spectrum'."
"Thames Town, United Kingdom"
Wow, thank you.
Got it!
Oh! Hey, man
Thanks.
Hey! Look out!
Sorry.
- Hi, Susie.
- Hi.
Can I sit there?
Yes.
What do you want?
- Just give me the usual.
- Okay.
Hey, Jie.
- Talk to you later.
- Fine.
Hey, no fighting...
Get away!
Behind you!
Be careful, I will come back again!
Thank you, thank you.
- Hey...
- How is it?
Are you okay?
Ken, get out with your friend, get out!
What?
- Get out!
- God!
My Jesus!
So what plan do you have now?
I really want to learn
Chinese martial arts in China.
Chinese martial arts in China?
Is there anything particular you want to learn?
It's always an idea for me to learn
Chinese Kung-fu, but...
I only want to learn Choyleefut.
Choyleefut?
Yeah, what?
Nothing, it's a good choice.
Well, here I am.
- Well, take care, man.
- You too.
When I was in China,
I always wanted to view the moon
in a foreign country.
Now, I am standing under the moon
on a foreign land,
Except the style of living,
I have found that the moon is no different
from the one in China.
Is there something wrong with you?
Big Bro.
Let's have some beer.
I am sorry, it's a bit messy.
It looks like you haven't got any girlfriend yet.
Why are you here in UK?
Business trip.
So I came to visit you too.
This is for you.
- Mobile phone?
- Yes.
I already got one.
That is old, it's time to change a new one.
It's a nag to change a new phone.
I have to input all names and phone numbers again.
Whenever we meet something new,
we won't get used to it at once.
So you have to try to overcome it.
This is same as learning how to be a man.
If you don't try, you'll have no progress.
Don't just stick to the same place.
Understand?
Big bro, where is your next stop?
I am tired, my next stop is home.
Home? Which home? China?
No matter how one achieves,
He must know where his root is.
He must know how to go home.
Let me ask you,
You've lived abroad for quite a long time,
What have you found?
I haven't thought of this question.
So, you have had no goal.
Instead of wasting time, why not go home earlier?
When will you go home?
I'll leave when everything is fixed
at the new school, how about you?
Take care.
It's cold, better wear more clothes.
It's weird! Whenever I see his back,
I always have a very strong sense,
This nagging guy...
He is my dad.
"Pan-America International"
Now we can see is...
a famous school of martial arts in China,
The famous Choyleefut School of Martial Arts.
The students from this school...
They are all over the world.
About this Chinese Kung Fu craze,
Along with their strength,
The power will be unlimited.
These two are the principal masters
of this School of Martial Arts.
Chen Tien-hong and Chen Tien-lai.
Chen Tien-lai is now teaching abroad.
Both principles and kung-fu of Choyleefut.
Chen Tien-lai has travelled all around the world,
He has visited every schools
of Choileefut in the world.
If we want to control this strength,
These two men form the origin.
This project spends much resources of the group,
And it sure has certain risk.
Of course it is.
But I trust Yu-fei's ability.
Just go ahead.
Yu-fai, have a good show.
Yes, boss.
Hey, yeah I am Jie.
I am going back to China
and I am wondering if you'd like to come along.
You don't have to if you don't want to.
Bye man, see you soon.
Sorry, are you Mr. Chen Tien-lai?
Yes.
You never told me that your family
owns the martial arts school.
What? You never asked!
Like it make no difference if I told you earlier.
Master, thank you.
Dude, what does that sign say?
That one?
Yeah!
Come on, I know you know Chinese.
You just read it.
Listen up! It's called...
Choyleefut martial arts school.
I've got it, I have got it at last!
Your Chinese improves a lot. Let's go.
Be careful!
What's up? Why did you fall?
What's up?
This is my uncle.
Uncle, I am back.
Uncle, how are you? I am Ying-jie.
Hi, Jie.
This is my Japanese friend
who I met in United Kingdom.
Takeda Koron.
You can call me Ken, nice to meet you.
Good... Not bad.
Hey, I've got something for you.
This is nice!
I bought it in UK for you.
It's an imported stuff!
Come on, let's go in and talk.
Ask your friend to come along.
Watch out!
Senior, I knew it's you!
Nice move, huh?
Thank you for not being tough.
Of course, because you're my junior!
My senior, and this is Ken, my friend from UK.
You're lucky, men.
My wife has cooked something you love eating.
Let's get in.
Coming...
These dishes are what Jie likes most.
Why took you so long?
Thank you, my sister-in-law.
Come on!
That sounds odd, better call my name.
Jie, is your dad on the way home?
He asked me to come home first.
He said he'd be back when his work is over.
We haven't seen for a long time.
I think your dad is talking
something bad behind me.
Come on, let's cheers for the friend from afar.
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
Cheers.
What's up with you?
Are all the schools of martial arts
the same in China?
Why do you ask this question?
I think this school isn't like a school.
I know this school isn't that conspicuous.
You know, my uncle you met today...
He is a great kung-fu master.
Don't you believe in me?
Not only my uncle,
My dad is great in kung-fu too.
How about this?
I'll take you to meet my uncle tomorrow.
I'll ask him to teach you
the authentic Choyleefut.
All right.
Let's go to sleep.
I heard from senior that...
Some visitors from a company came to the school.
Why were they here?
I don't know.
Why stopping me taking photo?
You'd behave yourself.
You can't take our ancestors' photos
without permission.
I think you'd behave yourself.
Please act like a gentleman.
Young men,
is there any misunderstanding?
He is so impolite.
Am I impolite?
Senior, can they take our ancestors' photo
without permission?
No, so this is your fault.
Miss Xia is my friend.
She wants to learn kung-fu here.
But I doubt that...
Your teaching is worth to learn or not.
What did you say?
Well, I just want to view
the authentic Choyleefut.
So you are here to ask for a fight, aren't you?
Okay, I'll let you view the authentic Choyleefut!
This is what you called authentic?
Since you're the guest, I don't want to hurt you.
Senior.
This is Choyleefut, what do you think?
I finally viewed the authentic Choyleefut.
So, you can leave now.
Hi, I am Xia Yu-fai,
Project director of Pan-America
International Investment Group.
This is our martial arts consultant,
Zuo Zhang-hong.
They are his students.
Our group would like to acquire your school
of martial arts.
Once your school is acquired,
You can enjoy excellent terms.
Including spacious training hall,
advanced training equipments,
And you can participate in international
martial arts competitions.
Sure you can be rich and famous.
I see.
So, please go back and tell your boss that...
About this school of martial arts...
We won't sell it.
Who are you? Can you represent this school?
I cannot, but my father Chen Tien-lai can.
He will be back soon.
He would definitely say no.
Really? So you mean...
Chen Tien-lai can decide the fate
of this school, can't he?
That's great.
May, please give me the Letter of Intent.
You can see the signature of your dad on it.
His intention is so clear.
If you agree,
We can proceed with the second step
of acquisition.
No hurry to give any statement.
I have a letter from Chen Tien-lai too.
Actually, the acquisition of your school...
is to raise your standard and strength.
And it can promote your name too.
This school has a history of over a hundred year.
Our standard is definitely not under yours.
How to prove it?
Why not have a competition between us?
The winner should win two of three games.
The winner will decide the fate of this school,
what do you think?
I don't think this is necessary.
But it sounds fun.
Okay.
All right, I'll get the contract ready
and come back to you.
Oh no! I think I've made a mistake.
Big bro, where are you now?
What did you father write in the letter?
The school is so important to my dad.
I don't understand why he promised to sell it.
Are you worrying about the race?
A total of three should join the competition.
Except my senior and I,
I don't know who can join us.
Don't worry.
I can join the competition too.
I have already thought of it, but...
Don't worry, I can learn Choyleefut too.
Trust me, dude.
You promised.
I can't imagine this would become so complicated.
And Ken is dragged into the mess!
Stop!
When you play the rod, be flexible!
Senior.
Forget it.
Why?
Since Uncle Chen agrees the acquisition,
Why should we fight?
Anyway, we may not sure win.
If we aren't confident, why go for the race?
I'll study hard.
We may not lose in the race.
You are so proud of yourself, aren't you?
Working hard isn't a matter,
Most important of all is to keep our school well.
I want everyone to know that...
Our school can overcome this challenge.
Now the school is okay, isn't it?
A big commercial group is going to acquire us.
We will be rich and famous when we join
international races, isn't that great?
Jie, it's you who should consider, not me.
Go back and think about it.
Senior.
You must consider the reputation of Choyleefut.
The sponsor of this competition...
Chiguo Air-conditioner sponsors 10 million.
Yi-fung Group sponsors 8 million.
Tai-cheong Trading sponsors 5 million.
The total money from the sponsors...
It has already reached 58 million.
Good, you've got a great record
just on the first day.
It's really a miracle.
30 million out of the total sum
of money is because of...
our martial arts consultant, Mr. Zuo Zhang-hong.
We have to keep working hard.
Before the competition, our target is 80 million.
Yes.
Hubby, come and try it.
I bought you a big and sweet water melon.
Honey, this is as sweet as you.
Cut the crap and eat your fruit!
Well, I think you have something to tell me.
Should I tell you anything?
Someone told me that the school is to be acquired.
Is it true?
Come on, don't be nosy.
You don't love me now.
I don't want to talk to you!
Honey...
Don't get mad, okay, I'll tell you.
Actually I don't know the details
of the acquisition.
It's because Uncle said yes already.
But Jie disagrees.
So they are going to have a competition
one month later,
Each side will have 3 fighters
to join the competition.
The winner will have the final say.
So, there must be some good prizes
for the competition, right?
Say, how about any money award?
I am not sure about that.
You're stupid!
Why don't you ask?
I am not asking...
You don't love me now.
You don't love me now!
You don't love me at all.
Where are you taking the water melon to?
Welcome.
My friend is over there.
I didn't expect you come for the contract.
Are you scared? You still have time
to change your mind.
Yes, I am worried that...
If you lose, you'll lose face too.
Cut the crap!
You can take it back
and study well before signing.
Good terms!
The winner will get 3 million.
Pan-America International is always fair.
You'll get the reward which you have contributed.
Okay, I won't send you to the door.
Are you asking me to leave like this?
So, what do you want?
At least you can buy me a drink.
I've got a date.
If you want to drink, you can go to another table.
I'll pay the bill.
Take your time, I won't bother you dude.
Poor girl, how can she take a cool man
as her boyfriend?
Thank you for coming.
Uncle, what should we do about the competition?
Where is starts, where it will be fixed.
Ken and I will try our very best.
But the point is, we still need one more guy.
You really want to compete?
Have good practice first.
So start from the basic training first.
Start from the basic training?
We only have one month's time.
God has fixed everything.
If the 3rd one is going to show up,
He will show up at last.
Now, don't think anything about the competition.
Have some handstand practice now.
It will let you view from another angle.
What are you doing here?
Why are you here?
I paid the school fee,
so why can't I come to school?
If you want to learn kung-fu, go for my senior.
We are now having secret training,
not open to visitors.
Secret training?
You mean handstand is part of
your secret training?
Be serious, otherwise, just give up.
By the way, I didn't say
I come for learning kung-fu.
I just come and walk around.
I like to stay wherever I want.
Are you falling for me?
Leave her alone, let's keep on practicing.
Okay.
Another week has passed.
Senior hasn't promised to join us.
Until now, I am still confused that...
Why my dad wants to give up the school?
What is his motive?
Can Ken and I get the last victory?
Why do you stay up this late?
Master.
I just can't sleep.
Do you want a chat?
Let's go.
Master, did I do a wrong thing?
Everyone has his own way of thinking.
You can't say it right or wrong.
I don't join the competition,
it is for the good of the school.
Our school has a history of over a hundred year.
All the students from every generation...
They all want to contribute something new
for the good of the school.
I am the same.
Let me ask you one question,
Do you love your wife?
Yes.
Will you dump your old lover...
Because of a new love?
Of course not.
It has a long history,
older the age, deeper in love.
Go to sleep now, I have got to sleep too.
Good night, master.
Are you all right?
Miss Xia, I am sorry.
Jie, take her over there and take a rest.
Come on.
Be careful...
Does it hurt?
How about this?
Not that serious, just a slight twist only.
It'll be all right soon.
I really appreciate that!
You don't come for learning kungfu,
But why do you come here everyday?
And, this is not your office.
Please don't wear high heel shoes
here again, okay?
None of your business!
You're okay now.
When you're home, put some ice
on the wound to comfort it.
Wait for me.
What are these shoes for?
Do you think we have high heel shoes for you?
You still have a choice,
Either leave here without shoes,
Or, you can wear these soft shoes.
Are they okay?
They don't match!
Look at you guys!
Look at your pose! It's poor!
You don't show any strength at all.
If I don't join you guys,
how can you win the race?
Wait!
Senior, what did you say?
Can't you hear my words?
Without me, how can you guys win?
He means he wants to fight.
Look at you! How can you practice like this?
My master just doesn't want to make any comments!
Master, please say something fair,
If I don't join them,
Will they have any chance to win
See? Remember what I told you?
The third one will show up sooner or later.
You have heard what master said, haven't you?
I am so important! Work hard, men!
Master, please say something fair.
I can't hear your words, please say again.
This is great!
Si-hai is weird today.
He doesn't want to join the race, does he?
Why does he practice so hard now?
It's hot! It's hot!
Si-hai is practicing under such hot weather.
He would definitely stink when he is home.
Do you agree with him to join the competition?
Sure, I am supporting!
They will have an award of 3 million if they win.
3 million!
Si-hai, work hard...
Hubby, I love you!
What is she doing?
I think she really loves senior so much!
She said so, I don't mean it.
- Aren't you satisfied?
- Excuse me.
Go practice!
She is so cute!
Master, is she Jie's girlfriend?
Master, is there something wrong with your eyes?
Do you need some eye-drops?
This is great! You look better now.
Do you think this is nice?
Have you changed because of me?
Come on! I came here for you.
Please come to my office at 3 tomorrow.
I'll show you something.
I know you would date me sooner or later.
Tomorrow at 3pm, don't be late.
I am leaving.
See you tomorrow.
Hi, I have an appointment with Xia Yu-fai,
my name is Jie Chen.
All right, please wait.
The appointment is 3 o'clock in the afternoon.
I came early.
Please go over there and take a seat.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Who is he?
He doesn't seem to be our colleague.
You came early.
I seldom be late.
I'd like to let you visit...
the training process of the
Pan-America International Group.
Are you interested?
Let's go.
How do you feel?
Have you eaten yet?
Harder please.
Jie, where have you been?
You are so serious about this competition,
aren't you?
Do you have to practice?
What's up? What's happened?
What's wrong with your hand?
Fighting with someone?
This is the difference between our trainings.
Hitting the metal balls and sand bags.
It will ruin your hands for sure!
For karate players, we also have similar practice.
That's why the lethality of karate is stunning.
The punch's speed is fast and strong.
Actually you are a great karate player,
Why do you want to learn Choyleefut?
This is all because of my grandfather.
In the thirteenth year of Taisho,
My grandfather was the bodyguard
of a senior official.
This senior official of Japan...
Once helped a Chinese named Sun.
Because of a chance,
My grandfather met the bodyguard
of that Chinese man.
They appreciated each other
and learnt martial arts from each other.
At last, the kung-fu of that Chinese bodyguard...
Impressed my grand-father very much.
My grandfather lost,
But what impressed him not
because of the guy's kung-fu,
But also the ethics.
Because of that chance,
It brought him a new face of Bushido spirit.
That is a stage which karate player
can never reach.
Later, my grandfather finally knew that,
That kind of kung-fu is named Choyleefut.
At last, they became buddies.
The greatest wish of my grandfather was...
He wanted to learn Choyleefut.
What a pity that he has got no chance.
So I want to come to China to learn Choyleefut.
It is to make my grandfather's wish come true.
You came for Choyleefut
because of your grandfather!
Not exactly.
Actually I love kung-fu.
Sure, I can tell.
Now, it's time for me to teach you guys.
Actually, every school has its own strength.
Take Choyleefut as an example.
We fight with techniques.
In our fights, punch, kick, bump, push,
pick and jump...
They are ever changing.
Even you have strong punches and strong kicks,
If you can't hit me, it's useless.
But if you are hit by me instead,
Possibly some bones will be broken at last.
What if you are punched first?
Isn't it possible?
Tell me, tell me...
How can I get punched?
- What's up?
- Go...
Uncle, don't ask now.
What do you want?
Take this spicy goose leg, come on.
Some wine too.
These are my favorites!
Uncle, can you teach us now?
Because of these food and wine,
I will teach you anything you ask for.
Uncle, you promised!
What's up?
Teach us something really powerful.
Well, nothing is really powerful!
I mean the most powerful stance of Choyleefut!
No powerful stance at all!
It's not like novels!
Uncle, why do you eat up the food then?
Isn't it for greeting your uncle?
Don't be disappointed.
I have fixed everything.
Tomorrow, you will have a new kind of training.
Sure you will find them interesting and funny.
You lost, it's your turn.
Go!
Uncle, we have stood here for half day.
What are we waiting for?
Yes, I think you're wasting our time.
I am waiting for your question!
Actually you are not psychologically ready yet.
What do you mean?
Let's take an example.
If you have a doubt unsolved,
can you learn something whole-heartedly?
I don't quite understand.
Come on, come and hit me.
Again.
Jie, Si-hai, what have you seen?
You are fast.
I am not fast.
I just know what you guys will act.
When you meet your rival,
When they already know how you act,
You'd act something which you don't even predict.
This will then confuse your rival.
Do you guys understand?
I am asking you!
Go...
Hello?
Staying up late?
It's early now, how is your practice?
I am not used to that.
Why?
I am not used to not seeing you
for one whole week.
What do you want?
I will be off 2 days later.
Can you apply for a leave?
I'd like to have some fun with you.
"The birthday of Zuo Zhang-hong"
But I have an appointment in the afternoon,
I am only free in the morning.
Great, no problem, I'll come and pick you up.
Okay.
- Okay, bye!
- Bye!
Hubby, I checked with the property agent today.
There is a nice flat around.
With a sitting room and a living room,
just costs 800 thousand.
What for?
I check it for you.
I've got no money to buy any flat.
If you win, you will have money then.
That is the money for the school, not for me.
You risk your life for the school!
If you win, why will the money go to the school?
I fight for the name of the school.
If there is any award,
it sure will go to the school.
You don't want a baby.
You don't want us to move out.
You just want to live here
to take care of your master.
Okay, I just listened to you!
The truth is, you don't have a penny!
But have you thought of my feeling?
Until now,
I have no youth, I have no family.
I have nothing! I...
You don't love me now, you don't love me!
What time is it now?
Do you know you are one minute late?
One minute may not be important to you.
But this is very important to me.
No, it's about the car...
All right, it's my fault, you are right.
Sorry, don't get mad!
Move now. What's up?
Buckle up please.
Miss Xia hasn't come back yet.
It's all right, I'll be here waiting.
All right, please help yourself.
What's up?
Give it to me...
Give it back to me...
Jie, you signed the contract with our group,
Isn't it wrong for me to stay this close to you?
What did you say?
Come on, this is our personal time.
Look at the beautiful sun!
Here you are. Have an early rest.
Have you forgotten?
I am sorry, I know today is your birthday.
No need to say sorry to me.
I have always told myself...
I'll be happy if you are happy.
If you enjoy two men wooing you at the same time,
I am willing to take it.
Please don't say that.
Guys, listen, the three masters here...
They are from different schools of martial arts.
This is master Dongjia from Thailand,
he plays Thai Boxing
This is Master Liu, a master of Hong Style
And this is Master Li, a Tai-chi Master.
Master, do you want us to learn from them?
Not learning.
- You'll be hit by them.
- What?
Just defense, no attack.
If you guys want to win,
First you need to know how to be defeated.
Experience will help you grow.
More fights, more chances to win.
Uncle, why don't you go to sleep?
It's not time to sleep.
Uncle, you haven't changed at all.
Your words are always funny.
Come on, you don't know
how to rub your wound at all.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
Have your father given you any call?
Nope. He seems to have disappeared!
I called him several times,
he just didn't answer the call.
Has he called you?
I have no phone.
What's up? Are you missing him?
Yes, but...
I don't miss him everyday.
When a kung-fu master has reached certain stage,
It's really hard for him to find a matched rival.
Your father is the same.
Hey, you read your father's letter,
What did he wrote?
He wrote many things,
and he mentioned your name too.
So, what is it about?
Okay, I can tell you,
But you have to tell me one thing first.
Why did my dad leave here alone for his world?
And you have stayed behind?
Junior.
There is another world outside,
do you want to go with me?
I think it's shapeless and illusive!
As an old Chinese saying,
better take a solid step.
Do you really want to go along the stream?
At least I can view it.
Different people have different wills.
Well, let's walk our own way.
But every roads lead to Rome.
It's like a novel!
I've got it, Uncle,
You intentionally let my dad choose going abroad.
It's because I don't know English.
Come on, stop pretending!
Uncle, for this competition,
Do you think we have a chance to win?
The path is under your feet,
You'd choose your own path and walk.
Okay, I'll pick the stream as you did.
And I'll guard this old pond.
All right, thank you, Uncle.
I am going to sleep now, good night.
Jie, but you haven't told me
what your dad wrote about me.
I just lied, he said nothing about you.
Goodnight!
Jie, I'd like to talk to you.
I am downstairs.
Hey!
What's up?
Come on, why do you pull a long face?
About the competition tomorrow, just work hard!
What's up? Are you mad at me?
Stop! Stop!
What do you mean?
Get lost!
I think we should not meet again.
Yu-fai, about the relationship
between you and Jie,
It will affect the result of the competition.
It's up to your decision.
Yes, boss.
I really regret...
I regret not treasuring the minute
which I stayed with you.
If God could spare that minute to me again,
I think, this minute...
This minute would have become
the most precious minute in my life.
Sister-in-law.
You'd press with skills!
Let me do it. You'd better go out.
Let's get out now.
Honey, I am sorry.
I am sorry!
I haven't heard that word for years.
Do you know why?
It's because my hubby is an honest guy.
He hasn't done anything wrong to his wife.
But his wife...
His wife has sometimes pushed him
to do something beyond his wish.
Come on!
What my wife wants me to do...
Is what I want to do!
Got it.
Well,
I heard that your rivals are tough guys.
Can you win?
I worry that you'd get hurt.
Why not put it this way, I'll talk to your master,
I'll tell him that you'd quit.
Who am I?
- You're Si-hai.
- That's right.
I am the senior, I will never lose.
You'd better go out and view my show.
Okay?
Senior, let's go.
The competition is about to start now.
Are you ready?
I will sure win.
I believe that you'll win too.
After the race, I'll go back to Japan.
Why do you leave in such a hurry?
I'd like to pay a visit to my grandfather's grave.
I want to tell him that
I've learnt the authentic Choyleefut!
Sure! So, will you come back?
Of course I will.
I don't want to leave my buddy behind.
- Come back as soon as possible.
- Sure.
Ladies and gentlemen, how are you doing?
Welcome to the First Kung-fu Competition...
Which is organized by
Pan-America International Group.
We'll have three races today,
the winner should win two out of three.
It is a competition regardless of
kung-fu schools and types.
So all the players of this competition...
They can use any stances from any schools
to beat their rivals.
Let me introduce the first two players.
One of them is Mr. Ren Si-hai
from Guangdong Province.
He is representing Choyleefut.
Another one is from California, America,
Mr. Qian-xin,
representing Pan-America International.
The competition starts now.
Close.
You have got the courage to stand on stage,
It's nice, man!
Better take my punch first.
Box
Hubby, stop fighting!
Hubby! Stop! Let's stop it.
Hubby, I beg you, stop!
- Come on, stay calm...
- Hubby!
Senior!
Honey, listen to me.
Let me fight.
Even I have to lose,
I don't want to lose like a chicken.
No!
Sister-in-law, trust Senior.
You're good! At least you can
come to the second round!
I just can't imagine that.
Close
Box
One, two, three, four, five, six
- One...
- Hubby!
Two, three...
I can't lose the face of the school!
Four, five, six, seven, eight!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven
Hubby!
Honey!
Senior has wakened up!
Senior!
I am not dead.
You scared me! You've finally wakened up!
If I knew that this is so dangerous,
I wouldn't have let you join it.
Senior, your rival was punched and fell.
I think that you didn't lose at all.
Don't cheat.
I am inferior.
This is the result.
Si-hai.
You've finally grown up.
Uncle.
Dad.
Master, I am so sorry.
Silly boy, the race hasn't finished yet.
Who can tell the result?
Ken, charge up.
Okay.
Are you Ken?
Yes, Uncle.
Do you have faith?
Sure!
You guys remember.
Everyone can build his own path.
Wining or losing doesn't matter,
most important is,
Have you ever tried your best.
I got it.
It was a rival!
So hot and exciting!
Now, here comes the second race.
X-man is now representing
Pan-America International.
He comes from Florida, USA.
And the representative from Choyleefut is...
Ken, Takeda Koro from Japan.
Ken, charge up...
Charge up...
I heard that Ken is a karate master
of level tenth.
Will he play with karate,
Or Choyleefut?
All right, the race begins soon,
let's wait and see.
I will win!
Close!
Don't look too hard.
You'll have a nightmare.
Box!
- One, two, three, four...
- Bravo!
Five, six, seven...
Close.
Box!
Come on!
Close.
Box.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight...
Nine, ten!
Yes!
Now, it's tie.
Who do you think will win?
No matter who the winner is,
We'll be the final winner.
Big bro.
I don't have any encouragement for you.
Just fight your own way.
Daddy.
After winning this race,
I have many things to talk to you.
I haven't heard you calling me daddy
for a long time.
From your back,
I can tell you've already grown up.
Sooner or later, you can sure go beyond me.
The two races were so exciting.
Each side won a race.
That means, the final race,
that is the third one...
It will tell who the winner is.
Whoever wins the competition,
They will get an award of 3 million.
Super fight!
The one who represents
Pan-America International is...
He came from California, USA,
The martial arts consultant of Pan-America
International, Mr. Zuo Zhang-hong.
And the one who represents Choyleefut is...
he is the key master of the school,
Mr. Chen Tien-lai... Mr. Chen's son.
Chen Ying-jie from Guangdong Province,
I want to defeat you in front of her.
Come on!
Close.
Box
Yu-fai, you haven't made
any wrong decision before.
I hope this time is the same.
Don't you yield?
Enough, don't dream of another round.
Good, this is what I am thinking too.
I will beat you now!
Box
Choyleefut?
Out of your expectation?
I will make you convince your failure!
He is your student too, right?
One, two, three, four...
Five, six, seven, eight...
One, two, three, four, five...
Six, seven, eight, nine...
Ten!
- We won!
- Bravo!
Bravo! We won!
Senior!
You wrote a nice letter.
I can't imagine you would train up
your successor by a race.
I must thank for your match.
I...
I am sorry.
I won't let you leave me again.
- What's up?
- Say something... Go.
Master, the award of 3 million...
What million? I don't know.
Ying-jie, where is your dad?
He has just been around.
Dad, where are you going?
I am leaving for Ethiopia to operate
a new school of martial arts.
I'll leave this school to you.
What?
"Choyleefut went though the Opium War,"
"Taiping Rebellion, The Xinhai Revolution,"
"as well as the Japanese invasion of China,"
"it has been the biggest school of
martial arts in southern China,"
"and it is also counted as a protection project"
"of a state-level intangible cultural heritage."
"Moreover, Choyleefut is the earliest
Chinese martial arts"
"which has been spread abroad
and achieved a fine reputation"
(subtitle from http://shooter.cn by SPlayer976
"of Chinese kung-fu over the past century."
(subtitle from http://shooter.cn by SPlayer