Harry here super simple guitar.
I'm sweating up and playing this one cool say hopefully you know you don't.
You have great fun learning it because we have different licks.
There's also these
cool stuff you get to just play or play.
All right so one of the keys these cool lakes that even I have a hard time playing nice and clean.
Every time I play it great.
If you are you're my teacher but I have to do to quit playing runs VDU.
You'll be given a free for me Course and every teacher record would just play some guitar and clicking
a link to it all in close up.
All right so here are the close up.
So let me show you the intro first so when goal like this and take a middle finger put on the third
fret second string and then we're going to do is we're going to pick we're going to play the first and
second string at the same time.
Then I'm going to slide through
the lead with my ring finger I'm going to grab the fourth fret third straight in life from the forefront
of the second fret and do a pull off.
So altogether
I have to practice a little bit
OK.
And then E major and I want to hit the major hitting the whole Major again for the third first three
kind of bass strings three to four strings.
OK.
And then that's giving me space to do this kind of effect here.
So I hit the top strings and then I went down with the big and gently and went for the first two to
three strings down here.
OK.
So
I actually aim for the sixth string low and you could hit more strings just now and for the sixth one
then with these two fingers on this line for the Fourth and Fifth Third.
So I let it slide.
Major
So
and again Major aiming for the top kind of bass strings.
Right.
OK.
So and when I'm sliding in here I'm holding down the fifth and the fourth straight.
I'm aiming for those two only those two I'm not trying to hit any other on but
the fourth and fifth string.
OK.
So
then I'm going to get up for those kind of bars here.
All right then comes the cool thing that you can do.
This is just one possibility to be showing you a few.
So I'm hitting the open fifth straight day Hameroff with my middle finger on its second fret.
I let him play the old hammer and that is two times
the third time I'm doing a hammer on him I'm staying here and that's leading me into my first quarter
which is the C major.
All right so I play the whole thing for you know just so you can get a feeling how it all fits into
place.
And then we're going to be learning some other stuff too.
There's probably got to be a two part video because there's just so much to cover.
So
that's leading us into a C major.
Now if you're good or you could just go
to the G
right.
Or if you kind of feel comfortable playing with a pick and hitting the right strings you could play
basically bass
so bass
then that little lake that I already showed you in the intro.
So that's kind of one possibility so.
All right.
So when you get to the D and other cool things you could do would be to hit the D with your pinky grab
the US for that for the bottom the strings and do a pull off with your pinky
hand so down
on play a little bit differently.
I played with the downstroke.
So sort of what you can do with you can do it.
So it's important to get downtown OK.
And not only hitting the bass and kind of getting a few more.
You don't worry about it too much if you only hit the bass if you get two or three strings.
OK.
Just see with your ear what sounds good to you.
So what we did we played them we went to a and b.
All right.
OK so now let me show you another few cool things that you could do.
So let's do that as we're going to start with the CG and we're going to go down down.
The thing that I showed you.
So now it's a little trying to pull up with my pinky
and now what I could do once I get to eat every time I get to that a set of goit what I can do is go.
So that's another little lick that I'm going to teach you now that I can make up and always use when
I play.
So let me teach you the Lick Lick goes like this.
All right so I'm hitting the open A hammered on down the second period and then I'm playing that opened
string
now with my fingers still on this.
Now I'm going to hit it again
with my ring finger or the sixth string third fret opening opening
play for you.
OK.
And you see those different things you can do.
Sometimes I go sometimes I go
sometimes I just kind of hit the notes.
I can't stop them from reading by putting the right hand.
So there's different things you can do experiment with them.
I'm just showing you different possibilities to try to inspire creativity within you when you play stuff.
All right so again on that you made the
link one more time.
I'm going on when I get back to this though a pole bending ever so slightly
rather than I'm going
and again on the 6 6 string the same thing
you don't want to overdo it but you want to get a little
a little bit in there if you can if you're a total beginner.
This will be hard for you.
So these are just different possibilities that you can do.
OK.
So that's not possible.
Number Twos are possible.
Number one when you get to that one
possibility number two is
that after that there's this like an hour to show you alteration to that would be to play here.
Let me show you that.
So now I'm on the first major and I'm bearing down on the fourth third and second string.
Now what I'm going to do is I'm going to hit the No.
And a hammer from level nine I'm into it.
So it's Hammer.
So
hammer
that leads you back to the seat too.
So instead of going we're doing it here.
I do that pull up.
I'm actually aiming only for these two strings.
The second the third string in the fourth string.
I told you to hold in the second one.
Actually that one isn't as important we just need these two strings.
So the third string in the fourth string.
So if you hit the second string it's OK but the two are enough.
OK.
All right.
So let me show you endeavor Asian.
Let me just play through it one time and then I'm going to teach you this
kind of a little walking line.
All right.
So then play for us to go sing
and now the tricky part is hearing
it's really tricky to get because he fastened a little tip.
Are
with your ring finger only him for that one no time and the rest of the core by pleather of the court
after you got this done.
OK.
So that's kind of the trick here where the easier way is to go.
Hendrix did this.
He might have to play C and he might have looked back.
I'm actually not sure.
All right.
So let me you one other way that you could play that I did in the intro that I'm going to teach you
this this thing.
So here's one more way to go.
So Bass
what I'm doing is I'm playing hammering down and playing a bass
a bass and now I'm grabbing this kind of well a little like a small f shape and sliding to the G so
k so bass so small thing like the G.
And now what I would do is I'm going to slam down on the G with my pinky on the fifth string first fifth
first thing Fred.
So get in the car with a finger there cool off with lead paint you right after that.
So I came to practice that to build strength in the pinky.
Then as I take my ring finger slide to Fred and bear down on the third fourth and second third fourth
string so.
So that's
correct.
And that's actually D-CT.
I'm just playing a different bass on it.
It's kind of an inversion.
Don't worry about that.
So.
So once we slide from in here what we could do is take her pinky and hit lines.
So
and do to pull off fret third string
Garlett a pen.
So that is the same as this G shape.
And now we're going to hit it.
But now the some other thing you we're going to play the third string.
I've had some Halling
that's leading me back to the now here you can do either you can do.
After that you can do
OK.
So these are just kind of tons of different possibilities that you can use to play through with this
crazy chord progression.
And Hendrix played it different every time too.
So it's a really great one to just experience it.
So last thing in this lesson is this.
We're going to hit the third fret fifth string after that.
All right.
So it's hard it's with the stuff man but I'm doing it.
So we're hitting the third for fifth string.
All.
OK.
So
in my first three I'm going down to of it straight.
So all right.
I don't know how to play this and talk through it at the same time it's really hard.
I'm just going to play it really slowly and you're going to have to kind of just watch and try and play
along.
So
in
the
so that's
I can't talk I'm sorry I can't listen.
User use you will get it.
All right.
That's it.
Tons of ways to play through this chord progression.
Thanks so much for checking out this last if you like at least give me a thumbs up don't forget to hit
the subscribe button click on play.
Click it.
All right.
Please leave me and tell me where you live.
Of course.
Listen if you like.
Go on.
I love you.
All right.
See you soon.