Homemade food
following the principle of frugality
can transform the most mundane into the spectacular
From the ground, Wu Yegen shoulders back leaf mustard
When the leaf is fresh
it is bitter and astringent
To be a true delicacy
it needs time
to dry in the sun
fading the bright turquoise
Salinity stimulates the exudation of cellular juice
and kills harmful bacteria at the same time
so that the leaf mustard can ferment
in a secure environment
More than ten days later
leaf mustard turns over a new leaf
accepting the gentle baptism of the early spring sunshine
Dehydrate again
Aromatic substances concentrate and accumulate
In the early April of Shaoxing
the air smells of special fresh flavor
Then
leaf mustard has a new name
dry mustard
With dry mustard
My wife made several dishes
which were my daughter¡¯s favorite homemade delicacies
Besides pork with mustard
people in Shaoxing also make soups with dry muatard
In the hot water
dry mustard uncurls
the rich flavor
releases slowly
Cooking with bamboo shoots and shrimp
the liquor color is red and clear
These ingredients provide their own taste in the soup
Who cooks so well?
Thank her
Leaf mustard continues fermenting in the jar
the longer it ferments
the more mellow it is
In the Andes
a ridge of 4000 meters above sea level
a mystic ceremony of ancient Inca Empire
is performing
Sacrificing food and wine to the Earth Goddess
is an important cult before family party
Cooking food on land
is called ¡°pachamanca¡± by the local people
which means the earth pot
Potato, corn and sweet potato in the ground kettle
native to South America
are Incas¡¯ staple food
Sweet potatoes
are highly adaptable to edatope
Therefore, they are spread all over the world
and even influence the population distribution
Thank all the gods
Thank Mother Earth
for giving us rich Pachamanca
Around the 16th century
sweet potato across the ocean
came to China
Fujian Province is one of the earliest landing places
This rhizomatous plant
had solved several historical famines
and was planted across the country quickly
The sun is shining gloriously
Lin Chunyin does not dare to slack off
He want to catch every autumn sunshine
Today Chinese people eat sweet potato
not just for filling the stomach
I used to play this all the day when I was a kid
I never played it
Chunyin, just hit it twice
Well
Now we have so much sweet potatoes and liquid
Pick up the breed with a higher content of starch
Shredding
Soaking
Separating starch
Subsiding for a night
The starch caked
In Lin Chunyin¡¯s memory
When sweet potatoes are harvested
mother always makes such food with complex procedures
Even though he has already got married and settled down in Beijing
this food still appeals to him
This year Lin Chunyin decided to return home with friends
to learn this craft
Shall we cover it with cloth?
It will be thick after stirring
When sweet potato starch is heated
it will be charming translucent
It is flexible chewy, and mild sweet
that is a popular dessert
Steam thoroughly
and pour again
It needs 3 hours
when 15 layers are well done
After molding
starch cake weighs 18 kg
Drying in the shade and dehydrating gradually
the hardness of starch cake is appropriate
To be an easy cooked ingredient
it still needs some efforts
With the sunshine and wind
potato vermicelli dryed thoroughly
and got the final color and texture
Pure potato vermicelli
is tolerant
which can absorb all kinds of tastes easily
Cereus sinensis
also called garlic
can be used in stewing
With its thick juice
the intensity of its umami is triple that of crab
Potato vermicelli with super adsorption
can be cooked for a long time
so that each vermicelli can fully absorb the richness of Cereus sinensis
With fully pouring of lard oil
the level of rich taste has increased greatly
The Lins are also preparing dinner
With fresh vermicelli
seasonal seafood
a simple bowl of vermicelli soup is made
Sweet and delicious
Taste great
Taste of home
does not refer to a particular food
The whole family sit together around a table
which is a more true and complete taste of home
Someone wanders outside
and comes back to home
Someone is far away from family
and goes throughout the world
In the early morning, Li Geng leaves the work shed
He has not seen his family for more than 300 days
His workmate Zhang Jie also must rush to the construction site on time
Their construction site is located in the South American continent
16000 km from China
Within less than 40 years
more and more Chinese people work overseas
Nowadays, the number is over 10 million
In the Santa Elena water construction site
Li Geng communicates with the local people without any obstacles
The assistant zhang jie has also no problem
Humans have firm taste memory
especially for the vast majority of Chinese people
The local rice is a little hard
which is unacceptable
and they only have vegetables like tomatoes and onions
They seldom eat green vegetables
If we only eat green vegetables
they will say that Chinese people only eat grass