I booked Moby-Dick!
And all you have to do is probably
have dinner with her. She's a widow.
If you're holding onto your pills then
I think you still have not decided.
Unbelievable.
They don't show your fetus
hand on my fetus hand.
- So what did you think?
- It was embarrassing.
He just needs to
express himself,you said.
- Look at him!
- This is a reaction to pot.
I have an appointment. I'm
wondering if you can stand in for me.
- Like a free dinner?
- I do not negotiate with degenerates.
I am cutting you off.
- She wants to see me again,Ray.
- She said that?
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Sync:3P
Hung
Season 2 Episode 06
Okay,guys,why don't you
tell me why you're fighting.
How can I help you if I don't
know what the problem is?
What's going on at the house?
- Mom saw a beaver.
- She thought she did.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nobody else saw it,so you
draw your own conclusions.
Are you calling her a liar?
Well,where did it go? Beaverland?
- Guys.
- Maybe one of your fat friends ate the beaver.
Yeah,or maybe mom ate one of your
stupid scones and hallucinated it.
Guys,guys,knock it off.
What's up with you two?
You never used to
fight like this before.
Tell your mom she can borrow
my traps if she needs to.
- You tell her.
- Well,your mom and I...
Are not in the best place right now.
Because she's having a baby with Ronnie?
You guys are divorced. What do you care?
I don't. I'm just trying to be helpful.
Mom,I'm excited,I'm excited.
What do you want from me?
We need to celebrate life's victories.
Are you coming to my
dinner or not,Tanya?
Mom,look,I think it's great that
you're chair of cinema studies,
but,you know,I have a life too.
Uh,I have to go.
Hi,Frances.
Thank you so much for meeting me.
I'm,uh,so sorry.
What happened was not
right and not professional.
We don't bait and switch like at.
I promised you one thing and you got...
if you'll permit me,
I would like to reintroduce
you to Richard free of charge.
I'm not interested in Richard.
I understand.
I'd like to book Mike.
Mike?
You like Mike?
You guys had a good time?
Well,yes,we had a nice time
under the circumstances.
Mike was very considerate
and he has a very
attractive speaking voice.
I'm so happy to hear that.
So I would be willing to book him again.
That is if we could work
it out on a weekend basis.
I... a weekend basis?
Let's face it,Tanya,
your hourly rate is too high.
I want a flat rate.
Flat rate?
$1500 a weekend,
unlimited hours.
$1500?
that's fair.
I will call Mike and I will...
- I will let him know the details.
- Good.
I'd rather not talk money with...
it's odd,but I'd be embarrassed.
Somehow it's nicer to pretend.
Ray,Ray,we did it! We did it!
- We did it! We did it!
- What?
- We did it!
- Hey,will you put that away?
This is a neighborhood.
Where'd you get that?
Mike.
Frances is very taken with Mike.
Frances wants Mike to come back.
Ray. Ray,wait.
Seriously,look at this.
Ray,come on. Come on,Ray.
- Shit.
- I know,it's not what we planned.
It's not what we planned,but
it's a terrific turn of events.
So Frances paid all that money for Mike?
Yes,for the whole weekend.
Ray,she can't get enough of him.
So you... you go to Mike
and you talk to him for me.
And you make the introductions
and you explain to him that
I'm in charge of negotiations.
You just screw Lenore,Ray.
This is a whole new business model.
This is me and you and Mike.
Tanya,I need you to
give that money back.
- What?
- He likes her.
He won't even take the
500 bucks for the date.
He thinks it's about dinner
and being her companion.
Like a dating service. He's got
no idea about the rest of it.
Okay okay. So we go
to him and we ask him
and we see what he says.
He's a grown man. He can
make his own decisions.
I've known Mike for 15 years.
Not gonna do it.Okay?
You know,for the first time,
the guy's got a spring in his step.
Maybe they have a shot.
What?
Why do you want me to fail?
I don't want you to fail,Tanya.
I want us to succeed,okay?
Just not with Mike and not th Frances.
I know how hard you
worked on this whale,okay?
But we can find other...
How are we gonna get other clients
when you keep driving them away?
You find some reason
to sabotage them all.
I do not do that.I try hard.
Okay.
Look at this.
Just look at... look at this.
Um,this... this is what
Mike got after one night. Okay?
This is more than you ever
brought in in a whole week.
Okay? So what does he got,I'm
wondering,that you don't have?
Cut it out. I think maybe
he and Frances hit it off.
I mean,Mike got lucky.
- Obviously.
- Yeah,you're jealous.
You don't want Mike around
because you think he'll outperform you.
- Ridiculous.
- You can't stand to think
that somebody might be a
better lay than Ray Drecker.
Tanya,I never got a shot with her.
Remember me?
I am the guy who gets the crazy ones
and the married ones
and the pregnant ones.
Yeah,you do. Yeah,you do.
And where are all those
satisfied customers now?
Where is Molly? Where's
Claire?Where's Moby-Dick?
She's with Mike,Ray.
And me and you,we're with no one.
And I just think it's time
that we ask ourselves why.
Thank you,John. We will get back to you.
- Ron.
- One second,honey.
- I'm getting rid of the exterminator.
- What did he say?
So there's no beaver scat.
There's no other indicators.
Plus this isn't even
their natural habitat.
But I saw it,Ron.
There was a beaver sitting right there.
Beaver is dirty animal.
It carries giardiasis. Beaver fever.
I know what I saw,Ron.
Why won't you believe me?
I'd love to,but a very competent
man just told us otherwise.
- The beavers,they gnaw at foundation.
- We got it,ma.
Destroy property values.
Let's just see if this
beaver turns up again.
Ron,I am not bringing a baby
into a house full of beavers.
It's always something with you,Jess.
Today it's beavers,tomorrow
what... locusts?
It's not her fault you
have beaver problem.
Damn popcorn.
Frances met Mike and she
couldn't get enough of him.
Was I missing something?
What did he have that I didn't?
There you are.
- Hi.
- Where is she?
She's in the back reading room.
- Okay.
- Wait,Ray.
Look,I know we're acting
like everything's normal,
but I sense something is up.
Are you still mad at me about Jessica?
- Did you see her?
- I did.
Then I'm still mad about it.
Don't be,Ray.
I know you are having all these emotions
because she hired a
gigolo and almost got you.
But that's not my fault.
How was I supposed to know
Jessica is your ex-wife?
Look,I am her only friend,okay?
She needs me.
Why would I tell her about
us? Why would I do that?
I'm your pimp. I protect you.
I don't get why you're
being so suspicious.
Did Tanya put anti-Lenore
ideas in your head?
I'm gonna be late,Lenore.
Fine,she's back there.Second table to
the left,dark hair,red flowered dress.
Thank you.
- Richard?
- Hi.
Hi,I'm Liz.
You like libraries,huh?
Yeah,I love 'em.
And I figured,you know,I
don't know you so...
You,uh,want to walk around?
Yeah,sure.
Great.
I'm thinking we just talk right now.
What would you like to talk about?
About sex.
Well,say anything.
Right,um... the thing is,
I don't love sex.
Why not?
I don't understand what the deal is.
I... I mean,I'm normal.
Everything about me is normal.
It's just ever since I was a kid
I would see these women in movies
and they would be
screaming,"oh yes,oh yes,"
and sweating and fucking and loving it.
And for me sex is like not that.It's...
Maybe,uh...
You had the wrong lover.
Exactly. Maybe.
So I thought,you know,someone
who knows a lot about women,
someone who's a total stranger to me,
a white guy like you who's
not gonna know anyone I know,
might be good.
I mean,you are an expert,right?
Kinda.
So what do you think?
I think I'm the right man for the job.
Hey,Jess.So the kids said you
had a beaver running around.
Anyway,if you want i
still have those traps.
- He called me.
- Really?
Offered to help with the
beavers.I didn't call back.
Meanwhile,Ron does nothing.
I mean,maybe I should call him.
'Cause believe me,Ray
would be over in a flash.
Do you think he's still hot for you?
Who knows? I don't care.He's so...
Every time I look at him I
think,"that's over."That is over.
I can't."I can't go there."
But he's sexy,don't you think?
Sometimes.
But then at other times
he's just so stuck.
I know,in that burnt-out house.
Yeah,he can't get it together.
How did you know Ray's
house is burnt down?
What?
You just said Ray's burnt-out house?
Oh,'cause I ran into him.
You did?
Why didn't you tell me?
I know I should have,but...
Okay listen,Jess. I
got his phone number.
I feel bad. I like him.
You like him?
It's just I always date jerks,you know?
And he's like a real
guy. Like straight up.
You know?
If it bothers you I
won't take it further.
You're asking my permission to call him?
I swear I'll do whatever you want.
I don't want to hurt you.
Okay,I... call him.
I think you should call him.
You're single,he's
single.I mean,definitely.
Definitely. And do,you know,
whatever.
Thank you.
This is Ray.I lost my
old phone in the fire.
So make sure and leave your number.
Ray.
Hi. Sorry it's 2:00
in the morning but...
Those beaver traps
you were talking about,
could you bring them by tomorrow
and leave them out front?
Why? Why is it everybody all at
once?It's like there's all this crap.
And I never thought I'd
say this,but I think.
Ray might be deliberately
trying to sabotage me.
- Who's Ray?
- My prostitute.
Oh,right. That one ho that you share.
That I temporarily
share. Don't rub it in.
- Thank you,sir.
- I'm just fucking with you.
Thank you. Come on.
So should I give the money back or what?
- You're asking me?
- Well,no.
I mean,yeah. I mean,I can't keep
it.I'd be wracked with guilt.
- For how long?
- What do you mean?
For how long would you
be feeling guilty,huh?
For a minute? An hour? A month? A year?
- What?
- I don't know.
I've never taken anything
before.So how would I know?
Number one,you didn't take the cash.
You earned it. And number two,
there are worse things than guilt,girl.
Let me see this. She's cool.
I got ya.
Hey,come here. You like this?
- It would look good on you.
- Really?
It is sweet.
Hey,do you want this?
No,I can't afford it.
No,you don't got to afford it.
You just got to tell me do you want it?
You could have just left them.You
didn't need to ring the doorbell.
Yeah,you sure you don't need
help setting these things up?
Ronnie can do it.
I mean,he's... he's not home now.
But he's gonna be home any minute.
I'm not sure he believes me.
There's no lake so...
What do you think?
Well,if you saw a beaver
then you saw a beaver.
What's taking so long?
This is delicate business.
You said few minutes.
Well,I like my thumbs.
Your shirt's inside out.
So?
So you gonna leave it like
that or are you gonna fix it?
Are you happy?
Yeah.
It's nice of you to help.
Once an eagle scout
always an eagle scout.
You were never an eagle scout.
Clearly I got my
beaver trap merit badge.
- Better concentrate on this.
- Hi,Ron.
Ray just stopped by with some traps.
I thought I said I was
taking care of this.
- I know,but...
- I'm sorry,what is that thing?
This is your standard beaver trap.
It'll take care of your beaver problem.
I don't have a beaver problem.
Well,if you did,you
know,it's a clean kill.
Get those death traps off my property.
Ronnie,Ray was just trying to help.
What the hell?
You said to dismantle it.
That's how these things work.
Not these traps. These
traps,they're humane.
They do not kill the animal.
If you ever used those things before
you'd know that they malfunction,
misfire,break the beaver's legs.
That's not true.
Then you'd have to shoot the beaver
or hit it over the head with a shovel.
I'm going to ask you
one more time nicely,
please take those traps
back to your house.
Good luck.
He just showed up.
Lisa,how perfect.
From one chair to another.
Trust me,it's the only way you're
gonna keep your department in line.
Here,pass that down.
You are all so thoughtful.
Thank you. Anyone,more vino? Yes.
Wait,one more.
One more over here. One more.
Oh,Tanya.
- What is it?
- Open it.
Oh my goodness.
The pendant is diamond encrusted
and the chain is 18-karat gold.
Oh,it's so urban.
I love it.
Tanya,this is a lovely impulse.
Well,mom,thank you. I
know it's not your style,
but I thought you'd get a kick out of it
considering how much I paid for it.
The diamonds are real.
Okay,sweetheart.
I mean,I paid a lot,you know?
It's from money I earned at my job.
From your temp job.
No. Actually I've started a new business
venture and it's really quite successful.
The fortune cookies?
No,mom,that's lyric bread.
And that's not what I'm talking about.
This is,um,it's... it's kind of
a new twist on an old industry.
Have I heard of it?
If not yet,then you will.
Our brand recognition among Detroit
women is growing stronger every day.
I recently brought on
our most lucrative client.
Do you have a website?
Actually,Marvin,we don't.
But that's a really interesting idea.
Okay,Tanya,you have
to tell us what it is.
When Tanya was 10,
she told me that "The New Yorker"
wanted to publish her haiku.
- I sent it in.
- Darling,you're an adult now.
Why don't you return this? Put
the money towards your rent.
Listen,you know,I think
I need some more wine.
We're not going home,I'm
just warning you.
Whenever you're ready.
Oh wait,I got it. I got it. I'm paying.
Tanya,there's no need.
Let's see...$840,gratuity included.
Tanya,put that away.
You're acting very strange.
- And you're...
- Embarrassing myself?
I'm not embarrassing myself,mom.
I'm proud of myself. I'm passionate.
And for your information,I'm
not a temp anymore.
I've got a new job now and
honestly I'm rolling in it.
And the best part of it
is I'm following my dream.
I'm doing what all you fine
people are afraid to do.
Chair of cinema studies? Bullshit!
Mother,I'm a fucking baller,mom.
It's a cute gift. It's very creative.
- Is that okay?
- Yeah,so far so good.
Cool.
- How about that?
- Still pretty good.
You know,you can tell me if
something's not working for you.
Um,maybe a little less talking.
Right. Okay,I can do that.
Come on. Come on.
It's all right. It's okay.
You know what? I'm good.
What?
It's okay.
You don't have to finish.
You don't want to?
Sorry,I just...
I get kind of bored.
Wait,because you're...
you're giving up too easy.
No,seriously,Richard.
It's... everything's...
this happens all the time.
Usually I just fake it,but
we can just skip that part.
Okay.
How about...
why don't I go down on you?
That's usually a big hit.
Oh no.
Thanks anyway.
Come on,Liz,you can't just...
Richard,it's fine.
I want to try again. Come on.
You know what? Guys
always want to keep trying.
But I am paying for
it and I want to quit.
I'm a human ice cube.
God,what am I gonna do?
- What are you doing here?
- I have concerns,Ray.
You don't trust me anymore.
I never trusted you.
So how'd Liz go?
Oh,it was all right.
She's a work in progress.
I don't know.
You'll figure it out.
You're really fucking sexy,Ray.
That's why I'm a fan.
I believe in you.
And I believe in your dick.
Don't ever doubt yourself.
It's kind of chilly out here.
Aren't you gonna ask me in?
Come on,we need each other.
Let me in.
Jess...
if you say there was a beaver
then there's probably a beaver.
Thanks,Ron.
It means a lot to me.
His leg is broken.
Oh God.
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Sync:3P
Hung
Season 2 Episode 06