Aren't you both going?
Spencer got tickets for me and Ezra.
Please, just don't go tonight, okay?
I have a bad feeling about this date.
That feeling is jealousy.
They had a big opening
at the Philadelphia Art Museum.
You went last night?
- Why is he out of jail?
- He's out on bail.
Why don't you save us
the cost of a trial and drop dead?
You'll have to do more
if you wanna become captain.
Who said
I wanted to become captain?
- What the hell?
- I take care of things myself.
You remember
that phony your sister used to date?
- Lan Thomas?
- We partied that whole summer.
- He's the poster boy for preppy.
- Convincing, isn't he?
- You wanna give it back to your teacher?
- What is that?
Stopped Mrs. Montgomery
from getting to Philly.
- Who's this from?
- Paige.
She's trying to bribe her way
to becoming captain.
They're from the same place.
These two were purchased
by a Spencer Hastings.
Does that help, dear?
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Ah, it's gonna be you
and your brother tonight.
And, uh, he wants to order in
from Sausage Heaven.
Again? Seriously?
Dad, closest thing they have
to a vegetable is a paper plate.
Listen, just tell Mike
that it's your night to pick, okay?
Okay. So you're
definitely not eating with us?
Uh, no. No, I've got this thing.
Uh, and it's with the head of the
department, and dinner's included, so...
- Have a great day, sweetheart.
- Okay.
Oh, hey, Dad, I need your pledge
for the dance marathon.
The deadline's today.
Oh, right. That's right. Uh,
my checkbook is in my jacket in the hall.
- Did you find it?
- What?
Um...
Yeah.
- Great.
- Dad, what's this?
Well, that's a ticket, uh, for the museum.
Is it yours?
No, no, it's, uh... It's your mother's.
Uh, her car broke down, and she needed
to borrow mine to get there.
So she was at the museum
on Thursday night?
Yeah.
I mean, I think so.
Uh, you know, actually...
...you should really
just, uh, talk to your Mom about that.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
Is my chemistry book over there?
Uh, I don't see it.
It's probably in the room, Spence,
not the front yard.
What happened to the Cavanaughs'
mailbox? Somebody hit it?
It's not the first time.
And I'm sure it wasn't an accident.
Every time I come home, Toby's
out there cleaning up some new mess.
- And please don't say he deserves it.
- I wasn't gonna say that.
Is that it?
Oh, thanks.
Do you still think
that somebody framed him?
Toby?
Do we really wanna have
this fight right now?
I have to save up my energy
for swim practice.
We're not on different sides
anymore, Em.
I know what it feels like to have
somebody say you did something...
...when you know that you didn't.
Are you talking about the bracelets?
I had never seen
that lady before...
...and yet she had my name
written down on two sales receipts.
We should go. We're gonna be late.
I owe you an apology.
You believed that he was innocent
from day one...
...and I jumped down your throat.
I said some really heinous things
about Toby.
You should apologize to him, not me.
- Hey.
- Hey. Cute boots. New?
Hmm. Ish.
What is with this line?
Ugh, all the vending machines
are on lockdown.
Someone's been breaking into them
after hours and stealing food.
I heard this one kid say
the alarm went off at 3 a.m.
- The vending machines have alarms?
- The school.
Someone's been sneaking out of
the building in the middle of the night.
I mean, who'd wanna be here
any longer than they have to?
Hmm, well, I might.
Going home just got scary.
This was in my Dad's coat.
He said it's my Mom's...
...but I'm starting to wonder
if he was at the museum too.
Your dad? No, heh.
Why was he so twitchy when I asked?
I mean, if they were there
at the same night as me and Ezra...
Aria, you're just on a loop.
- It was a coincidence.
- Is it?
You don't think it's weird...
- ...that my mom had a ticket the same...
- Yes, a weird coincidence.
Um, can you get my coffee?
I'll be right back.
Um... Oh.
We need to talk.
You know that thing
you did with Mrs. Montgomery's car?
Well, just pretend
like it never happened, okay?
Don't talk about it, don't blog about it,
don't tweet about it. Clear?
Can I speak now?
Okay, if you must,
but it's really annoying.
- The way I see it, you owe me.
- For what?
For doing that thing that I can't talk,
blog, or tweet about.
Was there a second watch?
Was anyone else keeping time?
It was a tie, Paige.
You and Emily tied.
So, what's gonna happen?
Who gets to anchor?
Can't make that decision yet.
All right, listen up, Sharks.
We'll meet tomorrow morning,
same place, same time...
...and have ourselves a little swim-off.
So I guess
we'll just figure this out tomorrow.
You figure it out. I need to win.
We should have met up earlier.
Aria.
- Hi, sweetie.
- Hey, Mom.
- Your ears must've been burning.
- Why?
I was just talking to the principal
about you and Mr. Fitz.
Why?
Well, he wants to take your class to
New York to see the Fitzgerald show...
...but the principal told him
there was no money.
- Do you wanna walk with me?
- Sure.
What's up?
So Dad wrote me a check this morning
for the dance marathon.
Okay.
And when I got to his checkbook...
...I found the ticket
that was yours to the museum.
I guess it was in Dad's car.
You didn't mention
you borrowed his car.
Oh, no, well, I didn't think I had to.
Why, did you have it
on reserve for the night?
No, I'm just confused.
Did you go to that exhibit or not?
Well, to be perfectly honest, no.
I skipped it, and I went out
to a really nice dinner instead.
- By yourself?
- No, uh, I was with a friend.
I gotta get to class.
I'll see you later.
Are you reading that fast
or fanning yourself?
What?
Um, sorry.
Where are you going?
Um, I left my lip gloss in the history stack.
Gotta find it, heh.
- What do you want?
- I'm calling in your debt.
Two losers just bailed on what they
owe me and I need some cash.
So, what do you want me to do?
Bust their kneecaps?
I don't want an enforcer. I want a date.
Heh, okay, absolutely not.
You're the homecoming queen,
Hanna.
You got a rep around here.
I need to borrow some cred.
- What are you gonna do with it?
- I need customers. With money.
Who need to know they can trust me.
- Yeah, well, they can't.
- They can if I'm with you.
So you got a hot party
tomorrow night?
I have a swim meet.
You can fit all of that under a cap?
Okay, I'm not swimming, freak.
I'm cheering on a friend.
Well, what is the point of a swim-off?
Why would the coach pit you
against each other before a meet?
She's using our combined times
to choose anchor...
...and right now, we're tied.
Well, you'll change that.
Maybe not. She wants it more.
Emily, you want it more...
...and it is okay to admit that.
You know who that's for, don't you?
Toby?
What are you doing?
I might be interested.
- Spencer, don't. You can't.
- Why not?
You'd be going there
for the wrong reason.
What if the same person
who gave my name to the bead lady...
...is the one who framed Toby?
What if that was A?
Can't you find that out
some other way?
Who else knows what he knows?
If I can get him to talk then...
You won't even get him to look at you.
He doesn't trust us.
He doesn't trust anyone anymore.
Maybe, but if I have one piece
of the puzzle and he has another...
...then we can put it together
and maybe help each other.
Hey. You're a little early.
I just wanted to tell you
I'm not coming to practice today.
- Why not?
- I have another commitment.
Why don't you come in?
Close the door.
- I can't stay. I'm...
- No, come in.
What are you trying to pull?
You gonna tell your parents...
...you can't stand me
so you're quitting the team?
I'm not quitting.
- I just have this other thing.
- Yeah, you can't avoid me.
- I live in your backyard.
- Well, this isn't about you. I'm...
I'm too concentrated in athletics.
It doesn't look good
on college applications.
So I just need to balance out
my schedule.
- Knock, knock.
- Hey.
Sorry to interrupt.
- I thought you had a marketing seminar.
- Oh, the professor cancelled.
I brought the tile samples.
The contractor needs a decision.
- Oh, great.
- Bye.
- I think your sister's quitting the team.
- Why?
I'm not quitting the team.
I'm just doing some tutoring.
- Well, anyone in particular?
- Toby Cavanaugh.
- What?
I signed up to help him
with his French.
I can't believe the school would
let anyone near him.
- Why are you doing this?
- I already told you.
Uh, what is this really about? That kid
murdered one of your best friends.
Don't tell me you're falling
for that martyr crap.
You can't believe
a thing that creep says.
Well, Toby Cavanaugh
hasn't cornered the market on lying.
I better go.
Hi.
I noticed this was on the ground
as I was walking up.
Wait. I'm here to tutor you.
Someone from the school
called to tell you, didn't they?
- Why you?
- Because I'm an AP French.
And I volunteered.
I have all your assignments together.
I worked out a schedule
for the rest of the semester.
If we meet for three times a week,
we can...
Here. You can't come in.
- Jenna's home.
- Okay.
Well, is there somewhere else
we can go?
I can't go somewhere else.
Well, will Jenna mind
if we sit out here on the porch?
Don't think about it.
It'll make you crazy.
How am I supposed
to not think about it? It's too freaky.
- Lf my Mom's car hadn't stalled...
- Well, it did.
Don't look a gift card in the mouth.
The universe gave you a pass.
Hmm. That's not the universe I know.
Look, it all worked out, okay?
And that's what counts.
Maybe the universe got a little help
from someone.
- Someone with really good intentions.
- Shh.
That's great. I can pick you up.
I can find you in the dark.
I've done it before, heh.
Okay, I'll see you soon. Bye.
Hey. So you're not going to
that department dinner anymore?
Oh, no. No.
Was that Mom you were talking to?
Uh, no, no, no, it wasn't.
Uh, so you sure you guys
are gonna be okay here alone tonight?
- Sure.
- Okay.
Okay, look, Aria,
even if it wasn't the universe...
Shh.
I'm just saying if it's not a coincidence,
then maybe...
- Come on.
- Where are we going?
- To follow my dad.
- Where?
- Lf I knew, we wouldn't have to.
- Aria...
Han, my Dad's about to have dinner
with somebody in the dark. Move it.
I, uh...
I brought you something.
L'Attrape-Coeurs.
The Heart Catcher?
It's Catcher in the Rye.
I guess there's no literal translation.
But it helps to read a book
that you already know in English.
How do you know I've read it?
I saw you once...
...at the Apple Rose Grille.
You were reading it.
What are you doing here?
Uh, Mr. Carinci wants you
to review the conditional tense.
- And the workbook has...
- What do you want?
What makes you think
that I want something?
Because you never do anything
without a reason.
Did Emily tell you that?
Nobody had to tell me that.
I think maybe you're being framed.
What changed your mind?
I think somebody might be trying
to do the same thing to me.
Maybe the same person.
How's that feel?
Not good.
Scary.
Why would somebody go after you?
What makes you so important?
I don't know.
Maybe you know something
you're not supposed to know.
Every time I think I know something...
...I get the rug pulled out from under me
and I end up on my ass.
I'm sorry...
...for what I said about you...
...and what I thought.
The sweater with Alison's blood...
...you said that you gave it to her
that night?
I did.
And then she got into a car.
With some guy,
I couldn't see who it was.
I'm not supposed to talk about this.
Do you know how the sweater
could've gotten back into your house?
Uh, I have to go.
- Oh.
- Thanks. For the book.
Yeah, you're welcome.
What are your thoughts
on genetic modification?
Aren't scientists playing God?
And how will it affect human health
in the long term?
So I'm against it.
He's different.
- How?
- I meant...
...he's different
than I thought he would be.
"How have humans altered the genomes
of species for thousands of years?"
Through artificial selection.
There's something about him that's...
I don't know.
Wow. A question Spencer Hastings
can't answer.
Interesting.
It's not that interesting.
- Am I finished with your homework?
- You are.
Thank you.
I keep trying to find a connection.
To Toby?
To Alison and Toby.
Me and Toby.
We're pretty sure
he didn't do it, right?
And yet somebody found a way
to make him look extremely guilty.
Spence, you can't figure all that out
sitting on his porch, conjugating verbs.
Well, you don't know
what those verbs are.
If he didn't tell you the first time,
he probably can't.
Are you sure
he even wants you to come back?
Yeah.
I think he does.
Why is my dad
walking into our high school?
Okay, weird.
Not really.
Think about it. He's probably
just going to see your mom.
Eh, that's ridiculous.
People lie, Aria.
I mean, hello.
Okay, what are they doing?
- Call your mother.
- Huh?
Right now. Call your mom.
ELLA Hi, Aria,
honey. I was just thinking about you.
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah.
Why wouldn't it be okay?
Uh, I didn't mean to suggest
that everything wasn't okay.
I was just, you know,
asking, checking, wondering...
...like moms do.
Where are you?
Home.
Shh. Shh. Shh.
Where are you?
Home.
Okay, so everything's okay, then?
- Yeah.
- Okay, I'll talk to you later, sweetie. Bye.
ARIA
Bye.
Okay, well, she says she's home.
Do you believe her?
I don't know.
Okay, what are you doing?
Tsk, that's not good.
- Mm. What? You used to like it.
- No, no, not that, this.
The lying, the sneaking around.
I feel like a teenager.
Yeah, it's fun, isn't it?
Listen, we should just tell the kids.
We can't. We can't tell them
until we know what this is.
Ugh, okay, I think I got everything.
Let's go.
Watch out for that.
Oh, my God, my parents are having
an affair with each other.
Hanna.
- What are you doing?
- Come up here.
Hurry.
What are you looking at?
This.
Someone sending a bunch of texts?
Spencer's laptop disappearing?
Our lockers broken into?
I mean, all this stuff happens at school.
This is A.
Let's just get out of here. Come on.
- Hanna, you're taking that?
- Yes. A owes me.
Hospital bills. Pain and suffering.
Tire marks on my cleavage.
It's nothing.
The lights are probably on a timer.
We should go.
Come on.
Caleb?
How's your eye? Any better?
Still burning. Ugh, you want a sharp stick
for the other one?
Hey, you know what?
It was just hair spray. It was light hold.
What were you doing in there?
I'm sort of, um...
I'm crashing here.
- You are? Why?
- What do you care?
Don't snap at her like that.
I have more.
Fire away.
Just give me my money back first.
I mean,
where do your parents think you are?
My foster parents don't care where I am
as long as they keep getting their checks.
Wait, I thought all that stuff
about the social worker was a joke.
Believe me,
my social worker is a joke...
...but, yeah, I do have one.
This is crazy.
You can't keep staying here.
Why? There's hot water,
vending machines...
...the principal's couch
is comfortable.
Well, they know
someone was here last night.
Hmm, yeah.
I got sloppy.
- Where are you going?
- Grab some dinner, then back to bed.
You know your way out, right?
Paige?
Are you okay?
No.
What happened?
You have every reason to hate me.
I don't even know why I'm here.
I don't hate you.
I would.
I do.
Don't say that.
I'm sorry, Emily.
I just wanted you to know that.
Wait, Paige.
Morning, Sharks.
How we all doing today?
- Ready to swim, coach.
- I'm sorry, I can't hear you.
SWIMMERS
Ready to swim, coach!
That's what I'm talking about.
It's our last practice before
this afternoon's big meet...
...so let's make it a good one.
Emily, there's not gonna be
a swim-off.
I just got word
that Paige will not be joining us.
- Why not?
- She had an accident...
...while riding her bike last night.
She's just a little banged-up.
She'll be back swimming in no time.
Okay, ladies, in the water, in the water.
Come on.
You're late. Let's go in.
Wait. Can we talk about last night?
What is there to talk about?
Uh, the fact that you're hiding out
in the AV closet until graduation.
What's your plan?
Do you wanna play guidance counselor
or do you wanna pay off your debt?
I'm cashing in on that favor.
Point out the kids
who have money to burn.
Fine. I'll trade you.
One name for one answer.
- Oh, hey, Bridget.
- Hey, Hanna.
- You know my friend Caleb, right?
- Sort of.
Hey.
Bridget Wu.
Total party girl.
Bring her a bottle of something strong
and she's your new best friend.
Where are you from?
- A lot of places.
- Okay, I gave details.
Seattle, Salt Lake, Denver,
Chicago and here. Your turn.
Lindsey Hoover.
Don't let the Jesus sandals fool you.
She's got cash.
- Her grandfather invented the stapler.
- Nice.
Wanna get tight with her?
Grow a hipster stache
and start talking about the Man.
Why don't you report
your foster parents?
To who? My social worker?
I've had four in the last six months.
They can't remember my name.
The last one called me Calvin.
When's the last time
you saw your real parents?
It's gonna take a lot more than names
to hear about them.
Truce. Got you a button.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
I need to be super rah-rah.
Now that I'm the coach's wife, heh.
It's a swim meet.
It's not even his sport.
Well, what's yours,
brother-in-law bashing?
- What's going on between you and lan?
- Why don't you ask him?
Something wrong with that picture?
I see my husband buying us hot dogs.
And I see you going out of your way
to humiliate him.
What was that lying crack about?
He does nothing but try.
When are you gonna give him a break?
When I figure out
why he rushed back to Rosewood...
- ...and rushed into proposing to you.
- You've got it wrong. I proposed.
I wanted to elope.
You have a problem with my marriage,
take it up with me, not him.
Well, him is the problem.
He's not been entirely honest with you.
And I am worried about you.
About what?
You have to ask him about Alison.
About what happened the summer
that she was killed.
Heh, you really are too much.
Did Toby Cavanaugh
put that idea in your head?
Hey. Sorry I took so long, they were
out of the, uh, spicy mustard you like.
- Did I miss something, or...?
- No. We were just talking about Alison.
Lan, I'll meet you inside.
Okay.
Look. I already lost one relationship
because of you.
You will not ruin my marriage too.
- Melissa?
- Coming.
When's Emily gonna jump in?
She's the anchor. She swims last
because she's the fastest.
Remind me. Which one's Lindsay
and which one's Bridget.
Bridget's the one
drinking from her purse.
Thanks. I'll be right back.
Come on, come on, come on!
Why are we sitting with Caleb?
Why not?
Hanna, I like stray dogs too,
but sometimes they bite.
Okay, well he's had his shots.
- Go, Emily!
- She's not swimming yet.
Come on.
Go, Emily! Go!
Um, you know what?
I'm gonna take the long way home.
- Okay, I'll see you later.
- Okay.
What's this?
My eviction notice.
I'm sorry.
- You know that I didn't tell anyone...
- I didn't go there.
Well, maybe it's for the best.
I mean, the place had small closets.
Hated that shirt, anyway.
Consider your debt paid.
Have a good day.
- Hey, if you need a place to stay...
- No, thanks.
Your mom starts asking questions,
someone calls Social Services...
...and it's just... It's a big mess, heh.
Wait.
There's an old couch in my basement.
My mom will never know.
Hanna.
Hey. God, here you are.
You're not gonna believe
what the sick freak did now.
- What are you talking about?
- Look.
I have to say, A is smart
trying to pit us against each other.
- Yeah, Aria, um, you know l...
- I mean, it's relentless.
Every time we shut a door,
A kicks open a window.
- I don't even know...
- I gave your Mom the museum ticket.
What?
- Why would you do that?
- A made me do it.
A has something on me and l...
A has something on all of us, Hanna...
...but there's nothing
that A would threaten me with...
...that would make me do that to you.
You're my best friend.
I know, and as soon as I put that ticket
in your mom's mailbox...
...I did everything I could to undo it.
- The reason your Mom didn't get to the...
- Stop talking.
There's nothing you could say that
would change the way I feel right now.
You okay?
You didn't return any of my calls.
I'm fine.
It's nothing.
I didn't know what to say.
I was riding home on my bike
and totally wiped out.
What were you thinking about?
How easy things would be
if I wiped out.
I'm kind of done with swimming.
Yeah, I used to feel that way.
Obviously, you got over it.
How did you get over it?
I started swimming for myself.
I quit trying be better than everyone
on the team and I just relaxed.
Sounds fun.
When's the last time
you swam for fun?
- Hey.
- Hi.
I got your message,
but I didn't totally understand.
This isn't going to work. Here.
Take it back.
I came here because I thought
that we could help each other.
We can't.
Just take it and go.
- Question.
- What's up?
Um, the towels in the bathroom?
Are they like, the fancy
people-are-coming-over towels?
No, you can use them.
I don't have to.
I can shake off and air dry.
Please don't.
What's going on?
You want me to leave?
It's not about you.
Aria's really...
...really mad at me.
You know that thing
I told you not to leak?
She found out anyway?
She's never gonna speak to me again.
You don't have to sit here and listen
to this. Just go take your shower.
It can wait.
- Good night.
- Wait, Spencer.
- Can we talk? About earlier?
- No.
It's late and I'm tired.
I know about you and lan.
He told me everything. The thing
you two had when we were broken up.
I can't hold that against you.
Did he tell you anything else
about that summer?
Whatever it is you're holding onto,
it's got to stop.
- I think he's dangerous.
- And I think you need help.
You keep wanting what I have.
- You know what, Melissa? It was...
- Spencer, I don't want to fight.
I realize I lost my temper earlier
and I'm sorry.
I've been
a little hormonal lately and...
I guess I should tell you...
Tell me what?
We're pregnant.
This is where you say
congratulations.
Good night, sis.
MAN
Learning French can be a fun activity...
...for families, friends,
civic groups or clubs.
By listening to these long-playing,
hi-fidelity records...
...you can speak fluently
in as little as six weeks.
We're going to start with the French
verb etre, which means "to be".
Ready? Let's begin.
I am.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org