Lovely. Our test
is a complete success.
We may proceed as planned.
Agreed. But we've operated
in shadow for too long.
Time for the Injustice League
to step into the light.
Admit it, you can't turn away.
Ha ha ha!
Sync and correction by Mlmlte | Corrected to 720p by Darkidan
www.addic7ed.com
You know they're a couple, right?
I believe I knew before they did.
- Do we tell them?
- It's not our place.
So if Zatara is our
babysitter of the week,
why's he still here?
And why's he eating my snacks?
Recognize Batman.
0-2.
Computer, national news.
The initial attack was short-lived,
but Metropolis was only granted
a short reprieve.
And despite the intervention
of Superman and the Justice League,
there seems to be no end in sight.
Should we get out there?
No. The League will soon have
the situation under control.
That's not why I'm here.
According to your Intel,
Sportsmaster supplied Cadmus'
blockbuster formula to Kobra.
Who combined it with Bane's venom
to create Kobra venom.
Which the brain used
to create his animal army.
And upgrade wolf.
The brain also used inhibitor collars
like the ones at the penitentiary.
Batman, is it possible that plant
thing's on Kobra venom, too?
I had Green Lantern run
a spot analysis.
Divine cellulose does contain trace
amounts of a Kobra venom variant.
These cannot be coincidences,
unrelated criminals are cooperating
with one another worldwide.
Exactly.
It's now clear our enemies
have formed some kind of secret
society of super villains.
The attack on Metropolis
is only the beginning.
You got that right.
Plant creatures have sprouted
in Gotham city,
Paris, Star City, Taipei...
[Static]
- Dude.
- It's not me.
Someone's cutting in
the satellite signal.
All satellite signals.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we interrupt your
regularly scheduled mayhem
to bring you this
important announcement...
From the Injustice League.
Ha ha ha!
We are responsible for
the attacks on your cities.
If you wish to save them,
a ransom of 10 billion
American dollars
is required.
Delivery instructions have been sent
to the United Nations.
There is no time limit.
But the longer
your governments wait...
The more we get to have our jollies.
Ha ha ha!
[Static]
Roger that, Aquaman.
The UN will prepare
the ransom as a fallback,
but it won't come to that.
[Video rewinding]
Count Vertigo, The Joker,
Poison Ivy, Ultra-Humanite,
Atomic Skull, Black Atom,
Wotan. 7 heavy hitters.
Probably behind everyone
and everything we've faced.
There's your secret society.
Not so secret anymore.
Perhaps after India they realized
we would deduce the truth
and saw no point
in hiding any longer.
Yeah.
That was their mistake.
Right now I say we go
kick some plant creature butt.
The Justice League
will handle the plants.
I have a different job for this team.
Oh, man. Uhh!
With the plants attacking so
many locations simultaneously,
there must be a central
control system.
Your mission is to destroy it.
You realize what you're
really asking them to do.
They're ready.
Ready?
Ready for what?
Ow!
Will you cut that...
Hello, Wally.
If the big guns are fighting plants,
who do you think we'll be fighting?
I don't know.
I guess we'll...
Ohh.
Well, Batman, I trust you're correct.
I trust you can locate the enemy.
Indeed. Wotan's informants
suggest sorcery
is part of how the plants
are controlled.
Robin, if you will provide
a holo-map,
I'll search for signs of
concentrated sorcerous activity.
[Speaking foreign language]
There. That is where you will find
the Injustice League's
central control system.
Coordinates locked in.
The Louisiana bayou.
We are on our way.
Captain Marvel.
For this plan to succeed,
the entire Justice League must be
seen fighting the plant creatures.
You, Zatara, and I
are needed elsewhere.
[People screaming]
Uhh!
[Speaking foreign language]
Aah!
[Laughter]
Ha ha ha!
Kobra venom's got nothing
on good old Joker venom.
Both work well in concept.
Yes, but we're putting
considerable strain on my baby.
[Buzzing]
[Speaking foreign language]
We will keep her
healthy and safe, Ivy.
But she requires more power.
Skull!
Stunning what a little
teamwork can accomplish.
[Alarm sounds]
Intruder alert.
What's in the duffel?
Plan "B."
- Ugh.
- You all right?
Dizzy.
Martians get airsick?
She does look a bit
greener than usual.
Not me, her.
I feel fine.
Not her, the bioship.
She's trying to shield us, but...
[Electrical crackling]
There it is, Atom. Go.
- Aah!
[All groaning]
Uhh!
He's hurting her.
No. No way I'm nearly drowning
3 missions in a row.
Wow. Uh, thanks.
M'gann, we need to get out.
Open a hatch.
Hello, M'gann.
Of course.
Out. Everyone out.
[Gasps]
[Panting]
She's in shock.
She'll need time to recover.
[All scream]
Vertigo.
Count Vertigo to you, peasant.
Uhh!
Robin, Miss Martian, disappear.
We will keep them busy.
You two fulfill
the mission objective.
- [Gasps]
- Uhh!
[Growling]
[Muffled screams]
[Alarm sounding]
[All shouting]
[Screeches]
Poor heroes.
Nothing they do is quite enough.
Ain't it grand?
Ha ha ha!
And impressive
how you simultaneous juggle
multiple scenarios.
I've had practice...
Juggling my multiple personalities.
Ha ha ha!
School's out!
[Children screaming]
2 are missing.
I blocked contact
with Aqualad and the others.
- Should we...
- Sorry, that's not the gig.
This is. The Injustice League
central control system.
Looks like that plant
is acting as an antenna
to control the other
plants worldwide.
Well, hello.
[Both grunting]
And good-bye.
Sorry, Boy Wonder.
I'm putting an end to your
little reconnaissance mission.
Hyah!
With so much power at my fingertips,
some might call me a control freak.
Others, just a freak.
Either works for me.
Ha ha ha!
[Plant screeching]
[Speaking foreign language]
[Grunting]
Aah!
[Groans]
They awaken.
You're certain this will hold them?
The cage is impenetrable.
Even the Superboy has
no chance of escaping.
You are not the only one trained
in the mystic arts, Wotan.
[Grunts]
Please, Atlantian,
do not pretend you're in my League.
[Grunting]
Robin, she's made contact.
Artemis?
No.
[All grunt]
Uhh!
Not me.
Stop those delinquents.
I hate monkeys.
Aah!
[Crackling]
Ahh.
I feel naked.
And not in a fun way.
We will make our own fun,
as we have been trained.
Maneuver 7.
Huh!
[Groans]
Ahh!
[Splash]
Where are Robin and the Martian?
[Growls]
[Grunting]
[Gasps]
My baby.
[Rapid beeping]
[Loud beep]
[Plant screeches]
Uhh!
Timber.
[Crackling]
Aah!
Children. Children foiled our plan.
Inconceivable.
Unacceptable.
Retributionable.
That last one might not be a word.
So sue me.
Kill them.
Kill them all.
[Gasps]
[Growls]
Uhh!
[Gasping]
[Groans]
Leave her alone. Uhh!
Enough!
Plan "B."
The helmet of Fate.
[Splash]
No, Aqualad, don't.
[Groans]
Oh, dude.
Wotan, you are mine.
Uhh!
Wonderboy, you are mine.
Ha ha ha!
Always wanted to carve this bird.
[Speaking foreign language]
Wotan has prepared for your return.
I can't see you, Martian,
but perhaps I'll hear you scream.
And perhaps I can be
of some assistance.
Hey, that's my souvenir.
Hold still.
[Growls]
- Aah!
- Artemis!
Surrender, sorcerer!
You cannot hope to defeat
our lord of order.
Aah!
I can defeat you, and I will.
[Speaking foreign language]
Not tonight, Wotan.
Uhh! Ha!
It's over.
There will be another day.
Another day?
Another day!
There will be another day?
Not for any of us.
Ha ha ha!
Joker made spores.
Don't breathe.
Fear not.
Fate has intervened.
What were you thinking?
How could you let him
put on the helmet?
Nabu will never release him now.
Kaldur will be trapped
inside Dr. Fate forever.
Nabu let you go?
He almost did not,
but your friend Kent
was most helpful.
He says hello.
We're done here.
The super villain secret society
has been neutralized.
As for your performance,
it was satisfactory.
Impressive.
The plant creatures have proven their
usefulness as potential weapons.
More importantly,
the so-called heroes
now believe our secret society
has been revealed
and crushed.
With the Injustice League
serving as our proxies,
we are once again free
to operate with impunity.
Sync and correction by Mlmlte
www.addic7ed.com
And shadows still conceal our light.
www.tvsubtitles.net