SIREN WAILS
Octonauts, to your stations!
Barnacles! Kwazii! Peso!
- Explore!
- Rescue!
- Protect!
Octonauts!
The Octonauts and the Enormous Elephant Seal.
Just look at these anemone, Peso!
They're so colourful. Each one looks like a flower or a...
A monster! Argh!
Oh. It's not a monster. That's an elephant seal.
A very large seal with a great big nose.
Like an elephant. SEAL SNORES
Is he snoring?
Elephant seals sometimes do sleep in the water.
I think something's wrong with his skin.
He's moulting - losing his old skin so a new layer can grow in.
See?
- Does that hurt him?
- Not at all.
Moulting is perfectly normal for elephant seals.
It's the same as when you grow too big for your clothes
and need new ones that fit better.
Elephant seals are supposed to moult on the beach, where it's warm.
Moulting in the cold water will make him ill.
Oh, no! He's nowhere near a beach.
Shellington, we have to help him!
Captain, we have an elephant seal emergency.
We need to bring him to the Octopod.
And he's really huge!
- SEAL SNORES
- And loud.
We have to move him, but he'll never fit into the GUP-E.
Hold tight. We're on our way. Sound the Octo alert.
- SIREN WAILS
- Octonauts, to the launch bay!
Tweak, we need to tow an elephant seal to the Octopod right away.
The GUP-C's ready to go, Cap'n. I've added an extra-strong towline.
- Good thinking. Kwazii, you're with me.
- Yiaow!
Tweak, open the Octo hatch.
Right away, Cap'n.
Shiver whiskers! He is huge!
Let's get him to safety.
HE GRUNTS
We've got him, Peso. Let's go.
- SEAL SNORES
- Through this door.
THEY GRUNT
Easy does it.
Argh!
There you go. Perfect.
Ooo! Whoa!
THUD! Oh!
SEAL SNORES
Phew! He's OK!
But, boy, does he snore!
SNORING ECHOES
Ah!
- Huh?
- Ah!
Peso, how's your patient?
His temperature is perfect.
As soon as he regrows his skin and hair, he'll be as good as new.
SEAL SNORES
- He's awake!
- Where am I?
You were moulting in the water. We didn't want you to get poorly,
so we brought you back to our ship, the Octopod.
Thanks for helping me.
The name's Leon.
I can't wait to get to the beach
and see my friends and family and...
Huh? Ooo! Oof!
I don't think you're ready to move yet, Leon.
Where is your beach? We'd be happy to take you there.
Well,... it's a beach.
HE YAWNS
With lots of moulting elephant seals like me on it.
Oh, boy! The whole thing makes me
really, really, really tired.
THUD!
He needs to rest while he finishes growing his new skin, Captain.
In the meantime, we'll look for a beach with elephant seals on it.
Activating Octo scope!
No elephant seals on this beach.
HE SNORES
Ah! We've been searching for Leon's beach for days!
We'll just have to try again tomorrow.
Now, let's get some sleep.
SNORING
MUSIC PLAYS
HE BARKS
BARKING ECHOES
Yiaow!
- Rrrr!
- MUSIC PLAYS
Are you alright, Leon?
I feel great!
And I'm looking good.
Check out my nice new skin and fur.
You've finished all your moulting? Congratulations!
- Chest bump!
- Whoa! Oh!
Oh. Sorry. I didn't mean to knock you over with that.
Oh. Not to worry. I'm fine.
I'm just excited to get to the beach
and play with all the other elephant seals!
Well, I'm afraid we haven't found your beach quite yet.
You haven't? But this is a special time
when all of us wake up and play games.
And I'm missing out on all the fun.
Don't worry. We'll find your beach.
And while we're looking, we can have fun here on the Octopod, too.
We can? Can we play some elephant seal games?
You know, like we do on the beach?
I'd love to. I'll show you the gamesroom in the morning.
OK. Let's start with one of my favourite games - wrestling!
- Wrestling?
- Yeah.
Elephant seals love to wrestle! Flipper to flipper?
OK. Flipper to flipper.
Whoa!
OK. We'll make it two flippers against one.
On the count of three.
One,... two,... three.
Oh! Ooo! Oh!
- Phew!
- Sorry about that.
Sometimes I forget how strong I am.
Oh, not to worry. I'm fine.
But maybe we should try a different game.
Mm. How about a race?
You're on. To the hallway!
- OK. I'll give you a head start.
- Thanks.
Ready? Steady? Go!
PESO PANTS
RUMBLING
THEY PANT
O-h-h-h-h-h-h-h-h!
Not to worry. I'm fine.
Whoa! Whoa!
RUMBLING
Whoa! Oof! Whoa!
Leon?
- Look out!
- THEY GASP
- Whoa! Oof!
- Oh! Oof!
Kwazii! On the beach! Elephant seals!
And not a moment too soon, eh, Captain?
THEY GIBBER Are you ok?
I'm great! This is even more fun than the beach! Let's do it again!
Attention, Octonauts!
We have found a beach full of elephant seals.
To the launch bay!
- Chest bump!
- To the launch bay.
Leon? Aren't you coming?
Um,... sure. I suppose.
Peso? Into the GUP.
Open the Octo hatch, Tweak.
- You got it, Cap'n.
- Wait a second!
I'm having so much fun here with you,
I don't want to leave now.
Sorry, Leon. The Octopod's just not big enough for an elephant seal.
The other elephant seals must miss you.
But I'll miss you guys.
KWAZII WHISPERS
How about if we race you to the beach?
A race? You're on!
He's fast!
Elephant seals are strong swimmers.
I won the race! Yeah!
Hey, Leon! You found us!
We were so worried about you.
Come on, let's play!
See? They really missed you.
I never would've made it here if you hadn't rescued me. Chest bump?
Er,... how about a hug this time?
Aw, shucks!
THEY LAUGH
更多产品请咨询QQ：799562590