it's a state where
centuries of american history
are etched in the land.
from remains of a mysterious
serpent mound...
to a majestic river
crossed by thousands seeking
freedom from slavery.
ohio.
it may just be
a stopping-off point
for some
on their long migrations...
but it's also home to many
who've played big roles
in america's history.
from two brothers
whose dreams of flight
made ohio the birthplace
of aviation...
to a young boy
whose fascination with the stars
propelled him to the moon.
and a talented young runner who
broke through the racial divide,
managing to beat hitler
and win olympic gold.
ohio is a powerhouse
of industry...
once home to the rubber capital
of the world.
here on the shores
of one of america's great lakes,
loyalty to hometown heroes
is fierce.
when one local sports hero
abandoned his fans,
he was labeled
a traitor for life.
it's a place where rock and roll
icons enter the hall of fame...
and where a monument
to a great naval victory
towers over the land.
it's easy to see why
this northern state is called
"the heart of it all."
this is ohio.
when october arrives
in southern ohio,
migrating birds take to the air
and head south,
over hocking hills,
one of the state's
most majestic landscapes.
sandstone cliffs
and remote ravines
hide beneath the sugar maples,
sycamores, and butternut trees.
here, autumn takes center stage,
blanketing the hills
in red, green, and gold.
but on this october day,
another annual spectacle
is giving nature
a run for its money.
it's homecoming week
at ohio university,
in the town of athens.
students and alumni
line the streets
to celebrate a tradition
that goes back 90 years.
a parade is the main event,
with colorful floats,
handmade banners,
and costumed dancers.
they wind their way
through athens' streets
before stopping to perform
for a panel of judges.
every year
one group of performers
is particularly impressive,
especially from the air.
the ohio university band,
known as the "marching 110,"
who call themselves "the most
exciting band in the land."
they're already legendary
far beyond athens,
thanks to their
high-energy dance moves
and youtube videos
that have gone viral
and attracted millions of hits.
when the parade is over,
the 110 heads down the hill
to peden stadium,
home of
the ohio university bobcats.
they're rehearsing for this
afternoon's homecoming game,
when the bobcats will face off
with their longtime rival,
the akron zips.
and during halftime,
the marching 110 will keep
team spirit soaring
with their signature moves,
including the diamond ohio,
a formation that spells out
their school name
in the shape of a diamond.
their impressive
choreography and spirit
has won them performances
at carnegie hall,
in presidential
inaugural parades,
and on "late night
with david letterman."
but athens is the place
they call home.
ohio university
has been located here on
the banks of the hocking river
since 1804,
thanks in part to a deal drafted
by president thomas jefferson.
that deal,
called the northwest ordinance,
helped ensure that
new territories, like ohio,
set aside land for universities.
it's tempting to wonder
what jefferson would have made
of the university's
most recent achievement:
ranking among america's
top party schools.
one well-known alumnus was no
stranger to that reputation.
in 1943, a freshman
named paul newman
joined the phi kappa tau
fraternity,
but he didn't last here long.
one night, he allegedly
rolled a beer keg
down a hill on campus.
when the keg crashed into a car
owned by
the university president,
newman was expelled.
before becoming a famous actor,
paul newman
then joined the navy,
hoping to become a pilot.
but his dream of flight
was dashed
when he was found
to be colorblind.
but here in the small town
of wapakoneta,
another young man
shared newman's dream of flight,
and his journey would soon
turn extraordinary.
in 1944,
a 14-year-old boy
named neil armstrong
and his family
moved into this corner house.
gazing out at the night sky
from his second-floor bedroom,
the young armstrong fell in love
with the idea of flight.
he got his pilot's license
just two years later
at the age of 16,
even before he could drive.
armstrong flew for the navy and
worked as a test pilot for nasa
before becoming an astronaut.
on july 16, 1969,
he and the rest
of the apollo 11 crew
lifted off from cape canaveral.
it was four days later,
on july 20th,
that armstrong set foot
on the moon.
while he inspired
millions around the world,
people here in wapakoneta
were especially proud
of their hometown hero.
that same day,
ohio governor james rhodes
proposed building a museum
to honor armstrong
and the state's contribution
to space flight.
just three years later,
the armstrong air & space museum
opened its doors.
from the air, it looks more like
a moon station than a museum.
inside is a gemini capsule,
a moon rock, and a simulator
that gives visitors a chance
to feel what's it's like
to land on the moon.
after his gravity-defying
travels and worldwide fame,
armstrong ultimately chose
to come back home to ohio.
he took a job as professor
of aerospace engineering
at the university of cincinnati.
but he wasn't the first in ohio
to explore
the mysteries of the skies.
in adams county, not far
from corn and cattle farms,
lies an archaeological mystery--
an ancient earthwork
that snakes across the land,
a site known today
as serpent mound.
spanning over 1,300 feet,
this prehistoric formation
poses a riddle,
one with twists and turns
like the serpent itself.
who created it?
and why?
early settlers believed
it was a shrine,
possibly a cemetery,
or even a place
for human sacrifice.
in 1901,
a baptist minister suggested
the serpent marked
the original location of eden.
carbon dating suggests
it was built around 1070 a.d.,
possibly by
the fort ancient people,
a native american culture
that once thrived here
on the land that's now ohio.
researchers have discovered
that features of the mound
align with both
the winter solstice sunrise
and the summer solstice sunset.
but the true intentions
of its builders
remain a mystery.
some believe they were
giving earthly form
to the constellation draco,
a celestial dragon that winds
around the big dipper.
ohio's native people
may have turned to the skies
for guidance,
but for sustenance,
they relied on the slow flowing
waters of the nearby ohio river.
this river valley was once
the home of the iroquois people,
who called the majestic waterway
that flowed through their land:
"o-y-o," or "great river."
it was from "o-y-o"
that ohio got its name.
the ohio flows more
than 980 miles,
from its start
in pittsburgh, pennsylvania,
to the mississippi.
with its particularly
smooth and clear waters,
thomas jefferson declared it the
"most beautiful river on earth."
but at the time,
it lay on the wild frontier
and acted as an uneasy border
between european settlements
to the south
and native americans
to the north.
after the revolutionary war,
the new u.s. congress
declared a vast swath of land
west of the river
as new territory.
today, that land
is now the five states
of wisconsin, michigan,
illinois, indiana, and ohio.
but in the late 1700s,
it was known simply
as the northwest territory.
and the first permanent
settlement in this new territory
was here on the ohio river--
a place called marietta.
it had been carved
out of the forest in 1788
by brigadier general
rufus putnam
and other veterans
of the revolutionary war.
after the war,
the u.s. government
ran out of funds
to pay its freedom fighters,
so it offered them land instead.
when it came time to name
their new frontier town,
they chose "marietta,"
after marie antoinette,
as a gesture of gratitude
for france's support in the war.
marietta soon played a key role
in the development of ohio,
since it was the gateway
to the rest of the state.
thousands flooded into the area,
and marietta and other
new settlements to the west
quickly boomed.
by 1802, the territories had
45,000 residents combined,
and soon, its supporters were
applying for ohio statehood.
but the question was
how would it enter the union?
as a free state,
or as a slave state?
as delegates raced to write
a new constitution,
a passionate abolitionist
named ephraim cutler
drafted a veto of slavery
to be included
in the state's bill of rights.
he managed to convince enough
delegates to get the veto passed
by just one vote,
which is how ohio
came to be a free state,
with slave states
just below the border.
over the coming decades,
the ohio river
became a symbol of hope
for thousands of escaped slaves
fleeing the south
on the underground railroad.
they called it
"the river jordan,"
for once they crossed the ohio
from kentucky or west virginia,
they knew they were
on their way to freedom.
in the dark of night,
slaves and their helpers
made the journey across
the ohio river in small boats
to houses of refuge
like this one:
the sawyer-curtis house.
for the owners
of these safe havens
and for the slaves themselves,
there was great risk.
even though slavery
was outlawed in ohio,
slave owners from other states
still had every right
to cross the river, too,
and seize any slave
that had escaped into ohio.
and in 1850, the u.s. congress
passed the fugitive slave act,
that not only required
escaped slaves
tells the powerful stories
of the more than 40,000 slaves
who arrived in ohio,
risking their lives
for a chance at liberty,
and of those here
who helped them make
their journey to freedom.
but escaped slaves
weren't the only ones
who found a haven here.
cincinnati had already attracted
others looking for opportunity,
especially german immigrants,
who settled here,
in the over-the-rhine district.
houses, markets, churches,
even breweries
look very much as they did
in the 19th century.
but the city that surrounds it
has gone through some
extraordinary changes.
what began
as a little town on the river
that catered to
soldiers and settlers
later exploded
into a bustling epicenter
of culture and commerce.
in 1854, poet henry wadsworth
longfellow crowned cincinnati
the "queen of the west."
the name stuck.
to this day
it's called the queen city.
when architects designed
the new great american tower,
they topped it off with what
they called its own tiara.
when it's not ablaze
with the setting sun,
cincinnati reds fans
light it red
when their team
makes it to the playoffs.
ohio has always prized
its sports heroes.
but one athlete would not only
make his home state proud,
he would inspire the world
by humiliating hitler
and winning gold.
ohio--
no matter what kind of barriers
its hometown heroes face,
many have found ways
to make history
by inspiring others
along the way.
and one man here changed the way
the world looked at race
by running in one.
in the 1930s,
ohio state university,
here in columbus,
was the track and field home
of olympic runner jesse owens.
raised in cleveland,
owens was breaking track records
even when he was in junior high.
many colleges
tried to recruit him,
but he chose to study here,
at osu.
owens went on to win
four gold metals
at the berlin 1936
olympic games--
a huge upset for adolf hitler,
who hoped the games
would showcase the supremacy
of his nazi athletes.
owens's achievement
was a great victory
in the battle
for racial equality.
although it would be many years
before
the civil rights movement,
the "buckeye bullet"
was ahead of his time,
and the competition.
his olympic record remained
unbroken for 48 years.
today, track students at osu
warm up at the jesse owens
memorial stadium,
perhaps with their own
olympic aspirations.
buckeye pride is everywhere
across the 1,700-acre campus
of ohio state,
from basketball to hockey,
baseball to tennis.
but at the heart of the campus
is one place where buckeye fans
really go nuts.
it's here, at ohio stadium.
the horseshoe-shaped bowl
is the fourth largest
in the nation.
more than 36 million fans have
warmed these seats since 1922.
for the most fanatical
buckeye disciples,
section 39a is the place to be.
known as block o,
fans here behind
the south end zone start cheers,
put on spectacular card stunts,
and keep buckeye spirit high,
especially when ohio state
faces its most rabid rival,
the michigan wolverines.
known simply as "the game,"
this faceoff has been called
the greatest sports rivalry
in north america.
despite their success
as a top college team,
the buckeyes have had their
dramatic ups and downs.
in 2010, the team was rocked
by "tattoo gate,"
when the star quarterback
and four other players
were caught selling
buckeye championship awards
for cash and free tattoos.
it ended
with player suspensions
and the end
of coach jim tressel's career.
despite the scandal,
bragging rights help keep
buckeye spirits soaring.
their players have won
heisman trophies seven times.
the heisman trophy is named
after ohio native john heisman,
who was born north of columbus,
in the city of cleveland
in 1869.
his legendary impact
on the sport lives on today,
at cleveland's browns stadium
on the shores of lake erie.
every time
a browns quarterback
shouts out "hike"
to signal the snap,
he's using a term
that john heisman invented.
ohio sports fans
take their devotion
to their teams and players
very seriously.
in the 1990s, the browns' owner,
an advertising executive
named art modell,
announced he was moving
the team to baltimore,
in part because cleveland's
existing browns' stadium
was outdated.
enraged fans protested,
and the city of cleveland sued
to keep the team in town,
arguing that a new
publically funded stadium
was already approved.
in the end, modell was allowed
to move his players to maryland,
but he had to pay the city
$12 million
and leave the team's name
behind in cleveland.
in 1999, a new cleveland browns
played their first game here
at the new browns stadium,
and many fans today are
just as devoted to the new team
as they were to the old one.
but not all ohio sports tales
have a happy ending.
cleveland is also the site
of one of the most famous
betrayals in sports history,
which hit fans hard here
at the quicken loans arena,
also known as the "q."
in 2003, the cleveland cavaliers
struck it big
when they scored the nba
lottery's number-one draft pick.
they chose ohio native
lebron james.
james quickly helped turn
the struggling team around,
leading the cavaliers
to the nba playoffs in 2006.
he became the pride
of many ohio sports fans.
but in 2010,
james suddenly announced
he was leaving the cavaliers
for the miami heat.
fans were outraged.
some burned
their lebron james jerseys.
the owner of the cavaliers
called the decision
a "cowardly betrayal."
james moved to miami,
but held on to his 35,000-
square-foot ohio mansion
in his hometown of akron.
it comes complete
with a bowling alley,
casino, barbershop,
and, of course,
a basketball court--
not to mention
plenty of security,
in case any betrayed fans
still hold a grudge.
lebron james
first caught the attention
of pro basketball scouts
here at st. vincent-st. mary
high school in akron,
a city better known
as the rubber capital
of america.
it lies just south of cleveland.
in greek,
akron means a high point.
the town lies
on the highest point
on the ohio and erie canal,
a once-bustling waterway
that connected lake erie
in the north
with the ohio river
in the south.
fly over akron today,
and giant rubber factories
appear in nearly
every direction.
but akron's rubber story
begins long before cars
sped down its streets.
according to legend,
the city's first rubber king,
b.f. goodrich,
launched his business
after watching a friend's house
burn to the ground
when the firefighters' old hoses
failed in the cold.
goodrich opened his plant here
in 1871--
first, making rubber fire hoses
and bicycle tires.
by 1888, he was developing new
inflatable tires for bicycles,
and later, for cars.
thanks to its specialized
labor force,
more rubber companies
opened their doors here,
and akron became the rubber
capital of america.
akron's streets bustled
as the rubber industry boomed.
in the early 20th century,
it was, at one point,
the fastest growing city
in the nation.
actor clark gable even worked
here at the firestone plant--
a brief pit stop
on his road to hollywood.
it was an actor friend
at the factory
who first invited clark
to see a play,
and the young man became hooked
on the idea of acting.
but by the 1970s,
radial tires from europe
were all the rage,
and business began to falter.
in just 15 years,
most of the big
tire producers here
were bought out
by foreign companies.
most of akron's rubber factories
closed for good.
the goodrich tire brand
is now owned by michelin,
and akron's legendary
firestone plant was closed
when the company was purchased
by japan's
bridgestone corporation.
bridgestone still makes
racecar tires in akron,
but the rest of
its manufacturing plants
are located around the world.
there may not be much rubber
left in akron,
but there's one place here where
the product that built this city
is on proud display,
covering an engineering marvel
that towers over
the akron international airport.
this rubber-roofed behemoth is
known as the goodyear airdock.
when it was built in 1929,
it was the world's
largest structure
without interior supports.
with nearly 364,000 square feet
of floor space,
it's big enough to house eight
football fields side by side.
and there's a very good reason
why it's so big.
in the 1930s,
the u.s. navy needed a place
to build massive
helium-filled airships
that could act like
flying aircraft carriers.
though some believed
these airships,
also called dirigibles,
represented
the future of air travel,
they made easy targets
for enemy aircraft
and didn't fare well
in bad weather.
airships never took off
like many predicted,
but this giant hangar
is still in use
by an aerospace contractor.
the downfall of the dirigible
may have put an end
to one dream of flight...
but it didn't diminish ohio's
lofty place in aviation history,
thanks to two brothers,
whose daring first attempts
to take to the air
would make ohio
the birthplace of aviation.
from its astronauts
to world-class athletes,
ohio has been the humble home of
dreamers who dared to aim high.
for one pair of ohio brothers,
it took a little ingenuity,
passion, and determination
to turn their dream of flight
into reality.
it all began just about 50 miles
north of cincinnati,
in the city of dayton--
a place known today
as the birthplace of aviation.
it was here
that wilbur and orville wright
ran a modest bicycle shop
and printing press
in a brick corner building that
still stands downtown today.
from their work on bicycles,
they already knew control
and balance would be critical,
so they tested their ideas
with unmanned gliders.
although the wrights
had managed to lift off
on the beach
of kitty hawk, north carolina,
they hadn't found a way
to stay in the air
for more than a minute.
but that was about to change.
the brothers convinced
a local farmer
to lend them a cow pasture.
the owner of this field
gave his permission,
but on the condition
that they clear
the runway of livestock
before taking off.
they also needed a place
to store their invention,
so they built a simple hangar
on the field.
a reconstruction
of that original building
now stands at the site.
after many attempts,
the brothers' dreams
finally took off.
in october 1905,
orville lifted up into the skies
in their handmade airplane
for their longest flight
to date.
he managed
to circle the field 29 times,
before finally
running out of fuel,
after staying in the air
for a record 39 minutes.
what may have excited
the wright brothers the most
was knowing that flight offered
a chance to see the world
from a new perspective--
something that their own hard
work tinkering with aerodynamics
had made possible.
"isn't it astonishing,"
wrote orville,
"that all these secrets
have been preserved
for so many years,
just so that we could
discover them."
five years later,
the wright brothers
were building
the world's first
mass-produced airplane,
which they named
the model b flyer.
costing $5,000 in 1910,
it was released
at about the same time
as henry ford's model t.
it's believed
that 100 of these planes
were mass-produced and sold,
including some to the u.s. army
and even one, some say,
to the mexican revolutionary
leader pancho villa.
today, aviation buffs
fly high over dayton
in this replica of the model b.
nicknamed the "brown bird,"
it's been soaring the skies
since 1982.
only a few pilots in the world
are qualified to fly it.
it's like riding
a motorcycle in the sky,
except there's almost
unlimited visibility.
it's built
to the exact specifications
of the original model b--
as a two-seater
with separate controls
that allows the pilots
to maneuver the plane's
pitch, yaw, and roll.
but not everything's the same.
the model b flyer's
original spruce frame
has been replaced with sturdy
but lightweight steel.
and instead of landing on wooden
skids, like the original,
this plane touches down
on harley davidson tires.
after their astounding success,
wilbur and orville
traveled the world,
but always came home to dayton.
orville later lived here
at hawthorn hill,
a mansion
with the wrights' endless flair
for clever d.i.y. gadgetry,
including a toaster
that could slice bread,
and what was called
a "circular shower bath."
but the wright brothers knew
that success required much more
than just new gadgets
and technology.
as wilbur put it,
"what is chiefly needed is skill
rather than machinery."
these sandy shores mark ohio's
northern border on lake erie.
the waters of this lake
may be peaceful today,
but in the early 19th century
they were filled with
battleships, cannons ablaze,
during one of the most
important naval battles
in united states history.
it all happened in the waters
off south bass island,
which now lies just south
of the canadian border.
in 1812, war broke out
between britain and the u.s.
that same year,
british forces captured detroit.
the u.s. navy feared
that lake erie could be next.
then, on september 10, 1813,
six british warships sailed
toward south bass island.
many feared it was
part of a british plan
to take complete control
over lake erie.
in response to the threat,
27-year-old united states navy
commodore oliver hazard perry
rushed his fleet into action,
here, in a place called
put-in-bay.
at first, the southwest winds
worked against perry's fleet.
the british ships
fired heavily on perry's ship,
the uss lawrence,
killing or wounding
nearly all of his crew.
desperate and
on the verge of defeat,
perry decided to risk it all.
in a small skiff,
and under fire,
he rowed to his nearest
fighting ship, the niagara,
and climbed on board.
then, perry and his men
sailed the niagara
straight towards
the british fleet.
the winds changed,
and so did perry's luck.
two british ships
became entangled
and were unable
to maneuver in defense.
almost immediately,
the british surrendered.
in a span of just 20 minutes,
perry had gone
from facing certain death
to capturing
every british vessel.
lake erie was now safely
in american hands.
today a memorial
to perry's victory
soars 350 feet
over the site of the battle.
with the british threat removed,
ohio's focus turned to trade.
ohio's farms were already
producing corn, wheat,
and other grains by the bushel.
but getting them to markets
was proving to be a challenge.
in the early 19th century,
the state government
commissioned new canals
to connect lake erie
to the ohio river,
helping create
a giant transportation network
that reached from new york city
to the mississippi river
and ultimately new orleans.
in the days before
trucks and trains
carried goods
across the country,
canals were
the highways of commerce.
farmers, merchants, travelers,
and industrial tycoons
all relied
on these watery routes.
long stretches
of ohio's early canals
have fallen into disrepair,
but some remain,
and offer a glimpse of how goods
were once transported
across the state.
to keep the boats
and barges moving,
mules often pulled them
from the shore
and could drag barges
all the way from toledo
to cincinnati.
in ohio,
the city that benefitted most
from this network
was cleveland,
thanks to a few
titans of industry.
one of the earliest
was john d. rockefeller,
the world's first billionaire,
who grew up
just outside of town.
in 1863, he and a partner
built an oil refinery here
on what's called "the flats."
it was the start of a business
that would become
the oil giant, standard oil,
parts of which would later go on
to become both chevron
and exxon-mobile.
rockefeller's success helped
transform this lakeside city
into a bustling epicenter
of industry.
steel quickly became
the city's backbone.
by 1880, nearly 30%
of cleveland's residents
worked in steel mills
south of town.
today, cleveland's steel plants
are still going strong.
these are some of the largest
plants of their kind in america.
and they still rely on
the winding cuyahoga river
to ship their goods to market.
today, bulk carriers carefully
navigate this narrow waterway,
just as ships have been doing
for more than a century.
but one wrong move of these
long, cumbersome carriers
can spell disaster.
this busy river was once
the embarrassment of the city
and may be one of the reasons
why cleveland was once nicknamed
"the mistake by the lake."
for years, standard oil,
goodyear tires,
sherwin-williams paints,
and republic steel
all dumped their waste
right into the cuyahoga river,
until one day in 1969,
when the river itself
caught on fire
while fish populations
have risen dramatically
in recent years,
high levels
of contaminants and bacteria
still plague this waterway.
but it's not just rivers
that are being reclaimed
in cleveland.
in the city's
university circle district,
old buildings are
being renovated
and new ones built
to reflect the changing
world around them.
this modernist cube,
designed by farshid moussavi,
is the new home for cleveland's
museum of contemporary art,
or moca.
its black glass panels
respond to the changing light
and activity on the street below
and are meant to help visitors
experience and reflect
on the passing of time.
even its shape is in flux.
moca starts off on the ground
as a hexagon,
but ends up as a square
at its roof.
just down the street,
another design undulates
more like crashing waves.
frank gehry's
peter b. lewis building,
home of the weatherhead school
of management,
is one of university circle's
most iconic structures.
here, some existing buildings
are being given a modern twist.
cleveland's museum of art,
which first opened in 1916,
is getting
a $350 million renovation,
which includes
a brand-new glass-roofed atrium.
but in university circle,
cutting-edge design is not only
reserved for museums.
this glimmering curved facade
is home to one of the most
innovative medical centers
in the world.
this is just one
of several buildings
belonging to
the cleveland clinic.
oprah winfrey, robin williams,
and even william randolph hearst
have all sought treatment here.
but the building
that kick-started
cleveland's modern building boom
isn't on university circle.
it's right downtown
and looks out over
the banks of lake erie.
this is the rock-and-roll
hall of fame.
nearly 300 legendary artists
have been inducted here.
and there's a very good reason
why this popular site
was built in cleveland.
many believe rock and roll
was born right here in town--
not the music, but the moniker.
in 1951, a cleveland dj
named alan freed
first came up with the
phrase "rock and roll"
to describe a new
beat-driven kind of music.
the hall's
glass and steel pyramid
was designed by famed
architect i.m. pei,
who once admitted he had no idea
what rock and roll even was.
but after seeing a few concerts,
pei understood
what it was all about
and decided that the best way
to capture the energy
of rock and roll
was with a pyramid design.
outside, painted replicas
of fender stratocasters
are part of guitarmania,
an art project that raises money
for the united way
of greater cleveland
and the rock and roll
hall of fame's
educational programs,
by auctioning off
the guitar sculptures.
the highest bid yet
was for yoko ono's
"imagine peace" guitar,
which brought in
$105,000 for charity.
ohio.
it's been home to innovators,
industrial titans,
and record-breaking athletes.
but for many out here
in rural ohio,
their ventures are best
when they're kept small
and in the family.
nearly 90% of ohio's farms
are family-owned.
corn and soy
are their top crops.
every fall, teams of modern
combines and trucks
roll out across the state.
these highly efficient machines
harvest acre after acre
of corn and other crops
with amazing speed.
but not all of ohio's bounty
is harvested the modern way.
take these
upright bundles of corn.
they've all been
cut and stacked by hand.
this technique,
called corn shocking,
allows the stalks to dry
without any rot.
hundreds of years old,
it's still practiced today
by the amish.
here in holmes county, they live
pretty much as they always have,
since they first arrived in ohio
nearly 200 years ago.
with close to 60,000 amish
in ohio,
this state has the largest
amish community in the country.
the amish believe that
modern technology corrupts,
which is why they still drive
horse-drawn carriages
and wear simple
unadorned clothing.
on narrow country roads,
their buggies can come in handy
to bypass traffic.
since the amish have cut off
many of their ties
with the outside world,
their way of life has remained
a mystery to many.
so when the news broke
of a shocking amish scandal,
it captivated the nation.
it began here,
in this small valley in 2011.
at the time, this was home
to an amish splinter group
led by a man named
samuel mullet,
who lived in this white house,
surrounded by dozens
of his followers.
some say that
mullet's strict bergholz clan
was actually a cult
and that he was known
to severely punish
those who didn't follow
his extreme interpretation
of his faith.
so, when members
of his group fled,
mullet was accused
of taking revenge.
in amish communities,
beards for men
and uncut hair for women
are treasured symbols
of religious devotion,
which is why many believe
they became mullet's targets.
he was accused of ordering
some of his loyal followers
to track down those he perceived
as his enemies.
the gang, now known
as the "bergholz boys,"
carried out attacks
in the dark of night,
holding down their victims,
and then cutting off
their beards or hair
with scissors
and battery-operated clippers.
mullet's own sister
was one of those attacked.
the fbi raided the settlement,
and mullet and others
were arrested.
prosecutors charged him
with hate crimes.
in 2013, mullet was convicted
and sentenced
to 15 years in jail
for his role in masterminding
the beard-cutting attacks.
but there's another twist
to this tale.
thanks to the modern technology
that the amish often shun,
it's been reported that mullet
is now a multimillionaire
and that his property sits
on a gold mine of natural gas
that fracking companies
have paid millions to extract.
with its rolling hills
and open plains,
ohio offers plenty of places to
carve out one's own community,
even for celebrities
with a cult-like status.
roughly 70 miles
northeast of columbus
lies an idyllic spot
called malabar farm.
here, surrounded by
forests and fields,
creative minds have found
a place to return to nature,
surround themselves with
the seasons' natural beauty,
and write a pulitzer-prize-
winning novel or two.
author louis bromfield
lived here,
at malabar farm,
in the 1940s and '50s.
but he was often not alone.
hollywood's biggest stars
at the time
considered the farm
an ideal getaway.
lauren bacall
and humphrey bogart
were married here in 1945.
at the time,
it was the tabloids'
most sensational story.
errol flynn, dorothy lamour,
clark gable, and others
soon flocked here.
but even stars
had to work on the farm,
thanks to bromfield's passion
for sustainable agriculture.
some locals remember
seeing james cagney
selling vegetables
at the farm's produce stand.
although the stars
have since moved on
to other glamorous getaways,
malabar farm has yet another
intriguing link to hollywood.
hidden in the trees,
this small cabin on the property
may not look like much.
but it's where
the powerful opening scene
of "the shawshank redemption"
was filmed.
starring tim robbins
and morgan freeman,
the film follows a banker
accused of murder,
his sometimes brutal
imprisonment,
and his inspiring friendship
with a fellow inmate.
much of the rest of the movie
was filmed nearby
at the ohio state reformatory.
this castle-like facility
was built in 1896
and closed in 1990.
that's when hollywood
saw an opportunity.
the gloomy
romanesque architecture
provided the perfect setting
for shawshank.
from the moment
character andy dufresne
walks through the prison yard
on his way to see the warden,
to his brutal stint
in solitary confinement,
the prison plays the role
of the ultimate antagonist.
the facility's goal
is to break the spirits
of all who enter its gates.
yet andy does not give up hope,
and his unflagging
faith in freedom
encourages those around him
who've long ago been broken.
the film's most iconic scene
takes place
under an oak tree nearby.
it's beneath this tree's
heavy boughs
where morgan freeman's
character, red,
digs up a buried message
and realizes it's time
to either "get busy living
or get busy dying."
severe winds nearly
took down the tree in 2011,
but true to the film's message
of hope and survival,
a good part of the oak
still stands tall.
for now,
its most serious threats
may come from
movie buffs and tourists
seeking out this legendary tree.
many fans of the film
make a pilgrimage here
to see the oak--
so many that the tree's owner,
a local attorney,
felt the need to fence it in.
but there's no fencing in
the bold spirit of ohio,
from those
who dreamed of flight...
even making it
all the way to the moon...
from the brave who dared to take
a stand against slavery...
to those who fought for freedom
when the odds were
stacked against them...
the innovative, inventive,
and inspirational
will always be found in ohio.