1 x 26 - alone
♪ beware ♪
♪ beware the bat ♪
Sync and corrections by masaca
- www.addic7ed.com -
Previously on
"Beware the Batman"...
Freeze, Batman!
I'm not that
Harvey Dent anymore.
Thanks to Batman.
Deathstroke's not dead.
Dane Lisslow, Slade Wilson...
All three the same man.
I couldn't allow Dent
to kill you.
But, now you and I will face
our destiny together.
Wake up, Katana.
Wake up.
Batman.
- Are you hurt? How did you...
- I'm not sure.
Explosion threw me clear.
Utility belt
must have torn free.
Hello, Batman.
Your body mass index
has changed.
Are you retaining water?
Once that fire catches hold, the whole
place could go in a matter of minutes.
Alfred.
Where are you?
I saw the helicopter go down.
We're all right.
We lost Deathstroke.
Are you picking up anything
from Gotham PD?
Nothing on Deathstroke.
But you should know that it looks like all of
Dent's SCU is descending on your location.
I assume you have a plan?
Thank goodness,
you're all right.
When we were cut off,
I thought...
Expecting someone else?
You tell me, what mask
are you hiding behind today?
Dane Lisslow?
Slade Wilson?
No more masks.
All right then.
I hope you remember
your training.
Did someone steal the Batmobile?
Is that even possible?
Alfred, lock down the Batcave.
Deathstroke's...
Hello, Batman.
Don't worry, Alfred's alive,
but whether he remains
that way or not
depends on you.
You know where we are.
Come alone.
Wake up, Harv.
Wake up.
Oh, goody, you're not dead.
That would have put
such a damper on our victory.
Victory?
What are you talking about?
Batman and our former
colleague, Deathstroke, have...
What's the opposite of
risen from the ashes?
Died.
The fires of revenge may burn
slowly, but they're burning now.
Batman dead?
It should've been by our hand.
Still, he paid
for what he did to us.
Nothing to stand in our way now.
Exactly.
Gotham is ours for the plucking.
Yes.
But you misunderstand.
When I said "ours",
I wasn't including you.
Deathstroke is leading you
into a trap.
Of course he is.
And by walking into it,
he'll lead me to Alfred.
Unless he kills you first.
At Bruce Wayne's funeral, Alfred
said something that stuck.
A single twig breaks...
But the bundle of twigs
is strong.
You're not alone.
Let me help you.
I don't want to bury Bruce Wayne
and Batman for real this time.
I don't intend to lose.
Barbara, I need you
to get the vehicle
and meet me at the entrance
to the Cauldron.
I'm disappointed.
I thought we were cohorts,
collaborators, partners.
Two's a partnership,
three's a liability.
"Three"?
It appears
we're not only parting ways,
but minds as well.
Why the long face?
Or, in your case,
two face.
Didn't you realize I could kill
you as easily I created you?
Freeze, Anarky!
Ow!
Way to wreck the moment, Gordon.
Welcome to the game, Harv.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine!
Better than fine!
You've always been
a boy scout, Gordon.
You should think about
running for Mayor.
We aren't interested anymore.
See you around.
"We"?
Before we begin,
i want to apologize for the Dane Lisslow
charade and his explosive finale.
Did you like the body?
Something I picked up
at the morgue.
You're an assassin.
Getting close to your prey
is your job.
Assassin? Yes.
That is who I am.
That is all Alfred Pennyworth left
for me when he destroyed my life.
Huh?
You and your other self,
Bruce Wayne,
have led an extraordinary
life, Batman.
Not unlike a life
i once saw for myself.
Where is he?
Where is Alfred?
He's waiting for you.
Well, what do
you think? Perfect?
Perfect? Could you have found
something more conspicuous?
It was the only vehicle
I could get the keys to.
Here, put this on.
From here on out, you're Oracle.
Okay, but why the disguise
all of a sudden?
Because I brought along
some friends.
You can come out now!
Cool.
I knew
you'd come alone.
Nice room, by the way.
Let Alfred go. It's me you want.
No, this is about both of you.
It will truly be an honor when I
kill you and take your place.
Wake up, Batman.
Wake up.
Alfred.
He's gone,
but no doubt not for long.
What do we know?
He's cut the elevator cables
and destroyed the hydraulics
to the Batcave's entrance.
We're trapped in here.
All three of us.
Your sons
have come home, Alfred.
One, a hero,
one, a villain.
And tonight...
You're gonna watch your son die.
What happened between us
is in the past.
Ah, yes, the past.
You couldn't leave it alone.
Had to start asking people
questions about Slade Wilson.
People who don't like former MI6
agents snooping in their business.
People who began to think
I'd been compromised!
People who tried to kill me!
I was trying to make amends
for what happened years ago.
CIA burned me because of you.
I lost my family, my life.
And you replace me with this?
A spoiled, rich boy?
Was it the money?
You saw a sucker in Wayne
and you dug in?
I chose Bruce
because I saw in him what I never
saw in you, Slade, empathy.
Compassion for
other human beings.
Even at his worst,
Bruce Wayne and Batman
are better men
than you ever were.
Stop!
One thing I discovered while I
was researching you, Batman.
You always plan ahead.
So do I.
You have an impressive
arsenal here.
Although keeping so much C4 in
one place in very dangerous.
I took the liberty of spreading
it throughout the cave.
Those explosives go off,
you die, too.
I'm going to give you
two choices.
Lay down your life
with honor to me,
or see everything
you built destroyed.
You forgot the third choice.
That detonator
has a 16-digit kill code.
Only I can stop the timer.
Then I'll just
have to convince you.
We're still sealed in here
with that C4 to contend with.
There's another way.
I can override
the door manually.
No. He's mine.
The Batcave's been rigged with explosives.
Not much time.
We're on it.
Please tell me
that's not how long we have.
Deathstroke has
planted C4 all over the cave
and locked his detonator
with a 16-digit kill code.
Detonator? Where is it?
It was knocked away.
In the corner, I think.
Nice pad.
This is my second time here.
Well, aren't you special!
Found it.
Oracle, what are you doing?
Detonators work on
frequency conversion.
If we can track the signal...
We can find the bombs.
Clever girl.
They're all over.
We'll never get them in time.
Don't be so sure.
How much can you lift?
It's fitting, the two of us,
brothers that we are,
meeting our end together.
Where is your honor? Face me!
You're not my brother!
And you don't know
the first thing about honor.
How do we disarm them?
I... I just knew
how to find them.
There's no time left.
Stand back.
You're too late.
Metamorpho?
Ow.
You're done.
Perhaps.
But so are you.
Or have you forgotten?
I know your secret...
Bruce.
Don't move.
As soon as we hand him
over to Gotham PD,
he'll reveal Bruce Wayne.
It's over, Alfred.
Perhaps not.
Batman protects this city.
He's protected all of you
at one time.
If the truth of who he is
beneath the mask is revealed,
that will end.
What can we do?
You're a scientist
and you can generate
any element.
Can you erase his mind?
Intriguing.
Uh, there is an enzyme, PKM-Zeta.
Give me its properties.
I can't let you do this.
This isn't just about Batman.
It's about Gotham,
and these outsiders who've risked their
lives to help you continue your fight.
Stand clear, everyone.
Where am I?
What are you people?
Well, that worked.
You're back in business.
Not just me.
We.
I'm not alone.
Not anymore.
Bravo, Batman.
Checkmate.
Shall we play again?
Sync and corrections by masaca
- www.addic7ed.com -