Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
All aboard!
Woo-woo!
Chuggington!
# We're trainees, we're making tracks
# Wheels to the rails Clackety-clack!
# Running on time Passengers to take
# Hauling loads, pick-ups to make
# Riding the rails
# A train-tastic crew
# Honk your horns, toot-toot!
# Toot-toot!
# Chuggington. Chugga-chugga Chugga-chugga. Chuggington
# Chuggington. Chugga-chugga-chugga Chugga-chugga-chugga
# Chugga-chugga-chugga-chugga Chuggington. Chuggington!
# Clackety-clack! #
- BREATHLESS:
- Old...Puffer Pete reporting for duty!
- You all right, Pete, you seem puffed?
- Smashing, thanks.
I've just been having some fun. What's this?
WHIRRING
- Ho-ho-ho!
- Ooh, a cow?
You are clever, Pete.
Takes a lot of puff out of me though.
- Right, better get this milk delivered.
- See you tomorrow, Pete!
Poor old Pete, look how hard he's puffing. He needs the day off.
- OUT-OF-BREATH:
- What's next, Vee?
Oh, dear me, Pete, you sound terrible!
- I think I've got a bit of...
- COUGHING
- ..soot in my throat box!
- Go and see Morgan and get it cleaned out.
Good idea, Vee.
Look, Vee has sent Pete to the repair shed.
She must be worried about him too.
- LAUGHING:
- Ooh, that tickles!
All done, Pete.
Thanks, Morgan. Ah, now, there's something I wanna ask you.
Back in a sec.
Here we are. Right, Hodge, that's all I can find in the workshop.
TOOTING
- HE LAUGHS
- All right, Pete?
- Never better!
- What are you up to?
- Collecting scrap metal.
- I'd better get out of the way,
- before you cart me off!
- Not you, Pete! You're in tip-top shape, mate.
SQUEAKING
- Unlike that cart, which is on its last wheels.
- I know.
But Terry 'ere's my old favourite.
I want Morgan to have another go at repairing him.
Oh, Pete,
- last time I patched this up, I said that was it.
- I know,
but I can't bear to part with Terry. He's been with me since I was young.
Leave him with me and I'll see what I can do. No promises.
- Thanks, Morgan.
- TOOTING
Poor old Pete doesn't look good.
- Shh! I can hear Morgan talking.
- He's too old and worn out, Lori.
Oh, it's so sad,
- he's over 100 years old, isn't he?
- Yes, but at the scrapyard,
- he could be turned into something more useful.
- Oh!
They want to send Pete to the scrapyard!
- But he's only a bit tired. Are you sure they meant him?
- Yeah.
- Who else is over 100?
- Should I go and find Pete?
- Why spoil his day?
- Let's wait till he comes back.
- They're going to tell Pete later.
- Good, we still have time to change their minds.
- How?
- We'll prove that there's PLENTY of spark left in him.
- Yeah,
- let's show them!
- Pete needs a nice, long rest. ..I know,
- I'll do all his jobs!
- Brilliant plan, Brewster!
DING-DONG! Pete!
- Pete?
- He left, Vee.
- Oh, could you give him a message?
- Yeah, no prob.
There are some wagons of manure to take to the garden centre urgently.
The smell is dreadful!
I'll let him know.
..Psst, Zephie, keep Pete out of the way and I'll take the stinky stuff.
- TOOTING
- Bring out your scrap!
- Eh, is Pete gonna let us take this old heap?
- Well, I can't fix it,
- but I think HE should decide.
- OK, we'll ask him gently.
TOOTING
Ooh, what a beauty!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
- Ha-ha-ha!
- FAINT WHISTLING
Oh, poor thing, he can hardly catch his breath!
- Pete, I've got a message for you!
- What's that?
- Get cleaned up in the Chugwash, then have a lovely nap.
- But I'm clean,
and I don't need a rest.
Still, Vee usually knows best.
TOOTING
- Message received and understood, Vee!
- Oh, good, I'll be glad when
- that terrible pong has gone, Pete.
- I don't understand.
- I had a good wash this morning.
- Hi, Vee, the manure's been delivered.
Goodness me, Pete's quick today!
Yeah, he's amazing! What would we do without him?
- Ooh!
- PETE SINGS
Puffer Pete to the rolling stock yard, please.
SINGING CONTINUES
BUZZING
Hi, these cars were filled with manure,
- I think they'll need a wash.
- Phwoar, I smell what you mean!
Who's the boxcar for?
- Pete, he's off to the orchard to pick up a load of apples.
- Oh, right.
TOOTING
- Was that Vee calling me?
- No, you must still have soap in your ears.
- You'd better have another rinse.
- Maybe you mean that I still smell!
- Zephie to Vee! Pete'll be there shortly.
- Thanks. Could you tell him
that after the orchard, there's a pick-up at the ice-cream factory
- for the safari park?
- I will.
Psst, Brewster, after this,
you have to take some ice cream over to the safari park.
Chugs away!
That should do the trick!
I think it's about time I did some work.
Ooh, that smell is abso-toot-toot-ely terrible!
- FAINT TOOTING
- Oh, dear!
I'd better go back for a scrub! Don't wanna be Old Pongy Pete.
- PANTING:
- I'm here for the safari park pick-up.
- Where's your refrigeration wagon?
- Oh, no, I forgot!
I can't go back. Can you put it in my boxcar? I'll ride like the wind!
I wouldn't recommend that, but the ice cream's for a party
and if it doesn't get there soon, the kids won't be happy.
Load him up!
- You're very brave, Pete.
- I never thought this day would come!
We had some grand old times. I'll never forget you!
You had a good run, mate.
- Come on, we should get going.
- No, Pete, you can't go to the scrapyard!
I've got to, it's the right thing to do.
- I've got to give Terry a good send-off.
- Terry?
Who's Terry?
Me old tender car.
He was on his last wheels and Morgan couldn't patch him up.
- So you're not going to be melted down?
- No!
Ha-ha, there's plenty of life in this old steamer yet!
Oh, that's good.
- BREATHLESS:
- Oh... Oh, this is hard.
- Pete, back from the ice-cream delivery already?
- What ice cream?
It's OK, Brewster went. He's done all your jobs today,
- so you could have a good rest.
- I hope he took a refrigeration wagon.
- I only saw him with a boxcar.
- Rattling rivets!
- Wait here, Terry!
- Don't worry, he's not going anywhere.
The ice cream's melted, Brewster.
- The children will be so disappointed.
- I'm sorry, Vicky,
I thought it'd be all right if I went really fast. I'm too tired.
- TOOTING
- Old Puffer Pete to the rescue!
I've picked up some cups and straws from the kiosk,
- so the children can have milkshakes!
- Oh, that's a great idea, Pete.
- They'll love that.
- Thanks, Pete. What are we gonna do without you?
- I'm not ready for the scrapheap yet!
- Oh, yeah, I got it wrong, Brewster.
That's brilliant news!
So I carted all that manure when you could have done it yourself?
- GIGGLING:
- Yeah, that made the whole depot really stinky!
The depot?
Ha-ha! I thought everyone was talking about ME!
- So I'm not Old Pongy Pete?
- No! You're fresh as a daisy.
- Wow!
- Just goes to show you youngsters
that things aren't always what they seem.
- THEY LAUGH
- You can say that again!
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org