A 4 year old boy has been found
dead in bushland
not far from the Brisbane River.
I found a jacket.
It had blood on it,
and it went missing.
Mr Linikus doesn't remember a jacket.
I think someone's trying to set me up.
Tell me what was in the bag that you
threw in the river.
And don't lie to me.
This isn't right! I love you.
He's taking me to see the fireworks,
or I swear I won't come back at all.
You are running out of track, Ben.
What else did he want to know?
How you got home.
It's the finish line.
Is she on her meds?
What do you mean?
You'll figure it out.
We could have another. What?
Nothing.
Now he's representing Christy, so
I've got to find a new solicitor.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
Sorry, I have to go.
Are you OK?
Yeah. Ignore what I said earlier.
No, it's fine, really.
So, see you... Soon,
yeah? Yeah.
We'll have dinner.
Great. Take care.
Hello? Dad?
Hey, Chook. Are you OK?
I hate it here.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
Look, I hate it that you're there too.
It's not home, dad.
I want us to be home!
I know.
Come and get me?
I can't.
Then I'll come over.
No, no. Sweetie, that wouldn't work.
Just stay at Uncle Malcolm's, OK?
I've got to go, but I'll call you soon,
OK?
Paul!
They haven't arrested you yet?
When do you go back over?
Friday next week.
What do you want?
Unopened.
This isn't for headaches, is it?
Bipolar disorder.
How long has she been on them?
She's been taking that stuff since I met her,
seven years ago.
They reckon she's been taking it since she was 15.
Why, not taking them?
What happens
when she doesn't take them?
Paranoid.
She used to accuse people of things.
Wake up in the middle of
the night thinking I was gonna kill her.
Well, I see what you did to her living room.
One night I woke up.
I had a pain in my side.
She'd stabbed me here and here,
before I got the knife off her.
Why didn't you tell the cops?
She was my wife. The mother of my kid.
Mr Gundelach.
Detective Cornielle would like to have a chat.
Mr Gundelach. What do you want?
How was Mr Murnane?
What do you want?
I just want to clear something up
about the night before you found Thom's body.
You went out drinking
with your friend, David Carroll.
Do you often go out drinking
to excess with Mr Carroll?
No.
What made you go?
Why do you want to know?
Because now I want to. Why?
You cheated on me.
I have a right to know.
Tell me who it was.
Did you fight about Ms Murnane?
We'd been fighting about a lot of things.
But it finished on the subject of Ms Murnane.
Jess Murnane?
You said you wanted to know.
I wave to her every fucking morning, Ben!
It's ancient history. It was five years ago, Chris.
Where are you going?
Are you going to go see her now?
No, I'm going out.
So you went out drinking with Mr Carroll.
A few hours passed.
He puts you in a taxi?
So he says.
You don't remember?
Maybe a Black & White Cab pulled up here?
Paid the driver in cash?
Shut the door?
Taxi reverses,
then drove down the street that way.
And then what?
I went home.
I opened my gate.
And then I went inside to bed.
Didn't go across the street?
No.
That's funny.
Because look at this.
What we can make of it, you pulled up,
paid the driver in cash,
shut the door,
cab reverses, and then...
What happened?
I must have made a mistake.
Maybe I thought I was on
the other side of the road.
I really don't remember.
OK.
Anything else you want to tell me?
Did you get home before me?
I couldn't have. Could I?
No, I don't remember.
Neither do I!
Ohhhh...
Uh... What? Ummm...
Yeah, I might have put something
extra in your drink that night.
You what?
You spiked... It's just liquid ecstasy.
Strictly speaking, it was GBH with
a little bit of molly to balance.
You're not supposed to mix it with
booze, but you were so stress, mate.
What does it do?
It's supposed to relax you.
Mate,  I can't remember half of what happened!
Yeah, well it can do that too.
Fucking hell, Dave! I'm sorry, mate.
I was actually trying to help.
What, and you didn't think
you should tell me this?
I didn't think it would matter!
Fuck! Ben-o, mate,
it's easy just show the cops this,
Yes
and they're off you and onto
her like flies to shit.
That's not enough!
It is, mate.
She's a psycho! This proves it!
It's not enough, OK!
They have so much more on me than that.
Well, you've got to find that bloody jacket!
What are you doing?
Ben?
Put that down, please.
What happened?
Put her down.
You should go.
You should tell me about the Teritol.
You really should go.
Or what?
You're going to do to me
what you did to Paul?
Get out!
Where's the jacket?
What are you talking about?
It's the one that I found,
the one that vanished!
You were here when I
chased that guy into the bush.
Where is it?
you think
you think I killed my boy?
You don't know!
You don't know! You don't know!
He was mine too.
You think you know, then?
You think you know what it's like
to lose a child?
You have no idea.
I did lose a child.
You've still got yours.
You'll pay for this.
Jess Murnane had a daughter.
She died.
Charlotte.
Sudden infant death syndrome.
Eight weeks old.
You knew about the Teritol?
And before that, the Balporoid, and the lithium.
And you know that she
stabbed Paul Murnane?
That's the jacket that I found.
That's the one that went missing.
Had you seen this photo before?
No.
Had you been in Ms
Murnane's bedroom before?
How'd you know it was in her bedroom?
How'd you find it?
She invited me in this morning.
What for?
It was on her bedside table.
And when did you find the
urn and the jumpsuit?
Jess called you.
What did she say?
That you broke in without her permission.
You took a photograph
without her permission.
And that you struck at her.
She hit me!
She's crazy. She lies.
And I think she killed Thom.
I know how it looks to you, OK?
I know you think that I did
this, but I didn't. I didn't.
I didn't know that he was my son.
I wish I had.
I wish I had. If I had have known,
I'd have loved him.
I didn't. Why?
Why would I kill him?
We'll find that out.
Thank you for coming in to see me.
We'll return this to Ms Murnane.
Two new messages.
Ben, it's Christy. Give me a call.
Ben, what's wrong with your mobile?
Call me!
Hello? Yeah, it's me. Is she there?
What? Is Eva there?
She's not with you??
Why do you think I've been calling you, Ben?
Is she there?
I just got home. She called before.
She wanted to come over.
Well, you'd better look. And you'd better
not be lying.
I don't know.
Eva?
Ben. Have you seen Eva?
I thought Christy took
her to her brother's.
Leave me alone, Ben.
Is she in here?
Eva! Is she here?
You've lost your daughter now, huh?
Feels horrible, doesn't it!
Eva!  If you've done anything to her?
Get out! Let me in!
Get out! Hey!
What's going on?
I've called the police.
If you've hurt her, I'll kill you.
Shit.
Mr Gundelach? Sir?
Sir, do you have a moment?
I need to ask you a few questions.
I'm gonna look for my daughter.
You can do what you want.
You can look in my house.
I'm gonna find my daughter.
Hi, it's Christy Gundelach.
Sorry I can't take your call.
Leave a brief message...
Yes? It's Cornielle. Have you found Eva?
No, I'm just checking
to see where you are.
You know where I am.
You guys are in my street.
I have just one question.
You had sex this
morning with Ms Murnane.
And?
Was it consensual?
What?
What are you talking about?
Cornielle?
What did she say? Talk to me, Mr Gundelach.
This is a very serious allegation.
I want to hear your side of the story.
My side?
Listen, I've got something on the stove.
Just give me a sec, will you?
Mr Gundelach?
Open up! Police!
Open up!
Where is she?
You're insane!
Where's my daughter?
Eva? Eva?
Get out! Help me! Eva?
He's in there!
Eva...?
Mr Gundelach, get down, please.
Where's my daughter? Get down.
Down! Now! Hands. Show me your hands.
Put them on your head.
What did she do with my daughter?
Where's Eva?
I didn't do it, Cornielle!
Arrest her! Arrest her!
Mind your head, Mr Gundelach.
Arrest her! Arrest her! Cornielle,
arrest her!
Sir. Sir?
What is it?
You better come have a look.
What the hell's goin' on?
Eva's been found safe and well.
Where? At her uncle's.
Kids, hey?
All that panic for nothing.
I want to get a solicitor.
Does Christy even know I'm here?
What the hell is going on?
Are you going to charge me or what?
The 49 year old fisherman was
airlifted to Cairns Base Hospital,
where he remains in a serious but
stable condition.
The police investigation into the murder of 4
year old Brisbane boy Thomas
Murnane has been reignited,
with the detention of the boy's mother
for questioning.
The 32 year old woman was taken from her home
by homicide detectives and is
assisting them with their inquiries.
This comes after the recent release
of Benjamin Gundelach,
who had been a figure of
intense speculation after finding
the boy's body in mid December.
Lawyers for the woman insist she (Hey.)
was not involved in her son's death,
and will fight any charges.
A police spokes...
What did you get?
Ah, massaman beef, green
curry and golden parcels. Yum.
Do you want to get started on the
mortgage papers?
We should eat first,
yeah? Good idea.
Where's Eva?
Eva?
Jeez, not again. Eva?
I'll have a look.
Come on, shug?
Hi. Hello.
Hot. Yeah. Um, dad's inside. Mum too.
OK. But I'm glad to catch you.
Better get these iceblocks inside.
This won't take long.
Had us all quite worried
that day you disappeared.
I told mum I was sorry.
Where'd you go?
Streets around Uncle Malcolm's.
I spoke to a bus driver.
Apparently a girl who
looked a lot like you
caught a bus out here that afternoon.
So?
So it wasn't you?
No.
I really gotta go.
Your father was quite desperate to find you.
He thought Ms Murnane may
have harmed you.
She killed Thom.
He broke in, which was wrong,
searching her house for you.
We found the jacket there.
I saw the news.
Before he went over, I was
talking to him on the phone.
So?
But he didn't hang up the phone.
We had to scrub the audio. At
first, it was quite feint.
Dad?
Dad? Dad?
You came back, and you put the
jacket in Ms Murnane's laundry.
1:16 pm. Resuming interview
with Eva Gundelach.
Now, Eva, I'm going to read back over
what you said before lunch
about the death of Thom Murnane.
Do you understand?
Anything I say that is in correct,
please stop me and tell me.
You said,
"It happened the night
mum and dad fought.
They'd fought before,
but this time was different.
It was loud and I went to listen.
I heard mum saying she
wanted to leave dad.
I'm not going to tell you who it was!
OK, you promise me you won't say.
Tell me who it was. It was Jess. Jess?
Jess Murnane?
You said you wanted to know.
"I couldn't let mum and dad break up.
Couldn't let Jess Murnane ruin our family.
I had to make her leave the street.
She wouldn't stay without her boy.
" If Jess didn't have Thom anymore, she'd go,
and leave dad alone.
"I waited till dad
got home.
He went to the door and he came back home.
He came back inside and
I waited for him to go to bed.
"I had a key because Tash used to
babysit for Jess."
Hey, Thom. Thom.
Wanna see something?
It's raining. It's OK.
Put your gumboots on. Hurry up.
"The jacket was just there."
Let's go.
"And I took him up the track."
Why? 'Cause. That's the way of the river.
I wanted to put him in the river
"But we didn't get to the jetty.
He didn't like the rain when
it got heavy."
I wanna go home. Come on,
don't you want to see the fish?
I want to go home.
Come on, we're almost there!
Thom! Mummy! Thom!
Thom! Get back here! Thom!
Mummy! Mummy! Mummy!
"So I hit him.
I hit him on the head with a torch."
I had to, to make him quiet.
"And then I didn't know what to do.
He was too heavy. It was too far to
the river. So I left him.
Things kept going bad when I got
back to our street.
His mum was already looking for him.
Thom! Thom?
"So I went behind Mrs Bailey's house,
where dad found that weird guy.
That's where I had
to leave the jacket."
Christy. Christy? Ben!
Where's the phone?
I thought dad
would still be asleep.
Must have been right behind me.
"Things kept going wrong.
I went back for the jacket it was gone.
And then I found out you were looking for a torch,
so I thought if I put dad's
torch back, you'd leave him alone.
On Christmas Day, I heard dad get
up early.
I followed him up to Mrs Bailey's house
and I found the jacket there.
" That weird man must have taken it.
"All I had to do was put it back in her house.
" Now "her", meaning Ms Murnane?
But mum mum made it hard.
"I just wanted us to
have a normal Christmas."
But it wasn't.
"I came back with Tash, but then she came over."
We'd only been gone a day, and she
was already after dad.
Thom was gone. We'd gone. But she
was still there.
"I took a bus from Uncle Malcolm's,
I got the jacket, and I waited."
Eva?
After that, I waited in my cubby.
When I got back home, dad wasn't there.
Dad?
You know, you should have listened
to dad when he said he didn't do it.
Is there anything else
you'd like to tell me?
I'm sorry.
None of this would have happened if
I just got Thom to the river.
Mrs Gundelach,
this is your copy for you to sign, as guardian.
It's alright, mum.
Everything's gonna be alright.
No, it's not. It's not...
Eva Abigail Gundelach,
I'm arresting you for the murder of
Thom Murnane.
You'll be taken to the watch house,
charged, and arrangements will be
made immediately.
You'll report before
the Children's Court.
I'm not sure what the magistrate
will decide for Eva.
Mr Gundelach?
Take care.