So this is the show?
This is what you're putting up there?
I've been staring at them
for, like, 10 days now,
you know, trying to
stay objective about it,
but, you know, it's really hard.
I mean, that's Franklin right there.
I've never seen Frank like this before.
I mean, this is intense.
Okay, you know what? Forget it.
God, what are we supposed to say?
I'm sorry, it's... it's
a little strange for me.
You know, you guys are just too
freaked out about your own stuff.
- Oh, right, okay.
- Freaked out about the pop-up.
- Make it about us.
- Freaked out about the wedding.
Just turn it right around.
- What are you talking about?
- Come on, you're not freaked out
about the wedding? You're
not freaked out about
your mom meeting Richie?
Listen, you fucker, you said you were gonna
stop talking shit about Richie.
I'm not talking shit about Richie.
Come on, we all know how Danna can be.
Okay, I know that, but
you mentioned Richie.
Like, please stop talking about him.
What did I say about Richie?
I'm talking about your mom.
Okay, I am actually freaking out right now,
so I'm gonna get another beer.
All right, will you
get me another beer too?
Sure.
He's incredibly high right now.
- He's like on the bug out.
- I know.
Look, you hired that guy.
You paid him to have
sex with your boyfriend
and then you shot it.
Now you're gonna show that to the world.
I mean, we're your friends.
What do you expect us to say?
Jesus, man.
What... am I gonna do?
I'm starting to get
worried about the traffic.
It's gonna be fine, Mom.
And I'm sorry about my phone.
Are you sure you have
time to stop by the hotel?
I'd hate to be without it today,
but I don't want you to
be late for the photos.
I'm not gonna be late for the photos, okay.
I'll stop by. I'll get your phone.
It's gonna go so quick.
How's Megan?
Oh, she looks beautiful, just lovely.
- Good.
- I'm so glad
she didn't go for that yellow dress.
- That would have been a terrible mistake.
- Right.
- Hey, Dad.
- Hey, come on.
Where are you? We're waiting for you.
I know. I'm on my way.
Well, we're really excited to meet your...
friend.
The wedding planner was thrown
to have to deal with
a last minute plus one,
but I made sure that they squeezed in
an extra chair at our table for Richard.
His name's Richie.
Is it not short for Richard?
No, Mom, it's just Richie.
Oh, do I need to change
it on his place card?
There's a card?
Look, okay, I got to go right now.
- My phone!
- I'll talk to you later.
Yeah, I'll get your phone.
Oh my God, you shaved.
Yeah, you like it?
I love it.
Come on, we're late. Let's go.
I just... I got to show you. I...
- I spilled some coffee.
- Oh, shit!
Yeah, the bus driver was
driving like a maniac,
but if I keep my jacket closed like this...
No, no, come on. I'll get you a new shirt.
- You can't tell.
- It's okay. Come on. Come on.
All right, you know, I'm just
gonna go with a white one.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- I don't know. This is...
- The other way.
I'm such an idiot.
No, no, no, it looks good.
It looks good with your...
new face.
- You okay, Pato?
- Yeah, totally.
Totally excited.
- For real?
- Ugh, I just got off the Skype with my mom.
Oh, okay.
But she's totally excited to meet you.
You know you say "totally" a lot
- when you get nervous?
- I do?
- Totally.
-  Okay.
Give me your arm. Here you go.
- Okay, okay.
- And that side, and that side.
- Where's my tie?
- I got it here. Let's do this.
Come on, we're late.
- Hold on.
- You got to button your pants though.
Oh no, come on.
Oh, shit!
- What is it?
- I didn't turn my wheels.
Fuck. Oh, God.
- I can pay for half of it.
- No, no, no.
Don't be silly. I
borrowed the car from Dom.
Fifty-eight fucking dollars!
Jesus!
Okay, so here it is on the corner.
Does that say Punjab Chinese?
Yes, it says Punjab Chinese.
Bombay meets Shanghai, I like it.
It's fusion.
Anyway, Lynn's friend's with the owner.
So they closed it in March,
but they have the lease until next week.
What?
So we get to rush in and rush out again.
Anyway, everything's here,
which is awesome because we
just need to freshen it up a bit.
- Gotcha.
- You know?
It's a one-night-only affair.
Oh, hey.
- Lynn, this is Doris.
- Hey, hi.
Hi. Hugo.
No, it's not just another pop-up.
It's the beginning of a...
a Portuguese culinary revolution.
Whoa. So...
Uh, when are people supposed
to be eating in here?
In about 28 hours.
Excellent, okay.
We're gonna need some swiffers.
- I just... a minute, okay?
- You're blocking traffic.
I know, I normally hate people like me,
but it's only gonna take a moment.
Okay, here he comes right now. See?
- He's on his way.
- You gotta move.
This is loading only.
You don't have the... where's the phone?
The front desk is saying they
don't have your mom's phone.
- Are you serious?!
- Yeah, or at least she wouldn't give it to me
'cause I don't look like a Murray.
What are you doing? Jesus.
I promise you, five more
minutes. Here, take this.
- Yo, man. Hey! What are you doing?
- Richie, stay!
Hey, Pauline. Agustín.
Uh, listen. This...
I hate this, but it's just not...
it's not coming together.
So I'm gonna have to bow out of the show.
Sorry.
Uh, I hope you have enough
time to find somebody.
Okay, uh, yeah. Thanks, bye.
Acquaint yourself with the basic dynamics
of a real bowtie.
- A standard bowtie consists of...
- What is that?
What is this voice? What is this video?
- It's so cheesy.
-  I don't know.
It's some weird YouTube Playboy thing.
Okay, you know, ah... cold hands.
You know what? Let's
just forget the bowtie.
- I got it.
- Let's forget the bowtie.
- I like a challenge.
I need to look at the phone
to look at the Google Maps.
- Could you just stop with the bow?
- Shit. Whoa.
When I say stop, I mean stop!
Okay, please.
- Okay, you know what?
- Pull over.
No, I'm just trying not
to get us killed right now.
I get it. Can you just pull over?
Okay, let me get off the
bridge first, all right?
What? No, don't get out of the car.
What are you doing?
Come on.
Come on, get out.
- You need to chill out.
- I'm chilled out, okay.
Here, smoke this. I'll drive.
You can relax, okay?
You brought pot to my sister's wedding?
To meet my family?
- Yeah, I did.
- What the fuck are you doing?
I'm not gonna smoke a joint right now.
All right, you know what?
I told you this was too soon.
I don't need to go to this thing.
- Go, have a good time.
- What, you're leaving?
- Yeah.
- No, come on, Richie.
Get back in the car.
Richie!
I'm not gonna follow
you. We're already late.
Don't. I'll be fine.
Shit.
Listen, I had the shop make
up some options for the tables.
- We have a plumbing issue.
- I know.
I got a backed up prep sink over here.
I called the plumbers.
They're on their way.
You know, I also was thinking
maybe we should paint these columns.
Well, then it will smell like paint.
Well, I can get some industrial
fans in here for over night.
It's not worth it.
We need to deal with
basic kitchen function,
and getting word out, and...
Well, then, if you could just make a call
- on the flowers.
- Flowers? Jesus, Lynn.
Are you listening?
I'm sorry.
- It's just...
- No, no, no, I'll...
You know, I'll leave the flowers here
and then whenever's a good time,
you can...
Okay.
So you think it was food poisoning?
Yeah, um, or something like that.
He actually started to
feel a little bit better,
but I told him it wasn't
worth it to risk it.
No, not if it was food poisoning.
Mm-hmm, it's a bummer too
because he was totally excited to...
meet you and Dad and Megan.
Oh, she's going to be disappointed.
Okay.
I am not going to get
upset about this grass.
The Langels have already
made a comment about it.
Well, the Langels make a
comment about everything.
Hmm, apparently,
the church gardener is being treated
for prostate cancer,
but it's just going to look
terrible in the pictures.
Well, this church needs to
get it's priorities straight.
Don't they know this is a Murray wedding?
What the hell's he doing here?
Who's that?
Is that Richie?
No.
Hi.
Hey.
Kevin, this is my mom, Danna.
- Hey, mom.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- You too.
Okay, eyes right here, guys.
Good.
- This is so crazy.
- Yeah, this is really strange.
I just thought it was weird
we both had weddings on the same weekend,
but you had your
sister's. And we had Gus's.
- Yeah, and Gus and Jon... ?
- Used to be lovers.
- What?
- Yeah, it's a big secret.
- I'm joking. They're best buds...
- God, you can't say that.
I can do what I want. Best
buddies from Dartmouth.
But I only met Gus the other week.
Really? He's very sweet.
- He's always... isn't he sweet?
- Yeah.
So where's Richie?
He, um...
I...
I kind of fucked up.
- Ooh.
- Yeah, in a big way.
Hmm.
Well, I'm glad you're here.
It's good to see a friendly face.
Yeah, it's good to see you too.
- Yeah.
- Hey, Patty.
Will you please come take
a photo with the bride?
Will you excuse me? I'm gonna
go take some pictures now.
No, no, hang on. Hang on a second.
- This is not gonna work for the bowtie, is it?
- Oh, right.
Can you do this?
- Yeah.
- Okay, everyone, right here.
Family.
- It can mess with your head, can't it?
- Yeah.
Whenever I go home,
I just regress to being 14 again.
I stay in my room, sulking,
playing Tetris.
Ooh, slick as fuck.
- You're a lifesaver.
- Yeah, go get 'em.
All right. I'm here.
Sorry.
- Can I get that...
- Glad to see you could finally make it.
Yeah, Dad, good to see you too.
Can we get the brother to line up
- with the other groomsmen there?
- Oh, yeah right.
- Back here?
- Yeah.
- Just step back over there.
- Sure.
- All right, can you see me?
- Yeah.
If I can see you, you
should be able to see me.
- Okay.
- All right.
Looking good.
- A little bit I think. What if I check?
- Great.
You got a bit red there.
Everybody's happy? Yeah?
Come on, babe. We're almost there.
So I called Pauline about the show.
- What?
- Could you slow down, baby?
Please. You're walking so fast.
Thanks.
I pulled out of the show.
Yeah, right. What, just now?
This morning.
Are you serious?
Yeah, you said you didn't want me
showing the pictures anyway.
So I figured...
I had to get you that gig.
I begged Pauline to let you in.
- What, you...
- Wait, wait, wait. What are you doing?
You said she asked you.
Oh, yeah, well, she mentioned it.
- Then I had to organize it.
- Begged her to... to what?
To let your loser boyfriend
- put up his fucking finger paintings on a wall?
- Calm down.
You needed help. You were stuck.
All right, and I knew you weren't
gonna let me give you money.
This is what you've been doing
since I moved in. Don't you see that?
- What I've been doing?
- Yeah, I don't need you to fucking save me.
I need you to... just be there for me.
Be there for you?
I fucked a guy on camera
so that you could make art.
- Does that not count for anything?
- Oh, come on.
I've seen the pictures, okay.
You didn't do that for me.
This wasn't some charitable
art donation, okay.
You were in fucking heaven.
Holy fucking shit.
- You're jealous that I got with CJ?
- No!
I'm not jealous. That's
not what it's about.
Can you even fucking hear
yourself? You set it up!
That's not what it's about, okay.
Could you just listen to me?
We're you just using him and me to get off?
No, listen. I paid him.
You paid him?
You paid a whore to fuck me?
How much?
It's $220...
an hour.
You can't even pay rent.
I know. I know it's fucked up.
I've been nothing but
supportive of your shit,
and you've been lying
to me since you moved in.
I want to fucking tear
your eyes out right now.
I just...
Fucking asshole!
So hit me. Hit me.
Hi, welcome. Have a seat.
- Eat your face off.
- That's perfect.
- See?
- Awesome.
It's like casual. You know what I'm after.
Just be you, basically.
So if I see a cockroach, I can scream?
- You can scream.
- Wait a second.
Dom, you're gonna be
out front as well, yes?
No, I'm gonna be in back.
It's fine.
Doris used to hostess
back in the day, right?
Yeah, in high school, Marie Callender's.
I was fired.
I'm... I'm sorry, but
I think that's a mistake.
You need to be out front.
Okay, hold on. Guys!
How many times? What did I say?
I said communal, right?
So that means no two-tops,
no four-tops.
Just like this, and like this,
and like this, all right? A moment outside?
All right, kids, move the tables.
Part of what we're selling here is you.
You're the main attraction.
And Taj too, of course,
but he's got to stay back there
or no one gets to eat.
Look, you know I appreciate
your funding this.
- Funding?
- But when it comes to how it's run,
I don't need you taking care of me
and watching over me
like I'm some teenager.
- Teenager, huh?
- Yeah.
Hmm, hadn't thought of it like that,
but now that you say it...
Here are the keys to the car, son.
- Don't stay out too late.
- Oh, come on.
Lynn, I didn't say I wanted you to leave...
I am your partner in...
in this.
Or is there something
else that's on your mind?
Are you angry with me?
Okay.
Look, um, you're right.
Tomorrow is yours,
so I'm gonna go.
- You need to do what you need to do.
- Come on.
- No, it's okay.
You just...
Lynn.
You see that guy over there?
The hot jock gone to seed?
Yeah, that's Cody Heller.
He's cute.
I grew up across the street from him.
Our dads are best friends.
And when we were home,
he was always really cool.
But then at school, he
would completely ignore me.
Total... cunt.
Ooh, that word sounds really weird
coming out of your mouth.
You say it all the time.
Yeah, but I'm English. We can make it work.
Really? That's like a rule?
- It's not a rule. It's a fact.
- You can say it, though.
Okay, okay.
So, um, I'm making Jon propose to you.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
Uh, mainly because I've
not been to a gay wedding
and that needs to happen yesterday.
- So...
- Don't worry. I told her
we're still way too young and
dangerous for that to happen.
Correct.
Come on, don't you want
to snatch this guy up?
You guys are both really handsome?
You should just...
Oh, yeah, yes.
Maybe one day.
Darling.
And then Patrick could be the bridesmaid.
Oh, wow, thank you. Very funny.
I was thinking more the flower girl.
Oh-ho, fuck you.
All right, flower girl.
- I got to go.
- Okay.
Hey, what's up? It's me.
Listen, I am really sorry about today.
I could still come pick you up.
We'd be back in time for cake...
which is totally not a cake.
"Totally."
I guess I'm feeling nervous.
I wonder why.
Call me if you want.
At least it's out now.
You know?
You know, when I was with CJ,
when he was on top of me...
he was fucking me...
I looked over at you, just outside of it,
and you were just... just watching me.
That's all we've become.
You over there.
Me just... trying to change it.
I'm done. I just...
You got to get your shit out.
My shit?
All of it.
I don't want to live with you anymore.
Before we all dig in here,
I just want to, first of all,
thank all of you for coming.
And a little toast to our lovely Megan,
our not so very little Megan,
- but I remember when you were little.
- Oh yeah?
Like the time you would
take your brother there
and dress him up as the Little Mermaid
and then drag him through the
mall with all your girlfriends.
It's hard to believe you're
that same little girl.
But, uh...
we particularly like the
choice you've made here in Gus.
The good thing about
it... Gus loves to golf,
so I've got someone I can take
to the invitational with me every year.
And the really nice thing about it is
he has his own money.
So thank you, Silicon Valley.
Cheers.
Hey.
You okay?
I just needed some air.
Yeah, me too.
Oh, the chicken was dry.
Good thing you didn't have the chicken.
Yeah, I know. The salmon was pretty good.
So I'm sorry you didn't
get to meet Richie tonight.
Yes, that was a shame.
Would've been the first time
you've ever met a boyfriend of mine.
I know, yes.
And I hope he's feeling better now.
I don't know. I think maybe you
should feel a little relieved.
I don't think you'd
really like him very much.
And how do you know that?
Well, he's...
Mexican first of all.
All right.
And he doesn't really have any money.
Well, neither did your
father when I met him.
He was getting his Masters.
Yeah, well...
Richie's not going to
college any time soon.
He cuts hair in shitty barber shop
and he has no real ambition
to do other than just that
and play the bass guitar.
Sounds like a real catch.
Yeah.
I knew that's how you'd feel.
Well, now how do you expect me to respond
- after a description like that?
- You know,
you're the real reason
he's not here tonight.
Richie's not sick.
I was a jerk to him today
because I was so nervous
about introducing him to you
because I know he's not the kind
of person you want me to be with.
And what kind of person is that?
Someone like Kevin or Jon.
And what's wrong with that.
They seem lovely.
They seem just like you.
You don't get it, do you, Mom?
Everyone I'm ever with,
every guy I've ever been on a date with,
I judge him based on what
you're gonna think of him.
And it's really fucking me up.
I see.
Patrick.
I know I don't say everything
you'd like me to say all the time...
and I know I had problems
when you first told us.
But I've come a long way.
And I can't help wanting
what's best for you.
And I don't think you
can blame me for Richie.
If he's not here...
that's on you, sweetie.
Is that a pot cookie?
Well, it's actually a
marshmallow krispie treat.
It's legal now in Colorado.
Oh, you want some?
No, Mom.
It really helps since
I went off the Lexapro.
I didn't know you were on Lexapro.
Well, Patrick,
if you asked me how I was
doing every now and then,
you'd know.
Franklin?
Frank?
- Hey.
- Oh, hey.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
I'm super.
- What's happened?
- Oh, nothing.
Just today.
I used to like weddings.
- Jon's drunk.
- Oh, great.
Yeah, no, I can't stand
him when he's drunk.
Are you a little bit drunk?
- Yeah.
-  Yeah.
But, see, I'm a nice drunk.
Yeah, that's good to know.
What?
I was gonna kiss you.
I'm kidding.
Okay, 'cause that would be wei...
So what do you think?
Can I pull this off?
I think it is going to be
the finest night for all these
foodie fuckers in this town.
Are you kidding?
But it ain't gonna happen
without help, darling.
Okay, are you hearing me?
'Cause some people really
do just want to help.
Those are my favorite.
Hey.
40 grand for this.
You're, uh...
you're not gonna want
one of these, are you?