We can laugh ha-ha We can sing la-la-la-la
We can make anything
Hold my hand
Make a magical land
When letters get together we go alakazam
We can run, we can slide We can hide in a box
Are you ready for some fun with the Alphablocks?
Alphablocks!
WHISTLING
- Arrr!  - Why do you always say, "Arrr!"?
Because I'm a pirate.
What's a pirate?
I am.
- Why?  - Because I do piratey things.
Like what?
Er....
I've got a hat
And I say, "Arrr!" a lot.
And that's what pirates do?
I think so.
Fast!
Aaah!
Mm. Ah. P.
Map!
T... T...
A treasure map.
Arrr!
We found a treasure map.
Will you lead us to the treasure?
OK. But I'm not a pirate.
We need to get to the island.
- Who's with me?  - Absolutely!
Anyone else?
- Rrr.  - Ah.  - Mm.  - Sss.
Rams!
Baa! Baa!
Ah-ah!
Try again!
Ff...
- Rrr.  - Ah.  - Ff.  - Teh.
Raft!
Climb aboard, shipmates!
Arr! I mean, let's go!
Fff...
Fff... Fff...
Right.
Teh-teh. There's no treasure here.
Pity you're not a pirate, R. A pirate would know what to do.
What would a pirate do?
Arrr!
Listen and I'll tell you.
A pirate wears a black eye patch
And reads old maps for pleasure
A pirate sails across the sea in search of buried treasure
A pirate does exciting things and says, "Arr!" a lot
A pirate knows just where to look because "X" marks the spot.
Did somebody say "X"?
Leave this to me.
A pirate sings, a pirate swings
A pirate laughs... Ha-har!
This letter is a pirate
This pirate's name is Rrr!