Ahhh!
After 10,000 years, I'm free!
Its time to conquer earth!
Alpha, Rita's escaped!
Recruit a team of
teenagers with attitude!
# Go, go, Power Rangers #
# Mighty Morphin Power Rangers #
# Power Rangers #
# Go, go, Power Rangers #
# You Mighty Morphin
Power Rangers #
So Tommy, are you gonna go
to the beach with us tomorrow?
I really wish I could,
but guess what.
I'm trying out for
a karate commercial.
Whoa, you mean, like,
you could be on TV?
Yeah, can you believe it?
Oh, snap!
Did I stutter?
It's an audition isn't it?
Of course I want a limo!
Hello?
Better not get your hopes up
about that screen test
'cause I've got that
commercial in the bag.
Hmmm.
So you're gonna do
something like this.
Better do a little practice first,
just in case.
Boy, oh boy, I'm pooped.
I want a day off.
But you must lead us to victory!
I don't wanna. You do it!
Yes, my Queen,
and while you rest,
I shall obliterate
those pesty Power Rangers
with the worst monsters
the earth has ever seen!
Zack!
Sorry, Bulk!
This looks like a good spot.
It's a good spot.
Hey! Ya-ya-ya-ya-ya!
( laughing )
Your friend Tommy
is history, muscle brain!
I'm gonna get this commercial!
Ya-ya! Ya-ya-ya!
Ha ha ha ha!
Let's just wait and
see about that, Bulk.
Okay, we'll see.
Here! Get to work.
I need to get a tan
before the audition.
Come on!
I need to get a tan!
( grunting )
You airhead.
I wanna get a tan, not a bath.
( laughing )
# Tommy P's real brand mayonnaise #
# Mmmmm #
Here you go, Bulk.
Enjoy the view.
Oh yeah! Oh boy,
am I gonna look fresh
for that audition!
( snoring )
Ha ha ha! Perfect! The Rangers
have let their guard down.
Now I can take them by surprise!
The part's mine, Tommy.
You might as well go home now.
( laughing )
( yelling in pain )
Don't touch my sunburn,
you dimwit!
Next!
Not you, just him.
Could you take off
the sunglasses, please?
In here.
Okay, let's see what you can do.
Yeah. All right.
Check this out.
( imitates karate yell )
Oooooooowwwww!
That's a wrap.
Good, great.
Well, I think we've got our man.
Yeah?
Kiss hollywood goodbye, Tommy.
I'm their man!
( laughing )
( giving raspberry )
Hey!
- All right!
KIM: Good one, Zack!
TRINI:
I'll get it!
( gasping )
Oh my gosh.
Putties, attack them!
It's Scorpina!
And Putties!
ZACK:
Oh man, whoa.
It's Morphin Time!
Mastodon!
Pterodactyl!
Triceratops!
Saber-tooth Tiger!
Tyrannosaurus!
Jason!
Now meet my pet worm.
What is this stuff?!
I don't know.
It's pretty strong.
Zordon, come in. Come in!
My communicator's signal is jammed.
Are any of yours getting through?!
No, what do we do?
Well, can we teleport out of here?!
No, and there seems
to be no way out!
Well keep looking.
There's got to be a way.
Throw them down the cliff
and into the ocean!
We're moving!
And it feels like we're on water!
Hang on, guys!
Ay-yi-yi-yi-yi, Zordon!
The Power Rangers are in trouble,
and we can't get through!
They will be both brave and
clever and break the cocoon.
Meanwhile,
we must contact Tommy.
( beeping )
Okay, what have your years
of karate done for you, Tommy?
Well, it's really helped me
discipline myself...
especially with my schoolwork, plus,
it's given me a lot of self-confidence.
Great!
Well, let's see what you can do.
Okay.
Whew! Well, Tommy,
we'd like to talk to you.
Ai-yi-yi-yi-yi!
Zordon, tommy's not answering!
You must keep trying, Alpha 5.
The air's getting thin.
It's hard to breath!
Yes! ( laughing )
Whoooooaaa!
Let's try our weapons!
Maybe we can blast
our way out of here!
Set them on low power
and fire on my mark!
3, 2, 1 fire!
They're breaking through the cocoon!
Ai-yi-yi-yi-yi!
Teleport them to their Zords
as soon as they escape, Alpha 5.
Warn the Rangers, Goldar sent down
Babe Ruthless,
the baseball monster.
- Hyah!
All right, log on!
Mastodon!
Time to kick it!
Triceratops! Online!
Pterodactyl! Ready to fly!
Saber-tooth Tiger!
Powered up!
( laughing )
( growling )
Play ball!
Let's do it!
Batter up!
Try my curveball!
Whoa! Oh man!
He's got Jase pinned down.
We gotta do something!
Right!
Let's come in from either side
and draw him away from Jason!
When Babe Ruthless
pitches his lightening,
all in its path shall be punished.
Rangers,
we have to take him down!
Everyone power up your weapons
and give it all you've got it!
Yeah! Way to go!
Yeah! That was awesome!
Morphin!
( beeping )
Zordon, what's happening?
The Rangers need your help.
They're at the industrial complex
in Downtown Angel Grove. Hurry!
I'm on it, Zordon!
Dragonzord!
All right!
Time for Dragonzord power!
All right! It's Tommy!
Great shot! Now let's pull it
together and show him what we got!
Nothin' to it but to do it!
Switch into remote!
Here I come!
All right!
With Dragonzord in Battle Mode,
we've got ourselves
a whole new ball game!
Jason!
We need the shield!
You're right, Billy.
Power it up!
It's bottom of the ninth,
and we need a home run!
All right! Let's do it!
Think you won the first round?
Well the worse is yet to come!
Yes, Zordon!
Scorpina is back in Angel Grove.
She's probably back in human form!
Let's go get her.
ALL:
Power Rangers!
Well, it's the power geeks!
Trap them, my pet!
And you better make
the cocoon strong!
Huh?!
This doesn't look good!
Oh no. If he traps us again,
we might never get out!
He's not gonna get us again.
We need Dinozord power now!
Let's go!
Let's do it!
Zack here!
In the groove again!
Billy! Back on track!
Trini! Ready to rock!
Kimberly! Set to soar!
Rangers!
Power up your Crystals!
ALL:
2, 1, power up!
Morphin!
Let's show him some
Megazord power!
Megazord sequence
has been initiated.
Megazord Activated!
Tommy, come in!
We need your help!
( laughing )
At last! Victory is mine!
Prepare for final destruction!
Right here, Rangers!
Morphed and ready!
( trumpet fanfare )
( cheering )
Time for Megadragonzord power!
ALL:
Log on! Full power!
RITA:
Nincompoops!
I take one day off,
and look what happens!
You'd think you bumbling fools
could do something simple like
destroy the Power Rangers,
but nooooo!
But, my Queen!
Don't you ever go after
those Power Rangers
again without me, understand?!
I didn't have anything
to do with it!
Don't be mad at me.
I didn't--
It was those stupid
monsters Finster made!
Stop yammering!
Why can't I ever win?
So how was the beach
yesterday, guys?
Well, it wasn't
exactly relaxing, Ernie.
TV ANNOUNCER:
And on the local front,
those amazing heroes
the Power Rangers
have once again successfully
defeated another attack
on the city of Angel Grove
by Rita Repulsa
and her seemingly endless
hoardes of monstrous thugs.
While the city sustained
some property damage,
no harm befell any of the citizens,
thanks to the incredible
Power Rangers.
Wow, great stuff, eh?
I tell you, you gotta love
the Power Rangers.
TV ANNOUNCER:
Well that about wraps it up.
Tommy, when are
we gonna see your commercial?
I can hardly wait myself.
I got the part, you know.
Oh really?
Say folks,
have you ever tried karate?
You might think you can learn
this intricate art on your own,
but if you tried, you could
end up looking like this.
Pretty miserable, huh?
Go sign up for classes at
the Angel Grove Karate Center
and you could look like this.
ZACK:
All right, Tommy!
TV COMMERCIAL: Come in today
and learn how to master karate
at the Angel Grove Karate Center!
( laughing )
BULK: You call yourself a
manager, Skull? This is your fault!
Captioned by Grant Brown