- SIREN WAILS
- 'Octonauts, to your stations!'
Barnacles!
Kwazii!
Peso!
- Explore!
- Rescue!
- Protect!
Octonauts!
KWAZII YAWNS
These night missions are tough, Captain.
We've been working so late, it's nearly morning.
At least all's well in the ocean.
- BARNACLES YAWNS
- It'll be great to get some sleep.
Aye.
- LOUD RUMBLE
- What's wrong?
Hmm? Nothing.
VERY LOUD RUMBLE
- If nothing's wrong, why do you keep growling?
- Huh? Oh, that's not me!
It's my belly. I guess I'm hungry.
Hm, come to think of it, my belly's feeling a bit empty too.
How about you, Peso? Are you hungry?
There's a monkey?! Where?
Ha-ha! No monkey, Peso. We're all just tired and hungry.
I see a nice sea-grass meadow coming up.
What do you say we stop there for breakfast?
- Aye!
- Yes, please!
I'm so glad Tunip packed all this food for us.
Me too. I'm starving now.
Ooh, kelp cakes - my favourite!
Bleugh! Liquorice flavour - my least favourite!
I can never get these thingies to work.
Oops! Ha-ha! Sorry.
Mm! Strawberry-jam flavoured kelp. Now that's more like it!
I'll have some of that, please.
Look over there!
Sea horses!
What in the seven seas...? Look at those two!
They're dancing like some crazy underwater merry-go-round.
I've never seen anything like it!
Let's investigate.
A-hem! Excuse me! Sea horses!
We couldn't help but notice your amazing dance.
Aw, thanks, man.
It's a sea horse thing. We do a special dance of love.
And change colours to show how much we like each other.
Yeah. I'm Sonny and this is Janice.
We are the Octonauts.
I'm Captain Barnacles and this is Kwazii and Peso.
Good to meet you, Sonny and Janice.
Isn't she wonderful?
One look and I knew she was the one for me.
Oh, Sonny! You're so sweet.
They certainly look happy together.
Captain, they, em...seem kind of busy with their dance...
and everything.
Hm. Let's, er, head back to the Octopod.
Bye, Janice and Sonny.
- So long, man.
- Be happy!
How much further, Captain?
Not too far. Water is getting a bit rough though.
- BEEP!
- 'Octopod to GUP-A. Come in, please.'
We read you, Dashi. Is everything OK?
There's a big storm heading this way.
Suggest you return to the Octopod as soon as possible.
Thanks, Dashi! We're on our way back now. Barnacles out.
Avast! Look at the fishies, mates.
They're all heading for cover.
When a storm approaches, fish know to head for deeper water.
It's safer down below. We'll do the same.
Phew! Home sweet Octopod.
This storm could last a while.
- It's a big one, Captain.
- Hm.
- Huh?
- Oh! Whoa!
Look, it's Janice!
- She's in trouble!
- Argh!
Peso, sound the Octo alert!
- SIREN WAILS
- Octonauts, to the launch bay!
Octonauts, our sea horse friend Janice is lost in the storm.
We're going out to save her.
GUP-A's all powered up and ready to go, Cap.
Peso, Kwazii, into the GUP-A.
Yow!
Tweak, open the Octo hatch!
Right away, Cap.
Hold on, Octonauts.
This could get bumpy!
Grrr! Ugh! Agh! Ugh!
Ya! 'Tis a rough one, maties! Yow!
Flappity flippers! You're enjoying this, aren't you, Kwazii?
Aye! There be nothing like an ocean storm to make a pirate feel alive!
Ha-ha!
Ugh! Keep your eyes peeled for Janice.
I don't see her anywhere.
There she be, holding on by her tail!
Aaargh! Oh!
Grrrr! Ugh!
Oh! Whoa!
I'll get as close to her as I can and, Kwazii, you...
- Kwazii!
- Yow!
I'm coming, me hearty!
Oh! Whoa!
Ugh!
- Ah!
- Oh!
Gotcha!
I'll get the water tank ready for Janice, Captain.
Good thinking, Peso!
Thanks for saving me.
How did you get dragged into this storm?
The water just swept me away. Sea horses aren't very good swimmers.
We go where the water takes us.
Come to the Octopod and rest till the storm is over.
But we need to find Sonny. The water pulled him away too and I'm worried.
He's about to have our babies.
In that case, we'd best... What did you say?!
Sonny is about to give birth to our babies. I hope he's OK.
But...daddies don't have babies, mums do! Don't they?
Not when you're a sea horse.
Daddy sea horses carry babies in a special pouch
until they're ready to be born.
Well, I'll be a sea monkey's uncle!
Janice, on my honour as an Octonaut,
we'll find Sonny and make sure he's safe.
Barnacles to Shellington and Dashi.
- Captain?
- Go ahead, Captain.
We need to find out which way the storm is headed.
A sea horse has been swept along with it.
- Aye, sir!
- Leave it to us.
Got it! Captain, the storm is moving over the reef
and then past some big rock formations.
We'll send a map right now.
Good work, Octonauts.
We'll search the reef first.
Do you see him?
Ach, not yet.
We'll check the rocks next.
Look out!
What if we can't find him?
Don't worry, we won't give up!
We still need to search that kelp forest up ahead.
We don't want to get the GUP-A stuck in this kelp.
We'll get out and search for Sonny.
- Sonny?
- Are you here, matey?
- Sonny!
Hm, at least the storm is finally calming down.
But where's Sonny? I guess we'll never find him.
Ah! Look!
A sea horse!
Excuse me, are you Janice?
Who, me? No, I'm Kwazii and I'm not a sea horse, I'm a...
I'm Janice.
Janice! Thank goodness you found us!
Sonny is about to give birth! You're just in time.
Oh! Where is he?
Please take us to him now. I'm a medic - I can help.
Over there. Near that seaweed.
Come on, Sonny. Oh...
Congratulations, Janice. >
It's a boy!
And a girl!
Oh, my!
And another girl.
And a boy and a boy
and another girl
and a boy
and another girl!
Hey, Janice!
Sonny! I'm so glad I found you!
Janice, you're safe!
Meet the children.
Dada!
Our children are so beautiful!
How can we ever, ever thank you?
Oh, it was nothing. All in the line of duty.
BABY SEA HORSES GIGGLE
Aw, they're so adorable!
- What are their names?
- That little guy is Barney, short for Barnacles.
That handsome nipper is Kwazii.
- That one's Peso.
- That's his sister Kwazetta...
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
E-mail subtitling@bbc.co.uk