Hello, Doug, this is Dr Frasier Crane.
I'm listening.
'It's about my mother. She's getting on
now and she hasn't much of a life.
'She doesn't want to do anything,
go anywhere.
'She literally hangs around the house
all day. It is very frustrating.'
Can we go back for a second?
You said your mother "literally"
hangs around the house.
It's my pet peeve:
You mean she figuratively
hangs around the house.
To literally hang around the house
you'd have to be
a bat or a spider monkey.
- 'Can I tell you my pet peeve? '
- Sure.
'I hate intellectuals with superiority
complexes who nitpick your grammar
'when you ask for help.
That's what I've got a problem with.'
I think what he means is,
"that is a thing,
with which he has a problem."
It's time for a station break.
We'll be back after this message
from "Pizza, Pizza, Pizza".
Wanna hear my pet peeve?
You're in a store, the clerk
is helping you and the phone rings.
So he starts taking care of them.
You go, "I came here in person,
while some joker at home
"in his underwear is getting
first-rate service." Don't you hate that?
Actually, I do most of my shopping
by phone.
This got me thinking about my father.
He doesn't do much, either.
He just sits around watching TV
or doing the occasional crossword.
- What does your mother do?
- Wisconsin Attorney General.
- No, really?
- Really.
Oh... I guess that helps fill her day.
She says, "Crime never stops,
even in the dairy state."
I don't think public office
is for Dad, but...
Maybe I can find him a hobby.
Any suggestions?
Mom likes to water-ski a little.
She hikes, oil paints...
Oh, she likes archaeology.
She's on a dig in Honduras right now.
Well, maybe I could get him
a wood-burning set.
Is Dad still asleep?
Yes, with the dog.
Eddie's legs are going like mad.
He's dreaming of chasing rabbits.
But why is your father twitching?
Just about done with this thing.
Your dad will love it.
I was walking through the hobby shop.
It was "Eureka!"
I actually said, "Eureka!"
Ah, yes. There are a million stories
in the naked city.
Now, if we could just find a naked one.
Dr Crane! You naughty boy!
Peeking in on other people's privacy!
If people were concerned
about their privacy,
would they leave their blinds open
where you can see the mantel mirror
that reflects to the waterbed?
Your father's coming.
Stand in front of it.
We'll make this a surprise.
- Hi, guys.
- How was your nap?
I had the strangest dream.
A woman with bad breath
was licking my face.
Hey, where'd you just come from?
I got a surprise for you.
Hey, a telescope! That's a beaut!
What's the occasion?
- I just thought you'd like it.
- That's great, thanks!
I saw on the news,
there's a bunch of falcons
on the Columbia Tower.
- I can watch them from here.
- Forget the falcons.
You can see everything in that building.
I'd lock people up for that.
It's innocent. Just think of it as having
like 100 more channels to watch.
Just look,
people going about their lives.
There's an old couple watching telly.
Next door, an attractive young woman
is working at a computer,
while below her a burly man
is sopping up a large pool of blood.
- Oh, God!
- What?
Oh, Daddy!
Nah, that's tomato juice,
you can see the can.
- Yes, she is a looker!
- There's a voyeur in all of us.
Let's see what else
the Seattle skyline has to offer.
I say we make a strict rule. If anybody
does anything nasty, we move on.
Agreed?
I said "agreed"?
Yeah.
There's a lady with a telescope
looking back at us!
- What shall we do?
- Hide!
Every time I do something bad,
I get caught!
Hi! How you doing?
What are you doing?
- She's waving, I'm waving back.
- Don't do that.
Why not?
Wait, she's writing something!
She's holding it up.
It says, "Hello, there, stranger."
- Daphne, get me that pad and pen!
- What for?
I'll answer her.
Write down, "My name is Martin."
You shouldn't encourage her.
I don't want people looking in on us.
I don't think I made my bed today.
Is she writing anything else?
- Yeah..."My name is Irene."
- Her name's Irene.
- Thank you.
- Wait, she's writing something else!
"Is that Dr Crane from the radio
hiding there behind you?"
It does not say that!
Oh, it does say that!
Hello!
- Her oldest son is an accountant.
- He was the breech birth?
- No, that's the dentist in Boise.
- Oh, right.
He's got the wife that won't let him visit.
I can't stand her.
Morning, Dad, Daphne.
Morning, Irene.
When you were a kid, what was that
skin condition you had on your butt?
Pityriasis rosea.
- How do you spell that?
- Why?
Irene and I
are exchanging family histories.
- Don't tell your girlfriend about that.
- She's not my girlfriend!
You've been exchanging notes
for the last three days.
If you were in the sixth grade,
you'd be sitting in a tree, k-i-s-s-i-n-g.
- Let me borrow that pad.
- What are you doing?
I'm going to help along
your little romance
and maybe save a small forest.
- I'm giving her our number.
- No, don't do that!
- Why?
- She'll think I'm being too forward.
You met peeping into her apartment.
She won't call.
- Want to bet?
- Yeah, five bucks.
(Phone)
- Aren't you going to answer it?
- You get it.
Dad, it's for you.
Hello? No, no, this is Frasier, hi.
I'm fine.
It, uh...
gets a little flaky
when the weather is dry.
- Tell her I'm not home!
- She knows you're home.
She can see you through the telescope.
- Come on, you're just a little nervous.
- Hello?
Hi...
Yeah, it's nice hearing yours.
Can you hold on a minute?
Would you two get out of here?
I'm getting a very good
feeling about this.
- You really think he's interested in her?
- Yes, I think so.
Do you want to hear something cute?
I made him this rich coffee cake.
You know what a sweet tooth he has.
And he wouldn't even take one bite,
because as he put it, "Women
don't like a spare tyre on a man."
That's so cute.
Oh, it's funny.
The twists and turns of fate.
If I had tried to set Dad up
with a woman, he would've refused.
But I go out, get him a telescope
and it kindles this romance.
It's kismet.
- Well?
- What?
- What happened?
- We talked.
Was she nice, interesting?
What did she say?
- A lot of stuff.
- So, you'll be seeing each other?
- She wanted to, but I said no.
- Why?
She's not my type.
Oh, coffee cake!
We got any butter around here?
You know the pompous twit
who's president of my wine club?
At the meeting, I convinced my fellow
psychiatrists to play a prank on him.
Thinking he was tasting
a Chateau Petrus,
he was in fact
sipping a Fourcas-Dupre.
- You see, we'd switched the labels.
- What scamps you are.
There he was, proclaiming the Petrus
to be the superior wine,
and none of us
could contain our laughter.
His face must have turned redder
than a Pichon-Longueville.
Of course, as so often happens,
roughhouse turns to tears.
At the end of the evening,
he tendered his resignation.
That must have ruined the evening.
- Not really, I'm the new president.
- Kudos, indeed.
Oh! Are Dad and his lady friend
still playing telescope footsie?
- What was her name?
- Irene. No, they've broken it off.
Already? I thought it was going well.
It was, then they spoke once
and then Dad said she wasn't his type.
It's over. He's cut her out of his life.
I just don't understand why he did that.
Who knows
why anybody does anything?
Remind me again
what you do for a living.
It was one phone call.
How can you make a judgment
about someone from one phone call?
Remind me again
what you do for a living.
I suppose it could be any number
of reasons - fear of rejection, shyness...
Maybe she just wasn't his type.
If only we knew someone who was.
I know! Maris's lovely Aunt Patrice
is in town visiting from Washington DC.
Maybe we should set Dad up with her?
I've met Aunt Patrice. She's a loon.
Do this for me.
When Aunt Patrice visits, Maris dives
under the duvet
with a two-week migraine,
and I'm left holding the bag,
literally and figuratively.
No, I don't think so.
I know Dad. Don't meddle.
- At least say hello to Aunt Patrice.
- I'm not driving out there.
She's out in the car.
- You left her in the car?
- I cracked open a window.
Oh, then she's fine.
No, calm down, son.
Listen to Daddy.
It's just a bad dream, I promise you.
Senator Thurmond is not in your closet.
That's a good boy. All right.
You go back to bed now...
I love you, too.
I'll see you next weekend.
OK, bye-bye.
- How's Freddy?
- He's fine.
He thanks you
for the toy gun you gave him.
Or what he can remember of it before
Lilith smashed it with a croquet mallet.
Oh, it's such a beautiful night.
The city is lit up like a jewel.
Oh, look, there's Irene!
She's sitting in her window
wearing a stunning green dress.
But her face... It's so sad!
Oh... Oh, she's holding a note.
It says,
"Martin, was it something I wrote?"
Will you cut it out.
Irene is not sitting in her window!
All right, but she might as well be.
(Doorbell)
- Ever met a woman who's not the one?
- Yes. Five years after I married her.
Hello, there Frasier.
Niles! I was specifically
not expecting you.
You remember Aunt Patrice?
Of course, Aunt Patrice.
I don't recall when we met,
but I remember
a lot of laughing, dancing.
- My husband's funeral.
- Yes! Of course!
Of course,
the laughter was to hide our tears.
- Let me take your wrap.
- We were driving and I thought,
"We're just a couple of short ferry rides
from Frasier's." So...
...we decided to pop over.
Is this the charming gentleman
you were talking about?
You bloodhound,
you've treed another one.
Yes, this is my dad.
How are you, Patrice?
I'm Martin Crane, this is Daphne Moon.
- Nice to meet you.
- Please.
What brings you to Seattle?
I came to see Maris,
but she's taken to her bed again.
I still have no idea how tall she is.
Patrice and I've had a great time.
If you call sitting in your waiting room
reading old magazines a great time,
then, yes, we had a laugh riot.
Now I know where Maris
gets her sense of humour.
Why don't I pop in the kitchen
and get us all some refreshments.
A capital idea.
We'll join you and give these kids
time to get to know one another.
- I told you not to bring her here.
- I ran out of ways to entertain her.
We went to the arboretum,
a fashion show,
we even spat off the top of the Space
Needle. I'm sorry, I cracked.
That woman is not Dad's type.
You never know when love can bloom
between two different people. Daphne?
I never thought opposites attract.
Neither do I. We're alike.
- We can't leave Dad alone with her.
- I'm sure they're doing fine.
D'go y'gou sp'geak g'g -speak'g?
- I was afraid of this.
- What?
D'go y'gou sp'geak g'g -speak'g?
Niles, I think
she's having a stroke or something.
No Dad, it's just g-speak.
- Come again?
- She trots it out at parties.
You just put a "g" in every syllable.
So, you would be M'gar'g 'tin g'Crane.
Just say it with me.
Come on: M'gar'g 'tin...
I don't think Dad's interested.
- Oh, b'ge a good sp'gort, N'giles.
- What?
- "Be a sport, Niles."
- B'ge a'g sp'gort, ta-dah!
Dad, you still have your billy club?
It's in my top drawer.
It's all the rage in Washington.
You know who speaks it all the time?
G'george Ste'g 'pha'g 'no'g 'poul'g 'os.
I got pizza rolls but the expiration date
was yesterday. Are we game?
That's not necessary, Daphne.
We don't want to spoil our appetites
for that dinner in 20 minutes.
That's right, that dinner in 20 minutes!
I told you we shouldn't have
just stopped by.
- These people have plans.
- How I envy them.
It was such a pleasure meeting you.
- Likewise.
- Oh, no. You can do better than that!
(Giggles)
Oh, I look forward to
my next trip to Seattle!
If you're ever in Washington.
I'm in the b'gook.
What the hell was that?
- I feel sorry for the poor thing.
- I feel sorry for Niles.
That's who I'm talking about.
- You know I saw what you just did.
- What did I do?
When she went to hug you,
you moved away.
- Wouldn't you?
- You moved away from the window.
You didn't want Irene to see you.
You care about her.
Go chase yourself.
You do. Something is stopping
you from having a relationship with her.
You won't let go of this thing!
- No, I won't.
- All right.
- Irene's middle name is Rose.
- So?
Rose is a nice name.
It was Mother's middle name.
- Yeah.
- Oh, Dad.
Look, you can't feel guilty about that.
Mom's been gone for six years now.
Your feelings for Irene are separate
from those for Mom. If Mom was here,
- she'd want you to get on with your life.
- OK. When I'm ready.
Thanks Frasier. I guess I don't say it
often enough but you're a good kid.
Thanks. There's something
I don't say often enough...
There's nothing
you don't say often enough.
Right, Dad.
I couldn't help but overhear.
That was a very nice thing to say.
Yeah, he's a good kid.
Strangely, I could have sworn
Irene's middle name was Marie.
- No.
- I can check. I still have all our notes.
All right, I had to tell him something.
He just won't believe me
when I tell him Irene isn't my type.
- You sure?
- You gonna get on my back, too?
No, but I was wondering
if the reason why things didn't work out
between you and Irene was... well...
- What?
- Well, maybe...
if you weren't a bit self-conscious
about your hip?
That's ridiculous.
I'm glad to hear that. You don't have
anything to be self-conscious about.
With that silvery mane,
twinkling blue eyes and whisky voice,
you're quite a package.
- Yeah, I'm quite a catch.
- You are.
And you know as well as I do,
history is full of sexy limpers.
For instance, Franklin D Roosevelt.
Of course,
he didn't limp so much as roll.
Toulouse-Lautrec.
Although he was a little person.
Still, he did well with the ladies.
Of course, they were all prostitutes.
But he was French -
there's no explaining their taste.
- What's your point?
- I guess I don't have one. It's just me.
But there is one little thing,
every time you went to the telescope
to see Irene, you hid your cane.
I just put it off to the side
so I wouldn't trip over the damn thing.
I knew there was a good reason.
It must feel awful silly
when that cane trips you up.
- Hurry up! She'll be here any minute.
- All right.
Have I got this tie on right?
It needs a minor adjustment.
What's all this hair on it?
The only way I can get the knot right,
is if I tie it on Eddie first.
Has dating changed much
in the last 40 years?
Well, the wardrobe
is a little different, but...
your ultimate goal is still the same.
- I'm glad you changed your mind.
- Me too. Thanks for our little talk.
Yeah, my pleasure.
Let's see, you got a hankie. Terrific.
- Got your keys? Don't be out too late.
- Frasier!
Just busting your chops.
(Doorbell)
Oh, my God!
Will you two relax?
A word to the wise...
If she asks you up to her place
after dinner, close the drapes.
Hi, Irene.
Nice to finally meet you.
# Hey baby, I hear the blues are calling
Tossed salads and scrambled eggs
# Mercy!
# And maybe I seem a bit confused
Well, maybe, but I got you pegged
# But I don't know what to do with those
Tossed salads and scrambled eggs
# They're calling again #
Good night everybody!