this will be the day we've waited for
this will be the day we open up the door
i don't wanna hear your absolution
hope your ready for a revolution
welcome to a world of new solutions
welcome to a world of bloody evolution
in time-your heart will open minds
a story will be told
and victory is in a simple soul
本字幕由RWBY Translation Group翻译，翻译：（你们填吧），初期字幕&时轴：茶刀子 后期&特效（望天
(Vomit)
Ruby and Yang:WHOAAAAAA
Yang: The view from Vale’s caught nothing on this.
Ruby:Oh sis, that kid’s got a collapsable staff!
Oooh she’s got a fire sword!
Ruby:Oow…
Yang: Easy there, little sister…
They’re just weapons.
Ruby: JUST WEAPONS?
They’re an extension of ourselves.
They are a part of us!
OOOH they’re so cool!
Yang: Well, why can’t you swoon over your own weapon?
Aren’t you happy with it?
Ruby: Of COURSE I am happy with Crescent Rose!
I just really like seeing new ones.
It’s like meeting new people.
but better
Yang: Ruby, come ON. Why don’t you go try and make some friends of your own?
Ruby: But why would I need friends when I have you?
Yang: Well….Actually my friends are here now and I have to …
Ruby: Wait! Where are you going?
Are we supposed to go to our dorms?
Where are our dorms?
Do we have dorms?
Ah…I don’t know what I am doing…
Weiss: What are you doing!
Ruby: Ah.Sorry..
Weiss: SORRY? Do you have any Idea of the damage you could’ve caused?
Ruby:Uhhh…
Weiss: Gimme that!
This is dust! Mined and purified from the Schnee Quarry!
Ruby: Uh…
Weiss:What are you? Brain dead?
Dust! Fire! Water! Lightning! Energy!
Uh… Are you even listening to me?
Is ANY of this sinking in?
What do you have to say for yourself?
Ruby: Achoo!
Weiss: Unbelievable!
This is exactly the kind of thing I was talking about!
Ruby: I’m really…REALLY sorry!
Weiss: Ugh! You complete dolt!
What are you even doing here?
Aren’t you a little young to be attending beacon?
Ruby: Well…I….uh…
Weiss: This isn’t your ordinary combat school
it’s not just sparring and practicing, you know.
We’re here to fight monsters so
watch where you’re going!
Ruby: Hey, I said I was sorry, princess!
Blake: It’s heiress, actually.
Weiss Schnee
heiress to the Schnee Dust Company
one of the largest producers of the energy propellant in the world.
Weiss: Finally, some recognition.
Blake: The same company infamous for its controversial labor forces and questionable business partners.
Weiss: Wha…How dare….The nerve of…
(Ruby:Creepy laugh)
Ugh!
Ruby: I promise I will make this up to you!
HAmm...
I guess I’m not  the only one having a rough first day…
So, what’s
Welcome to Beacon
Jaune:Hey
I’m Jaune.
Ruby: Ruby
Pffft….Aren’t you the guy that threw up on the ship?
Jaune: All I am saying is that motion sickness is a much more common problem than people let on!
Ruby: Look, I’m sorry.
Vomit boy was just the first thing that came to mind.
Jaune: Oh yea? What if I called you crater face?
Ruby:Hey, that explosion was an accident!
Jaune: Well, the name’s Jaune Arc, short sweet, rolls off the tongue, ladies love it.
Ruby: Do they?
Jaune: They will
Well…
I hope they will
My mom always says that
never mind
Ruby: Ehehehe
so-I got this thing
Jaune: Whoa! Is that a scythe?
Ruby: It’s also a customizable, high impact sniper rifle.
Janue: A what?
Ruby: It’s also a gun.
Jaune: Oh….THAT’S COOL!
Ruby: So what do you got?
Jaune:Oh Uh
I got this sword?
Ruby:Ooooo
yea…I got a shield, too.
Ruby: So…What do they do?
Jaune: Whoa! %^#@*&$!
The shield gets smaller
so when I get tired of carrying it
I can just...put it away
Ruby: But…wouldn’t they weigh the same?
Jaune: Yea….it does.
Ruby: Well…..I’m kind of a dork when it comes to weapons.
I guess I did go overboard in designing it
Jaune: Wait…you MADE that?
Ruby: Of course!
All students at signal forge their own weapons!
Didn’t you make yours?
Jaune: It’s a hand-me-down
My great great grandfather used it to fight in a war.
Ruby: Sounds more like a family heirloom to me
Well, I like it.
Not many people have an appreciation of the classics these days.
Jaune: Yea…the classics.
Ruby: So why did you help me out back there? In the court yard.
Jaune: Eh…why not?
My mom always says, strangers are just friends you haven’t met yet.
Ruby:Hm...
hey where are we going?
Jaune:Oh, I don’t know, I was following you!
You….You think there might be a directory?
Maybe a…food court?
Some sort of…recognizable landmark?
(Ruby: Snicker)
Jaune: Is that….Is that a no?
Ruby:(Laugh)That’s a no.