Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
All aboard!
Woo-woo!
CHUGGINGTON!
# We're trainees, we're making tracks
# Wheels to the rails Clackety-clack!
# Running on time, passengers to take
# Hauling loads, pick-ups to make
# Riding the rails
# A train-tastic crew
# Honk your horns, toot-toot!
# Toot-toot!
# Chuggington
# Chugga-chugga-chugga-chugga
# Chugga-chugga-chugga Chugga-chugga-chugga
# Chugga-chugga-chugga-chugga Chuggington. #
CHUGGINTON!
LAUGHTER
It's a caterpillar!
- Ha-ha-ha!
- Good one, Emery!
EMERY'S HORN TOOTS
HORN TOOTS
Hello, young E-mail!
S-s-super day! Innit, P-p-puffer Pete?
You've got me down to a T, young earwig!
HUMMING
- Having a chug-wash?
- Oh!
- Don't forget to wash behind your gears!
Oh-ho-ho! You do make me laugh, you're so funny!
DING-DING-DONG!
Attention, Chuggers! Today a TV crew will be filming here!
Please just go about your business and be as helpful as possible!
WOW!!
Emery, you're a star in the making if ever I saw one.
- You must make sure they film you!
- No, who'd want to watch me?
Oh-ho-ho, come on! You'll be perfect!
Emery, the crew need someone to show them around. I said you'd help them.
Wayhey! On my way, Vee!
HORN HONKS
Brewster, did you hear about the TV crew?
- Yeah!
- With your brains and my good looks, we're gonna be famous!
Pfft! Yeah, right!
- Brewster?
- Yes, Vee.
- Emery is helping the TV crew today,
so I'd like you to fill in for him.
Cool! Today I'm a passenger train!
- I LOVE it!
The cool buildings, the dramatic skyline, it's so...so...urban.
I'm Emery. I'll be your wheels today.
Mind the gap between the doors and the platform.
This chugger is ready to depart.
EMERY'S HORN TOOTS
Chuggers! This city's beating heart, its pumping muscles!
Let's lift them out of their humdrum lives and make them,
for a nanosecond, EXTRAORDINARY!
Wow! Looks like Alwyn was right! I AM going to be on TV! I could be a star!
La-la-laaa! La la la la!
La-la-la-la...
STOP!
Look! An ordinary chugger, doing an everyday thing!
That's what we want!
La-la-laaa! La la la la! La la la la la laaa!
Choo-ch-ch-ch... Oh!
Hello!
Aaand cut!
I expect it'll be your turn next, Emery.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Mind your bumpers, coming through, ha-ha!
Oooh, gorgeous!
Aaaand action!
Aaaand cut!
Fabulous! Oh, he's cute!
- And so shiny!
- Ha-ha-ha.
OK. Who's next?
I know...you!
I can't believe it!
Who's the oldest chugger in town?
Yep! I'm 150 years young! So I could tell you a thing or two!
Did you know, that back in the glory days of steam, oh, we're going back
some time now, I was just a young, young chugger..
..and he'd say - that's Speedy McAllister,
the one I talked about. Or was it Cannonball Cooper?
- "Pete" he'd say,
- DING-DING-DONG!
Puffer Pete to the rolling stock yard!
Message received and understood, Vee!
SNORING
- And cut!
- Don't have to, the tape ran out 30 minutes ago.
OK! Now, let's hear from the young generation.
I'm young!
Yeah, you are!
So why don't you take me to meet some of your friends?
Ohhh!!
So yeah, there's always some stuff that needs to be fixed.
Because, you know, stuff breaks.
Huh? Aah!
LAUGHTER
Ha-ha-ha-ha! Did we get that?
- Yeah.
- Ha-ha-ha!
But I'M the funny one!
Time for one more shot, let's make it a good one.
I know! A passenger chugger!
My turn at LAST!
HORN TOOTS
- Good luck, Emery!
- Thanks, Alwyn!
- Where do you want me?
- Um, could you back up?
More.
Perfect!
Wait there till we grab this last shot!
Huh?
Aaaand action!
But he's doing my job! I'm the passenger chugger!
Approaching platform! Preparing to stop!
Watch your step, please!
And cut!
Cool! When can we see it?
- There'll be a screening later.
- Honking horns! I can't wait!
I'm gonna be a star!
You can come back now, um, what's his name again?
Invisible!
Fine! I know when I'm not wanted.
EMERY MUTTERS
We need something to tie it together.
- A presenter?
- Oooh, I like! Who can we get?
We need someone fabulous, obviously. Talented, magnetic...
Not too magnetic, there's a lot of metal around here, ha-ha!
And funny! You know who'd be perfect? Emm...emm...
emm...emm...
Emery?!
Action Chugger!
Huh?!
I'm helpful, I'm strong, I get the job done!
Look out, film crew! Here I come!
Action Chugger, reporting for duty!
Mic him up!
BEEPING
There's a message coming through! A chugger's in distress!
Sorry! Gotta fly!
Someone needs ACTION CHUGGER!
He's number one! He's helpful, he's strong! Oops, hold on, he's gone!
- Ha-ha-ha!
- Hey, who is this guy? He's funny!
Huh?
Think you could make more jokes?
- Does Puffer Pete talk a lot?
- Ha-ha! Who needs Action Chugger?
We've got...Hilarious Emery!
Ha-ha! This'll be the funniest film ever!
HORN TOOTS
Special announcement!
This chugger is taking you on a tour of Chuggington!
ALL: YAAY! WOO! YAY!
This'll be good, Emery's so funny!
I always could spot talent!
Here we have Alwyn, a bit past her prime.
What's behind your gears, dear? You're covered with grime!
Oops! Pardon you!
Ha-ha-ha!
Oh! Well, really!
Now, we go to Hodge, Eddie's good mate. He's a bit clumsy, look out!
Oops! Too late!
I was just nervous because of the cameras!
I'm NOT clumsy!
- 'I'm 150 years young!'
- The oldest chugger round here is Puffer Pete.
He talks so much, he can put you to sleep!
ALL: OOH!
I think I've seen enough!
It's time to leave Chuggington, so I'll take a bow.
My name is Emery, bye-bye for now!
YAAY!
Hooray! Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Huh? Why'd they all leave?
- I think you hurt their feelings.
- But my jokes were really funny!
Now that I think about it, maybe you went too far.
Oh no! I didn't mean to! They're all my friends! What can I do?
I've got an idea - mic him up!
Special announcement!
EMERY'S HORN TOOTS
This chugger wants to apologise.
What I should have said was Alwyn is an engine with such style and grace
and Hodge always puts a smile on my face.
If you want a great story, give Puffer Pete a call.
Chuggington really is the best place of all.
I was trying to be funny, but my jokes went too far!
Having friends means much more than being a star.
Please forgive me.
Well, seeing as you put it so nicely, youngster...
..of course we will!
- Yeah!
- That's more like it!
Be yourself! We think you're funny just the way you are!
Friends?
ALL: FRIENDS!
And that's a wrap!
ALL: Ha-ha-ha-ha!
# Chugginton
# Chugga-chugga-chugga-chugga Chuggington
# Chuggintgon
# Chugga-chugga-chugga Chugga-chugga-chugga
# Chugga-chugga-chugga-chugga Chuggington! #
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org