What are you doing here?
Oh.
Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
I just need some clean clothes.
You know your way.
Yeah.
That was all.
You know the dangers of starting to box again.
Let me worry about that.
You don't want anything to do
with my life for now, right?
Okay.
I'm sorry for bothering you. Next time I'll knock.
Hey, Olli.
I urgently need an espresso.
I want to surprise Marlene with a design for a suit.
A fancy dress for her first stage show.
What do you think?
Classic-conservative or rather provocative-sexy?
Olli?
When did he stop talking?
Do you know what a shitty feeling it is?
To come home to an empty apartment
where nobody's waiting for you?
You ran into Christian.
He was here earlier and picked up some stuff.
And? Did you talk?
No! And I wouldn't know what about.
We're having stress and he immediately
hops into bed with Jessica.
But I've accused him of that so many times,
I can't even hear it myself anymore.
I thought a bit of distance would be good for us, but...
Everything reminds me of him.
The books, the cups... - Olli.
You have to take another step. Get past this.
I know it's easier said than done, but...
Deal with your memories.
How am I supposed to do that?
Make sure that a new phase
can begin between the two of you.
Without these memories
standing in your way all the time.
Come on in.
Olli?!
It's you. Hey.
I'm sorry for interrupting, but... it's important.
Has a package arrived for me?
No, this is your stuff.
The rest is outside.
W...W...What do you mean "my stuff".
What's that all about?
I'm sorry, Christian, but there is no other way.
I can't think about you and our relationship
if I constantly come in contact with your things.
I simply can't cope.
Well, it looks to me like you
want to end our relationship.
No.
But I realized that it's not enough
for you to move out,
while our whole life and all our stuff
is in the apartment.
I'm sorry.