Youtube subtitles download by mo.dbxdb.com
>> Sonny: [exhales]
ALL RIGHT, LET'S HOPE THAT
T CAN KEEP WILL AWAY LONG
ENOUGH.
>> Will: T, HI.
>> Tad: OH, HEY, WILL.
>> Will: WHERE'S SONNY?
>> Tad: OH, HE JUST WENT OUT FOR
A SECOND.
HE SHOULD BE RIGHT BACK.
>> Allie: WILL!
>> Will: OH, YOU'RE WAY BIGGER
THAN ARIANNA.
>> Allie: 'CAUSE I'M HER AUNT.
>> Will: YES, YOU ARE.
THIS IS A GREAT SURPRISE, DAD.
>> Lucas: YEAH, I'M GLAD TO SEE
YOU HERE TOO.
>> Will: TOO?
YOU MEAN YOU GUYS DIDN'T COME
HERE JUST TO SEE ME?
>> Lucas: OH, NO, NO.
YOUR SISTER'S DANCE CARD IS
FULL.
>> Allie: RAFE!
>> Rafe: OH, MY GOD.
HEY.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
APPRECIATE THAT YOU TOOK ARIANNA
OUT FOR THE AFTERNOON, GABI.
BUT ARE YOU SURE THAT YOU CAN
STAY OUT THAT LONG?
NO, I'M NOT UP TO ANYTHING.
OKAY, THANKS AGAIN.
IT'S PERFECT.
[cell phone rings]
>> Rafe: WELL, THANKS FOR
BRINGING ALLIE BY TO SEE ME.
>> Lucas: YEAH, NO PROBLEM.
DIDN'T HAVE MUCH CHOICE.
SHE'S KIND OF LIKE HER MOTHER
THAT WAY.
SHE GETS WHAT SHE WANTS.
>> Rafe: YEAH.
>> Tad: WILL?
SONNY NEEDS YOU BACK HOME AT THE
APARTMENT.
>> Will: HE DOES?
WHAT FOR?
>> Tad: I'M NOT SURE.
HE JUST SAID HE NEEDED YOU BACK
HOME, BUT NOTHING TO WORRY
ABOUT.
IT JUST SOUNDED IMPORTANT.
>> Will: WOW.
OKAY, YOU GUYS HAVE FUN.
>> Lucas: WE'LL SEE YOU LATER,
OKAY?
>> Will: ALL RIGHT.
>> Will: WHAT'S THIS ALL ABOUT?
>> Sonny: [clears throat]
GABI TOOK ARIANNA OUT FOR
THE AFTERNOON.
>> Will: T TOLD ME YOU SAID I
HAD TO GET HOME RIGHT AWAY, THAT
IT WAS URGENT.
>> Sonny: IT IS.
IT'S URGENT FOR US TO BE ALONE
AND TO HAVE NO INTERRUPTIONS.
>> She
>> Sonny: MM.
>> Will: IS SOMETHING WRONG?
>> Sonny: IT'S JUST I SORT OF
PLANNED THIS ALL OUT.
>> Will: WELL, GABI'S GONE.
WE'RE HERE ALONE.
WHAT'S YOUR PLAN?
>> Sonny: [clears throat]
>> Will: NOT TO BE A KILLJOY,
BUT ISN'T IT A LITTLE BIT EARLY?
>> Sonny: I WAS KIND OF HOPING
WE MIGHT HAVE SOMETHING TO
CELEBRATE.
>> Will: THAT IS SO SWEET.
YOU TRULY ARE, LIKE, THE MOST
THOUGHTFUL GUY IN THE WORLD.
>> Sonny: OH, SO YOU KNOW WHAT
THIS IS ABOUT?
>> Will: OF COURSE I DO.
>> Will: SUCH A COOL IDEA.
A PRE-CELEBRATION OF ARIANNA'S
CHRISTENING, JUST THE TWO OF US.
>> Sonny: YOU KNOW, LET ME HAVE
THIS BACK HERE.
YOU'RE REALLY MESSING WITH MY
ZEN HERE, WILL.
>> Will: WHAT? YOUR ZEN?
>> Sonny: SEE, I WANTED TO TALK
ABOUT ALL THIS BEFORE.
LIKE, ABOUT HOW YOU'RE A
WONDERFUL FATHER AND HOW MUCH
YOU LOVE ARIANNA.
>> Will: BEFORE WHAT?
>> Sonny: BEFORE POPPING THE
QUESTION.
>> Will: WHAT QUESTION?
>> Sami: HEY.
>> Tad: HI.
>> Sami: SO I THOUGHT WILL AND
SONNY WERE GONNA BE HERE.
>> Tad: UH, PLANS.
THEY HAD PLANS.
>> Sami: OH. WHAT SORT OF PLANS?
>> Tad: UM, WELL, NOT PLANS
EXACTLY.
UH, SOMETHING CAME UP.
>> Sami: WHAT?
WHAT CAME UP?
>> Tad: UM, I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, THEY DON'T TELL ME
EVERYTHING, SO...
>> Sami: YOU KNOW, MAYBE THEY'RE
JUST BACK AT THEIR APARTMENT
WITH THE BABY.
WE'RE GONNA GO CHECK,
SWEETHEART.
>> Tad: NO, NO, NO, NO.
CAN YOU NOT DO THAT?
SEE, THIS IS--
IT'S KIND OF SPECIAL.
AND IT'S KIND OF A SECRET,
AND I DON'T WANT TO SCREW IT UP.
>> Sami: [sighs]
>> Tad: GOOD ENOUGH?
Si: YEAH.
YEAH, THAT SOUNDS GOOD ENOUGH
TO ME.
YOU'RE A GOOD FRIEND.
>> Tad: THANK YOU.
>> Sami: COME ON, BABE.
>> Tad: [exhales]
>> Lucas:
>> Sonny: WILL HORTON,
WILL YOU MARRY ME?               Subtitles End: mo.dbxdb.com