In the land of mountains, moorlands and lakes
lies a valley of wide open spaces and fertile fields.
This is the eastern corner
of Cumbria. Its farming heart.
I am in the Eden Valley.
This place is sometimes called
Cumbria's best-kept secret.
But not any more. Thanks to the
World Sheepdog Trials, people
have flocked here from all over the
globe to watch the experts at work.
High above the valley in the fells,
far away from the sheepdog trials,
I'll be getting a taste of sheep
farming at its most extreme.
When the winds howl,
the rains pour and the snow falls,
life here can be pretty tough.
So, just how is this piece
of hi-tech kit going to help?
I'll be finding out.
While back at the sheepdog trials,
just as the rain really gets going,
Helen and I go head-to-head
in a challenge of our own.
We've got this in the bag.
Farmer's daughter versus farmer's son.
And I'll be taking a close look
at radical new proposals
to change our planning laws.
They could lead to many more houses being built.
Would that ruin some lovely parts of our countryside
or revive many rural communities?
That's what I'll be investigating.
Also tonight, Adam's herd is facing
another test for bovine TB.
He doesn't want to lose any cattle,
but one in particular is on his mind.
Eric has got a real place in my heart now.
If he got TB and had to be put down,
that would bring a tear to my eye.
The lush green slopes of the Eden Valley.
A hidden jewel...
set between the rocky peaks
of its better-known neighbours,
the Lake District and the Pennines.
And at the heart of the valley is
the 75,000 acre Lowther Estate.
Today, the estate is host to
the World Sheepdog Trials,
an international event that will
draw crowds of up to 40,000 people.
It's the latest event
in the estate's 800-year history.
Once the Lowther Estate was so large,
you could walk from the east coast
to the west coast
without ever leaving it.
But by 1957, life wasn't so sweet.
In a bid to avoid inheritance tax,
the roof was stripped off this once
magnificent castle.
The building, left to rack and ruin.
Now, thanks to a £9 million grant,
it has been restored and the rest
of the estate is not doing too bad either.
I'm meeting estate manager
Richard Price to discover
how they are making this historic
estate fit for the 21st century.
Where is the money coming from
for all of this work?
The actual castle project is being
put into a trust,
the Lowther Castle Gardens Trust.
And the money for that is coming
from the public sector,
large funding organisations like
the North West Development Agency
and things have moved forward very fast.
And very proud of what is happening with that.
It is very much the hub
and the crown of the estate.
And how much does having the
World Sheepdog Trials here help?
It means a lot for the local community.
It brings a lot of income
into the local community.
While the World Sheepdog Trials
are bringing 240 shepherds
from around the world to Lowther,
they do have plenty of their own
sheep to look after.
The estate runs 5,000 of these mule sheep.
They have a hardy Swaledale mum
and a lean, muscly,
Blue-faced Leicester dad making them
rugged for this environment,
but ideal for the table.
John Harrison is the estate's head shepherd.
He's working hard behind the scenes to get
the huge amounts of sheep ready,
in the right place for the trials.
So, John, are you tempted to have
a go at the trials this year
because you could?
Former English national champion.
Well, I mean, it would be nice to but I haven't
competed for about 10 or 12 years now,
so I've probably lost the edge.
It would be nice to have a go,
I must be honest.
Sure. There are handlers coming
from all over the world.
I'm not sure what they'll make of the mules.
It will be interesting to find out really.
The interesting thing is, every handler
gets a different set of sheep.
This is a nightmare for you
to keep things moving around?
We have over 1,200 sheep to get ready
for the trials in the next four days.
Luckily, we have a good, strong committee
and a lot of helpers to help as well.
There is a lot of work involved,
early mornings and late nights unfortunately.
What does it mean to you as head
shepherd to have the world trials?
It's tremendous that it has come here.
And also for the local environment.
You know, with all the people
coming in and the local community,
it is fantastic for that as well.
Back at the trials,
the competition is well under way.
I have arranged to meet up with
Katy Cropper who won
One Man And His Dog in 1990.
'Well done, lass, that is
what I call a good trial.'
The first woman to do so.
Katy, here is the BBC Television trophy.
That is something to keep, isn't it?
Wonderful, wait a minute.
She now lives and works right on
the doorstep in the Eden Valley.
What a wonderful thing to have the
World Sheepdog Trials here.
Yes, it's gorgeous.
This is God's country.
As you can see, it's the
most stunning, stunning scenery.
The trial field looks fantastic.
There is a tremendous feel to it.
It couldn't be more perfect for
the trial. It is not easy.
Field number one is quite a tricky course.
Some of those sheep are quite contrary.
I actually did the course
the night before the actual trial.
How was it?
Lovely. I think I should have won it!
There are some right rough ground
going from the shedding ring
to the pen so you wouldn't be wanting
to wear your Jimmy Choos
because it really is quite rough.
But for the dogs and the handlers, that win this,
it is a big deal, isn't it,
the World Championships?
Fantastic!
And it can be quite lucrative.
Oh, I'm sure.
Depending on who the person is that
wins with their dog,
you never know,
the dog will be worth a lot of money.
We've got the best dogs and the best
handlers from all over the world.
But not the best of the weather.
Heavy rain is affecting the trials.
Later I'll be meeting a couple
of the international competitors
who have braved the Cumbrian climate.
In just a couple of weeks' time,
the Government's consultation
on making radical changes to
our planning rules comes to an end.
The proposals couldn't be more controversial.
But what difference will they really
make? John has been to investigate.
England's planning laws rose
out of the ashes of World War II,
to prevent a free-for-all in building.
But fast-forward to today
and they've created a bureaucracy
with 1,300 pages of planning guidance,
causing delays which cost the economy
an estimated £3 billion every year.
Now, the Government has decided it's time
to speed up the whole planning process,
in a bid to get more homes built
and kick-start the economy.
All those pages of guidance
will be cut to just 52.
But these proposals have
exploded into a war of words
between ministers
and deeply concerned heritage groups.
The protection for the green belt...
I'm not a left-winger.
I'm not a fanatical.
..rather than replacing...
What's causing the uproar is
the Government's idea that
councils should have a presumption
in favour of what they call
sustainable development.
In other words,
they should be more likely to approve
new housing than turn it down.
So, would these new laws ride
roughshod over the countryside,
or would they throw a vital
lifeline to rural communities
with an uncertain future?
To try to shed some light on
what the proposals could mean,
we've picked two villages in Somerset with
very different prospects for the future.
First, East Coker in the south of the county,
a quintessentially English village.
Good morning, John.
Good morning, what a beautiful day.
1,400 people live here
including Martin Sowerbutts
who is taking me on a visit to the local church.
Here we are, John.
If we go up the tower I can show you
what we are talking about.
Right up the top, there.
'But we're not just heading up high
to get a bird's-eye view
'of this lovely village of 900 homes.'
Many more to go?
About halfway I should say, John.
Martin wants to show me a development
site for up to 3,700 houses
which could be built right on their doorsteps.
Well worth the climb! What a view!
Fantastic, isn't it?
So where exactly is this proposed
development going to be?
You see the brown field ahead of us,
it will span across there,
to the left, behind this tree.
To the outskirts of Yeovil?
It will join on to the outskirts of Yeovil
and go right across to the houses on the horizon.
It will look like, essentially,
gravy pouring down from Yeovil
into the Vale of East Coker.
All the area they're going to build
on is grade 1 agricultural land.
The finest and most fertile available.
It accounts for something less than 5%
of all agricultural land in England.
And to build on that,
well, I think it's criminal.
Although sites like green belts
will still be protected,
proposals to defend premium farmland
like this have yet to be approved,
leaving them at risk of development.
Many see East Coker's case
as the sort of battle that could
take place right across the country,
if the new changes go through.
To give you some idea of the effect
it'd have, I have a photograph here
which gives a representation of what it would
look like if this development went ahead.
You can see all of the houses here
would be covering that area there.
'Although this artist's impression has been
done for those opposed to the development,
'it's undeniable that this many
houses will have a dramatic impact.'
So how far
is this village going to take it?
Well, we didn't want it, but we think
in some ways we're a test case.
With all the assets East Coker
has got, the heritage, the farming,
the quality of the land, if we can't
actually make our case stick,
then we think that nowhere
in the country's going to be safe,
particularly under the new planning framework.
The Government says new planning guidelines will
put power back in the hands of local people.
Here, in South Somerset,
they're not so sure about that.
The woman who represents East Coker
on the district council
says her colleagues have little alternative
but to do what the Government wants.
My preference would have been to spread
the houses amongst the villages,
because I believe that protects the school,
the shops and the pub
and other community facilities,
but what the Government wants
is to have the development
on the edge of towns with employment land
and with retail provision within
that area along with the houses,
and so that is what the district
council's had to put into their plan.
What you're saying is, it's not
really your local district plan,
it's a plan that the Government
is imposing on you.
Certainly, if we don't have
a local plan which goes this way,
developers will be able to come along and say,
we are going to develop here, or wherever,
and we won't be able to refuse them
because we haven't identified somewhere
else more suitable for them to go.
I certainly don't want it to be
a free-for-all for developers.
The council say the development
would bring benefits to the area,
but can't be specific
until plans are finalised.
So are existing businesses
positive about the proposals?
Good morning. Hello there.
Could I have the local paper, please?
No problem. That's 70 pence, please.
I suppose you'll be glad when the new
houses are put up, good for business?
No, we don't think so, actually.
We believe with the size of
the estate it's going to be,
they'll bring shops with them,
possibly a mini supermarket,
and we think it's going to
draw customers away from us.
'In East Coker, it's hard to
find people in favour of
the proposed development,
'and that's the big concern about
these possible planning changes,
'that they
simply won't take into account
'the views of local people
if they're against development.'
But in other places, there are those
who believe these plans
could actually work in their favour.
I'm on my way now to a village
about 20 minutes away
called Queen Camel,
where the people there
are wanting new houses.
People power is working here,
because the community is doing what
it appears the Government wants them
to do, namely, ask for more housing.
Parish councillor Rosemary Heath
Coleman helped put together a plan
for the future of their village.
We've been selected by
the Government as a guinea pig
for a neighbourhood
development plan.
How many affordable homes
do you need here now?
Well, that's still a question
to be answered,
but if I said to you 20-ish,
we will build, I hope,
according to the need.
And that's the difference.
Here, we're talking about
a few affordable homes wanted
by the community to help sustain
their village, whereas in East Coker,
they fear a whole new town
will be forced onto their doorstep.
While the children of Queen Camel
enjoy playtime,
the village has been given
a £20,000 government grant
to plan for the future.
You have got a lively school here.
We certainly have.
What difference do you think the
neighbourhood plan is going to make?
It will be good to have our numbers
rising again.
We have fallen over
the last few years,
though we've turned a corner now and
we are beginning to increase again.
So, the whole point
of the neighbourhood plan
is that it's going to allow people
who can afford to live
in the countryside
to be here
with their young children.
Absolutely, that's what we want.
You want a real mix
in the countryside,
not just lots of old people,
young families, too.
So is this what the new planning
regulations will bring about,
or is it more likely to be
mass development of the kind
feared by East Coker?
Well, in fact,
there may be a third way,
that no-one's anticipating,
as I'll be revealing later.
It's grey and it's cold.
I'm on my way to meet some
hill farmers.
Not these guys. They wouldn't know
one end of a sheep from another!
But what they're doing
could make a real difference
to the way hill farmers work.
These guys aren't
playing around with a kid's toy.
This is £30,000 worth of
military technology that's been
adapted for civilian use.
We'll find out
more about that a bit later on.
Meg! Meg!
Here are a couple of farmers
who stand to benefit.
Father and son Chris
and Richard Harrison.
Unlike our men in black,
they know all about sheep,
and when I caught up with them,
the sun was actually shining.
I'm here to help bring
these Swaledales down off the fells.
It's the time of year when the lambs
are weaned off their tired mums,
and we couldn't do it without
the help of a good working dog.
Chris, I'm in awe of your dog.
How easy was she to train?
Meg, she was a natural, really.
She more or less trained herself!
From about eight months old, she used
to run left, right, sit, stop,
and you just had to add
commands to it.
So "get away" is go right?
"Get away" is go to the right,
"get by" is go to the left.
OK.
I'm doing well if I can get my dog
to sit in one place for 30 seconds.
Meg, get away!
She's not moving. Try again.
Meg. Get away!
You haven't got
the right tone of voice.
She's looking.
She just listens to me, really.
Meg, get away, Meg.
Get away!
I thought she was just out of range,
but you're right, it is me!
'I've got to crack this,
'because I'm taking Matt on
at the sheepdog trials later.
'Chris reckons
it's all in the name.'
We tend to give dogs names
with just one syllable.
My dogs have been called Twig,
Rock, Meg.
It's for command reasons, really.
When you shout, if it's just one
sharp word, they can understand.
So Meg's good. We had a Bob.
But we also had a Mandy.
Bob's a good name for a dog,
but I'm not too sure about Mandy.
She was a nice dog,
I'm not sure she was that efficient.
I'm not doubting she was a nice dog!
So if I'm going to beat
Matt Baker, I need a woman's dog.
I think so. You need a dog
that will listen to a woman.
Insert your own punchline there!
Well, Meg doesn't listen
to a word I say,
so I'm hoping Jack
will pay more attention.
I doubt it very much.
He doesn't listen to me very much.
Thank you.
How old is Jack?
He's just turned two.
So he's a bit more mischievous?
He is a little bit, yes.
He's a young dog but
he's still learning, just as I am.
Bye.
Say his name. Jack, bye.
Bye. Go on, they're looking!
Bye, Jack.
Well, Richard's bound to do better.
He's had more practice than me.
But I am trying.
Maybe I'll be more use
down on the farm.
'Things can get tricky
when you stand in the wrong place.'
That was my own fault. I knew that!
'And noisy.'
THEY BLEAT
Remember, though, this is
the first time these lambs
will have been without Mum.
They really sound like
they're saying, "Mum!"
You're going to be fine.
You're going to love it out there.
These lambs will stay on low ground,
grazing and growing up.
Their mums are back off up the fells
to winter on high ground.
And I mean high ground.
Near 2,000 feet.
With the kind of winters they get
round these parts, that's harsh.
Remember these two?
Well, they reckon their fancy
flying machine could be the answer
to our hill farmers' prayers.
When the snow gets deep
and the tractors won't budge,
then this bit of kit
comes into its own.
It's designed to fly over
hard-to-get-to terrain.
Just the job when
your sheep are thousands of feet up.
A special camera underneath
streams live video pictures
back to a laptop,
but the cute bit is,
you can tell this flying shepherd
exactly where to go.
Can you get it to fly from A to B?
I can indeed.
I can demonstrate that now.
I can set some waypoints up here.
Then what it will do,
if I now set this waypoint active,
what it will do now is fly between
the three waypoints that I've set.
You can now see on the camera
it's turning to the right. Oh, wow!
The craft flies right over
Chris the farmer's flock.
The tiny white dots you can
just about see are his sheep.
Can you send the camera over our
heads? Yeah, that's very easy to do.
You grab the centre of the orbit
we're currently on.
Set it active, and there we are. Oh!
We're quite small, aren't we?
We are. With this current camera,
we will look very small.
We can see there are people there.
The technology was developed to be
used in war zones like Afghanistan,
so the Cumbrian hillside
shouldn't be a problem.
But what does our farmer Chris
think of it?
The cost of this
is probably out of the way
for the hill farmer, but maybe
a contractor who has one of these,
and say there's the Commons
or the Lakeland fells
where there's vast, open spaces,
where you can't get to
with a quad bike,
maybe the commoners
could get together
on a day when they're
going to gather the Commons
and get the contractor in,
send him out to have a look
to see where the sheep are at,
so they could save time
by going to certain areas
on the moors and Commons.
So just hire one?
Just hire one for the day.
This is a prototype, but it's
already attracting the interest of
outfits like the mountain rescue.
It would make a difference in terms
of getting people off the mountains?
Absolutely, yeah.
You could imagine a scenario where
somebody's thrown a quad bike over.
At the minute,
the option is you put runners,
fast-running guys will go up the hill
and follow the track
and see where the guy is.
Well, we just throw this in the air,
let it go hunt him down,
and then we can go in with a vehicle
ready to rescue the guy.
After about 20 minutes aloft,
the craft is ready to land
all by itself.
Ouch!
Quite a robust little thing,
isn't it? Heavy landing.
So, I think we all agree
it's got a future,
but does that mean
the end of the working dog?
I don't think so.
I don't think it makes you worry
about early retirement just yet.
You're all right, Meg.
There'll be a few dogs back at
the fourth World Sheepdog trials
that'll be pleased to know that.
At the Lowther Estate,
behind the scenes,
the competition is in full swing.
Growing up on a sheep farm,
sheepdogs have always been
a big part of my life.
It's a real treat for me to be here.
I trained my first one
when I was 14.
This is where all the handlers
hang out before they nip off
to the post.
This is Karin and Lyn,
how did you get on out there,
as you're from Norway?
I was pleased with the run,
pleased with the dog,
but it won't be enough.
Right. It's a long way to come,
isn't it,
for one shot?
Is the sheepdog trialling world
quite similar in Norway,
as to what you're experiencing here?
It's nearly the same,
the same type of courses,
the sheep are a bit more heavy.
Yeah. Same rules but the sport
is not as big as over here.
There are handlers from America,
from the Faroe Islands,
and even Japan and Brazil.
This is the Brazilian team
over here.
Good to see you, how are you? Nice.
Now, it's going very well for one
particular member of your team.
We could expect to do well,
but maybe not that well.
Right. And what do you make
of Cumbria?
The farm area and stuff,
it's pretty.
And the environment,
we enjoy ourselves very much
in the world trials.
And you're the breeder of the dog
that currently has the second
highest score in the world.
Yes, shouldn't have sold it!
This is a lovely touch,
you have your crook in this.
Actually, I brought this for my wife.
While you've been here? Yes.
Oh, isn't that lovely?
She gave me the visa to
come by myself so I have to
bring something back.
You keep smiling and wish
the team all the very best.
Hopefully your score will remain
in the top two. We'll keep
our fingers crossed.
Now, the second part of
John's investigation.
Earlier, we heard a tale
of two villages.
East Coker, which is facing
the prospect of thousands
of new houses forced on it,
and Queen Camel, where the
community's driving a project
to build 20 affordable homes.
Two very different examples
of the way Westminster
would like to free up
the planning laws.
The Government says that its proposed
changes to planning
are aimed at making more land
available for housing,
and so boosting the economy
in the process.
But already there's a lot of land
that's been given the go-ahead
for housing,
but where nothing is happening.
Not only are there enough
brownfield sites out there
to build around 750,000 homes,
up to half of which may be
in the countryside,
there are also countless rural sites
that have been bought,
but not developed.
This is a rather nice place
for a walk, isn't it?
It is lovely at the moment.
Did you know that they have,
back in 2009,
obtained consent for 1,200 homes?
To be built on these fields?
Quite a significant part of it
would be built on.
So why are there no houses
here then?
It's difficult to know -
lots of developers will have land
that they have planning
permission on, but won't
necessarily be building.
There may be many reasons -
generally developers will hold on
to land bank stock.
So how big is this land bank
at the moment?
There is some talk that there is
probably enough consent
for something like 700,000 homes
throughout the UK.
So that's about
two or three years' supply
of new homes
that are not being built.
That's right.
So if firms can't afford to build
on land that's already
earmarked for housing,
what difference will relaxing
the planning laws really make?
Local building contractor
David Pinckney thinks the changes
could be just enough
to kick-start the house-building
industry again.
I think the principle behind it
is very sound.
Anything that cuts down and
simplifies the planning process
is certainly going to help
contribute to more
development opportunities.
It will be interesting to see
how that works in practice.
Do you think this idea of
speeding up the planning process
will create more jobs
in the building industry?
I think it will
in the long term, yes.
If we can speed up the process
and encourage development,
it will certainly lead
to significant jobs
of projects such as this.
We're able to create over
1.5 permanent jobs
for every home we build.
If we are able to meet
the demand that's required,
certainly in rural communities,
we can create hundreds of thousands
of jobs in the industry.
But even if more houses are built,
will those who need them most
be able to afford them?
I'm going to meet a couple where
houses in their village
are way out of their price bracket.
How do you feel about a situation
where young people
just can't afford to live in the
places where they were brought up?
I think it's quite bad, really.
When you're brought up somewhere,
you really enjoy it as a kid,
got memories and stuff there.
And when you can't live and have
your own child live that life,
it's quite sad, really.
House prices here are just
out of your reach, are they?
Yeah, completely. They're way out.
'But there is hope for Chris
and Katie and baby Jack
'because they live in Queen Camel,
'where, as we heard earlier,
there are now hopes of building
around 20 affordable homes.'
And the new houses that are being
planned here,
I think there'll be an opportunity to
part-buy and part-rent.
That's right. That will get you
a bit more stability. Yeah.
Then you can own so much
of the house as well.
So, will you be very disappointed if
you don't get one of these houses?
I would be, yes, very disappointed.
Definitely.
From what I've seen,
it appears whilst these changes
have the potential
to give communities like Queen Camel
a new lease of life,
a combination of vague language
and putting more power
in the hands of developers
may also leave it open to abuse.
It seems inevitable that
the new planning regulations
will take some protection
away from rural areas
but only when we see it work in
practice will we know the true impact
on the countryside.
Shortly on Countryfile,
Helen's on the hunt for
buried treasure deep underground.
It's really quite gorgeous,
isn't it?
At the Sheepdog Trials, we go
head-to-head in the show ring.
Steady!
But, it's the rain that's winning.
And, what about the weather
for the week ahead?
The Countryfile forecast
will reveal all.
As well as its rain, Cumbria is
rightly famous for its sheep.
But that's not the only kind of
farming around here.
Business is booming
for a new brood of farmers,
supplying one of the biggest
free-range egg producers
in the country.
Katie's been to find out more.
14.5 million eggs come through
this packing plant every year.
Most of them come from farms that
are less than 30 miles away.
It's a huge hi-tech operation.
But in this story, it's not the egg,
but the chicken that comes first.
That's because all the eggs come
from free-range chickens.
But just what does it take to be
free range?
Well, these beauties
must be free to roam,
with at least an acre
for every 800 hens.
Like these girls in here.
There aren't any cages,
just water, food and a lot of room
to move around.
It might look a little bit packed
but they do have the option
to go outside.
They just don't always choose
to do that.
That's because of nurture,
rather than nature.
The chicken is a descendent
of the Red Junglefowl,
originally from northeast India
and southern China.
They are happiest in the protective
cover the jungle provides.
So, that's where these come in.
Should I hold the tree?
I'll hold it, how about that?
We are essentially trying
to create a jungle, is that right?
Not exactly a jungle but yes,
the principle of a jungle.
And why are you doing that?
It's to improve the welfare
of the hens.
To try and de-stress them
a little bit.
Have you found any results yet,
are these chickens enjoying having
more trees to roam around?
There doesn't seem to be a lot of
feather pecking going on,
which is a sign that they are
not stressed, are contented
and generally quite happy.
Feather pecking being
they peck each other.
They peck the feathers
out of each other.
It's not something
we've got a problem with.
This isn't just a scheme dreamt up
by Patricia,
free-range egg producers
across Cumbria
are planting trees to provide
happier habitats for their hens.
It's backed up by scientists
and big egg buyers, too.
Joy Clachan is a farmer
and a scientist.
Her research is part of
a nationwide study
backed by one of the biggest
purchasers of free-range eggs,
McDonald's.
Our research found they feel at home
in this environment.
It provides everything they need,
the shade, the shelter,
the protection.
As you can see, the birds
absolutely love it
and express so much
natural behaviour.
And is it not -
sorry to sound cynical -
a PR exercise for McDonald's?
Not at all, no.
For us, it's about proving
that commitment
to improving animal welfare.
Working in collaboration with
our suppliers and their producers.
The egg explosion in Cumbria is a
triumph that came from adversity.
The county was one of the worst hit
by the outbreak of foot and mouth
ten years ago.
It forced many livestock farmers,
like Patricia, into a rethink.
We decided we needed to think about
other options
so we didn't have all our eggs
in one basket
and we decided to look into another
means of farming,
and this was what we decided on.
How many hens do you have now?
10,500.
And you started with?
4,000 in the first year.
And we liked it so much
that we decided to expand.
Once collected, the eggs from
Patricia and 37 other farms
from all over Cumbria
come through here.
It's a hi-tech operation. Owner Dave
Brass is giving me a guided tour.
This is where the eggs come in.
This machine takes
a picture of the eggs,
it also senses which way round
the egg is,
because we want to put the eggs
into the egg box point down.
Do any eggs ever break?
It's going very fast, this machine.
In half a million eggs a day,
we lose maybe a couple of dozen.
Next piece of equipment is
a crack detector.
There are a lot of little
hammers in there,
and they hit the eggshell very
gently and listen to the echo.
Now, the machine, the computer,
knows where every faulty egg is
and every good egg is.
This is the bee's knees,
state-of-the-art machinery.
We use car-building robots to
put eggs in boxes.
If all eggs in this country were
produced in a free-range way,
would there be enough eggs
for the whole country?
In theory, yes.
You got to remember that
free range takes land,
and an area the size of Dorset
would be required for all of that.
So it's fitting that within
the rest of agriculture in the UK.
While the egg-packing technology
may be thoroughly modern,
it's thanks to ancient,
Asian ancestors,
that the egg producers of Cumbria
are giving their hens
a free-range future.
It's TB testing time again
on Adam's farm.
It's a moment
all cattle farmers dread,
but will Adam get the all clear
this time?
Today is a big day for us
on the farm.
We're TB testing.
We've gone clear now for 10 months,
and today is our
routine six-monthly test.
And usually, when the cattle have
been out at grass all summer,
we go down with TB again, so, I don't
feel that optimistic, to be honest.
And I've got good reason to worry.
I've lost more than 70 cattle to
this disease in the past 10 years.
These are my beautiful
White Park cattle,
the herd was really depleted
because of TB.
We were down to three cows.
So I went to Devon and bought seven
new White Park heifers.
They've all calved now and
it looks like a really lovely herd,
I'm really proud of them.
But I heard some very worrying news
the other day.
The farmer in Devon where I got the
cattle from had his routine TB test.
He hadn't had TB for two years,
he had 20 reactors.
20 animals that had to be
slaughtered.
So today, this herd,
I'm very, very nervous about.
Although the cattle were tested
before leaving Devon,
you can never be 100% sure
they're disease-free.
Cattle are creatures of routine,
and on TB testing days,
we're stirring them up,
moving them around,
there's bulls around that get upset,
they start roaring at one another.
And the cows are already
worried about their calves.
And I feel pretty stirred up as well.
Not an easy day.
White Parks are classed as
a minority breed,
and I've worked hard to help
conserve them.
Losing any would be a disaster.
So, as the vet arrives,
it's time to start the test.
And then, straightaway...
Reactor?
This is one of the cows
that we bought from the farm
down in Devon, and she's a reactor.
First cow of the test,
and she's reacted.
It's an absolute travesty.
Complete disaster.
'This one isn't looking good either.'
It's another one, Adam.
It's another one?
That's a new one too, isn't it?
Yeah. Oh, no!
You try and try
and build up your herd again,
and you've got to buy in cattle
if your herd is almost depleted.
We've always bred
our own replacements.
And what have we done?
We've either given them TB
when they got here
or we've re-infected our herd.
This is something my dad has seen
many times before,
and it doesn't get any easier.
Today,
this is just a total disaster,
I mean, to get two so far, out
of the new heifers, is just awful.
And I just don't know how
we're going to go on.
HE SIGHS
I feel terribly guilty, I may have
reintroduced TB to my farm.
What can you do?
To make matters worse, these two
White Parks are suckling calves
and that leaves me
with a bit of a dilemma.
It's a tricky situation with the
calves, because they haven't got TB,
and we can decide to
keep them on the farm and rear them
or we can have them slaughtered,
because they may be
at risk of carrying it.
And I can't make my mind up
at the moment,
I'm afraid I can't think straight.
So now, these animals that have
reacted to TB have to be tagged
and they take a sample of skin
from their ear which is the DNA
of that animal,
to stop any
higgery-jiggery-pokery with the tags,
to make sure that the animal
that's got TB goes to slaughter.
All looks well for the rest
of my White Parks,
until one of my original herd
gets tested.
This is one of our home-bred cows.
A heifer
who's running with the bull now.
Reactor.
Another one? Yeah.
She hasn't been with
the visiting cows for very long,
only the last couple of weeks.
And strangely, it makes me feel
a bit better that we had it anyway,
so we haven't introduced it to the
farm by bringing cattle with us,
it's just on the farm
and it seems like it's here to stay.
But we've lost another White Park.
All right.
Watch the calf. Mind the calf!
The vet doesn't find any more
reactors among the rest of my cattle,
but there are a couple
that are borderline.
This animal has got lumps,
but they're not big enough
to make it a reactor, it's what's
known as an inconclusive.
And so she will have to be tested
again in 60 days,
but like the rest of the herd
will be. Yeah.
All that's left now
are the last few of my highlands.
It's not often I have favourites,
but Eric has got a real place
in my heart now.
If he got TB and had to be put down,
that would bring a tear to my eye.
And thankfully,
it's good news for Eric.
Yes!
I'm not alone when it comes to
the terrible effects of this disease.
Last year, around 25,000 cattle
were slaughtered
due to bovine TB in England.
It cost us taxpayers
around £90 million.
The Government is currently
deliberating on whether
to sanction a badger cull in England
to control the disease.
'A solution, whatever it might be,
can't come soon enough for me.'
Right, so that's it,
the test is over,
we've got three reactors
that will have to be slaughtered,
and two are what are known as
inconclusives.
They'll have to be tested again
before a decision
can be made on them.
So, it's a real shame.
I was really hoping that
we were shot of it now.
We've gone 10 months clear of TB
and the animals have been
out at grass grazing all summer,
and they've got it again.
So we go on this continual circle.
After some time
away from the animals,
I've had a chance to think about
the reality of the results
and I've decided what to do
with my White Park calves.
I've isolated these three cows
that reacted to the TB test.
They have to be isolated to stop
the risk of them
spreading TB to the other cattle
that are healthy,
and they'll be slaughtered
in 7 to 10 days' time.
One of the dilemmas I've got now
is that these two cows have got
two calves that they're suckling,
and there's a risk that these calves
might have TB, so do I just decide to
put them down, to slaughter them?
Or do I rear them by hand-feeding
them bottled milk
and have them in a loose box to stop
the risk of spreading TB to many of
my other cattle?
And they're such lovely
little calves,
I think I've got to give them
a chance and I hope
the outcome is positive,
that these calves will survive
and get through the next TB test
and I will be able to return them
to the herd as healthy animals.
Next week, I'll be visiting
the shortlisted farms
for this year's Farmer Of The Year
as part of Radio Four's annual
Food And Farming Awards.
This is the high country,
the roof of England.
Where craggy mountains meet
vast open moorland.
And where market towns
touch the clouds.
Like this one. Alston
is one of England's highest,
we're 1,000 feet up and more
than 15 miles from the next town.
If it's remoteness you want,
you've got it.
There's been a settlement here
since Roman times,
those boys on day trips
from Hadrian's Wall
knew they were on to something.
Because the area around Alston
is loaded.
It's not so much a case of
there's gold in them there hills,
as zinc and silver
and most important of all, lead.
Lead is what put the area
on the map.
Mines sprung up all over the place,
and if you know where to look,
you can read its history
in the hillsides.
Even just looking at this bit
of the landscape,
you can tell that it's quite
a heavily mined area, can't you?
Yes, this whole top end
of the valley
is scarred, even where there are
bits that have been grassed over.
Right the way up to the top
and around the corner,
it's all lead workings
going back 300 years or more,
and you can see the landscape
hasn't recovered.
All that brown waste, it's all
waste heaps there, and the place
is practically hollow with
the amount of lead that's
been taken out.
Miners flocked to the area,
the population exploded,
but there was nowhere for them
to live.
Solution - build homes,
lots of them.
These were wonderful houses
by the standards of the day.
Although it was just one room up,
one room down,
for a family of up to 10 or 11,
it was much better than anything
the workers had been used to,
and they had outhouses
at the back and toilets,
and they had large gardens
in the front
where they were encouraged to
produce their own vegetables,
just for the sake of getting
fresh air and exercise after
being cooped up in the mine all day
in the pitch black and the dust.
They could come and be out
in the sunshine, would you believe,
and be healthy.
Even so, a miner's life expectancy
was just 45 years of age,
and most of that would have been
spent underground.
To find out what life
was like down there,
I'm joining a team of local
mine explorers.
Alistair, it's a lovely, sunny day,
yet we're going underground.
Is it going to be worth it?
It certainly will be,
there's a lot to see down there,
so, once we're kitted up,
we can make our way in.
OK. Boiler suit on, helmet on,
are we ready, team?
Lead the way, Alistair.
These old mines can be dangerous, so
it pays to have experts guide you,
but once you're in,
a whole new world opens up.
There are beautiful
dry stone tunnels.
You can still see the rails
used to wheel out the lead ore.
Here and there,
pit props hold up the roof.
But mostly, it's narrow passages,
blasted out of the hard rock,
flooded and dark.
But shine a light,
and the space glitters.
The miners weren't down here
for the views though.
They were working eight-hour shifts
in pairs.
It was hard graft and slow going.
Alastair, these are everywhere.
Are these sort of drill marks?
Yes, the miners would've drilled
in here by hand
in this part of the mine.
Once the drill hole was complete,
they'd put gunpowder into the hole,
pack it with clay,
and then put a fuse in.
When the rock was blasted,
it blasted this piece of rock away,
and leaves the drill hole there.
They'd blast about two foot a day.
It could take years to reach
the veins of lead ore,
but if they struck it rich
they'd work around the clock,
and all they had to work by
was candlelight.
You can see on the wall there, can
you see the dollop of clay? Yes.
That's what the miners would've used
for their candles.
They'd put the clay on the wall and
then stick a candle in as a holder,
and that allowed them to work hands
free and see what they were doing.
So the candle was
their only form of light?
Only form of light, yes.
One candle per miner.
What's this bit?
It's totally different, isn't it?
This is known as
a horse whim chamber,
and when the mines were working
there's a shaft on the far side there
that goes down to lower levels,
and there would be a pony walking
round in here,
driving a winching system that would
haul material up and down
the whimsey shaft.
Is this machinery?
Was that often used?
Yes, this is the remains
of the actual winching system.
So that stuff is
potentially 300 years old?
Yep, yep.
Original timber and materials there.
A time capsule, albeit
a little rusty and rotten now.
We've been going nearly an hour
and still no sign of the galena,
the valuable lead ore that kept
so many miners busy.
But it is there,
you just need a keen eye.
So this is it, is it?
This is what they were looking for?
I've got a sample here.
That's the actual galena itself
so you can see when it's first
exposed it's quite shiny.
It's really quite gorgeous,
isn't it?
It does have a certain percentage of
silver within it as well,
which helped make the mines
profitable in the area.
There's still plenty of lead ore
here, it just became uneconomic
to mine it.
Cheaper foreign lead put paid to our
home-grown industry at the start of
the 20th century.
An industry which had flourished
since Roman times had gone.
You could spend hours down there
and you might get lost
but you definitely
wouldn't get bored.
Shortly, I'm going to be sharpening
my shepherding skills with the help
of a few experts,
and fingers crossed it'll be enough
to beat Matt in the sheepdog trials.
But, before that,
here's the Countryfile
weather forecast for the week ahead.
.
This is the North Country,
where the Pennines rub up against
the Lake District.
Hidden between the two
is the Eden Valley,
my home and host to this year's
World Sheepdog Championships.
I'm here to take on Matt in a
sheepdog championship of our own.
Matt is very proud of his farming
heritage, but so am I,
and I know he likes to think
of himself as a bit of a dab hand
when it comes to handling sheep.
I, however, have no experience
handling sheep.
That's why I'm calling on you, Mark.
You're my guru for this,
because I'm throwing down the
gauntlet to Baker on my home turf
so I've got to win.
We'll do our best.
Come on!
I've enlisted the help of local
farmer Mark Elliott.
Together with his trusty dog Spot,
he's one of this year's
hot favourites.
To get him to come over,
I say, "that'll do"?
"That'll do, Spot", yes.
That'll do, Spot.
Be a bit more assertive.
That'll do, Spot!
That'll do, Spot. Spot! That'll do.
That'll do, Spot.
That'll do, Spot. Good lad.
He's not really listening to me,
is he? No!
'One word from me...and Spot does
just what he wants!'
How do I get him to go right?
The basic ones - for the right
hand side it's "way". Way.
And for the left
it's "come bye". OK.
Come bye.
That'll do. That'll do.
Come bye. Come bye.
Sit! Ask him for the way. Way!
'Hmm, this could take some doing.
'Luckily, Mark's going to be
right by my side for the showdown.'
Lie down, lie down!
That's it!
Spot, that'll do.
Right, let battle commence.
May the best presenter win
and never mind the weather.
Come on, Spot. Here we go.
How are you doing, Helen? All right?
I'm very good. You're fully trained
up then, I understand?
I'm good. Well, I say that.
You've had a lot of training,
I hear? Well, not with this dog
unfortunately.
My dog Meg is no longer with me
so I borrowed Tim from a good friend
of mine, Gus Dermody,
and not only have I borrowed his
dog, I've borrowed his outfit
as well
because the weather
has taken a turn for the worst.
So Gus is a judge...
You're literally
in the judge's pocket?
Yes, absolutely. Actually,
can I borrow your crook as well?
Yes, you can have that.
I'm fully kitted out now.
Right, well we're ready for this.
Aren't we, Mark? Yes.
Right. Spot is poised.
Will Spot listen to you,
do you think? Because I've got
no idea about Tim.
Apparently Spot isn't too familiar
to the female voice.
Right. So Mark's going to walk with
me and echo what I say.
You're just going to talk like that.
No problem. OK!
But there is a problem because
we'll be lucky if the dogs can hear
anything we say over this weather.
I'm hoping I've got beginner's luck.
An expert in the field, Matt's
first to take on the course.
Pretty wide around the pen here.
Tim! You've got to keep them
flowing all the time. Lie down.
'It sounds simple - get five sheep
through a gate and into a pen -
'but these girls are stubborn
customers.'
So through the obstacle, bearing
right, and now they need to head for
the pen. Lie down. Lie down!
Yep, he's got them in the pen.
Oh, well done!
Yay! Good boy.
What a good lad! Steady!
Not a bad start for Helen and Spot.
Oh, we've gone wrong. Way. Way.
That's not too bad. The dog's going
the wrong side.
He's keen, isn't he?
Come bye, you.
Good control there,
keeping the ship nice and calm.
Lie down. Lie down.
Go on.
Lie down, lie down.
Oh! It's a clean pen.
It's a very good pen.
Well, I thought that was impressive.
Very. Very good.
I certainly was impressed.
My word! Helen, what are you doing
on this field?
You should be up there, competing!
I think it's fair to say
I had a very good teacher who
chipped in now and again.
OK! To be honest, we could have
left Spot to his own devices.
He was quite happy out there
on his own. Brilliant.
He thoroughly enjoyed it. Look,
the sheep are sticking around. They
want to know who's won.
Gus, what's the result?
Really, you were level pegging,
but on a technicality you got it
because Helen went and moved
from the post, from the pen
when you set the dog off.
What?!
Yep, unfortunately for you...
That's a made-up rule,
I didn't even know about it!
Thanks ever so much. That's
all we've got time for this week.
Con-gratu-lations!
Next week we're going to be
in the Mawddach estuary in Wales
and we'll be revealing your
favourite entry of the Countryfile
photographic competition.
But, from Helen's neck of the woods,
it's come by for now. See you.
You looked so cool until that gag.
It's undermined the victory!