Get back! Who are you?
Who are you?
- I'm Willow Ufgood.
- What are you doing here?
I've come to find
the great sorceress Fin Raziel.
That's me! I'm Raziel!
This can't be right!
One of Bavmorda's spells
transformed me.
Believe me,
it could have been worse!
Well, this wand is for you.
It's from Cherlindrea.
Then the prophecy is true.
The princess has been born.
Take me to her.
It is Elora Danan.
Isn't she beautiful?
- That's Raziel?
- I don't know.
I expected something
more grand. Less--
- Fuzzy.
You must use the wand.
Turn me back into my human form.
- What do I do?
- You mean you're not a sorcerer?
Yes. Sorta.
I'm a farmer.
- But I do know a few tricks.
- Tricks?
Cherlindrea sent you?
You must learn real magic.
- Horses!
Quick! Take her! Hurry!
I knew he was a traitor!
- Sorry about this, peck.
- Keep your mouth shut.
I told you we'd find them
without your help.
- Give me that baby!
- No!
- Give her back!
- Leave me alone! Don't touch me!
This is the one
we're looking for.
We must take it back
to Nockmaar.
Lose your skirt?
- I've still got what counts.
- Not for long.
- Bring him.
- Over here!
We'll never keep up
with those horses.
- Then we will have to track them.
- That would take forever.
Besides, even if we find them,
they'll catch us...
stick us in cages, torture us
and finally devour us.
Are you suggesting we go home?
- Nah. This is more fun.
- All right.
Fine, then.
Come on.
I'm worried about Elora.
She doesn't sound good.
Hurry! Practise
the chant I taught you!
Tanna looatha--
I can't remember
the middle part.
Locktwaar!
That's the word
that pleads for change.
Locktwaar.
Elora's cold and hungry.
She knows me.
Please, let me take care of her.
I don't need help from a peck.
- What are you staring at?
- Your leg.
I'd like to break it.
You may find that difficult,
slave...
while I'm up here
and you're down there.
I hate that woman.
I found it, Kael.
That should make
my mother happy.
What are they gonna do to her?
Hither walha...
bairn deru bordak...
bellanockt.
That's magic?
Smells terrible.
- It's the life spark. It forms after--
- It stinks!
- This whole thing stinks!
- Ignore him, Willow.
- He's a fool!
- If only I had a sword!
If only you'd quit
talking about it.
Willow, you must transform me
to my human self.
But, Raziel, I'm not ready yet.
You'd better be.
Get me down.
Ow!
Why don't you help me get out of here
instead of chattering with that muskrat?
Muskrat!
When I change back to my former self,
I will crush this army...
and take Elora Danan
to Tir Asleen...
where she will be safe.
Ow! What'd you bite me for?
You need three drops of your blood
to put in the potion.
You could've warned me.
For beginners,
there's some pain...
but don't let anything
break your concentration.
Hither greenan bairn
claideb lunanockt.
- Hello, everybody! We have arrived!
- You are saved.
Don't interrupt.
Hither greenan bairn
claideb lunanockt.
What will you look like
if this works?
- Don't interrupt.
- Sorry.
Hither greenan bairn
claideb lunanockt.
I am a young, beautiful woman.
Concentrate, Willow.
Hither greenan bairn
claideb lunanockt.
You're losing me!
Hither greenan bairn
claideb lunanockt.
You all right?
Nice try, Willow.
Farmers!
Cherlindrea sends me farmers!
The Nelwyn
really butchered that one.
I'm sorry, Raziel.
You want out?
Easy. We can pick a lock.
Come on.
No. No, no.
Like this!
I know what I'm doing.
It's my spear. Leave it alone.
Let me do it.
Out of the way, rodents.
Take your hand off that.
You leave that alone,
you stupid, fat Daikini!
Dust of broken hearts.
You are free!
Come on, Madmartigan.
Let's get Elora Danan
out of here.
Yeah.
- It'll be fun.
- Come on.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
I feel good.
The dust of broken hearts.
Come on!
- Let me see!
- Let me see. You always see.
There's Elora, right there,
on those furs.
Hey, wait! Leave this to us.
It's too dangerous for you.
Only one of us should go in there.
I know what I'm doing.
Wait. No, no!
- I love you.
- Madmartigan!
What are you doing?
Get the baby!
Come on!
Wake from this hateful sleep.
It deprives me of your beauty.
- The beauty of your eyes--
- One move, jackass...
and you really will be a woman.
You are my sun! My moon!
My starlit sky.
Without you, I dwell in darkness.
I love you.
What are you doing here?
Your power has enchanted me.
I stand helpless against it.
Come to me now.
Tonight, let me worship you
in my arms.
- Get away from me!
- I love you!
Stop saying that!
How can I stop the beating of my heart?
It pounds like never before.
- Out of fear.
- Out of love!
I can stop it.
I'll kill you.
Death, next to love,
is a trivial thing.
Your touch is worth 1 00,000 deaths.
What goes on here?
Deceiver!
Stop him!
Get me out!
You are great!
Get on that shield!
After them!
They're getting away!
- Follow me, Rool.
- Where are you?
I don't know.
Oh, no!
Where did everybody go?
Maybe it was something we said.
What the hell happened up there?
You started spouting poetry.
- Poetry?
- Yeah.
''I love you, Sorsha.
I worship you, Sorsha.''
You almost got us killed!
''I love you, Sorsha''?
I don't love her.
She kicked me in the face.
I hate her! Don't I?
Kael! Kael!
Nockmaar soldiers!
Hide! Get the children!
Come on!
- Hide! Get the children!
- They're after us!
- We need a place to hide.
- Come on. Follow me. Quick!
I knew you'd get out
of that rattrap.
You left me to die, Airk.
I probably saved your life.
We were slaughtered, and I lost a lot--
Quiet!
Tear this village apart!
Look everywhere!
Find the child!
Tell Sorsha
I search the north bank!
Yes, General.
Quiet!
- Sorsha!
- Back.
Back!
Back.
- Keep the baby quiet.
- She needs to be changed.
- Nockmaar scum!
- You'll never defeat us.
- Give up the baby!
- Shut up!
- Why does Bavmorda want this baby?
- She's a princess.
- We're taking her to Tir Asleen.
- Tir Asleen?
Even if you could find it, peck...
she's right-- you'd never
get past the Nockmaar army.
There's an even bigger army
at Tir Asleen, if we can get there.
I've lost more than half my men
fighting Bavmorda.
Now you and this peck
are gonna take her on?
You always told me you served
no one, Madmartigan.
Since when are you a crusader?
He's not gonna help you, peck.
He's a worthless thief.
I'm not a thief, Airk.
He's not a thief.
Are you?
I serve the Nelwyn, Airk.
- Want to come with us?
- You'll never make it.
Then once again
we say goodbye.
- Over here!
- Sorsha!
Weapons down or she's dead!
Get to your horses!
After them!
This way!
As the crow flies, you fools!
- You're holding me too tight!
- I don't want you to get away.
Why? Because I'm your sun,
your moon, your starlit sky?
Get your hair out of my face
or I'll chop it off.
Did I really--
Did I really say
those things last night?
- In your tent?
- You said you loved me.
- I don't remember that.
- You lied to me!
No, I--
I just wasn't myself last night.
I suppose my power enchanted you
and you were helpless against it.
- Sort of.
- Then what?
- It went away.
- Went away?
''I dwell in darkness without you,''
and it went away?
Yeah.
Hurry! Kael's coming!
Madmartigan, come on! Now!
Madmartigan, come on!
They're coming! Away!
Go on!
Whoa! Whoa!
This way!
Tir Asleen!
At last, Tir Asleen!
Hello?
Why did I listen to you, peck?
''Everything will be all right
once we get to Tir Asleen.''
The only army around is the one that's
about to ride across this valley...
and wipe us out!
But Cherlindrea said
we'd be safe here.
Safe? Look at these people.
This place is cursed, peck.
It's falling apart. Open your eyes!
And it--
Trolls.
I hate trolls.
This is the work of Bavmorda.
Willow? The wand.
- Turn me back into my human form.
- Are you sure?
Good.
Hurry, Willow.
Transform me.
I can't do it.
I'm just not a sorcerer.
But you can be.
Speak and be one with the words.
Avalorium greenan...
luatha tye--
Oh, Willow, you're losing me.
Madmartigan, Kael's coming!
- Willow, you idiot.
- Raziel?
Arm that catapult up there.
Good work, Madmartigan.
What happened to you?
Assault!
Sorsha, battering ram!
Cut it down!
Faster!
Forward! Break it down!
Again! Again!
Willow, use the wand
on that troll.
Bellalockt!
Break it down! Forward!
Get him!
The other side!
Destroy the beast!
Find the baby!
Take that!
Madmartigan, help!
Get him, Madmartigan!
Here.
The baby!
Airk's army. Get Kael!
Airk's army!
- We are here!
- You are rescued!
- Charge!
No mercy!
Elora!
Willow!
- Elora's gone.
- Willow.
They've taken her.
There were too many of them.
Can you ride?
Let's ride.
I have the child!
We need towers
and a battering ram!
Break out the tents!
Make camp!
We'll assault at first light.
Where's Sorsha?
She has turned against us,
Your Highness.
Turned against me?
Prepare for the ritual!
This is not an army.
Quick. Hide.
Use the shelter chant.
Protect yourself.
- Why?
-Just do it.
- We've come for Elora Danan.
- You dare to challenge me?
You're not warriors.
You're pigs!
You're all pigs!
Pigs!
Avaggdu luatha bairn
off haefermore.
Sorsha!
Mother, no!
Kothon!
Avaggdu luatha bairn
off haefermore.
Begin the ritual.
This baby will not destroy me.
Come, thunder!
Come, lightning!
Touch this altar
with your powers.
We've come all this way
and now Elora Danan's gonna die!
No, we can still defeat Bavmorda.
She's too powerful, Raziel.
Transform me,
and I will destroy her.
Elements of eternity,
above and below.
Balance of essence,
fire beget snow.
- Locktwarr danalora luatha danu...
- Willow...
- believe in the words.
- tuatha, tuatha...
- Concentrate.
- chnox danu.
Locktwarr danalora...
- luatha danu tuatha, tuatha.
- Oh, no!
Don't give up, Willow!
- Has it been so long?
- I'm sorry.
Willow, we have work to do.
Give me the wand.
We must undo Bavmorda's sorcery.
Let them in now.
Tuatha grin chnox
y foel famau.
Black fires
forever kindled within...
let the second rite begin.
Quick, inside.
That won't breach the wall.
We can't get inside.
- Elora Danan will die--
- Unless we save her.
- Bavmorda's too powerful.
- No!
She cannot transform you again.
My spell is protecting this camp.
But can your magic
get us inside the fortress?
We can't do it.
Wait!
Back home in my village,
we have a lot of gophers.
- Willow, this is war, not agriculture.
- I know.
But I have an idea
how to get inside the castle.
Ocht veth bordak stira.
Madmartigan, you and I are soldiers.
The peck's plan will never work.
If the baby dies,
all hope for the future is lost.
I'm going to fight.
Me too.
All right, we've got to decide
who's gonna go and who's gonna stay.
Willow, all these years
I have waited to face Bavmorda.
It is you
that has made this possible.
Whatever happens,
I shall always admire you.
Your children...
will come to remember this day.
We call upon you to surrender!
We are all-powerful sorcerers.
Give us the baby,
or we'll destroy you!
Kill them!
Patience, Willow.
Courage, Willow.
Back to the castle!
Ocht veth nockthirth bordak!
Exile the child to the 1 3th night.
This way!
Nockthirth
plankton firth foreth forewar.
Ocht veth nock!
It's all right, Willow.
You don't have to go.
Light the 1 3th candle!
Raziel.
Mother!
Traitor child.
I must despise you now.
- I won't let you kill that child.
- Away!
Avaggdu...
strokt!
Your powers have gained
in strength, Raziel.
I have Cherlindrea's wand,
Bavmorda.
Elora Danan will be queen.
Now you die!
Furrochk flarem!
Claideb cla--
Clai main!
Lunano ockht!
Bachktu inno!
Airk!
Win this war for me.
Die!
Bring back that child, peck.
Who are you?
I'm Willow Ufgood.
I'm a great sorcerer.
Greater than Raziel.
Greater than you, even.
I'm the greatest sorcerer!
Is that the extent
of your powers, little one?
Now you will watch me draw
upon the power of the universe...
to send that child
into the netherworld.
Now, place it on the altar!
No!
No?
You stupid hag!
With my magic,
I'll send her into the--
Into a--
You're no sorcerer.
Into a realm
where evil cannot touch her.
Impossible!
- There's no such place!
- Helgafel swath ben helgafel.
You are a fool!
I shall destroy you
and the child with you.
- Damn fool!
- Bairn off danu famoww.
Goodbye, Elora.
Bohi bakstiy.
Helgafel!
Impossible!
You--
Willow, where's the baby?
It was just my old
disappearing pig trick.
Well done!
Willow Ufgood,
receive this book of magic.
You are on your way
to becoming a great sorcerer.
- Willow the Sorcerer!
- You make us proud!
Goodbye, Elora Danan.
Goodbye, Willow!
Farewell!
Willow! Willow!
Willow's back!
- Willow!
- Hey, Meegosh!
It's a bird!
He made a bird!
Kiaya!
- Willow?
- Kiaya.
- Dada! Dada!
- Dada, I missed you!
I missed you.