[CLOCK TICKING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
CARL AZUZ: It's been a
little over five months
since a major hurricane made
landfall in the Bahamas,
and it could be
another five months
before electricity is completely
restored to some places.
That's our first subject
of the week here on CNN 10.
My name is Carl Azuz,
I'm at the CNN Center.
The year 1851 was the first year
when officials started keeping
track of hurricanes, and
since then, at least,
no storm that's
hit the Bahamas was
as strong as Hurricane Dorian.
It made landfall
there on September 1st
as a category 5
hurricane, the strongest
classification of storm.
It weakened to
category 4 strength
as it passed over the islands,
but one thing that made Dorian
so destructive was its speed.
Hurricanes are damaging enough
when they pass over land
in a couple of hours, but
Dorian came to a near stop
when it was over the
Bahamas, blasting part
of the chain for
more than 36 hours
with unrelenting
wind, waves, and rain.
So many homes were
destroyed that even
now, there aren't enough
people living in the Bahamas
to rebuild quickly.
In the town of Marsh Harbor,
in the Abaco islands,
witnesses say it doesn't look
like anything's been done
to repair some hard hit
areas, and that stray dogs
are the only signs of life.
For some people who
evacuated or had
to leave after their
homes were destroyed,
they couldn't go back
if they wanted to.
There's nowhere
for them to stay.
The Bahamian
government is working
to set up domes, temporary
houses to address that.
And for those who are
trying to rebuild,
there's a sense of urgency,
because June 1st less than four
months from now, is
the official start
of the next hurricane season.
Volunteers have committed
to helping the Bahamas
rebuild and prepare.
- We know that the
waterline came up higher,
so we know for a fact
that there's going
to be mold behind these tiles.
So they had to come off.
DAVID EISENBAUM: We're
here in Marsh Harbor
on the island of great Abaco.
It really was the epicenter
of Hurricane Dorian,
and experienced the most
extreme damage from the storm.
All Hands and Hearts
has made a commitment
to be here for at
least two years
to help the community recover.
RYAN FORBES: We're so
thankful and so grateful.
And we are so
appreciative of the help
that you guys have given us.
You know, and the sacrifices you
guys are making is much needed.
DAVID EISENBAUM: We
are going to continue
working in the response phase,
doing mucking and gutting
and debris removal,
and sanitizing homes,
and begin to accelerate
more of the recovery
and rebuild work that we do.
- There we go.
Nice.
- Beautiful.
DAVID EISENBAUM:
The goal, really,
is to get people back
into homes and get
students back into schools.
The need here is for manpower.
We need volunteers.
We're going to need
thousands of volunteers
over the course of
the coming years.
- We're going to
have you guys added
in to a team for tomorrow.
DANA TARNO-GERKEN:
These people need a lot,
and they have the
time to give it, so.
It's an incredible gift
that we give and we get.
DAVID EISENBAUM:
10 second trivia.
Which of these films won
the very first Academy
Award for Best Picture in 1929?
"Wings", "All Quiet
on the Western Front",
"Grand Hotel", or "It
Happened One Night".
Though it was called
Outstanding Picture back then,
the award went to a World
War I drama called Wings.
In last night's Oscars, the 90
second Academy Award ceremony,
it wasn't just results that
the media were watching.
It was the ratings.
With tens of
millions of viewers,
The Oscars are one of, if
not the most watched show
in America that
isn't a sports event.
But in recent years, the
Academy Awards have seen
a decline in TV viewership.
They hit an all-time low in
2018 with 26.5 million viewers,
but they bounced back a
bit last year when the show
got 29.6 million viewers.
One thing unique
about last year's show
was that it didn't have a
host, and the Academy planned
to try that again last night.
We didn't have final
viewership numbers
when we put this
show together, so we
don't know if the
host-less approach helped.
But other awards shows in 2020,
like the Golden Globes and
the Grammys, saw lower ratings.
Regardless of how
that played out,
the business of nominating
stars, movies, and producers
is a big one.
- In 1929, studio
head Louis B. Mayer
handed out the first
Academy Awards.
There were only 270
guests, the winners
have been announced
months before,
and the whole thing
only cost $5 to attend.
- We've seen the American
motion picture become
foremost in all the world.
- Fast forward 90 years,
and today the Oscars
are awarded at a 3,300 seat
theater, tens of millions
of people watch
the results live,
and tickets cost
hundreds of dollars.
But the biggest difference?
Today's movie studios
spend millions
to convince the Academy that
their films deserve to win.
KYLE BUCHANAN: Sometimes
the amount of money
that a studio will spend
when they're campaigning
for an Oscar is even more
money than the budget
of the movie to begin with.
- That's Kyle Buchanan.
He covers all things Oscars
for the New York Times.
KYLE BUCHANAN: If you want to
get your movie taken seriously,
you've got to spend.
You've got to make sure that
there are ads out there,
that there are events, that
people are contextualizing
you as an Oscar contender.
- And why do studios spend
that much cash for an 8
and 1/2 pound statuette?
For a smaller studio
like A24 or Annapurna,
the answer is pretty obvious.
KYLE BUCHANAN: They're
making movies for, you know,
not a big budget
a lot of the time.
But in order to be seen when
the marketplace is choked
with these big blockbusters
and superhero films,
they need that sort
of extra headline
making ability than an
awards season can provide.
- But what about a bigger
studio, like Warner
Brothers or Universal?
As we've seen over the
past couple decades,
box office hits aren't often
considered Oscar contenders,
and blockbusters don't
really need the exposure
that a nomination brings.
Isn't the money
enough of a reward?
KYLE BUCHANAN: The people
who work on these movies
by and large are artists
who want to be appreciated
as artists by other
artists in town,
so when they are in
contention for an Oscar
it means something deeper.
It satisfies them in a
way that money can't only.
- So it's really about
talent acquisition
and talent retainment?
KYLE BUCHANAN: Yeah, it's
about making sure that people
are happy, you know.
We see it all the time.
When a star has had
success, and then
they want to do
something more serious.
They want to be understood as
an artist with something to say.
- Is that me?
- When Warner Brothers goes
all in on an Oscar campaign
for Bradley Cooper or Ben
Affleck or Clint Eastwood,
it's not just for
bragging rights,
or even a box office bump.
No, the studio spends that
cash to show commitment
to its stars, and
to keep them coming
back for future projects.
For example, Hollywood's
biggest studio, Disney,
is pushing harder and harder
for its top blockbusters
to be an Oscar contention.
- What next?
- But the race isn't just
between traditional studios
anymore.
So why does something like
Netflix want to win an Oscar?
I mean, it's already
the talk of Hollywood,
it's one of the biggest media
companies on the planet.
Why does it need
the little gold man?
KYLE BUCHANAN: I
think Netflix is
eager to disrupt any industry
it can get its hands on.
You know, they've
already changed the way
that we watch
television, now they
want to do the same for movies.
Just like any studio, they want
to be able to get in the Oscar
race so that top tier
auteurs will come
to them to make movies
instead of the big studios
that are out there.
If they can penetrate
this race, there's really
nothing that Netflix can't do.
They want to upend the idea
of theatrical distribution
being the end all, be
all of seeing a movie.
They want to change the
way you see a movie.
And if they can get
Oscar to validate that,
then they've gotten
almost all the way there.
- The Academy is getting
younger and more diverse,
and its nominees and
winners are shifting, too.
KYLE BUCHANAN: I think
it's good and necessary
to recontextualize what we
think of as an Oscar contender
because it means that a lot of
better movies that have maybe
even historically
overlooked by the season,
but have certainly not been
overlooked by audience members,
can actually get into the race.
- Over the decades,
the Academy Awards
have become bigger,
more expensive,
and maybe a bit more inclusive.
But in the end,
Louis B Mayer started
the awards to flatter stars
into working in his movies.
And today, studios
will spend more
than ever to do just the same.
KYLE BUCHANAN: When it comes
to this town, when it comes
to Hollywood, a lot of
people go into the industry,
or even before they
get into the industry,
they've stood in
front of that mirror.
They've practiced
that Oscar speech.
It is still the summit of
this industry in so many ways,
and a lot of people
want that to really
feel like they've picked the
dream that they've always had.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
CARL AZUZ: For 10 out of 10,
we present to you, The Starry
Night by Vincent van--
Vincent van-- how do you say it?
He's one of the most well-known
artists in the world,
but an audio guide at a
new exhibition in London
says Van Gogh.
And experts say that's wrong.
Some say it should be
pronounced "van goth",
some say "van gog"
some say "van coch".
This has been a controversy
since the artist was alive,
and that's reportedly part
of the reason why he signed
every painting simply, Vincent.
Who would have thought
the controversy
would still be van going so
long after he'd van gone?
Some might van
scoff at the idea,
some might get the
Impressionism that the debate
is better discussed on, let's
say, a cafe terrace at night.
Some will just van go
with what they van know,
and you'll never be able to
convince at them otherwise.
Beachwood, sounds like it could
have been one of van Gogh's
paintings, but we wrap
up today with Beachwood
High School in Beachwood, Ohio.
Thank you for subscribing and
commenting on our YouTube page.
For CNN 10, I'm Carl Azuz.
[MUSIC PLAYING]