So I'm going to talk to you about Hive,
which is a database that runs on top
of HDFS and
uses MapReduce to do its computation.
The whole idea was
started that Facebook and
it was to look at data
from nightly chron jobs.
They were put into an Oracle database but
that proved to be very a lot of
overhead and the data was very large.
So they developed an ETL
using hang coded Python.
And develop their own language called HQL,
which was a variant of SQL,
and what HQL does is a query language for
Hive.
It avoids some of the problems
that you get into with event,
if you have an eventually
consistent sort of system.
And you're looking at all these
things in a distributed maner from
multiple machines.
And HQL provides you a way to do that and
doesn't require
you to have a rigid sort of
SQL type of interpretation.
So what we're looking at with Hive is
a translation of queries
into map reduced jobs.
And this can run on top of Hadoop YARN.
It runs on top of Tez or Spark as well,
which gives you alternate ways to
actually implement it, and
sometimes those can be faster.
Again, note here that
the database itself is
not updated or changed in any
form while this is all happening.
You're assuming a read-only database, and
it's going to focus primary on
query part of the language SQL.
The implementations, so
there are missing pieces of SQL if
you like in HQL, but
they allow it to perform very fast.
So, Hive looks very similar
to an SQL database.
You can do a relational
join on two tables.
If you're on the table of word counts,
Shakespeare's collection of words in
a book, and you found a table of word
counts from a Homer on one of his books.
And you want to actually compare them,
you can do so.
And that would look like
an algorithm like this.
What you're doing to
select from Shakespeare's.
In here, and
you're going to get the frequency
of the words that you had selected.
And then you're going to join that
information with the same thing
applied to another
select applied to Homer.
So here's the Homer data with words.
And what you would like to do is just to
look at the ones that have some sort of
values in there.
So we're asking the frequency
counts are bigger than zero, but
in the Shakespeare and the Homer database.
And then we're going to order
the whole result of that select so
that what we have is a limit on
what we're going to print out.
And it's going to be ten and we're going
to be doing it in descending order.
And that's what's actually listed below.
The ten top frequency words that appear
in the join between Shakespeare and
Homer, and surprise, surprise the leads
the and it lead the pack there.
So, behind the scenes,
what is that example actually doing?
Well, what it does is to take the data
from these two collections, and
it creates an abstract syntax tree, which
is sort of just basically a set tubules.
And the words from those and
as you can see,
what it's collected here
is where those words occur.
It looks like a syntax tree where
you're taking the Shakespeare words,
you're taking the whole words and
then you're applying different operators
that are high primitives to those.
And, as you extrude you will
see that each of those Hive,
the HQL has been translated into this,
more sort of primitive sort of
language of looking at each individual
item and applying a function to it.
And what then occurs is
you take all of these and
you map them into what I'm all,
MapReduce jobs.
So for example, with the word, looking for
how many, or counting the number of words,
what you're going to do is be building
a MapReduce job that counts the number
of words from the Shakespeare job,
and then from the Homer job, and then
you're going to go down here with a JOIN.
You're going to write a similar MapReduce
job that maps these two things together.
So Hive as you've seen is
actually got a shell and
you can write pretty much
that language into a shell.
And the introductory
tutorials from Hive on our
Horton works, looks well,
builds that type of query
in the shell like that.
There's drivers that handle the sessions,
fetch and
execute there's a compiler that does
the parsing and the planning and
optimizing how the map reducers will
be performed and what analysis goes on.
And then, there's an execution
engine that takes all of this
description that sort of
abstract syntax tree and
executes it as different
MapReduced jobs with HDFS and
all the metadata to build the results,
which it then stores back in HDFS.
Hive uses a traditional
database to store its metadata.
It's a sort of namespace
containing a set of tables.
Those table definitions contain
column types, physical layout,
holds partitioning data.
It could actually be used to store data in
a variety of different, databases,
depending upon what you want.
But if you can map them
into something like Hspace,
you can get a much faster implementation.
The Hive has a warehouse directory
in HDFS, as to built for Hive.
And provides,
there's a tutorial that provides lots of
examples on the warehouse in Hadoop works.
The tables are stored in sub
directories of warehouses of warehouse.
The partitions from
subdirectory of the tables
Allow you to access pieces of each of
those tables on different machines.
And then you're going to use
MapReduce over the whole thing
to actually aggregate it.
The actual data is stored in flat files.
They are delimited text or
sequential files.
And they can be customized to use any sort
of format, but mostly just text files.
So this whole thing sort
of ends up looking like
an HDFS with blocks holding ASCI text.
That's actually input to do the
manipulations by your map reduce programs.
[MUSIC]