"Temple of God of Chivalry"
"Birthday of God of Chivalry"
The host of the Ceremony
offering joss sticks please
Wait
Today is the birthday of God of Chivalry
All martial arts schools
are paying their respects
A host of high esteem
should conduct the ceremony
how could we let a kid like him do it?
Master Wu, the ceremony is usually hosted
by Lin Zan Tian school every year
Why?
Master Lin is the main
in Shaolin's line of succession
and respected by all
I have heard of his name too
he couldn't be this young
Master Lin is recovering
from illness in the village
this is his head pupil
Master Cheng
If master Lin were here
I'd have nothing to say
but since he is not
this matter has to be discussed
Would you, the Manchus School
lead the ceremony?
That could be a possibility
That's a joke, God of Chivalry is Han
why should we let you Manchurians do it?
The court respects God of Chivalry
and there's no distinction
between Han and Qing
why can't the Manchurians do it?
This is bullshit
Master Wu
since you are aware
the court respects God of Chivalry
we must go by the old rules of
celebrating his birthday
and not cause any trouble
Offering the joss sticks
Who is this?
He is master Lin's pupil master Law
Damn, another pupil from Lin's School
So is today's ceremony
all taken care of by Shaolin?
As per rules, the leader
should perform with the sword
Since you've said it
let's invite master Law to perform
after which a representative
from the Manchurian school
will also perform
to let us appreciate their skills
But this is not
according to the old protocol
Master Cheng, what do you think?
Alright
Get the knife
Brother Law, give him the blade
He should be ashamed of his technique
You dare look down on us?
You dare hurt people in the festival?
Brother Law is injured internally
I fear he couldn't be saved
He's dead
Attack...
Let's go...
Hand over the murderer
You are making trouble,
do you want to rebel?
Our people have been murdered
why put the blame on us?
All we need is to capture the murderer
It's hard to find the murderer
in a gang fight
Sir, please take a look
we are all empty handed
our brother has been eviscerated
the weapon is still here
This is not a gang fight
This is a gang fight
The best we could do is not charge you
if you keep at it
you'll see what you'll get
The authorities have been monitoring
you guys from Shaolin closely
Wu Chung Ping to see the General
I ordered you to establish
a martial arts school
how's your progress
in eliminating the Shaolin rebels?
General, the Guangdong people are tough
and those who practice martial arts
are stiff necked
Rubbish
Yes, our school has recruited
many Manchurian pupils
and our numbers are great
Don't be too optimistic
I hear that in the your town
there are south Shaolin rebels
General, they couldn't cause much harm
You dare hide things from me?
I dare not...
The Shaolin rebels
always look for causing trouble
The court has decreed several times
that they should be suppressed
yet you and your men
cause trouble at the festival
and were clobbered
We've been disgraced,
how should you suffer for this?
Mercy, General...
General, although he is guilty
in view of his loyalty
let him make up for it
I'll spare you this time, rise
Wu Chung Ping
I await your instructions
You boast your kung fu is good,
yet I don't think so
I am useless...
I knew just you alone
would not be able to suppress those rebels
Master He Lian
who's a kung fu expert
has assisted me all these years
He is my confidante
I deliberately asked him
to go outside the border
and invite his two pupils
who are both skilled martial art heroes
This is Ba Gang
This is Yu Bi
Don't let their young age fool you
no weapons could harm them
When they start to
purge the Shaolin dissidents
you'll know what I mean
Right
These two are our master's
favorite pupils
Get to know each other
Yes
Who is in charge of Shaolin school?
Lin Zan Tian
However he is old and sick
and not in town anymore
he's a hermit in the village now
All martial arts schools
are a threat to the court
The three of them will help you
and start with Shaolin school
to annihilate them all
Yes, with the three masters
we'll be invincible
Dad, you've been sitting here
since morning
you have a lot on your mind
you should take care of your health
I am old and not much to worry about
I only fear that
under the reign of the Manchus
the court treats Shaolin as a threat
For the future...
Dad, all your pupils
are good and strong fighters
Yes, it's precisely because they are young
and hot blooded
that I am even more worried
You'd better rest inside first
Uncle Lin, sister Zhen Xiu bullied me
Zhen Xiu, look at you
If you continue to big mouth
I'll teach you a lesson
If you are fierce like that
I'll warn Bao Rong about you
Is he here?
I saw Bao Rong board the boat
I came to tell her with good intentions
but she beat me instead
Ah Wai, you...
See where you can run
How come you are so reckless?
Are you blind?
Watch your way, understand?
Miss, it's you who bumped into me
it's not my fault
Who are you calling 'Miss'?
Open your eyes wide and see
Brother, wait for me
So you are uncle Lin's pupil
I'll tell him to punish you
The Manchu school
is constantly causing trouble for us
they are betting on the Qing's support
to do whatever they like with us
Could brother Law have died in vain
having been killed by them
at the Festival?
The homeland has been torn apart
We Shaolin boxers
with seniors like Fang Shi Yu
and Wu Hui Qian
have died many heroic deaths
Why should you need to struggle
for a petty host?
Had you given them
the right to lead the ceremony
there would be no trouble
We'll do as you say
As you have crossed them in public,
they will not give up
you must be on your guard at all times
"Lin's martial arts school"
I said I wouldn't go, yet you forced me to
Stop your nonsense,
what did the teacher say?
He scolded me
and asked us to be restrained and patient;
To uphold morals,
widely recruit students and
wait for the right opportunity
to overthrow the Qings
Brother, hearing what teacher said
did you tell him
they came to look for trouble
and killed brother Law?
Yes, but he said
we should not have vied for the host
and developed a grudge with them
They are sure to come back
and cause trouble
"Main line of succession of Shaolin"
Relax. If they come back
that's even better
we'll have the chance to avenge
brother Law's death
I can't believe, our seniors
such as Fang Shi Yu and Hong Xi Guan
were evading the enemy all along
and dared not hit back
Teacher must have his reasons
to instruct us so
we should listen to him
What else did teacher say?
Li Yao told you all
He only utters some words
after you prick him
it is a waste of time
"Manchu martial arts school"
Assemble everyone at the school tomorrow
Yes
If you could get him interested
I'll pay you ten taels of silver
Really?
You'll lose,
Yu Lin is famous for charming people
You want to win the silver, right?
Yes
Come
See? You've lost
Don't be impatient, watch
Master He, these 2 masters
have practiced Child kung fu
don't ruin their training
Wait and see...
Well? Still can't win me?
This Master Ba he...
What about him?
What happened?
Master Wu, our brother
has attained the acme in Steel Armor
which covers even his private parts
Wow, that's great
I've heard that
the Priest White Brows of Er Mei
knew such kung fu as well
You better come with me
I have another kind of skill
"Manchu martial arts school"
Masters, please
"Lin's martial arts school"
Wu
From where did you get them?
The good thing about you
is you're thick skinned
Li Yao, come back
This guy is too sensitive
Who'll come up and fight?
You are...
Never mind that
Nameless upstarts
are not eligible to fight
Wang Jing He
Fine, strike 3 blows first
then I'll return three blows
I don't want to take advantage of you
I afraid you can't
Follow me outside
Brother, be careful
Brother Wang
Watch this
He struck me three blows
but I haven't retaliated
What are you doing out here?
Is there such a rule
when a Shaolin disciple
competes with others?
Come on then
I'll die standing
Step down
It seems Shaolin's kung fu is no big deal
the practitioner is like a paper doll
it only took three punches
to end the fight
Your Qi Gong is not bad
Don't try taking turns to tire him,
I'll handle you
Attack...
Go...
Brother, let's talk
when we see the teacher
Strange, they've gone
They must have gone that way, let's go...
Master
We didn't want to start any trouble
but they led some men
to our door to fight
Master, brother and his men
died a cruel death
You met two true masters
Follow me
Hey
Master
One of them practices Steel Armor
the other Qi Gong
and both have reached
the acme of their art
They are invincible?
There's no such thing
there's always someone better
Steel Armor makes the body muscles
tough as a log
and makes one insensitive to blows
but the groin remains vulnerable
Rolling Eagle Claw
Qi Gong can dissipate the power of blows
When one is at his best
he could rebound the power of the blow
and injure the one who initiated the punch
However,
it cannot withstand attack by fingers
The Eagle Claw
This used to be Shaolin's style
but it is not my expertise
besides, I am old and weak
With your foundation of kung fu
and the right teacher
you could win in three months
Teacher, brother Chen and me...
The King of Eagle Claw
His Eagle Claw
is at the highest level
Eagle Claw, Rolling Eagle Claw
You could follow his mentorship
Though he has been a recluse
for many years
I think he might help you
in this matter
Get up
Your teacher is a real pain
How many years have you spent with him?
7 years
8 years
7 and 8 years
your kung fu should have established
some foundation
I want to test you
Be careful
Your teacher must want you
to learn this kick
What a speedy kick!
Right
You must coordinate the kick
with your body movement so
that even if
your opponent knows you'll kick his groin
he still can't escape
Careful
Sir, I want to learn the Eagle Claw
You have the patience?
Yes
This river has many carps
they only taste good
if caught by hand
I love carp
you should catch fifty a day for me
and don't see me till you do so
I am not afraid of you
Why have you doused me with water?
You did that to me first
I have nothing to say to a kid like you
Who says I am a kid?
You know nothing but making fun of others
Look at you all,
pulling a long face all day
That wouldn't make your enemy get hurt
I have nothing to say to you kid
Don't stop
Coward, he dare not come after me
Practicing all day and ignores me
Ah Wai
Who are you talking to?
Who are you calling 'coward'?
Who keeps practicing and ignoring you?
I have not been lazy
Exactly fifty, all caught today
Sir, you should teach me
the Eagle Claw, right?
I have been doing this routine for a month
Let me look at your hands
Tomorrow onwards
you go to chop trees in the forest
I want a branch
as wide as the diameter of a bowl
each three feet long,
and I want a total of 50
Chopping down trees?
Yes
Brother and I come to learn from you
He practices kung fu every day
while I go catching fish
Now you want me to chop down trees
You can leave
The fishes are so nice
Brother He
Do you know the progress of brother Mai?
Talking to you is no better than
talking to a rock
Li Yao, aren't you afraid of nothing?
How come you look so scared
when you see Ah Wai?
Never mind, I'll go for my practice
If I am as idle as she is
she will be scared too if she sees me
You are asking for pardon
Ah Wai, it's been agreed
that you 2 won't quarrel again
How come you do it again?
She agreed not to argue with me?
Ah Wai
You'd better keep your mouth shut
No more tricks, I hope
Good, all the trees
have been chopped today
Fifty altogether, no more no less
I don't want any bark on it
Alright, let me slice them slowly
No need to
No need? You want me do it barehanded?
That's right
Senior, I understand
Should we go back
to Teacher's place first?
Better go to Qing School first
and learn the situation now;
And then go back to
Teacher's place to discuss
further about the combat
Good
If the General knows that
you have trashed over ten
martial arts schools
in the past few months
he would be very pleased
Any further instructions
from the General?
He asked you to be careful of runaways
There'll be trouble
if you can't kill them all
With the three of you,
what are we afraid of?
Teacher, we've caught
four Lin Zan Tian's students
Bring them in
Yes
Go
What are you doing?
Move...
Men from the Qing School
have caught four Master Lin's students
The Qing guys have captured
four of our brothers
Let's go and rescue them
You've to practice martial arts
everyday at our school
Why haven't you come?
We are Hans
How dare you talk like that
Who else isn't convinced?
Stop
There are some runaways
who are here to look for death
There's a lot of audience here
It's a good opportunity for
our experts to show their skills
Eagle Claw! Yu Bi, watch out
Ba Gang
From now on whoever dares to
go against us will be dead
These people are not convinced
We can't let them go
They will surely go back
with information on us
We have to uproot them this time
Hurry and tail them
Yes
Report to the authorities
and hang their bodies
in front of
Lin Zan Tian's martial arts school
"Two Shaolin disciples cause trouble
in the Qing School"
What's going on?
Hurry and come out
What's happening?
It's Brother Ho and Brother Mai
I've caused them death
Teacher
Brother Ho kicked Ba Gang's groin for sure
why isn't he hurt?
I didn't expect his Steel Armor
to have attained
the level of priest White Brows
It means he could draw in his groin
Teacher, brother Mai's Eagle Claw
could have tackled his Qi Gong
But Yu Bi was prepared
and Brother Mai couldn't defeat him
Teacher, what are we going to do next?
You have some rest first
Li Yao, Chen Bao Rong, come here
Teacher said that
Master Liang has a very bad temper
You have to be patient
Yes, you want to learn Wing Chuen kung fu
I'm afraid this is even harder
Let's go
Where has Li Yao gone?
He's gone to study under a famous teacher
Let's go in and tell dad
Dad
The Qing dogs are here, go quickly
Teacher, we'll not leave you
Dad, what's to be done?
There is no other choice
are you really not leaving?
Teacher, please instruct us
Go, let the Qing dogs know that
Shaolin disciples would rather die
than yield
Dad
Leave at the back while
the four of them fight
Dad
Do as I say
Tell Bao Rong to remember this hatred
Quick, get Ah Wai out of here
Uncle Lin
Old fool, you'd better surrender
Shaolin disciples never yield
Ba Gang's Steel Armor kung fu
has reached the same level
as priest White Brows
Back then
Shaolin disciples annihilated the traitor
by the efforts of
Hung Wan Ding and Wu Ah Biu
Priest White Brows could only be killed
by the Tiger and Crane Fist combined
Li Yao, you have to train very hard
otherwise you'll fail
Are you determined?
Bao Rong, show me your skills
With these fight skills
you can't take Yu Bi unawares
Won't you be making the same mistake
as Mai Han
You could only take him by surprise
at close range
Wing Chuen advocates close range power
it is also a branch of Shaolin
and originated from Great Master Wu Mei
If you cannot release your power
within an inch
you'll die in vain
Get lost
You want to learn
the Tiger and Crane Fist?
Master Liang, listen to me
Are you leaving or not?
Li Yao, the only one who could teach you
the Tiger and Crane Fist is Master Liang
He is eccentric
and you have to put up with him
and beg him to teach you
Master Liang
Still talking bullshit
I have read your teacher's letter
It is a paradigm shift
for you to change
from the wide stances of Hung Fist
to using power through short punches
I am a man of few words
if you don't think
you could make it just go
I will work hard
Master, good morning
Teacher, I have trained for a month
By just watching me practice
and trying to force me
to show the real technique
Forget it
"Tai Yu restaurant"
That way please
How did you get on with
what I told you to find out?
Lin Zan Tian Martial Arts School
has already been destroyed
by the Qing School
What about Lin Zan Tian?
It took me a lot of effort
to see Master Lin's daughter
Master Lin killed himself
Thank you for showing me the way
Isn't it enough for you
to pass the night in the open?
Thank you teacher
What did teacher Lin say to you
when he sent you here?
That you're considerate
and warmhearted & the only one
whom Hong Zhi Guan bequeathed
the Tiger and Crane Fist
Only you could teach me
Since the opponent's Steel Armor kung fu
has reached the same level
as priest White Brows
he must know that
the eyes are a vulnerable spot
If you use the Crane style
to attack his eyes
how could he not
successfully defend himself
As teacher said
after I have learnt
the Tiger and Crane Fist
I should only fight with the Tiger Fist
and not reveal my knowledge
of the Crane style
until I get the opportunity
to strike successfully
You could imagine
even if you knew the Tiger and Crane Fist
If you fail to attack successfully
with the Crane fist
your opponent would be on the alert
and you could still die at his hands
I have thought about it
I can teach but it's up to you
to defeat your enemy
Yes
Bao Rong... I have been here a long while
but I did not want to distract you
so I agreed with Master not to see you yet
Why aren't you practicing?
I've failed.
Going to tell my teacher I'm quitting
Dad can't hear you anymore
When you left a gang came...
What are you doing?
Teacher, I always feel
there are people outside
Nonsense. Get up
I have made it
Still a long way to go
How many inches left?
Five inches
You can only defeat your enemy
with two inches
I could practice
I wonder about the progress of Li Yao
He's smarter than I am,
he must be far ahead of me
Ah Wai is looking for him too
I've told Ah Wai not to show up
I'm afraid that he'll be distracted
Ah Wai, if you keep peeping from outside
sooner or later he'll find out
I have a way to deal with him
Did he suspect
the food I cooked for him?
Yes, he stopped and
thought at each mouthful
I wonder what he was thinking about
Master Liang, don't be too harsh on him
Stop talking nonsense
Master
When did you come?
When you were still outside
Master Liang's house
What a hard month it was
but seeing teacher practice each day
I established a good foundation
You are shameless
How pitiful you looked
when you were scolded by Master
Careful or he'll scold you
for peeping outside the wall
Don't worry
Master Liang is very kind to me,
he won't scold
How's Master Lin?
What about Sister Zhen Xiu?
They are not worried you've come?
Sister Zhen Xiu went to
look for Brother Bao Rong
What about Master?
Someone came to the Lin residence
the day you left
Master Lin...
You...
I have to practice kung fu,
stop meddling with me
What's up? Say something
Even you have nothing to say?
What more could we say?
Master Liang said
he only could teach me kung fu
Whether I could defeat Ba Gang
depends on my own
You are leaving early tomorrow morning
You've got to eat something
"Main line of succession of Shaolin"
We must rebuild the school
and the reputation of Shaolin
Master, please bless us
and help us take revenge on the Qing dogs
"Manchu martial arts school"
Who is it?
Hurry and go...