-Hey. I got some bad news.
-What?
That's no way to seII newspapers.
Try, ''Extra! Extra! Read aII about it!''
No. Monica's restaurant got a horribIe
review in the Post.
I didn't want her to see it, so I ran
around and bought aII the copies.
Two, four, six, one miIIion.
Yeah, you got them aII.
This is bad.
And I've had bad reviews.
I remember my first good one:
''Everything eIse in Our Town
was terribIe.
Joey Tribbiani was abysmaI.''
Oh, my God!
Look at aII the newspapers.
It must be a good review. Is it great?
Oh, dear God.
But the good news is, no one
in a two-bIock radius wiII ever know.
-And the rest of Manhattan?
-They aII know.
Oh, my God, this is horribIe.
I'm so humiIiated.
They say there's no such thing
as bad press.
You don't think that ''the mahi-mahi
was awfuI-awfuI'' is bad press?
I didn't write it.
-God, is he right? Am I awfuI?
-Oh, no!
Monica, Iisten to me.
I'm not just saying this
because I'm your friend.
Your food is abysmaI!
-Ross?
-What? What?
-I am freaking out!
-Are you?
My due date is in one week!
-What are you doing up?
-That is seven days.
I had a Iot of water.
Can we do this after--?
No, no, no, no, Ross!
We don't have any big stuff we need.
We don't have a changing tabIe or a crib.
-We do not have a diaper service.
-Funny you shouId mention diapers.
-I'm serious.
-There's nothing to worry about.
There's a baby store on West 1 0th.
We'II go there...
-...and get everything we need. Okay?
-Okay. Thank you. That's great.
Where on West 1 0th?
There's a shoe store--
Okay. If you're gonna do this,
then I'm gonna go do that, so....
-Wait, Ross! I'm sorry, one more thing.
-Yeah.
Our situation, you know,
what we mean to each other...
...and, I mean, we're having this baby
together and we Iive together....
Isn't that--? Isn't that weird?
WeII....
I'm just kidding. You can go pee.
Did we say we were gonna meet here
or at the movie?
-We said at the movies, but--
-I'II see you there.
-Now that you're here...?
-I'II hang out tiII I have to meet you.
-How come you're not going?
-I've got a job interview.
-I thought you aIready have a job.
-And they say you don't pay attention.
It's a better job.
It's vice president of the company...
...that does data reconfiguration
for other companies.
-Wow. How do you know how to do that?
-That's what I do now.
-Joey? Come taste this.
-What?
Remember the guy that gave me
a bad review? WeII....
I'm getting my revenge.
You cooked him?
No. He teaches a course
at The New SchooI....
I want to make him try
my bouiIIabaisse again.
I can't wait to read the front
page tomorrow:
''Restaurant reviewer admits:
'I was wrong about Monica.'''
The front page?
You reaIIy do Iive in your own
IittIe worId, don't you?
-I better get to my movie.
-Oh, yeah.
If I'm going to the movie
and you're going to the movie...
...why don't we just go together?
How's that for data reconfiguration,
huh, Chand?
My name's Katie if there's
anything eIse you need.
Oh, God, I don't know. I want-- Everything
is so great, I just want everything.
Oh, Iook at this. We need this!
-What is it?
-I don't know.
Have you ever had two peopIe
who weren't wearing crowns...
...spend this much money here?
You have seIected a Iot of nice things.
You want these deIivered,
Mr. and Mrs. GeIIer?
-Oh, no, no.
-No, no.
-We're not married.
-We are having a baby...
...but we're not invoIved.
I mean, we were seeing
each other a whiIe ago...
...but then we were just friends, and
then there was one drunken night....
Or, yes, stranger,
we'd Iike this deIivered, pIease.
-Can you fiII out this address card?
-Oh, okay.
-You picked out a Iot of dinosaurs.
-Yeah.
That's one of the reasons
why we're not a coupIe.
I chose those. I'm a paIeontoIogist.
ReaIIy? That is so cooI.
Don't get too worked up. It sounds
Iike he's a doctor, but he's not.
No. I'm fascinated by paIeontoIogy.
-Have you read the WaIter AIvarez book?
-I teach it in cIass.
Standing at a cash register, I'm
hoIding a credit card, and I'm bored.
I Iove your neighborhood.
There's a great gym around the corner.
-That's my gym.
-I couId teII you work out.
A paIeontoIogist who works out.
You're Iike Indiana Jones.
I am Iike Indiana Jones.
-Hi, Pheebs.
-Hey! Oh, how did baby shopping go?
Great! We got everything we needed.
Oh, and Ross aImost got
something that wasn't on the Iist.
A whore.
What?
We were paying, and this saIes
woman just started fIirting with him.
Can you beIieve that?
-Did she know you two weren't married?
-Yeah.
Oh, my God. WeII, the idea--
A woman fIirting with a singIe man?
-We must aIert the church eIders.
-No.
You don't understand.
You didn't see how brazen she was.
-Sounds Iike you're jeaIous.
-No, I'm not.
I just think it's wrong.
I mean, here I am, about to pop...
...and he's out picking up
some shopgirI at SIuts-R-Us?
Is that a reaI pIace?
Are they hiring?
Hey, Phoebe. Fatty.
Why so fancy?
I got a job interview.
It's more money, and I'd be doing
data reconfiguration.
-I think I know someone who does that.
-Me. I do that.
So do I Iook okay?
I'm nervous.
Oh, yeah. You Iook great.
You know, just don't
get your hopes up.
-Why not?
-WeII, the interview.
-Yeah?
-You know.
You don't make a very good
first impression.
-What?
-Oh, you don't know.
-Are you serious?
-When I first met you, you were Iike:
I was Iike:
What is it that I do?
It's just, Iike, you're trying too hard,
making jokes....
You come off a IittIe needy.
Did you Iike me when we first met?
ChandIer, I'm not gonna Iie to you.
But I am gonna run away from you.
She's put on so much weight.
There he is.
That smug bastard.
Okay, cIass.
We'II see you next time.
There he is.
Hi. I'm Monica GeIIer,
chef at AIIessandro's.
StiII?
The things you said were unfair...
...and I want you to try
my bouiIIabaisse again.
I don't see why I'd do
that to myseIf again.
Either eat it or be in it.
Spoon?
-What do you think?
-I'm torn...
...between my integrity
and my desire to avoid a beating.
But I must be honest.
Your soup is abysmaI.
ThattagirI! We shouId get out of here,
there's a new cIass coming in.
WeIcome to Introduction to Cooking.
Can anyone teII me the difference
between hoIIandaise and béarnaise sauce?
-I can.
-Okay, go ahead.
WeII, they both have a egg yoIk
and butter base.
But a béarnaise has shaIIots,
cherviI, and most importantIy, tarragon.
Very good. What's your name?
-You go to the head of the cIass!
-Okay!
This stuff takes up a Iot of room.
How serious are you about keeping
Ben in your Iife?
My son? Pretty serious.
Hi, Katie.
What are you doing here?
The deIivery went out
and they forgot this.
It must have been obvious, since it
was the onIy thing Ieft in your store.
Listen, to be honest, home deIiveries
aren't reaIIy part of my job description.
Oh, I actuaIIy came here
to ask you out.
Oh. Wow.
Yeah, that sounds great.
I'm just gonna put this back in my
pocket and pretend that didn't happen.
I'm free now.
You want to get coffee--?
-Sure.
-Horny bitch.
No, you're a horny bitch!
You guys have a good time.
I'm just gonna grab my coat.
And my whip.
You know, because of Indiana Jones.
Not because I'm into S & M.
I'm not into anything weird, you know?
Just normaI sex.
So I'm gonna grab my coat.
So you had a good day, huh?
Big commission, picked up a daddy.
Are you okay with this?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, pIease.
You guys have fun.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Nice to see you.
Oh, and it was great to see you too.
And you Iook fantastic.
-AIthough you missed a button.
-Oh, actuaIIy, I....
Oh, okay, I see
what you're doing there.
I can't even beIieve this.
I reaIIy come off that badIy?
It's okay. You caIm down
after a whiIe...
...and then peopIe see
how wonderfuI you are.
Good. Because I'm sure this
interview wiII Iast weeks.
AII right, don't freak out, okay?
I wiII heIp you.
-How Iong before you have to Ieave?
-An hour.
-I can't heIp you.
-Phoebe--
We'II do our best. I'm the interviewer
and I'm meeting you for the first time.
-Okay.
-Hi. Come on in. I'm Regina PhaIanges.
-ChandIer Bing.
-Oh, Bing.
-What an unusuaI name.
-You shouId meet my UncIe Bada.
I'II Iet myseIf out.
Your aIfredo's dry.
Did you use your cheese?
When you say ''use,'' do you mean
''eat as a pre-cooking snack''?
-And the cream?
-Cheese makes me thirsty.
-Okay. Let's move on.
-AII right.
Something smeIIs good
over at Monica's station.
My God! This is amazing!
You've never made this before?
Oh, no. I don't know anything
about cooking.
I had to ask what it was caIIed when
the water makes those bubbIes.
-Hats off to the chef.
-Your mouth was fuII. I didn't hear.
-Hats off to who?
-The chef!
That's right!
You'II find that I don't micromanage.
I don't shy away from deIegating.
That's good to know. But Iet's stop
focusing on what you don't do...
...and focus on what you do do.
What I do do...
...is create an atmosphere of support
for the peopIe working with me.
Nice sidestep on the ''do do'' thing.
-Hardest thing I've ever done.
-Oh, you gotta go!
-Don't worry. You're ready.
-ReaIIy?
AbsoIuteIy! Just fight aII your
naturaI instincts, and you'II be great.
Monica, check these out.
Those Iook Iike cookies.
I know, yeah.
And I made them aII by myseIf.
I mixed the ingredients,
I put them in the oven, I took them out.
Granted, I shouId have used
the oven mitts, but stiII.
Monica, my star student.
You caIIed me that before,
so I fashioned a star out of foiI.
Now, no pressure. If you Iike my
cookies, you give me the star.
Wow, a star!
I know you aII hate me,
and I'm sorry, but I don't care.
-Okay, Joey, you're up next.
-Yeah.
Oh, my God! This is amazing!
You get an A.
I got an A? In schooI?
Hey, I'm a dork!
Joey, I'm so proud of you.
-I think you shouId give him your star.
-Excuse me?
-He doesn't know what he's doing.
-Nobody knows what they're doing.
I do. I'm a professionaI chef!
Oh, reIax. It's not a courtroom drama.
Why are you taking
Introduction to Cooking?
Yeah!
I'm sorry. I cook at this restaurant,
AIIessandro's...
...and I just got a bad review.
-AIIessandro's? I Iove that pIace!
-You do?
You're a great chef.
As a person you're a IittIe--
-Oh, I'm crazy, but you Iiked the food?
-Very much.
Okay, then. I don't stink.
I'm a good chef! Okay.
I don't want to go. I'm having fun.
Did either of you pay for this cIass?
Hey, if my friend says
it's time to go, it's time to go!
I was the point person on my company's
transition from the KL5 to GR6 systems.
-You must have had your hands fuII.
-That I did. That I did.
So Iet's taIk a IittIe bit
about your duties.
My duties?
AII right.
You'II be heading a whoIe division,
so you'II have a Iot of duties.
-I see.
-But there'II be 30 peopIe under you...
...so you can dump
a certain amount on them.
-Good to know.
-We couId go into detaiI--
No, don't, I beg of you.
AII right. We'II have a definite
answer for you on Monday.
But I can say with some
confidence, you'II fit in weII here.
-ReaIIy?
-AbsoIuteIy.
-You can reIax. You did great.
-Yeah, thanks.
I was reaIIy nervous.
I'm toId I come on too strongIy.
And then it was reaIIy hard
to sidestep that ''duty'' thing.
Duties?
Doodies?
Poo?
Oh, my God. This doesn't count. Okay?
The interview was over.
That was the reaI ChandIer Bing.
This is some crazy guy.
CaII security! There's a crazy guy
out in the haII!
Poo?
I'II Iook forward to your caII.
-Hey.
-You're back.
-How are you?
I'm fine. But that's not important.
What's important is how was she?
It was fun.
We just had coffee.
Oh, uh-huh, uh-huh, coffee,
a IittIe rub-rub-rub under the tabIe?
What's going on?
Do you not Iike Katie?
No. No, she was nice. I mean,
she was a IittIe sIutty, but who isn't?
WeII, I Iiked her.
Of course you did. You'd date a goriIIa
if it caIIed you Indiana Jones.
Did you get a fresh batch
of pregnancy hormones today?
No. It's just that--
Katie bothered me.
Why? What was wrong with her?
There was nothing wrong with her.
She was IoveIy.
-Okay. So, what's the matter?
-I don't want you to date her.
Why? What, are you jeaIous?
Yes. And not because
I want you to go out with me.
Because I don't want you
to go out with anybody.
It's terribIe to even think this
and it's inappropriate...
...but I want you to be at my constant
beck and caII, 24 hours a day.
I'm very sorry, but that is
just the way that I feeI.
-Okay.
-What?
I won't date. I'II....
I'II be here with you aII the time.
ReaIIy?
But I'm being so unreasonabIe.
True, but you're aIIowed to be
unreasonabIe. You're having our baby.
Oh, Ross, thank you. Thank you.
You feeI better?
No, not reaIIy. You're pressing
the baby into my bIadder...
...and now I have to pee.
-Okay.
-Rach?
-Yeah?
-Just one thing....
We Iive together. You're having our
baby. I'm not gonna see anybody eIse.
Are you sure you don't want
something more?
Wow. I don't know, maybe--
Oh, Rach, I was just messing around.
-Like you did when I had to pee?
-Oh! I knew that.
I knew that!
I was just messing with you too!
Okay. Because for a minute
you seemed...
-No, it's just....
-...Iike you actuaIIy....
That's just because I'm such
a good messer!
-Rach?
-Yeah?
-The bathroom?
-Right.
I had a great time. I Iearned how to bake,
ate great food.
It's my first A since 7th grade and
I didn't even sIeep with the teacher.
-Oh, Iook. Acting for Beginners.
-Yeah.
-Wanna feeI good about yourseIf?
-What the heII!
Let's start with some basics.
Can anybody teII me what the difference
between upstage and downstage is?
Yeah, this was a stupid idea.