-Hey.
-Hey. So, what do you think?
New haircut? NeckIace? Dress?
Boots? Boots!
Now, they're a IittIe more than I usuaIIy
spend on boots. Or rent.
Did you say you bought ''boots''
or ''boats''?
I know.
-I'II miss being abIe to afford food.
-I'm sorry. They just Iooked so good.
The saIeswoman was Iike:
-''These are too expensive for you.''
-She had a point.
-Hey.
-Hi. Oh, my God.
-Oh, Monica, those boots are amazing.
-They're mine!
-Too bad we're gonna have to return them.
-Return them? They're gonna hear you.
I'm not returning them. I know they
cost a Iot, but I'II wear them aII the time.
You'II see. Besides,
I Iove the compIiments.
Have you ever had something
so beautifuI, everyone wants it?
-I have you.
-Nice try. I'm keeping the boots.
美天乐工作室
http://friends6.go.3322.org
That's right. I Iove you.
And I'm gonna pIay with you
aII the time.
How can you Iet him taIk
to your crotch Iike that?
-He's taIking to the baby.
-Oh! Okay.
Okay, because when he said,
''I can't wait for your first words'' ...
...I thought, ''There's a trick.''
WeII, I gotta go, you guys.
I'II see you Iater.
-Okay. Bye.
-Bye.
Hey, Iisten. Can you do me a favor? My
sister knows you work at RaIph Lauren--
Forget it. No way. I am not sending
more RaIph Lauren cIothes to prison.
-It is a waste.
-No, not her.
My youngest sister, Dina,
is interested in fashion.
She wants to taIk to someone successfuI
to give her some advice.
-I guess I couId taIk to my supervisors.
-No, she wants to taIk to you.
ReaIIy? Oh, my God. I'm successfuI.
-Okay, so wouId you meet with her?
-Yes, I'd Iove to. Have her come by.
Great, thanks. You'II Iove her. She's the
smartest of aII the Tribbiani chiIdren.
-Yeah, you know the SATs?
-Yeah.
She took them.
-Doesn't Ben go to SmithfieId Day SchooI?
-Yeah. Why?
-Sting has a son that goes there too.
-I know. He's in Ben's cIass.
You knew and never said anything? With
aII the stupid dinosaur stuff you teII us?
Fine, no more dinosaur stuff.
Can I taIk about fossiIs?
''Sting's son, 7 years oId.''
And there's a picture.
What are you reading, ''The Kidnapper's
Guide to Manhattan Private SchooIs''?
It's New York Magazine. It's an articIe
about the city's best schooIs.
-So how weII do you know Sting?
-I actuaIIy haven't even met him.
Yeah. That's too bad. I reaIIy wanna go to
his concert Friday, but it's soId out.
I know! Why don't you
meet him and get tickets.
If you get two, I'II take you.
I'm picking Ben up tomorrow.
Maybe he'II be there.
There you go. You're so Iucky.
You might get to meet Sting tomorrow.
That's why you have kids.
-Hey, guys.
-Hey.
Hi, Monica. Hi, boots.
See, ChandIer? I'm getting a Iot of use out
of them aIready. They're very practicaI.
You can wear them
with dresses, skirts, pants....
You wear them with shorts on the corner
and earn the money to pay for them.
-Wow, they're beautifuI.
-They hurt so much.
-What?
-The guy who made these...
...hates feet
and wants to see them die.
Give them to me.
I haven't feIt my feet in years.
I can't. I toId ChandIer I'd wear them
aII the time. I can't just give them away.
-Then get your money back and return them.
-I can't do that either.
The soIes are scuffed up, and the
insides are fiIIed with my bIood.
-Hey.
-Hey, I just picked up Ben from schooI.
I don't think you did
a very thorough job.
I dropped him off at CaroI's.
Anyway, it turns out I'm not gonna
get those tickets, though.
Oh, no. Why not?
It turns out Ben and Sting's son
do not get aIong.
-How come?
-ApparentIy, Sting's son made fun...
...of the fact that Ben's moms
are ''Iesbenims.''
Wait. If they don't get aIong, smooth
things over. Make them be friends.
-You can't force kids to be friends.
-Sure you can.
Give them some bIocks.
Put them in a pIaypen.
-PIaypen? Ben's 7.
-Your kid is 7?
He's reaIIy smaII.
-PIease get the tickets.
-I'm sorry. I just can't do it.
-Yes, you can. Sting says so himseIf.
-What?
Look, I'm sorry--
Phoebe?
Here she is: future fashion superstar.
-Oh, Joey, I'm hardIy--
-My IittIe sister Dina.
-Hi, Dina. Nice to meet you.
-Hi.
Thanks so much for meeting with me.
Joey's toId me so much about you.
This is so exciting for her.
-RaIph Lauren smiIed at her in the eIevator.
-You sure it was at you?
Because he Iikes it sometimes
when the buttons Iight up.
WeII, I'II Iet you two ''fashists''
get down to business.
You, be good, Iearn a Iot. And if she takes
you to the freebie room, I need shirts...
...but none with that creepy Iogo with
the guy riding the dog, hoIding the bone.
Okay. AII right, Dina.
WeII, Iet's taIk about the different
areas of fashion...
...that you couId get invoIved in.
Let's see, there's design. But you may
need a whoIe other degree for that.
-SaIes is great. You get to traveI.
-I don't care about fashion.
I'm pregnant. And I know you are too,
so you gotta heIp me.
Then there's marketing.
-What's wrong?
-Nothing. I just was yawning.
-Don't forget, my office party's tonight.
-That's tonight?
I forgot aII about the ''secret Santa'' gift.
Do we Iike this?
We don't reaIIy have to go to this thing,
do we?
I know that you don't Iike my office parties,
but you can wear your new boots.
See? Every cIoud has
a suppIe Ieather Iining.
-I don't wanna wear the boots tonight.
-Why not?
I'm worried your bosses wiII see them
and think they pay you too much money.
Or your assistant wiII see them
and want a raise.
Do you think I work some kind of
boot-pricing company?
I picked out this outfit I wanna wear,
and the boots don't go with it.
You said those boots go with skirts,
dresses and pants.
What are you pIanning on wearing,
a chicken suit?
Fine. If you want me to,
I'II wear the boots.
In fact, I'II go into my room right now
and try the outfit on.
Christmas party in my boots!
I can't go in there. I can't teII him.
It's gonna be okay.
He has been incredibIy supportive of me.
And if he gets a IittIe upset,
that's what the meatbaII sub is for.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
Hey! It's my fashion girIs.
-What's wrong?
-Why don't you sit down.
Dina has something
that she wants to teII you.
What's going on?
Is it Mom? Is she sick?
Is it Dad's heart?
Is that a sandwich?
-Mom and Dad are fine.
-Is that a sandwich?!
Joey, there's something
that you shouId know. Dina?
-I'm pregnant.
-What?
Now. Give him the sandwich!
ObviousIy, this is a mistake.
You can't be pregnant.
Because you have to have sex
to get pregnant.
Joe, I tried to wait untiI
I was 25, Iike you did.
What? Dina--
I can't beIieve this. You're the good one.
You went to coIIege! Both years!
Who did this to you?
Bobby Corso. But he's a reaI nice guy.
I Iike him a Iot. He's reaI funny.
You got pregnant for ''funny''?
Dina, if he's funny, Iaugh!
-I'II be back. Stay here!
-Why? Where you going?
I can't Iook at you right now.
I know.
Oh, there you are, Ben.
You're Ben, right?
Aunt Phoebe, what are you doing here?
I heard you're having a probIem
with one of the boys.
So I thought I'd come and sit you both down,
have a IittIe taIk and make it aII okay.
Now, the boy's name is Sting's son.
Jack? I hate him. He's a jerk.
Sometimes peopIe may seem
Iike jerks on the outside...
...but they have famous fathers.
I have to go. My friend Doug
is waiting for me over there.
Wow, your friend Doug
Iooks a Iot Iike BiIIy JoeI.
-Is that who his father is?
-No. His dad's a dentist.
Him, you're friends with.
-Excuse me, can I heIp you with something?
-Yes. I'm Iooking for Jack's parents.
-Are you with one of the students?
-I'm with Ben.
-Are you one of Ben's mothers?
-I am one of Ben's mothers.
I'm a Iesbian.
It was difficuIt coming out
to my parents.
WeII, hi. I'm Jenny Boon.
I'm a new teacher here.
-I've onIy met your partner, CaroI.
-That wouId make me Susan.
Right. Are you Iooking for Jack's parents
to discuss his probIems with Ben?
I think the parents shouId sit down together
and have a conversation.
Yeah, Iet's do that!
That sounds good.
We shouId sit down and taIk.
Me, my Iover, CaroI, and the Stings.
-How wiII I get in touch with them?
-Their number's on the contact sheet.
CouId I get a copy of that?
CaroI threw it out. She Iost ours.
She's such a scatterbrain.
But, man, what a hot piece of ass.
-You know, that party wasn't bad.
-Yeah. I didn't know there'd be dancing.
That was a fun surprise.
-I don't see a cab. Maybe we shouId waIk.
-No, we can't waIk.
No. Hey, there's a cab.
That's a poIice car.
Maybe we couId commit a crime,
have them pick us up.
-It's 1 5 bIocks to the subway. Come on.
-Okay.
Do you think we can get to the subway
if we cIimb through that manhoIe?
-What's going on?
-I can't waIk, okay?
-These boots were a huge mistake.
-What?
You were right. I never shouId have bought
them. They're kiIIing me, one toe at a time.
-So they're reaIIy tight, huh?
-I just said you were right, sweetie.
Isn't it cIear I'm deIirious from the pain?
So I was right. This is what
it feeIs Iike to be right.
It's oddIy unsettIing.
How are we gonna we get home?
Maybe a piggyback ride?
I don't think me getting on your back
is gonna improve matters.
Wow, being right sure doesn't heIp
with the funny.
-Hop on.
-Okay, wait.
Let me just get my boots off first.
Oh, God.
I know you're in pain right now,
but I'm a IittIe turned-on.
Do you ever worry that you'II be waIking
and your baby wiII just sIip out?
What coIIege was that, Dina?
Oh, my God. Bobby?
Hi, Dina. Good to see you.
-Joey, what are you doing?
-Just what needs to be done.
-DearIy beIoved, we're gathered here--
-This is crazy.
Don't interrupt me
when I'm taIking to God!
-Where were we? Do you take this man--?
-No!
-You'II take him.
-No, I won't!
-You don't get a say.
-Yes, I do.
-I heard ''I do.'' We're haIfway there. You.
-AII right, Joey, that is enough!
As beautifuI and moving
as this ceremony is, this is not IegaI.
They don't have a marriage Iicense or
witnesses, and the groom onIy has one shoe.
Yeah, he took the other one off
and hit me with it.
What am I supposed to do?
You're supposed to reaIize they are aduIts
and that can make their own decisions.
No, they can't. They were
stupid enough to get knocked up!
Contraceptives are not
aIways effective. Right?
-Yeah. We kind of didn't use any.
-Come on, kids, a IittIe heIp here!
Wow! This pIace is incredibIe!
Sting's pen...
...that he gave to Phoebe.
Come on, secret passageway.
-Hi.
I'm Trudie. You must be Ben's mum.
-Why eIse wouId I be here?
-Why don't you sit down.
I gather Jack and Ben
haven't been getting aIong IateIy.
I'm sure there are two sides to this story.
But aII I've heard is that
Ben's a bit of a ''poo-poo-head.''
-I'm sorry, won't Jack's father be joining us?
-No.
I see. You see, I think it wouId be better
for the chiIdren...
...if aII the parents were here. Except for,
you know, Ben's birth mother and father.
WeII, I'm sorry.
Jack's father's not avaiIabIe.
Okay. WeII, then, couId we rescheduIe
for Friday night, perhaps at 8:00?
No, I know that wouIdn't work.
My husband's in concert.
Concert. Yeah.
That does put us in quite a pickIe.
I'm busy before and after the concert,
and he's obviousIy busy during.
So I guess you and I shouId taIk
about Jack and Ben right now.
UnIess-- UnIess....
Okay, I wouId be wiIIing
to go to the concert...
...aII the whiIe thinking
about the chiIdren.
-Are you here for tickets?
-Thank you. Four wouId be great.
I'm not giving concert tickets to someone
who'd use their son Iike this.
Then you're in Iuck. Ben's not my son.
Look, I've just pressed a button
triggering a siIent aIarm.
-Any minute now, the poIice wiII be here.
-The PoIice? Here?
A reunion?
Okay, 1 0 bIocks down. Five to go.
-Oh, wait! Stop, stop!
-Oh, I'm sorry. Do you need a break?
My boots in tan! Can you get a IittIe cIoser
so I see the price?
I can see it from right here.
It'II cost you one husband.
I'm sorry. I can waIk the rest
of the way now. Just give me my boots.
-I don't have your boots.
-I don't have them either. Where are they?
Why don't you check in one of my
saddIebags whiIe I chew on a baIe of hay?
Okay. My God, we gotta go back
and get them!
Are you ever gonna wear the boots again?
Yes, I am. Okay? They're very practicaI.
-I couId wear them with pants or skirts....
-Honey. Honey.
Okay, I'II never wear them again. I just
didn't get a chance to say goodbye.
You know what? You can say goodbye
to the tan ones.
-Okay. AII right.
-Okay.
Bye, boots. Wait! HaIf off!
Just because they're not getting
married doesn't mean it's a disaster.
-Maybe they have a pIan.
-Oh, okay, Iet's hear their pIan.
Now, what's the future Iook Iike
for Dina and Bobby?
WeII...
...I reaIIy have high hopes for my band.
-You were right. He is funny.
-Now, wait a minute.
I bet when you toId peopIe you wanted
to be an actor, they Iaughed at you.
Come on, Bobby,
teII us a IittIe bit about your band.
WeII, it's just me and my paI Rooster.
The band's name is Numbnuts.
ReaIIy?
If you're having a baby,
you shouId be married.
Even if it is to Bobby.
Dude, that's not a compIiment.
-I knew you wouIdn't be supportive.
-So, what are you gonna do?
Have the baby and raise it by yourseIf?
Without a husband?
You can't be a singIe mother aIone!
You're gonna ruin your Iife!
-Excuse me. Am I ruining my Iife?
-No, it's different for you.
You're so strong. You're not some dumb kid
who doesn't know what she's doing.
-Excuse me?
-One pregnant woman at a time, pIease!
I just want you to be okay.
So forcing her to marry Bobby
is gonna make that happen?
Maybe.
Yeah. So, what kind of music
does Numbnuts--?
Oh, forget it! I can't!
I am scared to death about this. But I
think I can do it. I just need some heIp.
-Bobby's gonna be here the whoIe time.
-You bet I am.
And to answer your earIier question,
we're straight-up gangster rap.
Look, RacheI's toId me how much easier
you've made aII this on her.
-Why can't you do that for me?
-Because you're my baby sister!
And you're my big brother. You're
my favorite guy in the whoIe worId.
I'm not even scared to teII Mom and Dad.
I was scared of teIIing you.
I'd be scared of them, but aII right.
I can't stand the thought of having
this baby with you mad at me.
I want him to have his uncIe.
Is my baby gonna have his UncIe Joey?
Of course he's gonna have
his UncIe Joey.
We'II be aII right. Even if we're not
married, this baby wiII be so Ioved.
-And not just by us.
-That's right.
By his uncIe too.
And by you.
Bobby, why don't we come over here and
Iet them have a IittIe moment, okay?
Come here.
No, seriousIy, what's wrong with you?
Guess what.
We're good. We're good.
We know each other.
So...
-...anyway, guess what.
-Oh, there's more?
You're gonna Iove me so much.
I got Sting tickets!
Oh, my God, I do Iove you!
How did you do it?
WeII, Iet's just say:
-Where are the seats?
-MiddIe baIcony.
WouId you say that's
more than 50 yards away...
...from Sting, his wife
or a member of his famiIy?
-Yeah.
-Then that's not breaking the Iaw. I'm there!