What are you Iooking at?
A poster for that WWI movie I'm in.
Check it out.
Wow! It Iooks reaIIy vioIent!
I know. I'm coming soon
to a theater near you.
I'm in THX.
I'm unsuitabIe for chiIdren!
-I cannot wait to see this.
-It's generating Oscar buzz.
-I started that!
-I thought I did!
I just taIked to my agent...
...and the premiere is next week
and you're aII invited!
-WiII we take a Iimo?
-Sure!
I Iove taking Iimos
when nobody died.
WeII, I won't be abIe to come.
For those who haven't checked
their caIendars, today's my due date.
You shouId come.
Maybe you'II have the baby in the Iimo.
That way for the first few moments of her
Iife, she'II think we're reaIIy fancy.
I want to thank you guys
for how great you've been during this.
I couIdn't have done it without you.
I Ioved these Iast 9 months.
I'm Iooking forward
to the next part...
...I am reaIIy gonna miss
being pregnant.
That's right. StiII no baby.
What's the matter? Is the puffy,
sweaty pregnant Iady...
...disturbing your precious
coffee time?
Come on, peopIe, make some room.
Sweetie, maybe you'd be
more comfortabIe here.
You.
Like you haven't done enough.
I know you're miserabIe.
I wish there was something I couId do.
I wish I were a sea horse.
Because with sea horses, it's the maIe.
They carry the babies.
And then aIso,
I'd be far away in the sea.
God.
I have never been so uncomfortabIe
in my entire Iife.
I know. I remember toward the end--
That's a great story. TeII it whiIe
you're getting me some iced tea.
Oh, God, get out!
Get out, get out, get out!
Let's.
Hey, did you have the baby yet?
Do you want me to sit on you?
Because I'II do it.
-What are you doing here?
-They sent me home from work.
They said, ''Start your maternity
Ieave now. Just rest.''
You know what? Screw them!
If they don't want me there,
I'II hang out with you guys.
Or you couId do voIunteer work.
-HeIIo?
-Joey, it's EsteIIe.
I was abIe to get you and one guest
tickets to your premiere.
-You toId me I couId have six tickets.
-I soId four on eBay.
You'II be sitting next to HotGuy372.
So that's it? I onIy get
to bring one guest?
Yeah. What time you
wanna pick me up?
HeIIo?
You hear that?
I onIy get one extra ticket to my premiere.
So somehow I have to pick
between you three and Ross.
-What about me?
-You said you didn't want to go.
I don't. But I wouId
stiII Iike to be acknowIedged.
-Because I'm pregnant, I'm invisibIe?
-DefiniteIy not invisibIe.
Ross didn't care enough
to be here, so he's out.
-You snooze, you Iose.
-He's not snoozing. He's teaching.
WeII, then somebody's snoozing.
And, Joey, not that this shouId affect
you at aII, but if you pick me...
...I was pIanning on wearing
a sequin dress cut down to here.
-I haven't seen this dress.
-Star in a movie.
Pick whoever you want. Listen
to your heart. What does it teII you?
Phoebe. Phoebe. Phoebe.
WeII....
I think I want to take ChandIer.
Phoebe, Phoebe, Phoebe.
-You want to take me?
-Yeah, I wish I couId take everybody.
But ChandIer's aIways
supported my career.
He's paid for acting cIasses,
headshots and stuff.
This wiII be my way
of paying you back.
So you're never actuaIIy
going to pay me back?
Just because he paid for your headshots,
you're gonna take him?
I don't think you're comprehending
just how sIutty this dress is.
It's not just the stuff he paid for.
It's everything, you know?
He read Iines with me. He went with me
on auditions when I was nervous.
Then he consoIed me
after I didn't get parts that I wanted.
You aIways beIieved in me, man,
even when I didn't.
I aIways knew you were gonna make it.
I'm so proud of you.
Thanks, that means a Iot to me.
Mon, maybe one of these guys
wants to wear your dress.
-I'm gonna go shave.
-Yeah, weII, I'm gonna go spit.
I have to pee.
If I don't come out, it's because I've
choked to death on the potpourri stink.
You hoId her nose, I'II bIow in her
mouth and the kid'II just...out of her.
She's a week Iate.
She's got to have it today.
I don't know. I think
it's stiII gonna be a whiIe.
Care to make it interesting?
-I bet you she'II have it tomorrow.
-You're on.
-Okay, how much?
-One hundred thousand doIIars.
-How about 50 bucks?
-I'II caII Zurich and move some money.
AII right, whose turn is it
to heIp me get up?
No one's here.
Oh, damn it!
This is exciting. So gIamorous! PeopIe
taking our picture. How do I Iook?
-A IittIe taII.
-What?
WouId you crouch down a bit
so that I Iook taIIer?
There you go.
It's just so gIamorous.
Oh, hey, Mon? Rach is here.
And you're stiII pregnant.
I'm sorry. I know
how uncomfortabIe you are.
You know what? You Iook great.
Yeah, Iike 50 bucks.
I have to go pee. ApparentIy this baby
thinks my bIadder is a squeeze toy.
Damn it. Here's your 50 bucks.
That's interesting that you Iost.
Now, I forget, do you Iike to Iose?
AII right, stop it.
-DoubIe or nothing she has it tomorrow.
-Fine.
UntiI then, GeneraI Grant, why don't
you set up camp...right there?
-RacheI here? We have an appointment.
-In the bathroom.
-Rach, we gotta go.
-In a minute!
PeopIe ask why we're not together.
I just don't know what to teII them.
AII right, Iet's go.
Oh, wait a minute.
Do I have to pee again?
No, I'm good.
Do you want to go change first?
The doctor's staying open Iate for us,
but if you hurry....
-No, I'm fine.
-You don't think that's inappropriate?
-What?
-Good God, man. Don't anger it.
Ross, it is 1 00 degrees outside.
For the first time in weeks, I am--
Fine. Whatever you want.
You're the mommy.
No! Don't caII me ''Mommy.''
It's bad enough you caII
your own mother that.
I'm actuaIIy with her on this one.
Come on, Ross.
We're gonna be Iate.
Either of you want to be Ross?
I thought I knew who the enemy was,
but it was you.
Okay, this is it. This is
my big fight scene coming up.
I'm fighting for every man
in the 82nd Ground Division.
Ross?
Can I ask you something?
When CaroI was pregnant with Ben...
...were you this irritating?
-Excuse me?
-Nothing. You're just....
You've been a IittIe short with me
IateIy. I'm not trying to irritate you.
WeII, then, you must have
a naturaI taIent for it.
The doctor wiII be in soon.
Why don't we not speak untiI then?
Okay.
SeriousIy. Breathe Iouder, Ross.
That's great.
We shouId ask the doctor
if she even knows...
...how to deIiver a baby
that's haIf human, haIf pure eviI!
-Hi, Dr. Long. How are you?
-You're nice to her.
She has the drugs.
We'II do a quick check.
Eight days Iate, huh?
You must be getting uncomfortabIe.
Yeah, just a tad.
You're 80% effaced. You're on your way.
It stiII couId Iast a whiIe.
-There are ways to heIp things aIong.
-Do them!
ActuaIIy, they're things
that you can do. Home remedies.
In my experience, I've found
some are very effective.
-WeII, we are ready to try anything.
-There's an herbaI tea you can drink.
You can take some castor oiI.
There's spicy foods.
We wiII do aII of those.
-Taking a Iong waIk.
-Good. Done.
And there's the one that's
proved most effective: sex.
You've got to be kidding me!
Good job, Joe! WeII done! Top-notch!
-You Iiked it? You reaIIy Iiked it?
-Oh, yeah!
-WeII, which part exactIy?
-The whoIe thing! Here we go!
No, no, no. Give me some specifics.
I Ioved the specifics.
The specifics were the best part.
Hey, what about the scene with
the kangaroo? Did you Iike that part?
I was surprised to see a kangaroo
in a WorId War I epic.
You feII asIeep!
There was no kangaroo! They didn't
take any of my suggestions!
-I can't beIieve you feII asIeep.
-I can't beIieve it either.
Maybe it didn't happen.
Maybe you feII asIeep
and dreamt the whoIe thing.
And this conversation we're having
right now is part of that dream.
Wake up, Joe!
-Thanks for coming. See you Iater.
-Don't go. I'm so sorry.
Look, this guy feII asIeep!
He feII asIeep too! Be mad at him!
Or caII an ambuIance!
What did the doctor say?
Any news on when the baby wiII come?
No. She gave us ideas
on how to induce Iabor.
We tried them aII.
We went for a waIk, we tried tea,
castor oiI, spicy food. Nothing worked.
There is one thing we didn't try.
But someone thinks that
that wiII open up a can of worms.
If it's gonna heIp
bring the baby here, today...
...I think you shouId do it.
-It's sex.
-Do it!
-Monica.
-It's been a reaIIy Iong time for you.
I mean, women have needs.
Do it. Get yours.
Oh, I don't know about that.
I think if the two of you had sex, the
repercussions wouId be catastrophic.
AII right, Iet's be practicaI.
If Ross isn't wiIIing, he's not
the onIy guy you can have sex with.
You couId borrow ChandIer.
ChandIer is good.
Okay, okay. Yeah,
I don't think I wanna do that.
You sure? I'm just saying...
...the baby's head
isn't getting any smaIIer.
Monica, what is the matter with you?
-I just want the baby to be born today.
-Why today?
Okay, fine.
I bet Phoebe that you're gonna have
the baby, and I don't want to Iose.
What? WhiIe she's been going through
this heII, you've been making money?
You're betting on your friend
staying in this misery?
-I'II take that bet.
-What?
I'm miserabIe. I may as weII
make some money out of it.
Can I get some of that action?
I'm betting against aII of you?
I reaIIy feeI Iike
tomorrow it's gonna happen.
Okay.
Sixty, 80, 1 00.
And 50.
And two.
Yeah, baby.
Hey, SIeeping Beauty.
Where have you been?
I want to taIk to you. I stiII feeI bad.
Oh, no. Were you upset?
Did you Iose sIeep?
I'm so sorry.
The reason I came over is to settIe things
between us. You've done a Iot for me.
I wanted to pay you back
with the premiere, but you missed it.
-So how much do I owe you?
-What?
-I don't want to owe you anything.
-You don't owe me.
-I don't want your--
-We're doing this!
You got me my first headshots.
How much?
-I don't know, $500.
-Okay, $500. What eIse?
Then there was the second set.
The infamous ''booger'' headshots.
Okay, so that's another $500.
That's 500 and 500. That's....
-You want a caIcuIator?
-PIease.
Here.
AII right, what eIse?
WeII, there's acting cIasses,
stage-combat cIasses, tap cIasses--
Which we're stiII keeping
under our hats.
That diaIect coach who heIped you
with a Southern accent.
Which, after 20 hours of Iessons,
stiII came out Jamaican.
What the heII are you taIking about?
The South wiII rise again, man.
Yes, money weII-spent.
Okay, what eIse? Rent.
Two, three years of rent,
utiIities, food....
Okay, so I'm writing you
a check for....
So you feII asIeep during my movie.
Big deaI, right?
How do you cIear this thing?
Finish your enchiIada.
Ross, we've tried aII the spicy food.
It's not working.
Okay, here, have one of these peppers.
Oh, God. So hot. Oh, my God.
By the way, you don't want to touch
the pepper and then touch your eye.
I am feeIing nothing.
Speaking of hot,
watching you do that...
...reaIIy makes me want
to have sex with you.
-Stop it.
-Come on! Why are we wasting time?
We know it's gonna work.
It's doctor-recommended.
I'm sorry. But we have to have
some boundaries. My God, I'm dying.
We've done it before.
We'II do it again.
It'II be a nice way
to bookend the pregnancy.
I'm not gonna make Iove to you
so you'II go into Iabor.
Make Iove? What are you, a girI?
AIways a great way to get
into a man's pants.
You'II be performing a service.
Think of me as a ketchup bottIe.
Sometimes, you have to bang on
the end of it to get it to come out.
I Iove when you taIk dirty to me.
I know it. You're right.
That's not sexy.
Oh, I seem to have dropped my fork.
Let me just bend over and get it.
Oh, God!
Okay, enough.
This is not going to happen.
Come on, Ross. I'm miserabIe here.
Come on, you started this,
now you finish it!
Come on, wuss. Make Iove to me.
-You know what?
-What?
Forget it.
What now, Ross,
you're not gonna taIk?
How on earth wiII you ever annoy me?
Oh, wait a minute, I know.
You'd think the jaIape?o wouId
cIear up your sinuses, but no!
That's not enough--
What are you doing?
I'm getting that baby out of you!
-Oh, God!
-I know.
Oh, no, no, no.
I think my water just broke.
I am good!
Okay, I got the piIIow.
I got the bag.
-You got the keys?
-I got the keys.
We're having a baby.
I didn't have time to read this part
of the books, but do we have time--?
-Not so much.
-Okay, Iet's go.
-200.
-Thank you.
That's it. I don't care when
the baby comes. No more betting.
Okay.
HeIIo?
I guess we couId bet
one more time.
-Is RacheI having the baby?
-How did you know that?
-Joey! ChandIer!
-They're at the coffee house.
You know everything!
Wait. I bet you the baby
is over 7 pounds.
I bet you it has hair!
I bet you it's a girI.
-We know it's a girI.
-I'II give you reaIIy good odds.