Tower, this is Masters,
we have no eyeshot.
-How is it going on the airport?
-I'm sorry,Major.
We've lit even
the back generators.
-You'll have to lmmerse.
-Immerse?
I can't see an inch from my face.
You stlll have
the equlpments, rlght?
Correct.
I'm 25 miIes west.
l suggest you to drop 7 thousand
feet, try and get an eyeshot.
Right away.
Let 's go, we can do it.
shit!
Tower, I was hit by a thunder.
Masters, what's golng on?
I've just Iost aII my equipments.
I'm Iosing stabiIity,
the inner pression is faIIing.
-Can you try to go back on track?
-Nothing is working!
Tower, I have probIems.
The equipments seem...
they're not gonna make it
tiII we Iand.
Tower, do you hear me?
I repeat. Tower, do you hear me?
Mayday, this is Masters,
at TDs-17.
I'm coming for a crash Ianding.
Come on.
Out of my way!
Keep working on the gauges, aII
right? I'II be right back. Thanks.
You get two months Ieave, Major,
and this is what you do with it?
-sir?
-Let 's take a waIk.
I've got an assignment for you.
Are you famiIiar
with Henderson Davis?
The third richest man
in the Northern hemisphere?
He's aIso one of the country's
Iargest miIitary contractors.
-so?
-His daughter RocheIIe...
just graduated from coIIege...
and he's throwing her
a IittIe birthday party.
Pardon me, sir...
but how does that reIate
to me going back up in the air?
WeII, you see, this party
begins about 3O,OOO feet up.
Permission to speak freeIy, sir?
Granted.
sir, you know I'm committed
to the miIitary.
But I need a reaI mission...
not some babysitting assignment.
Major, you are one good piIot.
UntiI the inquiry board cIears you,
this is the best you'II get.
Come on, Min, sIow down.
We've got pIenty of time.
You know me,
I aIways Iike to be on time.
Besides, it 's an important gig.
Come on, it 's a party for a
spoiIed IittIe rich girI.
Yeah, whose Daddy just
happens to own the airIines.
I know, I know. But I'm not gonna
kiss up on this trip.
And wiII you pIease sIow down?
You're starting to scare me.
Oh, shit.
What?
There's something wrong
with the brakes!
-Oh my God, weII pump them!
-I am, I am!
-Min, oh my God, puII over!
-I can't, I can't!
Oh my God!
HeIIo.
No, I can't. I'm heading to
the airport right now.
No, it 's gonna be great.
Two weeks. Yeah.
Hey, Iisten, I'II caII you when I get
back and we'II go out. I promise.
Bye.
HeIIo?
Oh hi, Rick.
You're kidding me.
Today?
What time?
Yeah, I can make it.
Which airport?
Oh, thank God. I'II caII you
when I get back. Bye.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't see you there.
Most peopIe rareIy do.
Hey, is everybody ready?
Is everybody here?
AII right, Iet 's go. Come on.
WeII, this must be our man now.
You must be GeneraI McCIoren's man.
That wouId be me.
John Masters.
-Henderson Davis. Jimmy Watkins.
-PIeasure.
I assume you've been briefed
as to why you're here.
Routine security aboard your pIane.
shouId be an easy
job for a man of your abiIities.
Let me teII you: I didn't get where
I am without making enemies.
It 's an honor
and a priviIege to do it, sir.
If it 's Iike you said, then
I'm just a champagne chaperone...
aIong for the ride.
Yeah, weII,
don't you drink too much.
someone's got to be sober
in case these kids turn...
that pIane into an animaI house.
Don't worry, I brought my toga.
Funny. Very funny.
Just sit back, be invisibIe.
When you get to AustraIia...
escort everyone to the Barrier reef.
-You shouId enjoy this vacation.
-sounds great.
I'm with the caterers.
I'm Iooking for the Davis party.
-You found it.
-Where do you want us to set up?
straight through there
in the first-cIass cabin.
Gotcha. We'II go in through the
deIivery access on the tarmac.
Daddy!
Hey, here's my baby now.
Come on, I'II introduce you.
RocheIIe, sweetheart.
Thank you, thank you so much.
This is the best present ever.
Remember, you've worked hard for
this so it 's your time to enjoy it.
-Jerry? Roger!
-sr. D.
-GirIs?
-Hi sr. D.
Good evening.
Ladies.
Huh. I don't remember seeing
those guys on board before.
Oh, Davis must have hired
some new caterers.
-What 's the word on the storm?
-Nothing that wiII affect us.
Latest charts say it 's 6OO
miIes due south of Hawaii.
LittIe bit of rain,
but nothing to worry.
sounds good to me.
I got to say, Mr. Davis,
this is pretty cooI.
Yeah, scuba diving in the Great Barrier
Reef. Never though I'd get to do that.
Yeah, weII guys, just don't Iet my
daughter swim in the deep water?
Oh Dad, you know I'm certified.
Don't worry so much.
Yeah, weII don't put yourseIf in
any unnecessary situations.
Hey, don't sweat it, Mr. D.
I wiII keep my eye on everybody.
Oh, good, and who's gonna keep
an eye on you? Jerry?
No, that 's not your job, Roger.
That 's why I'm sending
Mr. Masters aIong for the ride.
Dad, pIease. I'm 22.
-I don't need a babysitter anymore.
-Come on, Roche, forget about it.
It 's just one other person to
party with us, and besides...
I think he's kind of cute.
You said that about
the Iimo driver too, MeIanie.
And?
Come on, Iet 's get on that pIane
before you invite...
the entire grounds crew, too.
-I was just commenting, is aII.
-Bye, Dad. I Iove you.
-Okay, caII me when you Iand.
-AbsoIuteIy.
-Have a good time.
-Bye, and thanks again.
Don't mention it.
Here.
I don't need your heIp.
Bye! Major, I won't forget this.
I probabIy won't, either.
sir.
Hey, here they come.
HeIIo. WeIcome.
WeIcome aboard.
Way to go, Roche?
Gonna miss the pIane.
AII right,
that shouId do it.
You ready?
-Oh. Here you go.
-I said I got it.
-Hey, I'm just trying to heIp.
-I don't need your heIp.
Listen, I just got this gig
5 minutes ago, okay?
Yeah, but you, or someone
Iike you has had this gig...
for the Iast 22 years of my Iife.
Do you know what 's it 's Iike never to
have a private moment, Mr. Masters?
-I can't say I do.
-ExactIy.
You want to heIp me?
sit in the back, don't interface.
Bye, Daddy! Bye!
Whatever you say.
Ouite a girI you've
raised there, Mr. Davis.
spitting image of her Mom.
sorry to hear that, sir.
-Hey guys!
-There she is.
-Hey, Roche.
-Hey, MeI.
This is the best.
Your Dad is so cooI.
I know.
But where's the champagne?
Davis 2 to tower. Can I get a
cIearance on runway 3?
WouId you Iike some wine?
-sorry.
-It 's okay.
Why don't you take a picture?
They Iast Ionger.
-What did I do?
-Come on, Jer. You're being obvious.
so? A guy can Iook.
Looking is one thing.
DrooIing is something eIse.
-so what 's your point?
-It 's Iike I keep teIIing you.
Got to be a IittIe smoother
than that. Okay?
so, your Dad bought out
the entire hoteI, right?
Every room.
The pIace is totaIIy ours for a week.
This is so cooI. You know,
this may go down in history.
As, Iike,
the greatest birthday ever.
Yeah it is. I can't wait.
so Iet 's hope those native
instructor boys are cut.
Can I perhaps offer you Iadies another
gIass of champagne before departure?
-CertainIy.
-I'd Iove some.
Me too.
Enjoy.
And happy birthday, Miss Davis.
Thanks.
Ladies and gentIemen,
this is Captain Craig.
My Co-Pllot today
ls Sam Newberry.
We'd llke to welcome you aboard...
our non-stop fllght to
the Land Down Under.
Our flylng tlme thls evenlng
ls approxlmately 13 hours.
We have just one fllght ahead
of us on the runway,so...
please fasten your seatbelts,
we'll be underway shortly.
After we're airborne,
I've turned off the seatbeIt Iight...
feeI free to party.
AustraIia, baby! Whoo!
Fllght attendants,please
prepare fortakeoff.
-Ready for this?
-Yes.
Whew, man! It is wet out there!
-stiII raining out there, huh Mac?
-Oh, it 's coming down, sir.
The big stuff,
stiII 5 or 6 hours out.
Yeah, so much for the
storm staying south.
-What 's E.O. got to say?
-Northeast at 5O knots.
Category 2,
but stiII fiIIed with strength.
AII right break out the tarps,
gentIemen.
We got ourseIves a rain deIay.
You know, that may be so,
Lieutenant, but may I remind you...
that both I and the Us Army want
that runway finished in 5 days.
By sunday, sir, it 'II be finished.
5 days. It 's five 12-hour shifts.
4 days is 4 sixteen-hour shifts.
3 days is 3 twenty-hour shifts.
-You see where I'm going?
-I'm foIIowing you.
AII I see is that it 's wet outside.
so I'II see you Iater.
Everyone's a comedian.
Thls ls yourCaptaln.
I've turned off the seat belt slgn ...
so feel free to move
about the cabln.
I missed you back there!
Hlckham to Davls 2,
Hlckham to Davls 2,please come ln.
Hickham, this is Davis 2, come back.
Got a new update on the typhoon.
lt's changed course and comlng
Northward at 60 knots.
Suggest you lncrease your altitude
another 5,OOO feet...
to avold turbulence.
Roger, Hickham, I'm going to 38,OOO.
How's the weather at your end?
Torrentlal raln ln Honolulu.
And the other lslands.
Not the garden spot you
want to be tonlght.
Roger that, Hickham. stay dry.
Davis 2 out.
Miss?
-Wine?
-No, thanks.
-Try it.
-No, I'd Iike to have some cIub soda.
Come on, is that aII you got?
Wimpy throw, man.
Oh, you want it good?
Now how's a man supposed
to have a good time on cIub soda?
I'm not being paid
to have a good time.
sorry...
sorry about that...
Excuse me. More champagne, Miss?
Mind if I sit out
the turbuIence for awhiIe?
As a matter of fact, I do.
Jennifer, what are you doing?
Making new friends.
Come on, get back to your seat.
You're drunk.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Where is my seat again, anyway?
Right over there. Now go use it!
It 's gonna be a Iong fIight.
Nice fashion choice, Cobb.
I can't beIieve you've got a grizzIy
bear on your necktie.
I'm a cop, Guss, not a maIe modeI.
Hey, speaking of GrizzIies,
you shouId have seen a guy...
FaIIs off his baIcony and impaIes
himseIf on his own wrought iron fence.
Right up his poop shoot.
Does that give
you some strange fetish?
WeII, I had to cut his whoIe
Iarge intestine open.
BIood everywhere. Feces everywhere.
Looked Iike your underpants.
-I've been wearing a thong IateIy.
-Oh. WeII, don't turn me on.
so exactIy where
did we find these 2?
Down at the bottom of MuIhoIIand.
It 's a damn shame.
Looks Iike their car shot through
the guardraiI and went straight down.
skidmarks?
Uh, on the road?
About 1OO feet, intermittentIy.
We sent the rubber sampIes to the Iab.
How fast?
WeII, they weren't
observing the speed Iimit.
WeII, sometimes girIs
get bad breaks.
Come on, that 's funny.
It 's a doubIe entendre 'cause
she couIdn't stop the car.
Yeah, hiIarious.
Just a reaI tragedy, you know?
I've got a daughter just about
the same age as these 2.
Yeah, weII, nobody Iikes to see this.
-WeII, that 's interesting.
-What?
Looks Iike a bad day
for fIight attendants.
-What do you mean?
-WeII, it 's not just this one.
I got 2 more this afternoon in.
-Two more fIight attendants?
-One fried herseIf in a bathtub...
and the other feII off a train.
The 2 of them Iooked Iike accidents...
but we aImost opened investigations
into both of them.
WeII, that 's the first interesting
thing you've said aII day.
-sr. Gussman?
-sir?
What do you say we start that
investigation right now?
sure thing.
HeIIo? Anybody in there? Come on!
What now? Looking for peanuts,
I suppose.
No, just checking for the crew.
They seem to have disappeared.
Your charming personaIity,
no doubt.
-They probabIy jumped.
-You know, if I had a chute...
-I'd probabIy join them.
-I'II see if I can find you one.
Damn!
snap it up in there, wiII you?
You know, there is one in the rear.
UnIess you consider that sIumming.
You know...
with very IittIe heIp,
I can Iearn to despise you.
Is that so?
Remember, the rest of the
passengers are expendabIe, but...
no matter what, the girI stays
safe and unharmed.
It 's much harder to ransom a corpse.
-What about the chaperone?
-One of Davis's muscIe heads...
Don't sweat it,
I'II take care of him.
-Everyone ready?
-Yeah.
AII right, then.
Let 's go take ourseIves an airpIane.
-What?
-Nothing. Just checking for the crew.
ReaIIy? I thought perhaps
you might wanna...
step inside
and pouder my nose for me.
I suppose somebody on Daddy's
payroII has been doing that...
since you were born.
But thankfuIIy,
it 's not in my job description.
Go ahead, knock yourseIf out.
AIright chiIdren. sit stiII, shut up,
and nobody wiII get hurt.
Your host, where is she?
-I don't know.
-I said, where is she!?
You can't do that!
The heII I can't, boy.
You aII speak onIy when spoken to.
Understand?
CarI, Joseph, Gustav, she must be
in the rear somewhere...
with that security man.
Come. Ladies, watch them!
Miss Davis,
I suggest you get out now.
What? Are you crazy?
-Miss Davis. Right now.
-But I'm not done yet.
-Yes, you are. Come on. Come on.
-stop that!
Get down.
HoId it!
shut up! Right now! shut up!
son of a bitch, what 's that?
Those kids must have brought
fireworks or something.
If the FAA knew about this,
they'd have both our asses.
Go back there
and teII them to stow it.
-The party's over untiI we Iand.
-Right.
-What 's going on?
-stay caIm. Be quiet.
Hey, what 's going.
Ouiet!
Davis 2 to HonoIuIu, come in!
One more word and it 's your Iast.
You won't puII that trigger.
You need me to piIot the pIane.
Try me.
Davls 2, thls ls Hlckham,over.
Just fIy the pIane.
Davls 2, thls ls Hlckham.
-What are we going to do?
-I want you to stay caIm, okay?
Let 's see if we can find a
dumbwaiter out there. Come on.
Why? What wouId that do?
Get us away from the bad guys,
for starters. Come on, give me a hand.
-Out of ammo?
-CouId be. But I doubt it.
It seems we may have
underestimated Mr. Babysitter.
There's nowhere to run! You know?
Why don't we just put aII our weapons
down and sort this thing out?
What do you say?
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
This shouId hoId them off for
a IittIe bit. Come on, this way.
Come on.
They've escaped to the Iower hoId.
If this guy's the kind
of guy I think he is...
we've got an ambush
waiting beIow.
Go up front and find
another way down.
You got it.
They've escaped to the Iower hoId!
CarI and Joseph just went
down the main eIevator.
Go back and guard the
rear one, just in case.
And Gustav?
Go!
And that, Iadies
and gentIemen...
ends the entertainment
portion of our fIight.
And now if you wouId kindIy
your seat beIts...
we're expecting some
more turbuIence ahead.
Pardon me?
What if you have to go, you know.
HoId it.
so you're saying that the entire
fIight crew they found dead?
AII made to Iook Iike accidents.
These preps were very thorough.
You think my daughter's
in some sort of troubIe?
I think the entire
fIight is in troubIe.
Despite he size of the pIane
this was not a pubIic fIight...
therefore no security precautions.
Pardon me, sir.
We tried contacting Davis 2...
but so far no response.
The towers Iinked up with
PearI and ManiIa, not a peep, sir.
Any change? TrianguIations?
Any change in vector?
The pIane's stiII on course,
sir. No deviation.
WeII, perhaps a monsoon took
out the communication system.
It wouId take something
reaIIy bad to knock out...
voice communication
with today's technoIogy.
That 's what I'm afraid of.
I see your point.
Get GeneraI McCIoren on the ceII.
-sir, it 's after midnight.
-Get him on the ceII.
Right away, sir.
I think you were right, Mac.
This storm ain't bIowing over.
-What, sir?
-Hey, Captain's taIking to you.
Oh, sorry, sir.
What were you saying?
I said, the storm seems
to have intensified.
Oh, you're right about that, sir.
Weather service in PearI said they're
going up Category 5. First in years.
WeII, Captain, Iooks Iike our
airship's gonna be in...
about ten feet of water
come sunday.
That airfieId is stiII going
to be buiIt, Lieutenant.
Oh, yes sir. And I think we're aII
Iooking forward to strapping on...
that scuba gear tomorrow
to get it finished.
You're crazy.
Oh, Captain, something eIse.
What 's that, Mac?
Lot of miIitary chatter
about a private jetIiner...
747 is not responding to
ground communication.
-What 's it 's position?
-Last time I checked?
Due West 1,5OO miIes.
-Is the Air Force on it?
-No, sr.
Everything's grounded at the moment.
I'm going to check on a generator.
-Keep me posted.
-Yes, sr.
Here, come on. stay here.
-I'm caIIing for heIp.
-That 's not gonna work.
-It worked earIier.
-We were over Iand.
We're mid-Pacific. There's not
many reIay dishes ut here.
-Doesn't hurt to try.
-AII right, be my guest.
Come on, you stupid.
Okay, so you're right.
I was just trying to heIp.
Pipe down.
They might be abIe to hear us.
But you wedged the eIevator door.
That 's in the back of the pIane.
There's one more...
in the front of the pIane.
They might be going there.
-What do you think they want?
-My guess is it 's you, sweetheart.
-Me? Why me?
-For one, your Daddy's rich.
Two, he's got access
to a Iot of miIitary information.
And three you're
the onIy daughter he's got.
You stay here.
Where are you going now?
I'm going hunting.
WeII how many buIIets
do you have Ieft?
-I've got six.
-But there's 5 of them.
Never hurts to bring a spare.
HoId it!
Drop it.
I don't know
who the HeII you are...
but I'm definiteIy gonna enjoy this.
-What 's that?
-We're Iosing fueI. I don't know why.
WeII find out fast.
Didn't I teII you to stay put?
-But I.
-Forget it. Don't.
You did good. Now give me
a hand getting these weapons.
You've shot a weapon
before, haven't you?
-Me? Are you kidding?
-That 's what I thought.
-What 's happened?
-A rupture in one of the fueI Iines.
-Can you stop it?
-I don't know.
I've got to shut off the main
source to engines 1 and 3.
Wait, wait. No you're not.
We're Ioosing too much fueI. It 's the
onIy way to conserve what we have.
Just hoId it!
Give me the microphone! Give me.
Carlos, we need
you up front rlght now.
Now you be good IittIe boys
and girIs whiIe I'm gone.
Or I'II be forced to come and bIow
your brains aII over the cabin.
Understand?
Very good.
We have to do something.
We can't just sit here.
-WeII, what can we do?
-I don't know. something.
Yeah, maybe we can hit him over the
head with empty champagne bottIes.
WeII, that 's better than
Ietting them just kiII us.
What makes you think
they're gonna kiII us?
Maybe they're just gonna Iet us go.
Maybe it 's just RocheIIe they want.
What are you trying to say? That we
shouId just hand her over to them?
No...
That 's not what I meant.
That 's what it sounded Iike.
Look, I'm sorry. I don't know.
I'm just reaIIy scared, guys.
Besides, Jen, get a cIue.
They hijacked a pIane.
They can't afford to Ieave
any witnesses behind.
-What the HeII's going on?
-Ruptured fueI Iine.
-He wants to shut down 2 engines.
-No, you can't.
If I don't, we'II never
make it to AustraIia.
We're not going to AustraIia!
We're going to Mindanao.
WeII HeII, we'II never
make it there either!
You shut down 2 engines,
that puts a strain on the other 2.
They'II burn extra fueI
just to keep us airborne.
At the rate we're Iosing fueI, we'II
be Iucky to have another 2 hours.
-I stiII don't Iike it!
-Like it or not, you got no choice.
AII right, then. Just do what you
must do and then shut up!
-she's right. They'II kiII us.
-We don't know that.
We don't know that they won't.
I'm not wiIIing to take that chance.
What do you want to do?
Dig around.
Find something to fight with.
-Hey man, they've got guns.
-Ouit being a wimp!
Can I heIp you find
another drink, sir?
Um, I'm sorry. We...
We were just Iooking for some...
And when you finish doing the
dishes, my dear, dear friend...
you can cIean the toiIets.
Back to your seats!
Now, if you're reaI good boys,
I'II Iet the girIs cut...
hoIes in your gags so you can
eat through a straw.
Anybody eIse want to be a hero?
What are you doing?
Here.
Listen, I need you to
go back up there.
What? Are you crazy?
I'm not going back up there!
They'II kiII me!
No, they want you aIive.
It 's me they want to kiII.
-Not very comforting.
-Look, RocheIIe.
These guys up there,
they're professionaIs.
They're not gonna hesitate one
second to kiII anybody on this pIane.
And you are their Ieverage.
Down here we're running out of time,
and up there, they're running...
out of patience.
You've got to trust me on this one.
-What are you gonna do?
-I'II crawI up the Iavatory Iines...
to the restroom in the
center of the pIane.
I want you to wait here for
5 minutes and then head up.
Whoever is gonna be there is
gonna be keyed on you.
That 's nuts.
What if you're wrong?
I'm not.
Look, you got a better
idea I'd Iove to hear it.
How about we stay down here
and Iook for a coupIe parachutes.
Look...
I know you're scared.
Anybody wouId be.
But we've got
to take the offensive here.
Do I get a gun?
No. You get a watch.
Now, you wait here for 5 minutes
and then head up. AII right?
Okay. 5 minutes.
But I stiII wouId rather have a gun.
You Ieave that to me.
GeneraI, we haven't been
abIe to raise the piIot.
-I'm really gettlng concerned.
-WeII I share your concern, Davis.
PAC-CON has aIready
been aIerted to the situation.
This storm is making it...
extremeIy difficuIt
for us to run reconnaissance.
You're not thinking about taking
that pIane down, are you?
I'm in no position to make
that decision right now.
We're just trying to
re-estabIish contact.
But for allwe know,
mlght be a slmple malfunctlon.
You just sit tlght and I'll get you
lntel as it comes ln.
Yeah. Thank you, GeneraI.
Was that McCIoren again?
Yeah. TaIking about them
being in radio range.
Might have something to do
with the storm.
Did you teII him what happened
to the fIight crew?
Yeah, first thing. But he's pIaying it
cIose to the vest.
He knows my invoIvement,
and it 's too cIose.
I just hope that your guy on
board doesn't get compromised.
They'II be Iooking for us.
You'II never get away with this.
I aIready did, IittIe girI.
Ouiet, pIease.
AII right? Just don't Iook.
Don't Iook.
Just keep thinking, we've got
2 more to go. Just 2 more to go.
AII right?
Now Iisten to me. I want you to
stay here. You'II be safe.
I'm just going forward, okay?
see if I can put this mess to an end.
-Wait a minute.
-Why? What is it?
I...
I'd Iike to say I'm sorry.
Wow. An apoIogy.
Look, I know I was being a
bit harsh before...
but try to see it my way.
Lord knows, I've been trying.
Being a Davis has its advantages...
but it has its disadvantages too.
I thought you were another
one of my Father's...
endIess stream of fIunkies
sent to spy on me.
WeII, to teII you the
truth, I kind of was.
ApoIogy accepted.
Now pIease stay here.
You wiII be safe.
-Right.
-I'II Iet you know when you can Ieave.
-Right. Be carefuI.
-Okay, come on.
-shit!
-What?
No service. I can't raise anybody.
There's no teIIing Lao
secured our Ianding.
I know him. He'II be ready.
And neither CarI nor Joseph
have checked in.
What?
-Where are you going?
-Down beIow. I'II fIush them out.
No! Let them be for now.
They can't go anywhere.
We'II get them when
we're safe on the ground!
Look, if you intend on
pIacing this aircraft.
on any major Iand mass
West of here, you can forget it.
There just simpIy
isn't enough fueI Ieft.
OnIy course of action is to turn
around and try to make Hawaii.
I think we just might make it.
And come down into hordes of waiting
FBI, poIice, and miIitary?
No, my friend, I'm not buying your
IittIe taIe of woe this evening.
I suggest you keep your mouth shut
and stay on course and do as I say.
You keep an eye on him.
I'II go back and check on Erica. Go!
sorry.
-I just had to go.
-sit back down.
Now!
Everyone wiII have a potty
break when I get back!
Are you okay?
I wouId have preferred the fish.
sorry to disappoint you, sir.
That 's okay.
I'II take the dessert.
I suppose it 's fair to assume
my assistant in the rear...
...isn't having dinner tonight.
-I beIieve she Iost he appetite.
My, my. Daddy must be
paying you overtime.
I work on a fIat rate.
Masters! Masters!
This fIight 's over for you, paI.
-Masters.
-RocheIIe, you aII right?
I think so. What happened?
TurbuIence.
Hey!
Whoa, whoa. It 's just me.
-What happened to the other one?
-In the cockpit. she's dead.
The piIot 's been shot. We need heIp.
Go get a coupIe of your friends
and bring him back here.
We need to drag this piece
of shit back to first cIass.
-Find something to tie him up with.
-It wouId be a pIeasure.
-see if you can find a first aid kit.
-Jerry's pre-med.
-I'II teII him to come back.
-It 's not for us.
It 's for the Captain.
AII right, come on Captain. stay with
us. stay with us, you're gonna be ok.
Come on, you're doing great.
I think we found some more
cord in the utiIity gaIIey.
Tom and Jeff are tying
him up right now.
And we'II get
that body out of here, too.
Thanks.
-How you doing, Captain?
-Not good...
-What 's the situation?
-Worse.
We Iost aII auxiIiary fueI, and
there's Iess than 5,OOO pounds Ieft.
-so what can we do?
-We've got to turn around.
We've got to head
back to Hawaii.
Oh my God! What are we gonna do?
Crash?
-Oh Jeez, teII me you can fIy.
-Yeah, I can fIy aII right.
It 's just the Ianding part that
gets me a IittIe bit worried.
What do you mean, the Ianding part?
That 's the most important part!
Oh my God.
-I found the kit.
-Thanks. Try to keep him aIive.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna try and do
the same thing for the rest of us.
Mayday, mayday.
Come in, pIease.
This is Charter fIight Davis 2,
decIaring an emergency.
Low on fueI.
Changing course to Hawaii.
Can't make it back now.
Can't make it back.
What, Captain?
You're okay now.
It 's okay.
How's he doing?
He doesn't know what he's saying.
I managed to stop the bIeeding.
Is he gonna make it?
WeII if he is, we've got to get
him to a hospitaI soon.
-How Iong does he have?
-I don't know, it 's hard to say.
He's Iost a Iot of bIood.
A coupIe hours at the most.
Captain, can you hear me?
Yes.
I know you're in a Iot of pain, but
you've got to hang in there for me.
Okay. I've got to make it back.
I've got a daughter, too.
You're gonna puII
through this just fine.
You've got one of the
best pre-med students...
I've ever known Iooking out for you.
-Isn't that right, Jerry?
-That 's right.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
I'm gonna go up and taIk to Masters.
I'II Iet you know what 's going on.
Right.
No, he's right here.
Excuse me, sir?
We've made contact with Davis 2.
ApparentIy there was an
attempt to take over the pIane...
but your man put it down.
There's a fueI Ieak.
But most on board are okay.
-What about my daughter?
-Ask for yourseIf.
RocheIIe, my God.
Are you aII right?
Yes,Dad, thanks to Masters.
Listen, don't panic.
I'II get you out of this.
Let me talk to the pllot.
Okay! He wants to taIk to you.
This is Masters.
Come back.
Masters?
What are you doing in the cockpit?
The co-piIot is dead, and the
piIot has been severeIy wounded.
-Who's fIying the pIane?
-I am, sir.
Can you fIy that bird, Major?
I beIieve I can, sir.
-Excuse me, sir?
-HoId on.
Hey, Major, can my
daughter hear this?
-No, I'm on headset.
-Good. I owe you big time for this.
But you're not out of the woods yet.
My experts have analyzed
yourcoordlnates...
and the way
you're gulplng down fuel...
it won't be enough
to get you back to Hawall.
Wow, that 's fantastic news, sir.
Just what I needed to hear.
Any suggestions?
I've been in touch with
GeneraI McCIoren...
and we'II try to find
you a cIoser airstrip within range...
of your fueI capacity.
I'II have to Iet you know.
PIease do. Davis 2 out.
Is everything okay?
Oh yeah. CouIdn't be better.
-A 747, GeneraI?
-That 's right, Captain...
and there's no other
pIace to Iand.
Our runway won't accommodate
a pIane of that size, GeneraI.
We need at Ieast
another hundred yards.
WeII, Captain, then I suggest you
wake your men up and you...
get out there and you get me
that other hundred yards.
Look,you don't have much tlme
untll that plane's on top of you.
l know clrcumstances aren't ldeal,
but you do the best you can.
Yes sir, GeneraI.
Not ideaI circumstances?
Come on, Captain!
It 's the understatement of the century!
TeII me about it.
AII right, teII me if I got this right.
They want us to get out there,
cIear an extra hundred
yards of runway...
before that pIane gets here,
in a Category 3 hurricane.
That 's impossibIe!
What 's the matter, Lieutenant?
You afraid of getting wet?
I am.
It 's what our job is.
We do the impossibIe.
Mac, break out the rain gear.
We got some work to do.
AII right, men, Iet 's hit it!
Yes sir!
Davis 2 here.
Major, this is GeneraI McCIoren.
Yes,slr?
I need you to change the vector on
your coordinates as soon as you can.
Latitude 61 South...
Longitude 121 degrees East.
sir?
There's a smaII spot in the middIe of
the Pacific caIIed Neptune AtoII.
lt's a tracklng statlon. Or at least
it wlll be wh we're flnlshed with it.
But it's got a runway.
A runway? On the atoII?
You heard me, Major.
-Paved, sir?
-l can't be sure of that.
lt's gonna be rough,but at thls
polnt we have no otheroptlon.
You don't have enough
fuel to get to Hawall.
Now, they've got your frequency
and they're on ALS.
so as soon as you get
in range, they'II contact you.
Roger that, sir.
McCloren out.
We don't have enough
fueI to get to Hawaii?
I'm sorry that you had to hear that.
But I think it 's better that
you're in the Ioop.
so when were you pIanning
on teIIing us?
Just before we crashed?
Listen, RocheIIe, I'm not
going to Iie to you.
The deck is kind of stacked
against us on this one.
But I've done some of my
best work with worse odds.
I promise you that I'II do the best
I can to get you and your friends...
on the ground safeIy.
CaII me crazy...
but I beIieve you.
AII right, crazy.
Just keep me posted what 's
going on in the back.
You got it.
AII right, gentIemen!
There's not much time
to get this job done!
It doesn't have to be pretty,
and it doesn't have to be nice!
It just has to be a hundred extra
yards of runway. Understand?
We'II get it done, sir!
AII right, then.
-Mac, it 's WiIIiams.
-Yes, sir!
Did you hear from that pIane yet?
I got it on radar at the outer marker.
But stiII no voice contact.
Keep trying.
Let me know when you got her.
Yes sir.
Out!
L.A. Base to Davls 2.
Davis 2 responding.
Is that you, Neptune?
No, Masters, it 's Davis.
I'm on a relay through Honolulu.
I was just checking
in on your status.
WeII, to be quite honest,
sir, not good.
We're burnlng fuel much
fasterthan expected.
And there's no margln forerror
lf we reach the atoll.
What do you mean, ''if?''
I think you know what
I'm saying, sir.
Major, I know you're
doing aII you can.
How's my daughter hoIding up?
WeII, she knows the probIem
we're facing. They aII do.
lt wouldn't have been rlght to
keep them ln the dark.
Yeah. Major...
if the situation up there
starts to deteriorate.
I'd appreciate it if you couId bring
my daughter to the radio for.
sir, that 's Neptune breaking
through now.
I'm afraid I'm gonna have to sign
off and finaIize coordinates.
Yeah, yeah.
Davis 2, we've got you in ILs...
but we show your compass
deviating maybe 2 degrees.
PIease aIter heading to 1 Niner 1.
Change to 1 Niner 1.
Read you cIear Davis 2,
and do me a favor...
skip the ''Neptune.''
The name is Mac.
sounds good, Mac.
And it 's John.
Be nlce to see a lit runway
lnstead of all thls blackness.
WeII, I can sympathize
with you there.
Listen, we got a team out there
working on it right now.
Pardon me, Mac. say again?
I thought for a moment
you said ''working on it.
Uh, yes sir.
Didn't anybody teII you?
-TeII me what?
-Our runway...
couldn't accommodate a
plane your slze,Slr.
We've got a whole team
out there rlght now expandlng it.
Terrific.
Nice to know.
Let 's hope they're fast workers.
Hey, we're the Army Corps, sir.
We wiII have it ready.
You just keep fIying that pIane.
As Iong as I can, Mac.
As Iong as I can.
Captain,
we've got ourseIves a probIem!
For once you're right, Lieutenant.
That 's a probIem.
Mac, what 's the ETA on that jetIiner?
Less than 2O minutes, sir.
Dam nit, we need more time.
What 's the fueI status on the jet?
WeII, he bareIy has enough
to get here now, sir.
Listen, teII him to
begin his descent now.
Lower hls flaps,pull
back on the throttle.
That 'II reduce his airspeed and
cut back on the fueI consumption.
You understand?
I copy, Captain.
Over and out.
Lieutenant.
You take a couple of your men,
go overto the supply depot...
and pick up as much expIosives as you
can get your hands on. You got that?
Copy that, sir! One super-sized order
of semtex coming up!
I suppose you want
something to drink, too.
Thanks.
Water wouId be fine.
My kind of girI.
Why wouId you do this?
You put us aII in jeopardy.
Economics, my dear.
simpIe economics.
Don't worry.
It 'II be over very soon.
You got that right.
FIaps down
and Ianding gear down.
Roger that.
Hey Mac...
you wouIdn't happen to have some rum
on that isIand, wouId you?
Depends on who's asking.
For you, I might have about 3 cases.
Good. When we get there,
you mix up the drinks...
I'II bring the Iobster, some caviar,
and some crab Iegs.
Johnny, my man, you got a deaI.
Just don't teII the feIIas you got
Iobster 'cause they wiII scarf it.
Fine with me. I hate Iobster.
Why don't you get me some steak?
WeII, for you my man, I'II see if
I can accommodate you on that one.
I'II fire up the griII.
I Iike mine weII done.
Johnny, my man,
it wiII be ready to serve...
by the time you get here.
Just Iand that pIane for me.
Thanks Mac.
I'II get back to you shortIy.
Masters out.
Coffee?
Make sure everyone's
strapped into their seats.
It 's gonna get pretty hairy the
cIoser we get to the Ianding strip.
-I'II go make sure everyone's okay.
-Good.
Do you think we used
enough expIosives?
We'd better! You used
everything we had, right?
Every Iast bit!
That pIane's gonna
be here any minute...
and we stiII have
to Iight the runway.
WeII how the HeII are
we gonna do that?
We're gonna use an
oId WorId War 2 trick.
What WorId War 2 trick?
When they didn't
have Iights for the runway...
they dug a trough aIong the border
and fiIIed it with gasoIine.
The Iight from the burning gas wouId
be enough to give a Ianding corridor.
Now when the bomb goes off, that 's
gonna ignite the gas in the trough.
WeII isn't that gonna be dangerous?
I thought they were Ieaking fueI!
That doesn't matter, by the time they
get here they'II be running on empty.
Let 's get aII the men together and
start digging those troughs!
-Yes, sir!
-Let 's go!
Hey Mac. John.
Yeah. Go ahead, John.
Yeah,looklng for a status
report on the runway.
-And make it a good one.
-lt's looklng pretty clear,Masters.
The area's aImost cIear for Ianding.
AImost? We're running
out of time here.
It 'II be ready, aII right?
But I can't share the same
optimism on the weather front.
Man, the eye of the storm is
headed right for us.
What 's the current veIocity
of the eye waII?
Well, the wlnds are blowlng
East-Southeast across...
the runway at approxlmately
60 to 75 knots.
-75 knots?
-some gusts up to 1OO.
You can't Iand a pIane
in a crosswind Iike that.
More gusts
and we're troIIing for tuna.
I know, Buddy.
You might have to try a sIip move.
sIip a 747?
HeII. Mac, that 's something
you do in a Cessna!
Look, buddy, I know.
But if you don't...
she wiII roII over Iike
a st. Bernard in heat.
And the hits just keep on coming.
When that pIane is ten miIes out...
I'm bIowing those charges, so dig!
-We're through about 2OO feet, sir!
-Good job, Edwards.
Come on, men, we've got
to catch up! Let 's go!
This pIane feeIs Iike
it 's gonna break apart.
It might. I aIready Iost
haIf of my gauges.
Why don't you have a seat?
Enjoy the view.
some view.
If the gau ges aren't working, how
wiII we know if we've gone too Iow?
WeII, you'II see some fish
swimming by the window.
I bet you Iove every minute of this.
Oh, you must be taIking about
the part where your entire Iife...
is faIIing into the hands
of a man you utterIy despise.
Yeah. something Iike that.
WeII, despise is a strong word...
but if you crash this
pIane, aII bets are off.
Johnny,it's Mac.
We've got a little problem.
You know the winds
are getting stronger?
What 's it reading now?
The wlnds are gustlng
up to 11O knots.
Look,l got to shoot stralght.
You're not...
gonna be able to make a
dlrect landlngwithout a sllp.
- Easy for you to say.
-What 's he taIking about?
What 's a sIip?
It 's a perpendicuIar
4-stage approach.
The fuII fIaps are under the pIane
at an angIe into the wind.
In about 3OO feet before it 's
touchdown I correct he descent...
and take it nose-first
toward the runway.
What?!
In other words,
we're coming in sideways!
Oh Jeez, I shouIdn't
have come up here.
Maybe you shouId
warn your friends.
No, no, no, stay here.
Use the intercom.
Okay, okay.
Attention everyone.
We are mlnutes away
from our destlnatlon.
Make sure your seat
belts are securely fastened.
and prepare yourself for a landlng.
l know thls wasn't exactly
the vacatlon you expected...
but, we've got an experlenced pllot
flylng and I'm sure we'll all be safe.
Stay calm...
assume crash positlons,and we'll
have landed before you even notlce.
-How did I do?
-Like a pro.
Okay, okay!
AII right, we're gonna
bIow it, men! Come on!
Let 's get the HeII out of here!
Go, go, go!
Give me a detonator!
-You're hot, sir!
-Get down, men!
-What the HeII's going on, Lieutenant?
-I don't know, sir!
Give me the battery
from your waIkie-taIkie.
Here you go!
-The pIane, boss, the pIane!
-I'm working on it, I'm working on it.
-We're running out of time!
-I'm working on it.
I hope this works.
What 's with the fires, Mac?
Did you burn my steak?
Have to make some homemade
Ianding Iights to Iight your runway.
-Hey, thls ls not LAX,you know.
-Don't I know it.
This baby's being bIown sideways!
I'm beginning to sIip!
Rogerthat.
Piece of cake.
-Here we go!
-Oh my God!
How's it golng,John?
If we had deckchairs,
we'd be sIiding overboard!
Mac, I hope you boys
are ready for us!
We got it here.
Bring that monster down.
I'm trying!
We're stiII being bIown off course!
I got to giver her more throttIe!
Ready for touchdown!
I'm puIIing out of the sIip!
Raise the fIaps and back
up on the throttIe sIowIy.
You got it, Mac!
Get my steak ready.
I'm bringing this pig to the barn!
see you on the ground, Johnny.
I can't Iook!
Come on, Baby.
Oh, you're coming in too fast, John.
Come on, baby, stay on the road!
stay on the road!
Damn!
stay together, you bitch!
They're down! Oh my God,
the pIane is down!
Good work, son, I knew
you couId do it.
That was incredibIe!
Come on, guys!
We're not done yet!
Let 's go!
Oh my God, Masters.
You did it!
Let 's get the HeII out of here now.
AII right, everybody. Forget
your stuff. To the emergency exits.
Come on.
-I Ieft my jeweIry bag in my backpack.
-Wait, wait!
We're gonna need some heIp to
get the Captain out of here.
AII right.
-Any injured up there?
-We'II need a stretcher for the Cap.!
Come on!
Come on, carefuI. Go!
That 's it, that 's it. Keep moving.
CIear the area.
AII right, here we go. Away from
the pIane, pIease. Keep moving.
There we go, keep moving, Ma'am.
Go for it.
Mike, Ted, get these
peopIe to first aid.
That 's it, okay.
Go.
You 2 are next. Go ahead.
Come on.
What happened to our prisoner?
Okay, okay. Keep moving, champ.
Don't worry,
he's not going anywhere.
Neither are you.
Don't move.
My compIiments.
But Iet me ask you something.
Where do you think you're gonna go?
This isIand is smaIIer
than a postage stamp.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I just want to make sure you
don't Iive out the night.
I hate party crashers.
Good job. I owe you one.
ActuaIIy,
I beIieve we owe you one.
Thanks.
-You ready to depIane?
-Yeah.
Come on.
Come on, you can do it.
Come on, go!
Okay, here we go. Edwards,
get her to first aid!
Wait, wait, wait!
AII right, Iast one.
WeII, you must be Johnny.
Mac?
Here's your rum.
Your steak is on the Barbie.
-I hope it 's big enough for two.
-Why's that?
I might have a date.
Miss Davis, wouId you care to
have dinner with me?
-I'd Iove to, Major.
-Thanks.
My man, come this way.
WeIcome to Neptune AtoII.
Honeymoon capitaI of the Pacific.
Come on, cIear the area.