Today at One...
The Metropolitan Police
say their officers suffered
horrific injuries in yesterday's
sword attack in Hainault.
A suspect was eventually
tasered and arrested
after the murder
of a 14-year-old boy.
It's now known a female
police officer suffered
serious hand injuries.
The woman officer has
a very badly damaged arm,
really seriously damaged.
And the surgeon spent many,
many hours basically
putting her arm back together.
Police storm a university
in New York
where students had been protesting
about the war in Gaza.
A fall in UK house prices -
for the second month in a row.
And scientists try produce
a new type of bread that looks
and tastes like a white loaf -
but is still good for you.
On BBC London, we will have more
on yesterday's attack in Hainault,
as police continue to investigate
and a community comes
to terms with what happened.
Good afternoon.
The police officers wounded
in a sword attack in Hainault
yesterday suffered horrific injuries
- according to the Metropolitan
Police Commissioner Sir Mark Rowley.
He says one of the officers came
close to losing her hand and she's
had several hours of surgery.
A 14 -year-old boy was
killed in the attack.
one of the victims of the Nottingham
stabbings last year.
Graham Satchell reports.
Devastation this morning
at Bancroft's School in East London
and confirmation that
one of their students,
a 14-year-old boy,
was killed in
the sword attack yesterday.
It's the second time
in less than a year that
Bancroft's is in mourning
for one of its own.
Former student Grace O'Malley Kumar,
who was killed in a knife attack
in Nottingham, was
also a student here.
The final moments of yesterday's
terrible attack were captured
on a doorbell camera.
The 36-year-old man still carrying
a sword is cornered
and Met Police officers move in.
A taser is fired and then a female
officer approaches and again uses
a taser and the man
falls to the ground.
Police were on the scene in 12
minutes
and detained the suspect 22
minutes after that.
The bravery of the emergency
services was extraordinary.
Here an officer confronts
the suspect just feet away.
At this point, one person is already
dead and a number of others injured.
You've got officers
running towards someone
who's waving a sword.
What they do is absolutely
extraordinary and it's a privilege
to to work with them and lead them.
Come here.
Drop the sword.
Two officers who tried
to stop the man
ended up with serious injuries.
One nearly lost her hand.
Lock your doors!
I was talking to the family
and colleagues of the officer,
a woman officer who has
a really badly damaged arm,
really seriously damaged.
And the surgeon spent sort of many,
many hours sort of basically
putting her arm back together.
One eyewitness who didn't want to be
filmed describe the moment
of the attack.
Police were on their way
because sirens,
you could hear the sirens coming.
And then he started shouting
about God and whether you believe
in God and things like that.
I came at my house to go
to help the boy
as I know him and his family.
As I came out, he literally was five
feet away from me on the left.
So when I saw him, I went straight
back inside my house.
I wasn't sure if he'd been detained
or anything like that.
The investigation into the events
of yesterday morning will focus
on the man now in hospital
and under arrest.
Police have yet to interview him
but have said this wasn't a targeted
attack or terrorism-related.
Today, a school and a whole
community is trying to understand
why a 14-year-old boy lost his life
in the most horrific way.
Graham Satchell, BBC News.
A 17-year-old boy has been arrested
on suspicion of attempted murder
after three people were injured
at a secondary
school in South Yorkshire.
A child was assaulted and two adults
suffered minor injuries
at The Birley Academy
in Sheffield this morning.
Our Correspondent Nick Garnett
is outside the school now.
What more can you tell us?
Police were called after an incident
at 8:50am. They say than involved a
sharp object. Registration at this
school starts at half past eight,
the school for 11-16 -year-olds went
into planned lockdown procedures.
Parents were informed and children
were allowed to go home and all of
the children are now safe. A 17 year
boy has been arrested, or an
attempted murder, remains in police
custody. You can see the police car
behind me, that will remain here all
day. The Education Secretary Gillian
Keegan has said she's up disturbed
at what happened, the Prime Minister
mentioned that during PMQs. The
general secretary of the teachers
union, the NEU has been talking, he
said two teachers and people were
involved and that the government has
to recognise the scale of the
problem going on and adopt a health
approach to tackling youth violence.
There've been dramatic scenes
in New York where police have
stormed into Columbia University
to break up a protest
against the war in Gaza.
And there's also been violence
at a university in Los Angeles
where pro-Palestinian
protestors have clashed with
supporters of Israel.
In recent weeks, demonstrations
against the war in Gaza have swept
college campuses across the US -
they've been compared to the student
protests of the 1960s and '70s
against the Vietnam war.
From New York, Nomia Iqbal reports.
As the darkness came,
so did the violence.
The tension between
the pro-Palestinian protesters
encamped at UCLA and the pro-Israel
demonstrators boiled over.
Screams ring out as fireworks
are let off in the dense encampment.
Pieces of plywood
turned into weapons.
Thankfully I am physically safe. A
lot of my peers are not physically
safe.
It's not clear yet what
sparked the fighting.
The Los Angeles police
were called to the scene
at the request of the university.
The vice chancellor has
condemned the events
as a horrific act of violence.
On the other side of the country,
at Columbia University in New York,
where the protests originally
started, police entered the campus.
It comes nearly two weeks
since they last went in,
sparking huge controversy.
And a day after some demonstrators
seized a building inside campus,
breaking the windows
and barricading themselves in.
For the university
it was a red line.
Dozens have been arrested
in this new police raid.
Dozens of riot police are behind us
here. We are at Columbia University,
the actual entrance to the campus is
just to my left. You cannot get
anywhere near it. The police have
blocked it off entirely. Just
earlier we saw some students being
arrested. They had their hands
behind her back, with white zip
ties, being loaded onto buses and
further to the right to have more
student protesters, more
pro-Palestinian protesters on the
other side of the barricade
shouting, "Shame, shame, shame" at
the police. University are set a
deadline of Monday to clear the
captain. Students who did not agree
are now being suspended.
Protesters told us
they were hopeful talks
could still continue
with the university.
Their demands included cutting off
economic and academic ties
with Israeli institutions.
But given this latest police action,
hope for reconciliation
seems even further away.
Well in a moment we'll be live
with Regan Morris in Los Angeles,
on the violence that's erupted
there as we just saw -
but first Nomia, in New York.
And Nomia, these
protests against the war
in Gaza have been spreading across
college campuses for weeks now.
They have. And I think it is worth
mentioning that they haven't just
come out of nowhere. Just to let you
know, it is pretty normal here in
New York. A complete contrast to
last night when our team is here in
the thick of it, New York police had
carried out coordinated raids on
several encampments and several
universities here. But tensions have
been bubbling up, ever since October
the 7th, when there have been huge
divisions among students on campus
over how Israel has responded to the
Hamas attacks, the rising death toll
in Gaza, American support for Israel
as well. President Biden has been
across all of this. He has said that
free speech is allowed on campus,
but he has criticised some of these
protesters for being anti-Semitic
which has been denied by a lot of
the pro-Palestinian protesters, and
they are judging President Biden on
his response, which is crucial in an
election year when he will be
relying on young people to get out
and vote. And also, what it came
down to for many of the
universities, certainly here at
Columbia University, is that they
feel that is a distinction between
protest and disruption. They have
said that they want to get their
campus back under control,
especially considering we have got
graduation day just round the
corner, but how they have done it,
how they have got the campus back
under control, sending in armed
police to arrest students, for many
inside and outside the University,
that is deeply, deeply disturbing.
Over to Regan Morris in Los Angeles.
Bring us up to date on the violence
we have seen at the University
there. There were incredibly intense
clashes here overnight. I have
spoken with students on both sides
of that protest. Both sides say that
they were sprayed with pepper spray
or mace or bear spray, they are not
sure exactly what it was. We saw
bottle rockets being fired by
pro-Israel students on protesters,
into the Palestine solidarity camp,
and some students told me that they
came down with medical supplies when
they heard the bottle rockets, and
said that some people were hurt,
mainly from pepper spray in their
eyes. Heavy police presence here
now. University didn't comment,
there is a LAPD at our California
highway control. It is relatively
calm now, there are helicopters out,
lots of police keeping both sides
separate, but I have seen both sides
fortifying the lines with protesters
setting up barricades, as well as
the police. Thank you, Regan Morris
reporting from Los Angeles, and
thank you to Nomia Iqbal, in New
York.
The first migrants to be deported
to Rwanda have been detained.
The Home Office says a series
of operations took place
across the country this week,
with more scheduled
in the near future.
The government wants the first
flights carrying migrants to Rwanda
to take off this summer.
Live now to Westminster
and our political correspondent,
Hannah Miller.
Hannah, what more can you tell us?
There are still lots of questions.
We have no idea how many people have
been detained. The Home Office has
not given any details about their
backgrounds. It will be at least
nine weeks until the first flight to
Rwanda takes off and all of the
individuals who have been detained
still have the right to launch a
legal challenge, if they believe
that they should remain in the UK.
So, why are we hearing about this
now? The Liberal Democrats have
suggested this announcement has been
timed to coincide with the local
elections, which are taking place
tomorrow. Rishi Sunak, of course,
has made stopping the boats are key
campaign pledge and believe that
sending people off to Rwanda is a
key part of that. There are
questions also about the scale of
the whole policy. Official documents
showed that around 5700 people have
been earmarked as the first group of
people to be sent to Rwanda, more
than that, more than 7000 people,
have a dry on small boats so far
this year. -- have arrived on small
boats.
Hannah Miller, our political
correspondent, thank you.
The outgoing First Minister
of Scotland has told the BBC that
ending his power sharing deal
with the Scottish Greens
was the right thing to do,
but that the way he did it meant
he paid the price with his job.
In his first interview
since announcing his resignation,
Humza Yousaf said 'it's on me.'
Our Scotland Editor James
Cook is in Edinburgh.
You've been talking to him, what did
he have to say? I would say that the
First Minister was reflective and
regretful in this, his first
interview since announcing that he
intends to resign as SNP leader as
ultimately as First Minister of
Scotland. That had followed his
decision to chop the greens out of
government, a decision that so
angered the co-leaders of that
party, Patrick Harvie and Lorna
Slater and as he said, that was on
him, that decision was accepting
responsibility for it and it
followed divisions between the SNP
and the Greens and it should be said
within the SNP itself on economic
and social policy including the
issue of gender.
Well, for me, the
Bute House agreement
was coming to an end anyway.
It was coming to an end
in a matter of days,
possibly a matter of weeks.
That process almost had started
with the Greens, for example,
going to be putting
that to its membership.
It was votes of no
confidence coming up.
It was going to be
a party over gender.
Patrick Harvie, as you say,
and therefore, in my mind, whichever
way I looked at it,
whether it was a matter of days
or it was a matter
of weeks,
the Bute House agreement
was going to come to an end.
So that's why I see, as I have said
from the beginning, the ending
the Bute House agreement to me
was the right thing to do
for the party in the
country that I lead.
But I accept fully the manner
in which it was done clearly caused
upset, and therefore I've
paid the price of that.
He also talked about his concern. He
said that political debates were
routinely descending into what he
called a toxic cultural war, would
he endorse any of the potential
candidates to replace him, the
former deputy leader John Swinney or
former Finance Minister Kate Fords,
but at the moment, neither of them
have actually confirmed whether they
are running.
House prices fell for
the second month in a row
in April, according to the UK's
biggest building society.
Nationwide said UK house
prices were down by 0.4%
compared with the previous month.
It said the average home now
cost nearly £262,000,
around 4% below the all-time highs
recorded in the summer of 2022.
Our Cost of Living Correspondent
Kevin Peachey is with me.
Just talk us through some context
behind this? Economists had
predicted a rise in April and
clearly these figures have defied
expectations with a four albeit
quite a small one. Nationwide has
based these figures on its own
lending data and the picture will
vary depending on where you are
across the country. I think what it
shows is this wider uncertainty for
those thinking of buying a home as
to what is going to be happening, if
that demand is restricted in house
prices will fall. And all this is
down to mortgage rates, looking at
those mortgage rates and lenders
have been pushing them back up again
in the past couple of weeks.
Probably unsure about what the Bank
of England is going to do. If we
look at a fixed deal for two years
that now is close to 6% interest
rate so moving back up. Nationwide
says that first-time buyers in
particular are exposed to these
borrowing costs and also they face
higher house prices as you say,
still close to those record highs. I
spoke to quite a few potential
first-time buyers and they have
moved back in with their parents in
their 30s with all the stress and
strains that that brings as well and
nationwide are saying around half of
first-time buyers have been
rethinking their plans over the next
five years simply because it is
difficult to afford to buy a first
home.
Kevin Peachey, thank you.
24 people have died in China
after a highway collapsed
in the province of Guangdong.
Video footage shows a number
of cars which had fallen
into a large crater.
30 other people were
taken to hospital.
It follows weeks of heavy
rain and flooding in
the south of the country.
Our China correspondent
Laura Bicker reports.
It's collapsed.
It's a disaster, says this witness
after watching part of the highway
slide away into the darkness.
A hole just opened up
in front of us, said
others on social media who filmed
the aftermath in the early
hours of the morning.
In daylight from the air,
almost a dozen blackened vehicles
can be seen still smoldering,
embedded in the muddy banks
of what appears to be a landslide.
The tarmac and metal rails,
which once held up the highway,
are now scattered across the slope.
About 500 rescuers were sent
to the site, taking
dozens to hospital.
This is a major May
day holiday in China.
This route to the coast
will have been busy.
A week of extreme weather has hit
China's most populous province.
This tornado swept through power
lines and wiped out factories
in the industrial
heartland of Guangzhou.
Torrential rain and powerful storms
have also struck Guangdong.
Thousands of people were taken to
safety in the wettest April since
records began.
Laura Bicker, BBC News, Beijing.
Russia has put on display Western
military hardware
its troops have captured in Ukraine.
It includes British army vehicles,
as well as tanks
from the United States and Germany.
Our Russia Editor Steve Rosenberg
has been to look at them.
I'm in Moscow's Victory Park,
a World War Two memorial complex.
But this has got nothing at all
to do with the Second World War
and everything to do with Russia's
war now in Ukraine.
This is Western military hardware
that Russia has captured in Ukraine.
And today, the Russian military
is putting its war trophies
on display and letting the Russian
public in to take a look.
So, for example, there is this,
this British army Husky
tactical support vehicle.
As you can see, its windscreen
has been shot up, and
across the way there
are tanks as well.
There's a German tank, a Leopard
tank and an American Abrams.
As you can see, the place
is absolutely packed and
all of this hardware clearly making
an impression on the Russian public.
It's incredible, jaw-dropping.
It's amazing to think our guys
managed to get these trophies.
So why has all of this
been put on display?
Well, I think the authorities
here have two main aims.
The first is to reinforce
the Kremlin's narrative
that in Ukraine, Nato and the West
in general is waging a war
against Russia,
even though in reality it was Russia
that launched a full-scale
invasion of Ukraine.
But there is also a big
element of gloating here.
The Russians are increasingly
confident about the way
the war is going in Ukraine,
and their main message is written
on a sign over there.
And it reads, "Our
victory is inevitable."
Steve Rosenberg, BBC News, Moscow.
Now this week on the O'Clock News
we've been looking at the impact
of knife crime and yesterday
we heard from the family
of Mikey Roynon, who was just 16
when he was stabbed to death
at a party last summer.
Today, we hear from the neighbours
and first responders
who rushed to the scene
when Mikey was attacked.
Our West of England Correspondent
Dan Johnson reports,
and a warning you may find some
of the details distressing.
This is the ambulance service.
Is the patient breathing?
11 pm on a summer's evening and a 16
year old is struggling for his life.
He's been stabbed at a house party.
A birthday party has been
upturned by a knife attack.
Is the patient breathing?
No, no.
People living nearby
are trying to save the boy.
It was a scene of
carnage, basically.
When I got there, Mikey
was on the floor in the road.
We were trying to
find the stab wound.
We thought it might be on his leg.
There was blood
literally everywhere.
You're confronted by people
who are shocked, distressed.
Some people had blood on them.
I was trying to say to Mikey,
you're not on your own.
I'm trying to help.
We're here.
We're trying to help you.
Whether he'd already passed away,
I don't, I honestly don't know.
I remember saying,
no, he's not dead.
Let's keep going.
Knowing in your heart
of hearts that probably we're
going to be unsuccessful.
And...
And that was really sad.
You sort of, you don't
expect it necessarily.
And when it does happen,
it's just shocking and grotesque.
Mikey Roynon had been stabbed
in the neck with a zombie knife
after a confrontation erupted
at the party.
It was only when the other ambulance
teams arrived we were able to get
more eyes to have a look,
and we found the single extensive
stab wound right up hidden
in his hairline here behind his ear.
And then it just,
it was just silent.
Everything went silent.
And it was just, it was just eerie.
You can't measure the level
of impact it had for all of us,
for our families, for our
friends, for everybody.
It's had a huge impact and it's
changed all of our lives and it
will do forever now.
You feel the grief in every way,
like the whole family are broken
and there's nothing we can do
to put their world right.
It's just awful.
We feel guilty all the time.
You say guilty.
You mean because...?
Because I've still got my children.
..Because she's lost
her son and you've...?
She's only got, she only had
Mikey, and he's gone.
It's been nine months now.
It's exhausting, because you're
constantly on edge.
You're constantly, you hear
a helicopter and it's
just, it triggers you.
It was just dreadful.
Just looking at his face and...
Yeah, and that is, unfortunately,
his face at that point
is now what I remember.
Mikey's death here underlines
the devastation, not
just for his family,
but also for people here in this
community and beyond as well.
And then there are the three
young men who did this.
I'm not allowed to
tell you their names.
We don't know a huge
amount about them.
They may not deserve our sympathy,
but they've upturned their own lives
and those of their families,
too, and their fates
are to be decided by a judge
when they are sentenced on Friday.
Dan Johnson, BBC News, in Bath.
While Israel has been
fighting its war
against Hamas in Gaza,
its northern border with Lebanon has
seen daily exchanges with Hezbollah.
Like Hamas, Hezbollah is backed
by Iran and proscribed
as a terrorist organisation
by the UK government.
Hezbollah launched rocket
and drones against Israel
after the Hamas attacks
last October.
Well the Israeli
military have hit back hard,
hitting thousands of targets
in Southern Lebanon.
Our correspondent Carine Torbey has
been on patrol there
with the UN's peacekeeping force.
Travelling to south of Lebanon
is a risky journey.
Accompanied by the Lebanese army,
we moved closer to the damaged towns
dotted along this border area.
Israel lies on the other side
of that concrete and metal barrier.
Empty villages, abandoned homes.
Peaceful life here has been erased.
It feels like a no man's land.
This mangled mound of cement
and metal was a family home.
It was hit by an Israeli strike just
a few days before our visit.
Little left of the home it had been.
The family who lived
here left months ago.
Tens of thousands of
people have fled in fear.
Israeli military strikes that
were limited in scope have expanded,
leaving towns across the south
deserted and destroyed.
This was a coffee shop.
And next to it here was a two
story building standing.
Now it's reduced to this one
massive hole in the ground.
As we were leaving the area,
it was hit by an Israeli airstrike.
Israel says it hit 40 Hezbollah
targets on this day,
mainly in the border town
of Aita Shaab, just a few
miles from our patrol.
Hussein is from the town,
but he's now staying
with his family in an apartment
on the outskirts of Beirut.
They left with what they could carry
on the very first day
of the border hostilities.
We showed him footage of the town
filmed by us back in October.
He said many of the buildings
are now totally destroyed.
I told him that Israel
claims it is targeting
Hezbollah's fighters.
TRANSLATION: They are
targeting civilians' houses.
It's systematic destruction.
It's not true they are just
responding to attacks.
Back on the road, despite
the intense violence,
the UN peacekeeping forces
still think they
have a role to play.
Many people are tired
of the situation and I can imagine
people are tired also in the other
side of the conflict.
So I think it's time for peace.
The next challenge for UNIFIL
will be to help and support
the local population in returning
back to their homes.
Since the beginning of the war
in Gaza, this front has
been more of a sideshow.
Fears are that at any moment it
could take the centre stage.
Carine Torbey, BBC News,
Southern Lebanon.
Now, do you like white
bread but worry that
it's not good for you?
Well scientists at Aberystwyth
University are trying to produce
what looks and tastes like a white
loaf - but is actually just
as nutritious as wholemeal bread.
Here's our Science
Correspondent, Pallab Ghosh.
It's bread, only better.
These are the first batch
of nutrition-boosted loaves.
The aim is to make them look
and taste like
the sliced white bread
that most people prefer.
I've really found about this
project
is that white bread
is not good for you.
I was always aware of that,
but it's really reinforced it and
it makes you realise just how much
of the goodness
is on the outside
of that grain of wheat.
We want to know what are the actual
minerals present and what are
the vitamins and amino acids
and so on that are being lost
so that we can formulate a white
flour that is enhanced compared
to an existing white flour.
The scientists are working
with a flour-making firm
in Gloucestershire.
They're making loaves with added
cereal,
pulses and fibre
for the scientists to analyse.
Both these loaves are
nutritionally enhanced.
This one has bits of wheat,
such as wheat germ and bran
that are found in wholemeal loaves,
but in smaller quantities.
This one has all sorts
of different grains,
such as chickpeas, green peas,
and quinoa, all mixed in together.
Both of them are much
better for you.
But how do they taste?
Chris Hollister, whose idea it
all is, offers me a slice or two.
That's gorgeous.
And it tastes like
white bread as well.
That's the idea.
Yeah.
We want to make sure that people
are still receptive to it
and it's not too different
to what they're used to.
Around a fifth of the wheat grain
is thrown away
when making
flour for white bread.
And those are the bits
that are better for you.
Chris thinks that there's a way
of putting some of that back
without making the bread taste
like wholemeal,
which a lot of people don't like.
Currently, white bread flour has
to have essential minerals
such as iron and calcium added
to it by law.
But the scientists say that
mixing in natural cereals,
peas and beans will be much better
for you,
and they'll collect
the data to prove it.
If the nutritional quality
of that standard bread,
that bog standard bread,
is improved, their nutrition
and their quality of
life and their health
and wellbeing will improve.
Nutrition boosted white bread should
be available in the shops
in a couple of years.
The researchers say it'll be
the best thing since sliced bread!
Palab Ghosh, BBC News.
Time for a look at the weather.
Here's Darren Bett.
Good afternoon. Most of the
mistiness this morning is lifted but
across some parts of eastern
Scotland it is still quite great and
cool. If you have the sunshine it is
feeling quite warm with temperatures
at 20 degrees across East Anglia.
There are still some cloud around
producing some showers and we have
thick cloud moving up from France
that eventually will bring some
rain. That is heading into eastern
Scotland bringing some showers. But
across southern parts of England in
the Midlands we start to see the
rain gathering and that develops a
little more widely this evening
moving into Wales and affecting
Northern Ireland for a while. Then
some real downpours later on in the
south. Further north any cloud
developing more widely overnight.
Some lively weather by the early
hours of the morning across southern
England and South Wales, thunder and
lightning, some heavy rain and gusty
wind bringing disruption for a time.
The worst of the weather heading out
towards the west and eventually
turning drier in south Wales and the
South West of England. Further north
more sunshine developing more widely
but with that keen north-easterly
wind coming in we keep some low
cloud and cooler weather for North
East England and south east
Scotland. Not much warmer elsewhere
but a warmer day in north-west
England and Northern Ireland and
western Scotland at 20 or 21
degrees. Some warmer air heading
away from the continent but coming
across the cold North seat which is
why we had that mist and low cloud.
And that weather front is going to
bring some rain overnight and into
Friday with the rain moving further
north and bringing more cloud to
Northern Ireland. Some sunshine for
Scotland and Southern counties of
England. Temperatures will be
dropping in the rain, the highest
temperature on Friday in western
Scotland with 20 degrees likely. But
even here the weather will change
and Saturday we have cloud and
outbreaks of rain pushing north into
Scotland and Northern Ireland.
Further south some sunshine coming
through and feeling pleasantly warm
to start the bank holiday weekend.
More showers more widely for the
rest of the weekend.
Thanks, Darren.
And that's BBC News at One.