What are days for?
Days are where we live
They come, they wake us
Time and time over
They are to be happy in
Where can we live but days?
♪ When your body's next to me ♪
♪ I begin to sweat ♪
♪ When we touch, I lose control ♪
♪ Now you know what's next ♪
♪ Fantasizing all the time ♪
♪ Move your body next to mine ♪
♪ Well, I need your love ♪
♪ I need your love ♪
♪ Don't make me wait too long ♪
♪ Oh, I need your touch... ♪
Sorry.
No problem.
Come and get a pint.
♪ I can't let go ♪
Ten days in the Dordogne.
It's going to be Katie, Alex,
Rory, Biscuit, Douglas, and Fran.
And me.
- And you, Dexy, if you come. Will you?
- Hi, Dexy, darling.
Hello.
Don't go away.
- Have you sealed the deal, then?
- Shh. He'll hear.
And he's just carrying out
all them moves.
What about that one
on The Meadows?
I have never laughed so much.
I'm still laughing.
They're probably still there.
Dexy!
Okay. Tell me that you're coming
to France with the Marlborough lot.
Um... I'm not sure yet.
Caroline is keen, Dexy.
That's all I'll say.
And Annabel, but no surprises there.
Dinner in London, yeah?
- Dinner in London.
- To the last day of uni.
- Ever!
- Wait. Do it to the end.
"The end"?
What kind of a toast is "the end"?
All right, then. To the beginning.
To the beginning!
- To the rest of our lives. Whoa. Uh...
- Oh. Emma, you've pulled.
Who is that?
Dunno. But I bet he's doing...
...physics.
Wakey-wakey.
- Oh.
- Hi.
Hi.
- Cal.
- Hmm?
Callum?
But, Mommy,
it's not a school night.
Hi, Dex.
You feeling all right?
Mm-hmm. Mm.
Just going for a wazz.
All right.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
What a charming encounter.
Uh, sorry about that.
It's not your fault.
Are you all right?
Entirely.
Drink?
Um...
Okay.
You're an unlikely pair,
you and physics boy.
I... I think you'll find
that was 18 stone of computer science.
How do you know each other?
We lived next door in halls.
Ah, yeah, where the magic happens.
Yeah. That's where I met Tilly.
Oh my God!
I'm Dexter, by the way.
Yeah, I know.
I've seen you around.
I've seen you around too.
Dex, mate.
Thank you, Magnus.
Uh, we... we smuggled in a couple of cases.
Of all the rah things.
Well, should I get you
a pint of snakebite?
Oh my God.
What?
A snakebite, though.
Now I really wanna find a snakebite.
♪ S'Express ♪
♪ Come on and listen to me
Baby, now, ooh ♪
♪ Come on and listen to me, baby, now... ♪
Where did you see me
before tonight?
Uh, um...
The library.
You've never seen me
before in your life.
Let's get another drink.
♪ I got the hots for you ♪
♪ Boop, boop, ba, boop, boop, boop, ah... ♪
English. The Romantics, mainly.
I did my dissertation
on Elizabeth Barrett Browning
and the sonnets of the Portuguese cycle.
Do you know, uh, Cressida Adams?
Uh, no. Who's that, a poet?
No. She's, uh, the sister
of someone I know from school.
Oh.
Well, she does English, so...
Yeah. No. Still no.
Well, your dissertation
sounds a page-turner.
What? No, it does.
So will Magnus be along
with another bottle, or...
No, I doubt it.
All my friends have left, so...
♪ Licked my fingers ♪
♪ And I drove my car to the sea ♪
♪ I drove my car to the sea ♪
Um, this is me.
You should have said hello.
When?
When you saw me around.
♪ My love in a car ♪
♪ Should go forever ♪
♪ Deeper than any sea ♪
I'm just gonna put a tape on.
♪ But I'm open to persuasion ♪
♪ East or west ♪
♪ Where's the best ♪
♪ For romancin'? ♪
♪ With a friend ♪
♪ I can smile ♪
♪ But with a lover
I could hold my head back ♪
♪ I could really laugh, really laugh... ♪
What's your plan?
Do you usually ask
for a breakdown in advance?
Um, I mean, for your life.
The plan for your life.
Oh God.
Right. Okay.
Uh...
My parents are here
for graduation, obviously, and...
...they're driving my stuff back.
- So I'll stay in London for a few days.
- Uh-huh.
See some friends.
And, uh... then France.
And then China, maybe.
You know, see what that's all about.
Then India.
What?
That's your plan for the future?
Just go on holiday?
No, it's not a holiday. It's travel.
- Travel?
- Yeah, travel.
- Could you stop saying "travel"?
- What's wrong with travel?
No, nothing, I suppose.
You know, if you can afford it
and you don't mind, you know,
avoiding reality.
Well...
I think reality is overrated.
What a ridiculous statement.
And I didn't mean,
"What are you doing next month?"
I meant, like, the future future.
When you're, I don't know,
40 or something.
What do you wanna be when you're 40?
I don't know. Not 40?
Am I allowed to say "rich"?
All right, then. Famous.
- A bit morbid, this, isn't it?
- It's not morbid. It's exciting.
"Exciting."
Are you from Manchester?
No.
- Sheffield?
- No.
- Wigan?
Warrington.
I know what you're doing.
You're naming all the stations you pass
through on the train up from London.
But I bet you've never so much
as set foot in the north.
Newcastle.
Leeds.
Leeds!
And what happens in Leeds?
Nothing. Not to me, anyway.
What do you wanna do?
Uh, change things.
Do something
that actually makes a difference.
Like change the world, you mean?
Yeah. Not the whole world.
Maybe just my own tiny corner of it.
I can imagine you at 40.
Can you?
Go on, then.
Okay.
It's 2005,
and you're in this tiny, tiny sports car
with the roof down,
in Kensington or Chelsea
or one of those places.
Excellent. Carry on.
Um, and you've got
this little paunch that you've tucked away
under the steering wheel.
No paunch.
And the wind's blowing
through your widow's peak,
and you're feeling
very, very pleased with yourself.
And wife number three, or is it four,
smiles at you
with about 200 shiny white teeth,
and you smile back,
whilst trying not to think about the fact
that she's thick as mince,
and you've got nothing,
absolutely nothing, to say to each other.
♪ Once more with feeling ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ You know that's what I like... ♪
Course it doesn't matter.
'Cause we're all gonna be dead
in a nuclear war long before then.
You know, the thing
about northerners is that...
...you rate yourselves so very highly
for your sense of humor, but
actually, you're just really bloody rude.
- I can go.
- What? No, don't... don't go. Um...
No. It's four in the morning.
But if... if I'm so
vain
and shallow...
and corrupt...
Which you are.
...then why are you sleeping with me?
Sleeping with you?
Did I? Were you that forgettable?
♪ In a sky ♪
♪ So clear and blue ♪
- You need to brush your teeth.
- Huh?
I don't mind if you don't.
- You taste of wine and fags.
- And so do you.
Wait, do I?
I don't mind. I like wine and fags.
Okay, um...
Just... Be back in a sec.
♪ What to do... ♪
- Now where are you going?
- Just the bog.
The bog?
- The bog? I'm not familiar.
- No playing with yourself while I'm gone.
Did you just tell him
not to play with himself?
I don't know if you can recover
from that, man. I really don't.
Shush!
I'm being such an idiot.
He's used to these perky,
giggly, posh girls,
and I'm in there being rude
and sarcastic and twitchy.
♪ In their way ♪
♪ Saturday sun ♪
♪ Won't come and see me today ♪
♪ Think about stories ♪
♪ With reason and rhyme ♪
♪ Circling through ♪
♪ Your brain... ♪
- What do I do?
- Sex.
Do sex.
- Mm. Yeah, but...
- But what?
I mean, what's he doing here?
I mean, he's slept with most of our year,
most of the year below.
Has he just worked his way down the list
and got to me?
Think you might be overthinking this?
If he is working through a list,
it's your turn, baby.
Okay. Just go back in there.
Don't speak,
and let your body do the talking.
No.
No?
I'm gonna chat.
- Chat?
- I'm gonna get to know him.
What a waste.
Mm. Nice gown.
We call this look
"Academia by Night."
It cost 30 quid to hire.
Gotta get my money's worth.
Now, take it off and come back to bed.
Is that an order?
"Emma Morley."
"History and English."
"Joint honors, first class."
Mm, read it and weep, 2:2 boy.
Rude.
Incredibly rude.
Be careful with that.
Getting it framed, are you?
Actually, my mom and dad
are having it turned into wallpaper.
It's so late. No more talking.
Do you know... you know
there's nothing sexier than talking?
Uh, arguably, sex, but...
Um...
Okay.
Let's talk.
I love that sound.
Do you?
Blackbirds at dawn. Yeah.
Do you not?
No.
No, it makes me anxious.
Like I've done something
I'll regret.
That's why I love it.
Have you?
Have I what?
Done something that you'll regret.
Don't know yet. Ask me in the morning.
I think it is the morning.
Yeah.
Have you
done something you'll regret?
No.
We should try and get some sleep.
Why?
Nothing tomorrow.
Just the whole
of our lives stretching out.
Oh. You off, then?
I didn't wanna wake you.
Um, I was...
I was going to leave you a note,
but I... I couldn't find a pen.
No, it's fine.
Yeah, you can leave whenever you want.
Yeah. Um...
You see, my parents are here, and...
and we're heading back this morning.
I was quite drunk
last night.
I... I had a really nice time.
Yeah, I can tell from the way
you're searching for your shoes.
Yeah.
No. I... I, um... I mean it.
I'm glad we finally met
and talked and the other stuff.
Mm. Under the bed.
- What?
- Your shoe.
Oh.
I really was gonna write you a note.
What was it gonna say, this precious note?
It was gonna say,
"I've stolen your purse."
You'd find it tragically empty,
I'm afraid.
Mm.
Well, now where are you going?
To shower, get dressed.
Will you be here when I get back,
or should I say bye now?
Uh...
Well, do you know what?
I, um...
I might see if we can leave later.
Mm?
So did you?
Tell me!
Did you have sex with Dexter Mayhew?
Tell me now!
No.
So, what did you do?
Uh, we just... we talked and stuff.
Stuff?
What, hand stuff? Mouth stuff?
Foot stuff?
Em, no!
Don't you dare walk out on me!
Just tell me more.
- What does he smell like?
- Shh!
At the third stroke, the time...
- ...9:32 and...
- Uh...
Hi, Mom. It's... me. Um...
Is it okay if we leave a bit later today?
...will be 9:32 and 20...
Yeah, okay.
Don't change your plans.
If you've gotta go home, that's fine.
Oh no, it's fine.
Ah, amazing.
Okay, great.
Thanks. Yeah. Okay.
See you back at the flat.
Done.
Mm.
That's...
Hi.
Oh, hi!
Um, I'm Tilly.
Have we met?
Dexter.
Hi, Dexter.
Tilly.
Right. Uh, breakfast?
Breakfast.
♪ When I first saw you
Something stirred within me ♪
♪ You were standing sultry in the rain ♪
♪ If I could've held you ♪
♪ I would've held you... ♪
Emma got a first.
Do you know she got a first?
- Tilly!
- She already told me.
I didn't tell you. You opened my scroll.
"Opened my scroll."
So,
what shall we do with the day?
The first day of our properly adult lives.
Ooh. We should go out for lunch.
No. No. It's a gorgeous day.
We should be outside.
- Portobello beach? Oh, let's go swimming.
- No.
Emma hates wearing a swimming costume,
but she has a lovely figure.
She does.
Let's climb Arthur's Seat.
Well, never done it.
You've never climbed Arthur's Seat?
You've been here four years,
and you've never climbed Arthur's Seat?
I've been busy.
Doing what?
Studying anthropology.
Right. Let's go.
Oh, we could take a picnic.
♪ But I'd choke rather
Than swallow my pride ♪
Or...
♪ Rip it up and start again... ♪
You two should go without me.
I need to...
feed the guinea pig.
Are you all right back there?
Yeah, good.
Should I alert search and rescue?
It's the shoes.
I just wish they had more grip.
Is it the shoes?
Are we really going
all the way to the top?
It's not K2.
You're very nimble.
Like a mountain goat, me.
What are we gonna do
when we get to the top?
Admire the view!
Here we go.
Come on.
Oh my God. Dexy!
Who's that?
Shall we walk?
♪ Up, down, turn around ♪
♪ Please don't let me hit the ground ♪
♪ Tonight I think I'll walk alone ♪
♪ I'll find my soul as I go home ♪
Would you like some bread?
- Uh, no. Not for me, thanks.
- Okay.
- But you... you have some.
- Oh no, I'm fine for now. Thanks.
To one-night stands.
Are we drinking
to one-night stands in the future?
Because we didn't actually have one.
Yeah. No. Uh, no.
Is that a religious thing,
not sleeping together?
Hmm. Okay. Right.
So unimaginable, is it, that someone
might decline to have sex with you
that it could only be explained
as an order from God himself?
Shut up. No, it's just a question. I mean...
Maybe a stupid question, but...
My mom's Hindu,
and my dad's a lapsed Catholic.
So, no.
God wasn't involved.
I hope it doesn't feel
like a night wasted.
It wasn't a night wasted.
It was memorable.
Not having sex with you
was highly memorable.
What are you doing?
What does it look like?
I... am taking a picture.
Something to remember you by.
Oh, I look terrible. Hold on.
Okay. Cheese.
Oh no, not cheese.
Well, then, what?
Thieves that pass in the night?
Thieves don't pass in the night.
- That's ships.
- What do thieves do?
- Thieves are thick.
- So rude!
- laughs.
- Oh.
- You know it's St. Swithin's Day?
- What's that?
15th of July.
If it rains today,
it's gonna rain all summer.
- Something like that.
- It's not gonna rain today.
♪ I've been out walking ♪
♪ I don't do too much talking these days ♪
♪ These days ♪
♪ These days, I seem to think a lot ♪
♪ About the things that I forgot to do ♪
♪ And all the times I had ♪
♪ A chance to ♪
♪ I've stopped my rambling ♪
♪ I don't do too much gambling
These days ♪
Grip was all right on the way down.
Yeah.
Well, um, bye.
Will you come for a drink?
What, now?
Yeah.
We've got time.
I mean, I do. Do you?
Yeah.
Which pub shall we go to?
One near my flat.
Oh.
♪ Falling ♪
♪ Colour... ♪
- It's not far now.
- What number are you?
Seventy-eight.
- Forty-four, 46, 48.
- I've got a stitch.
Dexter! Dexter!
Where have you been all day?
- Dexter. Hello.
- Ah.
Hi.
Well?
- I left a message on your machine.
- What machine?
Yes. What machine, Dexter?
We're in a hotel.
In the room.
I phoned through to the room.
Mm.
Not a single one of these
seems to work.
Uh, this is my friend, Emma.
- Pleased to meet you, Emma. I'm Alison.
- Hi.
None of them.
Not a single bloody one of them.
And this is Stephen.
- Pleased to meet you.
- Yeah. You too.
Well, where have you two been all day?
I need to move the bloody car.
Oh...
Do you want to come in for a drink, or...
Or dinner.
Why don't you join us for dinner?
Uh...
Thank you. Uh, thank you,
but, um, I've got to get back. Um...
Are... Are you sure?
Yeah. Yeah.
Um, yeah, I'll see you around, maybe.
It was really nice to meet you.
- You too, Emily.
- Emma.
Emma. I'm so sorry.
Goodbye, Emma.
Well, have a nice life.
Yeah. Yeah, you too.
Have a nice life.
Oh...
Has she gone?
Sorry, Dexter. Did we interrupt something?
No, no, no... She's, uh... She's...
She's just a friend.
Emily!
I thought I'd lost you.
Sorry. They, uh...
They weren't meant to come down
until later.
And then I realized I don't have any...
any way of getting in touch with you.
- Oh, um...
- I don't have a pen.
Yeah. Hang on.
- You must have a pen.
- A pen!
Um...
Okay. So, uh... call me.
Or I'll call you.
Either way, one of us will call. Uh...
It doesn't... It doesn't matter who.
It's... It's not a...
It's not a competition,
is what I'm saying.
- You don't lose by calling.
- Yeah, I understand.
Okay. Here you go.
Um, I'm going to France until August,
and then I'm back, and I thought... thought
maybe you'd wanna come down and stay.
With you?
Yeah. Well, at my parents'.
I mean, not forever.
Just for a weekend.
- You don't have to.
- Yes! Yes. Uh...
- Uh, yeah, I'd like to. I will. Yeah.
- All right.
So...
See you around.
Yeah, I hope so.
I hope so too.
Bye, Em.
Bye, Dex.
- Bye.
- Yeah, bye.
♪ This is the day ♪
♪ Your life will surely change ♪
♪ When things fall into place ♪
♪ This is the day ♪
- ♪ This is the day ♪
- ♪ Your life will surely change ♪
♪ Your life will surely change ♪
- ♪ This is the day ♪