For 5 Thousand years
China never had any peaceful period for long
Because evils usually process those people
With supreme power
Like the brutal emperors in history
To fulfill their desires, lives were deserted
Civilian were the only class suffered
Luckily there were Devil Hunters
They sacrificed to battle against the evils
The evils were chained. But accidentally
Due to Battles and riots
The evils are released
And the world is in a bloodshed disaster again
The Japanese are coming
Don`t kill me
Japanese are coming
Don`t kill me, Help
Master, Japaneses is here
Help
Master, Help
Where is my wife?
She`s dead
Hurry
The Japs is massacring
Don`t
Look after my son
OK
Brother
Please let me go
Go help them, Hurry
Please don`t
Brother
Kong, be careful
What`s the matter?
Brother
He`s your brother, watch out
Be careful
What shall we do?
lt`s the Blood Demon, not me
Brother
Don`t come near, l can`t break away
Don`t come any closer
The Blood Demon got me
lf l`m caught, our people will be damned
Kill me, hurry
Brother, easy
l`m going to get you out
Stab me, hurry
Don`t let the Demon out
Stab me now
What about your son?
l`ll leave him to you, please bring him up for me
He doesn`t know he get the magic power
But l hope he can grow up like normal man
Any misfortune happens, just leave him to God
Stab me
Hurry, we don`t have time
Brother, l own you my life
l swear l`ll treat your son well
God will bless your soul
Where`s your brother?
My Dad won
Wise man must keep away from troubles
Why should l bother?
This is a painting against the Demon
You must take good care of it
Don`t use it unless it`s necessary
Hide the gavel at the Godness Temple
Hope Gods will bless the world
We`ll obey your words
Don`t let the children know too much
Just tell him his parent died in the war
l know where my father goes
Be a good boy
Bad luck, you again
lt must be the centipede emperor
Right? Kong is brilliant
Lot of people praise him
Checkmate
Safe
My uncle will win for sure
You think you are prophet
He lost already
Tung, go hang the paintings. New years` close
l`m studying
He`s free, why don`t you order him?
You are biased
l`m leaving for school
Be careful
lt`s going to rain, take your umbrella
No way you can win
Tung
Get lost, you don`t belong to this family
l don`t need your sympathy
Because you know kiss ass, that`s why
My parent only nice to you
Tung
Don`t block the light. Can`t you see l`m studying
Sorry, Tung
Uncle, you look pale
Be careful
Stop it. Kong said your father doesn`t look good
Superstitious
Crash capitalism
Crash all evil beings
Crash all oldies, bring up a new era
Long live Cultural Revolution
lt`s right to rebel
lndividual is nothing in this new era
Personal sentiment must be left behind
and indulge in the flame of revolution
Long live Cultural Revolution
We student revolutionists
firmly hold our position at the frontier
We must crash all the anti-revolution evil
and all those sting intellectuals
Down with Lui
Crash Education, Crash Cultural Department
You tell the people honestly
Why did you spray perfume in class
l have body odour, it smells
You are a capitalist
You want to use perfume to discourage
the student`s revolution spirit
You are a spy
On your knees
Down your fifthy spy
Down the Education Department
Down the Cultural Department
Down all intellectuals
Down all literates
Raise your ugly head, Lui
Look what teacher they send to us
Before young revolutionist like us
You are nothing but scum
You literal scum, on you knees now
Dad
l beg you
You belong to a black scum`s family
You don`t have the right to speak
She tries to poison me with sentimentalism
ls she a capitalist?
Yes
We must draw a line between us and evils
No personal feeling in anti-class war
Crash capitalism
Crash all evil beings
Please don`t beat him, he`s sick
l beg you
Take these evil beings away
Get out of the way
What`re you doing?
Hurry, get out of the way
Leave him to the mass
Take him away
Let`s go and see your father
What`re you doing here?
Chor
Auntie
Tung, try save your father
This is our family business
Tung
Comrades, we`ll be Red Guards
l`ll follow your displines
Tung, don`t
For revolution, l think, l talk, l do, l rebel
And fear nothing
Crash all evil beings
Today l`m going to do the right thing
l`ll break the relationship with my evil father
And draw a clear line
Chor, your name sounds traditional
And it comes from old society
Together with Kong, you`re evil beings
Scum of the society
You lead us to superstitious
You are anti-revolutionists
l will crash both of you
Kneel
Chor
Don`t hurt him, he`s sick
Please don`t
Kong, you must accuse Chor
Lenient if honest, severe if resist
My uncle is a good man, he`s not evil
He`s not your Dad. Why do you protect him?
l`ve nothing to say
You are out of your mind
Don`t talk to me, l`m not your son
l belong to the Party
l`m the son of New China
l have nothing to do with you
They are anti-revolutionists
They must be re-educate
You kneel down
Kong
Though l`m not well educated
l know what is right and what is wrong
lt never happen before for
the son to beat the father
Chor, confess to the people, loudly
l did nothing wrong, Tung
Stop calling my name. We are through
Today l am going to end your evil behaviour
Chor
We`re guilty
Chor, plead guilty
Who will accuse him? Come on
Ma, how about you? You`re their team leader
Alright, Comrades
Let me tell you their sin
He is absolute an evil being
He was a exocist before the country liberated
He cheated many of our people
Why don`t you tell our people before?
l am guilty
No need to bother you
l`ve prepared myself, look
l admit my sin
l`m rotten. l knew some bad people and
l made some mistakes
l decide to reform and learn from the mass
Please give me a chance
We must rid the evil from the root
Rid the evil
Rebel is right
Take care of yourself, Auntie
We must destroy the evils
Comrades, our country is burning red
We see our future, we see our light
We`re student of our Chairman
Comrade, l`m not easy forget
You taught me 2 years ago
And you opened my mind. l improved a lot
So let`s carry on our revolution
Tung
lt`s you, Kong
You are back
The Government forgive you, you must perform
l did well and my superiorgive me a chance
to pay my debt to the party
They said you`re one of the best doctor
Work hard
and we`ll do what our superior instructed
lt`s good you`re back
Mum missed you
Go and see what happen
We will move this mountain
Don`t panic
Move him over here
Hurry
Stop his bleeding now
Captain, it`s a chain
Pull it. l`ll go check it out
Yes Sir, Come on, Pull
Tung, this mountain look weird
l`m afraid something may go wrong
Get lost
Tung
Stop it! l have a bad feeling about this
Stop it now
This is a matter of the country
Not your personal buisness
Keep on pulling
These rotten cultural scums
We must crash the anti-literal authorities
You`re capitalists` ruuning dogs, black scum
want to try something?
We must crash black scums
Something stabbed at the heart, What is it?
Ancient treasures?
Would it be an ancient emperor`s tomb
Who is he? l feel l met him before
Don`t touch it, it`s weird
Don`t say such superstitious words
You want to be re-educated again
Kong, for the sake of the family, leave it
Comrade
Go
Pull him out, quick
Hurry
Watch out! Hurry
Kong, go!
Hurry
Excuse me
Your cap
Thank you
Tung, come over
His pulse is abnormal
lt seems something tries to force its way out
Looks like not that serious
Let`s welcome officier Lui
Welcome
How are you? Comrades
Dad
You grow stronger
Because of hard work
Officer Lui, this way please
Just call me Comrade
Yes, Comrade Lui. lt`s a long trip
Please take a rest
before you speak to everyone here
Officer Lui takes a long trip to visit us
Let`s make a warm welcome to Officier Lui
Thank you for your hard work
No matter what had happened, it`s history
You know him?
Now it`s time for reunion
Lui, Remember?
to fight against capitalist class
He got a bad time but now he`s clean again
The Government likes him and promote him
You punished him before
We just did our best for our country
Every one here was a warrior before
We didn`t have other alternatives
Let`s forget the past
To die for the country
ls a honour of revolution class
The Party will take care of his business
Comrade Lui
Take a rest here
Applause everyone
KlLL
Let go! Respect the leader
A anti-revolutionist just attacked our leader
We will investigate the case
And we will complete a detail report
on this accident
Then we go into meeting to discuss
How to avoid this happen again
The conclusion`ll be handed to our leader
Then pass to the seniors to examine
lf there`s proofs showing that there`s enemies
Hiding within us and create chaos
We`ll plan how to find out the enemies
And punish him according to the regulations
Excuse me, Officer
A lot of people is bleeding
Please allow me to take care of them
Comrade Tung
Comrade Shan
l know you joined the parade at Beijing
l remember it was on December 26
Everyone was ready at 3 in the morning
We kept waiting until 4pm the next day
Then our Chairman appeared
He was far from me. l only saw a shadow of him
l was moved, and l cried
Did everyone cry?
Some didn`t because their tears became urines
No man can control his bladder for over 10 hrs
But they couldn`t leave so their pants were wet
Don`t laugh. Don`t joke at revolution
Beware get punished when campaign come
l think you won`t do that
lt was a mistake, sorry
My father is a good man
Anyway, your reputation is restored
Shall we celebrate?
l want to visit your home tonight
and share your revolution experience
l don`t think it`s a good idea
Revolution is not buying someone dinner
Nor writing an poem, nor painting a protrait
Revolution is not leisure
Not elegant, not humble
Neither it`s not gentle at all
Revolution is violent
lt means a class overthrow another class
lt means bloodshed
Father
Political power means everything
You lose it, you lose everything
Father
Stop
Political power means everything
You lose it, you lose everything
l want to learn from Comrade Tung
Political power means everything
You lose it, you lose everything
Dear, revolution is a long road
l know, that`s why l want to learn from him
l`ll pay a visit to him later this evening
Since he is an experience revolutionist
Beside he is now no longer our enemy
We`re on the same frontier
l have no second intention
Just want to learn from him
What the hell l`m talking?
After that tragedy, Mum...
Please don`t mention those bad old days
Auntie
Kong, Mum is inside
Auntie, it`s me
l brought some pork for you
Preserve it will be nice
l am Kong
Auntie
Look, this is pork
l admit it
Auntie
l tell the truth
Mum
She is Comrade Shan
Her Dad is our city`s revolution officer
Just call me Shan
No, l don`t want revolution
Mum, don`t be afraid
She just come to say hello
Don`t panic
She was awarded sometime ago
Mum, don`t be afraid
Auntie, have some water
Kong, please stay with Mum. l`ll prepare dinner
Shan, she`s alright
Once l was red, flaming red
So what? lt means nothing
Today l`m red, then black tomorrow
Few days later, the campaign come
Then l`m red again
Sometimes l doubt myself
Can revolution be a lifetime career
Tung, you change a lot these years
You`re not active as before
Yes, l want a simple life
and stay by my Mum for the rest of her life
What l`m looking for now is peace
Mum is the only person l care
How about your uncle, is he released?
Chor, get down
Get him down or you all will be punished
Get down, don`t risk your life
Don`t be stubborn. Get down
Get down
Get down please
Mum
Go to see your father
l`m not guilty
Get down and we`ll talk
l`ll forgive you no matter what you did before
Chor
You must take good care of your Mum
Chor My son
Read, you must read as much as you can
Chor
Dead? Good! Long live the Chairman
Long live the Chairman
We have the same blood in our body
Do not start awar among our own people
Don`t go revolution
We don`t need a revolution
He`s dead. All he left is a painting
l met my father
Fu Hse Needle? Godness Marble?
Can they be found nowaday?
The Blood Demon
He`s dead
We are in the New Era now
Don`t give Mum a hard time. Just forget it
lt`s over anyway
l swear l`ll keep my mouth shut
You can trust me
Swear? We need loyalty, not words
Kong, you leave first
Look after my Mum for me
l tell you what l feel
lf it`s an old furniture
An old clothes or piece of torn paper
l can abandon them
But she is my mother
l can`t leave her like that
lf someone with power is processed
The world will be in chaos
More lives will be wasted
Everyone is forced to kill during revolution
Are they all Blood Demon?
Don`t you think Lui is strange?
Thank you very much
l`ll see you in the gathering day after
Comrade Shan is a nice girl
You interested in her?
No mood for that in this kind of situation
You`re kidding
Right to rebel, Long live Revolution
Hello Comrades
You 2 get along well with the Officer`s lady
You don`t have to worry anything
Have a cigarette
Please take care of me in future
You`re kidding. l don`t have the power
Then you must have a problem
Thank you
My stomach was in riot momments ago
Lucky that l kept recite the regulations
Now every bad scums were thrown out
All evils and enemies are driven away
By the working class
My Father and his parnter fought a devil
Before the country liberated
l heard that you were with them
Really? l remember nothing
Even if l can, l won`t tell you
l know my question is stupid
May be you`ll accuse me if l tell you
But honestly, l remember nothing
l was a kid and how can you expect me
To understand what they did
Now all l want is avoiding all troubles
So your business is not mine. Good night
You mean your father`s temper changes
He used to be very gentle
l have a strange feeling recently
Do you believe the Blood Demon rumor?
The world is bigger than we think
Our knowledge is limited
Though there`s no proof
lt was told my our ansectors since decades ago
There must be a reason for it
Then l`m Blood Demon`s daughter
No joking
Demon`s daughter, you are a spy
Tell me what do you like to find out
Let`s stop the nonsence
What is your interest?
Let me guess
Even when l`m listening to Beethoven#9
l just want to dance
Am l corrupted?
But now l don`t read the regulations anymore
That`s better
The best thingis nobody`ll treat as enemy
lf l`m mistreated, l`ll revenge
lf l`m gifted, l`ll reward
We must understand the truth of revolution
We will succeed only if we get the key point
The ``Ocean group`` must surrender
There`s only 1 rebel group in 1 city
ln this city, we are the only one
Correct
They say Chinese love peace. Wrong
They love War and l`m one of them
Our war plan against the ``Ocean group``
Must be ready in 3 days
Thank you
Comrade, we`ll follow your instruction
Fine
Comrade Wu
Do you have a problem?
No, but l`m afraid many student will die
ln the contact between us and the ``Ocean group``
lt`s not a big deal
China is over populated
Our enemies must die
Are you afraid?
Comrade Lui, l`m not clear about my mission
l like to have a 3 months sick leave
And let me think thoughly
Excuse me
Can`t you reconigze your father
Anything special, Comrade Ma?
l found an ancient treasure. lt`s valuable
Please take it
You try to pollut my soul with
This kind of Capitalist` luxuries
No, l didn`t mean that
Really? Now l order you a mission
Sorry for my ignorance
Thank you for teaching me
Please give me your order
l don`t care how you do it?
To blow, burn or any way you can think of
Just to destroy it
Yes, l`ll do my best
To destroy the enemies in front of us
Good, Comrade Ma, you`ll be promoted to
The Captain of our Counter Attack Unit
Your salary will be adjusted be $30
Now l want find a man call Kong
His ancestor was a devil hunter
l know him and l want him as well
His mind is polluted
l intended to bring him to you few days ago
He mentioned something about a needle
He also suspects you
Comrade Ma
My Dad ask me to take care the ancient treasure
This is his authorization
Go to arrest them now
lf you fail me, you`ll be damned
You want to join them to against me? Go!
Why?
l must tell you the secret before l die
l`ll tell the only way the kill the Blood Demon
You must listen carefully
One of you be be the bait
Allow Blood Demon process you
Then stab the neddle into the bait`s heart
Mum...
He is here
You can`t let it kill again
Someone must sacrifice and die with it
Mum, what happen?
The Ruwu Marble is at...
Where?
ls this the needle
Mum
At the Godness Temple
Kong, run. My Dad send someone for you
l get to go
All temples were cracked down in riots
lt`s all rocks only, let`s leave
lf not because of the project, it`ll buried foreve
Go
Don`t fail
The Temple. Don`t let them get away
You can`t against my Dad. You`ll lose
l don`t want to see you both dead
l`m not coward. l`m not afraid
Don`t sacrifly for nothing
Go, hurry
l don`t have time anymore so
l must tell you the truth
l love you
Take care
Go
Get them
You can`t escape from me
Tung, watch out
Get away Tung
Tung
My leg
Are you okay, let`s move
l can`t walk
Tung
Kong, you go first
There`s only 2 of us left
No, l carry you
Dying together is meaningless. 1 of us must live
Remember tell people that you`re a Red Guard
When you are on the road
Go now
Take care
You too
Kong, run to those places with riots
lt`s safer in those places
Where is the other?
l`m in trouble
Where are your parent?
You`re enemies of revolution class
You must go to reform class
l haven`t eat for a few days. l`m starving
Why take my bum?
Aren`t you ashame to rob a kid?
You bastards
We are bastards, and what are you?
l am a Red Guard
Me too. So what?
The Government say they don`t need us now
We are abandoned
See, the Red Guard`s badge
10 Kg for 1 cent
l`m also a University student
But one thing we are in common
We are both starving
Wait, Comrade
Let me cure you
Where is Kong? Talk
What makes you change like this, Dad?
l am your daughter
l`m not your father. To achieve my goal
A line must drawn between you and me
l`ll not trust anybody
You are not a human being
l am Blood Demon
Where did you hide Kong?
l won`t tell even you kill me
l don`t want you dead now
But worser than death, you`ll be a cripple
As long as Kong survives
Your plan will fail
A revolutionist msut be merciless
He can`t escape. l put a warrant on him
l am going to Beijing
To report our progress in this campaign
We are the invincibles
l`ve been waiting for you
l know you`ll return
l get the evidence of your anti-revolution acts
l can become human again
l succeed
Kong, help
lf l don`t kill you
l`ll be killed
The Chairman say anti-revolution is bad
l know
He also say be determine, willing to sacrifice
Get rid of difficulties to victory
Kong, l don`t want to die
l`ve been a liar for my life
They are locked in the black hole
You have to trust my last word
Kong, run, leave us alone
Why do you come back, it`s dangerous
He`s my Dad, no
What is this place?
Why am l here?
Kong
Use the needle to kill me
Shan
Tung, kill me
l can`t resist anymore
Kong
Kill me
Kill me now, quick
Do it, Tung
Kong
Do it
Hurry, kill me
Kong
Tung
Now
Kong
Hurry
l can`t stand anymore
Tung
Kill me before it`s too late
Do it
Who ever against me must die
l need blood
Hurry, it`s coming out
No
Kill me
No Kong
Kong
Shan
Mum, who is in the grave?
Your uncle
How did he die?
He sacrified to rescue many lives
ls he a revolution hero?
Did he die in the war?
Why do people like to fight?
Look, the sky become red
Like something is going to rise