♪ Take a cardboard box
add some paint and glue ♪
♪ Build a magic world
where your dreams come true ♪
♪ Once you step inside
nothing you can't do ♪
♪ Let imagination
run away with you ♪
♪ Come along with Julius Jr
♪ You never know where
you're gonna be ♪
♪ Come along with Julius Jr
♪ Step inside the box
and see ♪
(Giggling)
I can't find my pink
crayon anywhere.
This pink crayon?
Uh-huh!
The one I found under
my comic book collection?
[gasp]
Yay! That's it!
Ping, there's pink on
the plastic protector
of my rare
Super Sock issue 145
where he defeats
The Big Toe!
I'm sorry, Worry Bear.
[sigh]
No harm done.
But things need
to be put away
in their proper spots, guys,
or stuff gets wrecked!
You're right, Worry Bear,
it is a little
messy around here.
Ugh -
ow...
Huh?
Oh.
[sigh]
Mission: Clean-up!
Giraffe Boy, go long!
All right!
[laughs]
Boo-yah!
Balls in
the ball place!
[doorbell]
It's Chachi!
Shaka Brah's doggy!
[barking]
[laughs]
He sure seems happy to see us!
Hey, boy!
[laughs]
Not the nose!
That's my tickle spot!
Aw, he's such a good dog!
[giggles]
Let's play with him!
I don't know, Ping.
Shaka Brah might be
worried about where he is.
Why don't you two superheroes
take Chachi back to Icelaska
while we finish tidying up?
Yes!
Captain Invention
and Giraffe Boy
have a new mission:
Bring Chachi back home safely
before evil-doers
do evil to him,
and good dogs everywhere
have to bury
their toys in fear!
And -
before Shaka misses him!
To the Hall of Doors!
SHAKA:
Chachi!
You're back!
Thanks for bringing
him home, super dudes!
That was totally
super-awesome of you.
That's just
how we heroes roll.
[teeth chattering]
Aw, poor little guy.
Chachi just isn't built
for this cold weather.
Being a short-haired
Chihuahua,
he just doesn't
have the thick fur
like the other sled dogs have
to keep them warm!
Hm, maybe Chachi
would be happier
living somewhere warmer.
[whimpers]
Maybe you're right,
Giraffe Boy dude.
I would miss him so much,
but I'd feel a lot better
knowing he was warm and cozy.
What do you think, boy?
Would you like that?
[whimpers]
Not to worry, Shaka.
Captain Invention
and Giraffe Boy
are here to save the day!
And now we have
another new mission:
Find the perfect home for Chachi
so he's safe from the evils
of cold and snow everywhere!
[laughs]
C'mon, boy!
Wait a minute, Chachi dude!
You better take your
favourite pillow!
I'll miss you too, my friend.
But don't worry.
Soon, you'll have
a nice, warm new home,
and I'll come visit
you all the time!
Take good care of him,
super dudes!
We will!
I just know we'll find
the perfect place for Chachi,
right, boy?
Chachi?
Oh no, we lost him already!
He must have been
dognapped by evil --
[barking]
Oh, there he is!
But where's his pillow?
Hm, he probably
left it in Icelaska.
We'll get it later.
The Seashelly Islands!
SHARKY:
Arr, he's so cute!
I've always wanted a puppy!
Mission accomplished.
Captain Invention
and Giraffe Boy
have saved the day!
Your pirate name will be...
Chachi the Fearless!
[growls]
C'mon, boy.
Time to board the pirate ship!
DIAMONDBEARD: Arr,
'tis a pirate's life for me!
Right, Sharky,
me boy?
You bet,
Uncle Diamondbeard!
[whimpering]
Oh...
Oh, poor puppy.
You can't be a pirate dog
if you're going to
get sea sick.
Hm...
Maybe this isn't
the best place for Chachi.
[whimpers]
DIAMONDBEARD: Sorry we can't
keep the little pup, Julius.
But we pirates have
to sail the high seas!
It's what we do!
No problem, guys.
We'll find a better
place for him.
[whimpers]
Oh, hey, Chachi,
I'll give you a hand
with that.
Whoa!
[growls]
Oh, I get it.
You want to play,
is that it?
[gibberish]
Chachi, come back!
Fare thee well, pirates.
See ya later!
Chachi!
Chachi, where are ya, boy?
There he is!
Hey Chachi!
Where's your bandana?
[barks]
[laughs]
So, where to now,
Captain Invention?
Have no fear, Giraffe Boy!
C'mon!
MARV:
Oh, he's so cute!
We'd be tickled to take him!
[barks]
[laughs]
Mission accomplished.
Let's celebrate with
some bouncy bean dip!
ALL: Mmm!
[sniffs]
[barks]
[barking]
Chachi!
Are you here, boy?
[barking]
Chachi must have gotten into
my transformation potion!
[barking]
Luckily, I have
the antidote right here!
[stomach rumbles]
Aw, the little guy
must be hungry.
Hey! That's my
bouncy bean dip!
Chachi, come back!
I'll get him!
Chachi!
We're going to have
to find a new home for Chachi.
I'm not sure he should
be getting into
any more of your
potions, Marv.
CLANCY: I found him!
See ya later, guys.
Bye!
BREWSTER:
Why, sure he can stay!
What's one more
creature on a farm?
Yes!
[sheep bleating]
Looks like Chachi
needs some rescuing.
And a bath.
No worries.
Tool-Box-A-Lot!
On the spot!
[♪♪♪]
Tool-Box-A-Lot,
ready to assist!
[laughs]
JULIUS: Behold!
The Bathomatic!
CLANCY: Cool!
[♪♪♪]
[barking]
There!
All clean!
But I don't think the farm
is the place for Chachi.
He's not crazy
about the sheep.
[bleating]
[whimpering]
Well, he can always
stay with the chickens.
[loud clucking]
Or...not.
We'd better keep looking.
This is trickier
than I thought!
Where will we ever
find a home for Chachi?
I don't know.
Twirl-a-world?
BOB: Sorry, boys,
but Chachi can't stay here.
What?
Why not?
He's so cute!
Oh, he's a cute
little dog, all right.
But I just don't have time
to take care of him!
You don't?
Why not?
A puppy is
a big responsibility!
You have to feed him,
play tug of war, give him baths,
and make a nice bed for him.
It's...it's just too much
for one person to do.
Uh...wait a minute!
That's it!
Woohoo!
And then I realized
why are we looking
for someone else
to take care of Chachi?
There are five of us!
I'll bet we can
take care of a dog
if we all do it together.
Woohoo!
I'm in!
Yay!
A puppy!
M-hm.
We'd love for Chachi to
live with us, Julius.
I have some amazing
dog food recipes
I've been wanting to try.
But we've just finished
putting all our stuff away
in its proper spot.
I don't know where
we would put a puppy.
[barking]
WORRY BEAR:
Oh!
Looks like Chachi
is way ahead of me!
So this is where he's been
putting all his stuff!
Oh wow!
He's already set up
his own little spot
with his pillow, his bandana,
and his food!
What a smart dog!
He must have wanted to
live with us all along!
Looks like we finally found
the perfect home for Chachi.
Mission accomplished!
Oh yeah!
Woohoo!
I'll call Shaka
with the good news!
I'm sure he'll want to visit.
This is my crayon, Rosie.
And this is Worry Bear's
sock monkey, Rocky.
And this is my ducky, Squeakers!
[squeaks]
He's gonna live
right beside you.
Okay, well...
I'll just take Rocky now
and wipe him.
[barks]
Hey, that's my tickle spot!
He knows that
already, Worry Bear,
'cause he's our doggy.
Welcome home, Chachi!
♪ Take one step to the right
♪ Make a funny face
with all your might ♪
♪ Take one step to the left
♪ It's a dance
you can't forget ♪
♪ Wiggle to the left
♪ Wiggle to the right
♪ Raise your hands
up to the sky ♪
♪ Spin around, spin around
♪ Spin around
♪ With your hands
pointed to the ground ♪
♪ Woo!
♪ All you need to do
is start to move ♪
♪ Ah-ooh ah-ooh
ah-ooh ah-ooh ♪
♪ Jump up, jump back
♪ Ah-ooh ah-ooh
ah-ooh ah-ooh ♪
♪ Jump up, jump back
♪ When you follow
all the steps ♪
♪ It's fun to jump up
and back ♪
♪ Ah-ooh ah-ooh
ah-ooh ah-ooh ♪
Focus...focus...
Now!
Yeah!
[barking]
It's a doggone slam dunk!
Chachi,
you're the greatest!
[barks]
Boo-yah!
Can't touch us!
Uh-huh!
It's so great that
you've moved in with us!
Now we can play with
you all the time.
Can I play with
Chachi now Clancy?
I need his paws.
His paws?
[confused noise]
Chachi has
very special paws.
I need them
for my art project.
Well, okay.
But bring him back
when you're done.
We have more
practicing to do.
[laughter]
What a dog!
Okay, Chachi.
Here comes the music.
♪ A womp-babba-loo-ba
♪ Ba womp-bam-boo!
[♪♪♪]
[giggles]
[grunting and barking]
This is paw-some!
SHEREE: Chachi!
Where are you?
He's over here with me!
Can I play
with him now, Ping?
The Wandering Wardrobe and I
have been working
on a big surprise!
Um...okay.
[barking]
[laughter and barking]
But bring him back later!
We have a lot more
painting to do.
Ooh!
[laughs]
Master Julius!
Power level low!
[slows down]
Huh...
The Invention
Dimension sure uses
a lot of electricity.
Chachi, just wait
until you see
what we've cooked up
inside for you!
It's doggy dress-up day!
[barking]
[siren howl]
[laughs]
Hold it right there, Chachi!
I just have to
get some pictures.
[barking]
Wow, this dog looks
good in anything!
He could rock a lampshade!
[barking]
Chachi, I've been
looking all over for you!
It's time to
practice your tricks!
Um, bring him back
after, Worry Bear!
We have so many more
costumes to try.
Sit up!
Shake a paw!
[laughs]
Roll over!
Back flip!
Breakdance!
Whoa!
Chachi has so much energy.
[barks]
Hang on.
That gives me a great idea
for a new invention.
[♪♪♪]
Behold, the Chacherator!
ALL: Ooh!
Whoa, this is your best
invention yet, Julius!
What does it do?
The Chacherator
measures and captures
all his doggy energy
as he runs around
and turns it into electricity
for the Invention Dimension.
Nifty!
Chacheriffic!
Very
impressive!
Coolio!
[laughter]
[barking]
See?
The more he moves,
the more power he makes.
[barking]
Awesome!
C'mon, Chachi!
Let's shoot some hoops!
Nose dunk, woohoo!
Back leg slam, yes!
And a swisheroo!
[barking]
[panting]
[laughs]
[barks]
SHEREE:
That's it, Chachi!
Work with me!
Give it all you've got!
Don't forget to sm-eyes!
That's smiling with your eyes.
[laughs]
Chachi, sit!
Chachi, shake a paw!
Chachi, lie down!
Chachi, roll over!
JULIUS: Hey, Worry Bear,
can you come here a second?
Coming, Julius!
[yawns]
Look at this!
Chachi's energy level
is going down, down, down.
That's weird.
He was just doing his tricks.
Hm...
Maybe there's something wrong
with the Chacherator.
Better got and check it out.
Hey, what's this doing here?
Chachi must have dropped it.
But where is he?
BOTH: Chachi!
Chachi!
Chachi?
What's wrong?
We can't find Chachi anywhere!
Oh no!
Where do you think he went?
Well, we found his
Chacherator hat over there!
To the Hall of Doors!
Chachi!
Here boy!
Chachi! Here Chachi!
Come on!
Are you here, boy?
Chachi!
C'mon, boy!
[barking]
[gasp]
Chachi, is that you?
He must be in Icelaska.
Chachi!
C'mere, boy!
C'mon, Chachi!
JULIUS:
Shaka Brah!
[laughs]
Waddup, little dudes?
Shaka, have you seen Chachi?
We've looked for him everywhere!
Where could he be?
Well, it's just after
snacktime, so...
if I were you, I'd look
under the coffee table.
[barking]
Ah!
Under the coffee table?
Yeah! Chachi always
like to have a nap
under the coffee table
this time of day.
After his snack of exactly
three organic dog biscuits
and one cup of
free-range kibble,
and his water.
Which he likes
nice and cool.
Snack? Water?
Sure, he's always really
hungry and thirsty
after he comes in
from his run.
You do take him out for a run
every morning, right?
Um, does jumping
count as running?
Well, no, that's
more like playing.
Chachi loves to play.
He'd play all day
if he could.
But that's not good for
a little doggy dude like him.
He needs to rest
sometimes, right?
ALL: Uh... right.
Thanks for
the doggy tip, Shaka.
Good luck!
Later, little dudes!
[barks]
PING:
Chachi, we're coming!
JULIUS:
Come on, everyone!
Chachi!
WORRY BEAR:
Shhh, he's sleeping!
Oh, right...
Chachi?
[whimpers]
[quiet groan]
Chachi, there you are!
We're sorry, Chachi.
We weren't taking
care of you right.
We know you need
your snack.
And some water.
[giggling]
And I'm going to
modify the Chacherator
so it tracks your
food, water, and sleep.
That way we won't forget again.
Don't worry, Julius,
I'll never forget
now that I know
'cause I love Chachi!
Okay, I've also
programmed the Chacherator
to assign time so we each
get a turn to play with him.
See?
There's Worry Bear time,
Sheree time, Ping time,
Julius time, and Clancy time.
What about Chachi time?
From now on,
it's Chachi time
all the time!
[barks]
Here you go, Chachi!
Exactly three
organic dog biscuits
and one cup of
free-range kibble!
And a nice dish of water.
Nice and cool.
Just the way you like it!
[♪♪♪]
[barks]
[whimpers]
Oh, you want to put on
your Chacherator, do you?
Well, here you go.
[barks]
Okay!
Let's see how his
energy level is now.
[barking]
Oops!
Time for his run.
Hey, Chachi!
Want to go outside
for a run?
[howls]
Now that's what I call
Chihuahua power!
Whoa!
[laughs]
[giggles]
Now that's our Chachi!
Aw...
[laughter]
♪ Enjoy your friends
around you ♪
♪ They make you
laugh and play ♪
♪ The family
you look up to ♪
♪ May love and teach you
everyday ♪
♪ Show respect,
it's the best way you can be ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey
♪ It's a special feeling
♪ When you do something
good each day ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey
♪ It's a special feeling
♪ Be your best
in every way ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey
♪ It's a special feeling
♪ Be your best
in every way ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey