The global
singing phenomenon is back.
‐ ♪ Whoa ♪ ‐ Can you guess the
celebrities behind the masks?
Our secret stars have
42 Grammy nods, 140 films,
and are worth a reported
$287 million.
Wow!
‐ Give or take some change.
Incredible performances.
♪ Yes I'd catch a grenade
for you ♪
‐ Come on!
‐ You stole our show.
‐ ♪ Do you wanna go ♪
‐ More confusing clues.
My darkest moment
was when I went to rehab.
Well, you know, there's a
club in Vegas called Rehab,
and it's dark inside there.
And a crack panel
of celebrity detectives.
Can't you guys see?
It's so obvious.
This game is so easy,
and that's why I'm undefeated.
‐
‐ Each week,
the masked stars compete
to stay anonymous.
‐ Whoo! ‐ This is exactly
why "Masked Singer"
is a hit show,
for moments like this.
The weakest performers
are eliminated...
‐ Take it off!
‐ ...and unmasked.
- My God!
- Whoa!
- ‐ Last week...
- Hey!
...Panda had to "bear" it all.
Boxing champion Laila Ali!
Whoa!
Tonight, the masked
madness continues
with group D,
Eagle versus Flower
and Penguin versus Fox,
and another famous face
is revealed.
Your favorite who‐sungit
starts...
‐ Howard Stern?
‐ right...
‐ Bjork!
‐ ...now.
‐ Tell me!
‐ I will never!
‐ I can't take it anymore!
‐ Never!
♪ Who are you? ♪
♪ Who, who, who, who? ♪
‐ ♪ I really wanna know ♪
‐!
♪ Who are you? ♪
♪ Who, who, who, who? ♪
♪ I really wanna know ♪
♪ Who are you? ♪
Who am I?
Looks like I'm Nick Cannon.
Welcome to
"The Masked Singer."
We are an equal opportunity
masked singing show
for any and all walks
of celebrity.
We accept world‐class
athletes, comedians,
actors from film and TV,
politicians,
radio and talk show hosts,
people who love drama llamas,
and baby mamas,
we welcome them
with open arms.
But we are very selective
when it comes to
our celebrity detectives.
So let's welcome the most
exclusive panel in TV history,
ladies and gentlemen.
‐ Nicole Scherzinger.
‐ Hey!
‐ Jenny McCarthy‐Wahlberg.
‐ Whoo!
Robin Thicke,
ladies and gentlemen.
Robin!
‐ Thank you.
And finally,
give it up for Ken Jeong!
That's good.
That's good, Ken.
Yes! Catch it, Ken.
Catch it!
‐ Yes! ‐ All right,
well, let's get to it.
Tonight, the last new group
of celebrity singers
will face off
‐ two‐by‐two.
‐ Yes!
After each face‐off,
the studio audience and panel
will vote for their
favorite performance,
and the winner will get
to sing another day.
‐ Whoo!
‐ The loser of each face‐off
will perform again
in the smackdown.
The panel will then decide
who they want to see again,
and the loser will be unmasked
and sent packing.
Tonight, we've got the Flower
versus the Eagle,
then the Penguin
versus the Fox.
‐ Yeah!
‐ Bring it.
Time for our first
big face‐off of the night.
Let's all stop and smell
the Flower.
‐ ♪ If I was you ♪
‐ Nicole: Whoo!
♪ I'd wanna be me too ♪
♪ I'd wanna be me, too,
yeah ♪
‐ Wow! ‐ My God,
I love that costume!
Yes, Flower!
‐ She's already a diva.
‐ ♪ I'd wanna be me, too ♪
♪ I'd wanna be me, too ♪
‐ Right. It's a slow walk.
So lovely,
don't you all agree?
And I'm being told
the Eagle has landed.
♪ Going up to the spirit
in the sky ♪
‐ ♪ Spirit in the sky ♪
‐ Robin:!
♪ That's where I'm gonna go
when I die ♪
♪ When I die ♪
♪ They lay me to rest ♪
♪ I'm gonna go to the place
that's the best ♪
So cute! I love him.
Eagle! Eagle!
All right, Eagle,
don't fly off.
‐ Giving me a '70s vibe.
‐ Man.
All right, who's ready for
the first clues of the night?
Give it up for the Flower.
What's up, rosebuds?
Some say I blossom in every
field I plant myself in,
so becoming the Flower
was a natural arrangement.
I dipped my petals
in just about everything,
from cooking to clothing
to craft.
Cooking, crafts, clothing.
Martha Stewart,
maybe again there, Ken.
My whole life, I've done
everything to the nines.
I don't even go
to the grocery store
without lipstick
or pumps on.
But after sowing the seeds of
this empire with my bare hands...
She's a multi‐hyphenate that has at
least gotten a callback on "Empire."
I'm just ready to have
a little fun and be free.
I don't even have any makeup on
under this thing.
Shh.
This legend is here to be
a vision of love on this stage.
‐ Vision of love.
Mariah Carey?
But what's love got to do
with it anyways?
Did it say something about
what's love got to do with it?
‐ There was.
‐ Tina Turner.
Mariah Carey.
‐ Angela Bassett.
Good, good.
Good call, Nicole.
Here we go, pretty lady.
♪ Tumble out of bed and I
stumble through the kitchen ♪
♪ Pour myself a cup
of ambition ♪
♪ Yawn and stretch
and try to come alive ♪
♪ Jump in the shower
and the blood starts pumping ♪
♪ Out on the streets,
the traffic starts jumping ♪
♪ Folks like me on the job
from 9 to 5 ♪
♪ Working 9 to 5 ♪
♪ What a way
to make a living ♪
♪ Barely getting by ♪
♪ It's all taking
and no giving ♪
Wow!
♪ They just use your mind ♪
♪ And they never
give you credit ♪
♪ It's enough to drive you ♪
♪ Crazy if you let it ♪
♪ 9 to 5 ♪
♪ Full service and devotion ♪
♪ You would think that I ♪
♪ Would deserve
a fair promotion ♪
♪ Want to move ahead ♪
♪ But the boss won't seem
to let me ♪
♪ I swear sometimes
that man is out to get me ♪
Whoo!
Yes!
‐ ♪ Working 9 to 5 ♪
‐
Wow!
We're not worthy!
‐ We're not worthy!
‐ We're not worthy.
I think we just witnessed being
in the presence of greatness.
‐ That was unbelievable.
‐ Wow.
- ‐ Flower! Flower!
- I think I might be
a little nervous,
I'm just saying.
I'm a little starstruck
with all that voice
- ‐ coming out of the Flower.
- Yeah.
Jenny, you're‐‐
you're speechless.
I am so speechless,
but I just want to say
I am so incredibly blown away
by your beautiful,
soulful voice.
It's just magical.
‐ Amazing job.
‐ Wow.
This is my favorite genre
of music‐‐ heavy petal.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you so much, Ken.
Like, seriously,
that voice is so legendary,
as you referred to yourself.
It was such
a classic performance.
I don't even know how you could
hit those notes with all of that.
Hey, Ruth Bader Ginsburg
can do what she wants,
all right?
‐ That's all I'm saying.
‐ All right, panel,
are you picking up
on any clues
from the performance
or the package?
Okay, so what I got out
of the clues
was clothing, crafts, cooking,
and then "empire."
That really stuck out for me.
So of course,
I thought immediately
Taraji P. Henson from "Empire."
You don't
think she can sing like that?
Not up there. ‐ I agree.
I don't think it's an actress.
Just going off of the clue package
at first, "vision of love,"
so I thought
of Mariah Carey, um‐‐
Why do you think we've been
holding hands the whole time?
♪ Reunited and it feels
so good ♪
So, obviously,
it's not Mariah.
No. ‐ So then after
I heard the performance,
I knew it was someone
extremely soulful,
has a wicked,
a stratospheric range.
I thought I heard Patti
LaBelle's voice in there.
You know what?
You might be right, 'cause
when I was listening to it,
at the beginning
of the performance,
I had an handful of names
that I thought it could be
in the lower register.
But once she got to the end
and she hit those big notes,
hit those high notes,
there's only a few people
in the world of popular music
that I think could even hit those notes.
It's Jennifer Hudson.
‐ And then maybe Jessie J. from
the younger‐‐ ‐ Jenny: Jessie J.
You know,
from a younger generation.
Good guess.
She can hit those notes.
‐ She can hit those notes.
‐ That's a good guess, too.
‐ She can.
‐ That's an amazing wrong guess.
With a voice like that
and a flower outfit like that,
I'm going with Bjork.
You are Bjork!
You are Bjork.
Bjork wears flowers.
I get it.
Tweet it and hashtag it.
Ken says Bjork.
- ‐ It's so obvious!
- All right, panel,
it's definitely
question time.
Miss Flower,
what makes you the Flower?
That's right.
‐ She does, she does.
‐ Did that help you guys at all?
‐ Yes! You're a legend, Bjork.
‐ No one?
‐ No.
All right, that was
an amazing performance.
Keep it going one more time
for the Flower.
Our panel thought
one of these celebrities
might be under
the Flower mask.
Who do you think it is?
Well,
that was nerve‐wracking.
I never looked at the judges
because I was so nervous
when I was singing.
But at the end of the song,
when I saw everyone standing up,
I just felt so special.
She could still hit
those notes in that mask.
‐ Yeah.
‐ I was blown away.
That's the power of Bjork.
That's‐‐ she got
Bjork strength, man.
Coming up...
‐ ♪ ♪
What a voice.
...the masked insanity
continues.
Only Raven‐Symoné
grabs butt like that.
And later, one singer's
secret identity is revealed.
My gosh! My gosh!
♪ Who is that? ♪
We're back on
"The Masked Singer,"
ladies and gentlemen.
Now, how can you follow up
an iconic, legendary Flower
singing "9 To 5"?
With an Eagle serving up
some tasty Meatloaf.
Pay close attention.
Here are some clues
about the Eagle.
Good afternoon, class. Today we'll
be learning about me, the Eagle.
Studious and intelligent,
I have soared to great heights
as the face of my field.
‐ ‐ But now,
after a serious health scare
and the loss of a parent...
‐ Health scare, loss of a parent.
‐ Aww.
...I've realized
that life is too short
‐ to let my dreams fly by.
‐
I've spent so much time
listening to other
people's stories,
that I've neglected
writing my own.
Definitely maybe someone
that interviews people.
What about, like,
a Jimmy Fallon?
It's time to leave
the safety of my nest behind.
He's wearing a red bandana.
Is it Kid Rock?
I'm gonna prove I don't just
hang out with rock stars,
I am one.
‐ Radio host, talk show host.
‐ Yeah. Howard Stern.
He does have
Howard Stern legs.
♪ I would do anything
for love ♪
♪ But I won't do that ♪
♪ Some days it don't
come easy ♪
♪ Some days
it don't come hard ♪
♪ Some days it don't
come at all ♪
♪ These are the days
that never end ♪
♪ Some nights
I'm breathing fire ♪
I'm carved in ice ♪
♪ Some nights are like nothing
I've ever seen before ♪
♪ Or will again ♪
♪ And maybe I'm crazy ♪
♪ It's crazy
and it's true ♪
♪ I know you can save me ♪
♪ No one else can save me
now but you ♪
♪ As long as the planets
are turning ♪
♪ As long as the stars
are burning ♪
♪ As long as your dreams
are coming true ♪
♪ You better believe it,
that I would do ♪
♪ Anything for love ♪
♪ I would do anything
for love ♪
♪ But I won't do that ♪
♪ No, I won't do ♪
♪ I would do anything
for love ♪
♪ Anything you've been
dreaming of ♪
♪ But I just won't ♪
♪ Do that ♪
♪ No ♪
Yes, come on!
The Eagle has landed.
Eagle! Eagle!
Don't run over
the person, Eagle.
Ken, make some sense
out of this, man.
For an eagle,
it was amazing.
But I don't think
you're a trained singer.
What is he doing?
‐ ‐
He doesn't like that.
Eagle, where are you going?
He's like, "Hold me back, Nick.
Hold me back."
Well, you know, what's great is, like,
some of us have big voices
from out of this world,
and some of us need
to just find a way
to put on a great performance,
a great show.
‐ Exactly. Yeah. ‐ You came out, you
were in character the whole time.
‐ Where are you going?
‐ Be careful.
It seemed like you were kind of
throwing your talking voice
‐ by singing in an operatic tone.
‐ Right?
And when he had a chance at the end
to do something with the last note,
he went...
‐ ♪ No ♪
‐ Nicole: No, he didn't.
No, he didn't.
He did a slight crescendo.
He started out sotto voce, and
then he did a slight crescendo,
which added
a little bravado.
Listen to the singers.
Nicole, and clues that
you were picking up on
from this
vibrant personality?
Yeah, there was, like,
there was an older television
at the beginning of the package,
so it made me think
that it's somebody
a little bit more mature.
‐ No! ‐ Whoever it is,
they are hilarious.
I went off of the red bandana.
I mean, it might be
too obvious,
but I was thinking
who wears red bandanas?
Bret Michaels from Poison
is always rocking.
Bret Michaels,
not a bad idea.
You know, there was the health
scare, there's loss of parent,
and also, you know,
a rock star personality.
But I'm thinking Pauly Shore.
Pauly recently
lost his mother, so...
True. That's a good guess.
I'm getting some radio vibes
here because that clue of
listens to people's stories,
"now it's time to tell mine,"
makes me feel like
you've interviewed people.
‐ Yeah. ‐ And I kinda thought you
had the legs of Howard Stern
Yeah,
that's what I was thinking.
All right.
I was thinking that.
Or I was gonna say Adam Carolla
was the other radio DJ.
That's not a bad guess.
Ken, you look like
you have something to say.
I think you guys
are all wrong.
You do interview people
for a living.
You do listen to people.
You're very funny.
You're very witty.
I've been on your show. It sounds
like you're Craig Ferguson.
And Craig wears
jackets like this.
‐ He kind of walks around. He struts
like an eagle. ‐ Craig Ferguson?
‐ You're so wrong.
‐ Dude, I'm so smart!
Eagle,
what makes you the Eagle?
Like an eagle,
I can see things miles away
that other people may not see.
‐ ‐ Did that
help you guys at all?
The voice helped
a little bit, yeah.
‐ It's not Pauly Shore.
‐ No, it's not Pauly Shore.
Definitely not
Pauly Shore.
One thing we do know, the Eagle
definitely took over this stage.
I can't control him.
The Eagle reminds me
a lot like my comedy.
He's trying too hard.
Our panel thought
one of these celebrities
might be under the Eagle mask.
Who do you think it is?
Now it's time for our panel
and our studio audience
to vote and tell us who won this
first face‐off of the night.
The winner will keep it on
and sing another day.
The other will get a second
chance in our smackdown.
The results are in.
And the winner is...
the Flower!
♪ If I was you,
I'd wanna be me, too ♪
‐ Yes!
‐ Flower, congrats to you.
‐ Aww. ‐ You are moving on
and singing another day.
Who can go up against
the Flower? No one.
All right, all right.
We're not done
with you yet, Mr. Eagle.
You are coming back for the
smackdown that's coming up.
But right now it's time for you to
fly on back there. Get outta here.
We love you, Eagle!
- ‐ Eagle! Eagle!
- Aww.
‐ Ooh.
‐ That's a great guess.
And now we have a face‐off
between a very chill,
but formally dressed creature
and a more down to earth
showbiz animal
who should feel very at home
on this network.
Begin the march
of the Penguin.
♪ I can make your hands clap ♪
‐
‐ My gosh!
♪ I can make your hands clap ♪
Foxy ladies and gentlemen,
the Fox.
♪ When I'm walking with you ♪
♪ I watch
the whole room change ♪
♪ Baby, that's what you do ♪
‐ Wow! ‐ Look at that.
He's got a cane!
‐ It's Jamie Foxx. ‐ Jamie
Foxx from "Robin Hood."
And now, America,
let's learn more about a bird
who only flies when it sings,
the Penguin.
Penguins are incredibly
expressive birds,
so it's in my DNA to strive
for my voice to be heard.
My whole life, I've been told
I'm not pretty enough,
not smart enough,
not funny enough.
Clearly this bird
did not get the word
that her career is over.
That's so sad.
But life isn't always
black and white.
‐ Comedy club owner.
‐ Comedian.
On this stage,
I'm gonna sing for those of us
who dare to be different.
And trust me,
I don't need a permission slip
from anyone to be who I am.
‐ "I'm not your secretary." ‐
Jenna Fischer from "The Office."
I'm leading the march.
Who's with me?
Ca‐caw! Ca‐caw!
You know what's gonna throw us
is the fact that she said
her career was over.
It could be someone that just had
a lot of setbacks and obstacles.
I mean, that's hard
because in Hollywood,
let's face it, who hasn't?
♪ Take a seat ♪
♪ Right over there,
sat on a chair ♪
♪ Stay or leave ♪
♪ The cabinets are bare
and I'm unaware ♪
♪ Of just how we got
into this mess ♪
♪ Got so aggressive ♪
♪ I know we had
all good intentions ♪
♪ So pull me closer ♪
♪ Why don't you
pull me close? ♪
♪ Why don't you come on over? ♪
♪ I just can't let you go ♪
‐ ♪ Baby ♪
‐ Whoo!
♪ Why don't you just meet me
in the middle? ♪
♪ In the middle ♪
♪ Looking at you,
I can't lie ♪
♪ Just pouring out admission ♪
♪ Regardless of my objection ♪
♪ And it's not about
my pride ♪
♪ I need you on my skin ♪
♪ Just come over,
pull me in just ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Why don't you just
meet me in the middle? ♪
♪ In the middle ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Why don't you just meet me
in the middle, baby? ♪
♪ I'm losing my mind
just a little ♪
♪ So why don't you just
meet me in the middle? ♪
♪ Middle, in the middle ♪
♪ Middle ♪
Yes! Come on!
‐ Good job.
‐ Come on!
Good job.
‐ Wow. The Penguin.
Nicole, tell the Penguin
about her performance.
I think the performance
was great.
You came out strong, confident.
Though you may not do this as
a profession, right? Singing.
And I'm sure you were out
of your comfort zone,
but you still looked like
you had so much fun up there.
Yeah, great attitude.
Now, I definitely
was picking up on some clues.
Robin Thicke,
did you pick up on any?
The thing that I really picked up
on that might be a hidden clue
is Penguin, to me,
dances like Melissa McCarthy.
Have you ever seen
Melissa McCarthy dance?
It's my cousin, so, yeah.
I don't know. You know, I saw
the sign "not your secretary,"
so I was thinking maybe
Megan Mullally
plays a secretary on
"Will & Grace."
I agree with Nicole. ‐
Jenny: I think that's a good guess.
‐ Yeah. ‐ But the clues that I
heard that I was like, ""
Voice to be heard.
Not pretty, not funny.
Her career was over.
All those things kind of led me
to a, like, a Kathy Griffin.
You also marched,
kind of an activist.
‐ That's a good one. ‐ But then
I heard a tone in her voice
that made me go, God, for the second
season I'm gonna be saying this,
but it sounds like
Sherri Shepherd.
You know, knowing Sherri's
voice, I just don't‐‐
it didn't sound vocally like her
at all, you know what I mean?
‐ Well, to me it did.
‐ Yeah? Okay.
You said that last season and I said
that Sherri Shepherd would grab my butt.
‐ I did. Yes.
‐ Yep, you did.
And it was actually Ricki Lake
grabbing my butt.
That's right.
‐!
Well, let's hear from
the Penguin, shall we?
What makes you the Penguin?
Everything is not
as black and white
as it seems.
Maybe someone
who's colorblind?
Did that help you at all?
‐ Not at all, Nick Cannon.
Nick, do you know
who it is?
I'm catching a vibe.
That's all I'm saying.
Ladies and gentlemen,
one more time for the Penguin!
Our panel thought
one of these celebrities
might be behind
that Penguin mask.
Who do you think it is?
Only Raven‐Symoné
grabs butt like that.
‐ Raven‐Sym‐‐ ‐ Raven‐Symoné's a
good‐‐ that's a good guess, too.
That's a good guess.
This experience is so crazy.
I feel so good.
I don't feel
any judgment at all.
I'm just by myself being who
I've always dreamt of being.
Coming up, our final
furry singer makes his debut.
‐ Anthony Mackie.
‐ Wesley Snipes.
‐ I think it's Jamie Foxx.
‐ What?
‐ We're not on the same page?
‐ No!
‐ And later...
‐ Take it off!
Show us who you are.
‐ Whoo!
‐ Who is it?
Take it off!
I did not see
this coming at all.
Here we go.
‐
♪ Together ♪
‐ ♪ You whether ♪
‐ Sing it, baby.
‐ ♪ Whether ♪
‐ Come on, Ken.
‐ ♪ Times are good or bad ♪
‐ Hit that note, baby.
‐ ♪ Happy or sad ♪
‐ Wow.
‐ ♪ Let's ♪
‐ Ken can sing.
♪ Hidden talent
from Kendrick Jeong ♪
Your falsetto's stronger
than your regular voice.
Hey, you know what?
That's‐‐ hey, hey.
"Ken, can you just do
the rest of the series
in your falsetto?"
"Hey, guys, great job!"
‐ ♪ Who is that? ♪
‐ Welcome back to
a TV sensation
that's all pleasure
and absolutely no guilt,
"The Masked Singer."
‐ Whoo!
Right now we're in the middle
of a very tense face‐off
between a high‐flying singer
and someone who's,
gonna be foxy.
Let's make way for the Fox.
Are you ready for your
bedtime story, little one?
Ooh, a fairy tale fox.
All right, here we go.
Chapter one.
Foxes are clever
and nocturnal,
and I've definitely done
my best work at night.
‐ "Best work at night." ‐ A
lot of singers sing at night.
I dabbled in many
different genres.
From "Doogie" to "Doubtfire,"
I've laughed with them all.
"Doogie" and "Doubtfire."
It could be that he worked
with Robin Williams
and Neil Patrick Harris.
Over the years,
I've lived two different lives.
There's my on‐air
superhero persona,
who lives to entertain,
and then there's the real me,
who I am when I'm at home.
‐ Who's an on‐air superhero?
‐ David Letterman.
But under this mask,
my two identities
can finally become one.
Wish me luck tonight,
little fox.
Look how he stands.
It's like a dancer's stance.
Yeah.
♪ I was so high,
I did not recognize ♪
♪ The fire burning
in her eyes ♪
♪ The chaos that controlled
my mind ♪
♪ Whispered good‐bye
as she got on a train ♪
♪ Never to return again ♪
♪ Always in my heart ♪
♪ This love has taken
its toll on me ♪
♪ I have no choice ♪
♪ 'Cause I won't say
good‐bye anymore ♪
‐ Whoo!
‐ ♪ ♪
♪ I'll take these
broken things ♪
♪ Repair your broken wings ♪
♪ Into every part ♪
♪ 'Cause I know that's what
you want me to do ♪
♪ This love has taken
its toll on me ♪
♪ Baby, ♪
‐ ♪ She said good‐bye too many
times before ♪ ‐ Come on!
♪ Too many times before ♪
♪ Her heart is breaking
in front of me ♪
♪ I have no choice ♪
♪ 'Cause I won't say
good‐bye anymore ♪
♪ This love ♪
- My God.
- Yeah.
Wow, what a voice.
Fox! Fox! Fox!
Swagged out.
Giving us some soul up here.
Nicole, tell the Fox
about his performance.
‐ He is a natural. He knows‐‐
‐ Don't you think he's got some
Tony Awards
on his shelf at home?
I don't know
if he has Tony Awards
or he has some
platinum records as well.
Because he can sing,
he's so cool,
and he was effortless
the whole time.
True indeed.
Mr. Robin Thicke,
were you picking up
on any clues
from the performance
or the package?
He moved like
a professional performer.
Could be Broadway. He could
have been in a band before.
I didn't recognize
the voice right off enough
to think it was a solo singer.
But he could be more like
a band member
who knows how
to hit the beat,
knows how to land
at the right step.
I don't know. I mean, he seemed
like a solo performer to me.
‐ Yeah. ‐ You've got your voice.
You've got the talent.
You've got the "it" power,
so the clues that I took
that are really kinda going...
is the superhero on‐air,
working at night,
double life, very successful.
And then I kept thinking of,
like, who would that be?
Like, a Wesley Snipes
in "Blade."
I don't know
if he can sing though.
I don't know if his thighs
look like that.
Um, and then
I heard the voice,
and I was like
that's a Broadway.
That's like a Tony Award,
Leslie Odom, Jr.,
"Hamilton" voice, you know?
‐ No. It's not Leslie. ‐ You don't
think it's Leslie Odom, Jr.?
I don't think
that's Leslie's voice.
I was thinking someone from
the "Hamilton" cast possibly.
Then I was thinking
with the superhero,
I was thinking Anthony Mackie
vibes from "Captain America."
That's a good guess,
and he's a superhero.
- ‐ People don't know he can sing.
- He did say also
two identities to become one,
so this could be
his hidden talent
that he's unleashing
upon us right now.
Yeah. That's a good point.
Ken, you look perplexed.
I mean...
I'm really trying
to think right now.
You're a doctor, come on!
Shut up, Nick Cannon.
Let me think.
I think you are
an accomplished actor
who many people
don't know sings.
And I don't know if
you're in a superhero movie,
but I know that if you're
the person who I think it is,
he may have been in
a "Fast and Furious" movie.
He may have been in a "Transformers"
movie that I was a part of.
I think you're Tyrese Gibson.
Great to see you again, Tyrese.
Welcome to "The Masked Singer."
- Tyrese.
Thank you, Nick.
The way your look‐‐
vote of confidence
really helped me out.
‐ That ain't Tyrese.
‐ Mr. Fox,
you got us all guessing.
What makes you the Fox?
Well, I'm quick,
I refuse to be caged in,
and I'm crafty.
- ‐ Man. I know who that is.
- Crafty?
‐ You do?
‐ Yes, I do.
‐ I think I got it.
‐ I got it, I got it.
‐ Did that help you at all?
‐ What? Crafty and caged in?
‐ That helps? ‐ It just all
start clicking for me.
Yeah, I mean, it doesn't
fit the clue package,
but I think it's Jamie Foxx.
I think it's Jamie Foxx.
You just sound like Jamie F‐‐
‐ We're not on the same page?
‐ No!
‐ I thought we were on the same page!
‐ No! Abandoning you.
It sounded a little like
Jamie's tone at some point.
‐ Now I'm really confused. ‐ Well, one
thing we can definitely pick up on
is it was
an amazing performance.
Ladies and gentlemen,
a skilled performer.
‐ Who is the Fox? ‐ I have
no idea who this could be.
It's driving me crazy.
Our panel thought
one of these celebrities
might be under the Fox mask.
Tell us who you think it is
by using the hashtag
"The Masked Singer."
All right, it's time for the
audience and the panel to vote
for the singer who they want
to see perform again.
Vote for your favorite now.
Who will live to sing
another day
and who will keep
their mask on?
‐ The votes are in.
‐ Penguin! Penguin!
‐ I don't like this part. ‐ And
the winner of this face‐off is...
...the Fox!
♪ We out here dripping
in finesse ♪
♪ It don't make no sense ♪
‐ Whoo!
‐ I feel so bad.
Congratulations, Fox.
You get to continue
in this crazy competition.
Back to the lair with you.
Now, Penguin,
you will go head‐to‐head
with the Eagle
in our smackdown.
So go ahead
and lick your wounds
and get ready to sing
for your anonymity, all right?
‐ Penguin! Penguin!
‐ Yes, girl! Yes!
When we come back,
get ready for a smackdown
between Eagle and Penguin,
and the unmasking
of a famous face.
Don't miss the madness.
♪ Who is that? ♪
Welcome back
to "The Masked Singer."
Tonight, we've seen
the journey of an eagle,
a flower, a penguin,
and a fox.
But the Eagle or the Penguin
is about to learn
that not every fairy tale
has a happy ending,
because one of them
will be unmasked
at the end of the show.
How will that be decided?
This is the smackdown‐down!
Whoo!
‐ The smackdown, Ken!
‐ My cheek!
My precious cheek!
‐ That's right.
‐ My other cheek!
In this mouth,
a monogamous bird
that can fly anywhere it wants
and not just Philadelphia,
the Eagle!
‐ Jay Mohr had a radio show.
‐ Jay Mohr is not a bad guess.
Right there. Over there.
There you go.
And in this mouth,
a flightless bird that breeds
in large colonies
up to a thousand,
the Penguin!
- ‐ Yeah! Yes, girl! Yes!
- Yes!
Yeah!
‐ I have no idea who that is.
‐ She's funny.
I'm feeling comedian.
You guys know the rules.
We want a good, clean,
but slightly still
nasty fight, all right?
Get ready to sing
for your lives.
Eagle, you're up first.
Three, two, one.
- ‐ Smackdown!
- ‐
♪ You keep saying you've
got something for me ♪
Get it, Eagle! Get it!
♪ Something you call love,
but confess ♪
♪ You've been messing ♪
♪ Where you shouldn't
have been messing, yeah ♪
♪ Now someone else
is getting all your best ♪
My God, yes!
‐ Jeff Foxworthy. ‐ ♪ These
boots are made for walking ♪
♪ And that's just what
they'll do ♪
♪ One of these days
these boots ♪
♪ Are gonna walk
all over you ♪
Ooh! ‐ Eagle!
Eagle!
The Eagle's boots is walking
all over the Penguin's face!
- ‐ Penguin, you up.
- ‐
♪ Give it to me,
I'm worth it ♪
‐ Aah!
‐ ♪ Baby, I'm worth it ♪
‐ ♪ Give it to me ♪
‐ Robin: ‐
♪ I see you
in the spot like ♪
♪ Ooh, I love your style ♪
‐ Whoa! ‐ ♪ ‐
show me what you got ♪
♪ Now, come on,
make it worth your while ♪
‐ Give it to me.
‐ ♪ Baby, baby, I'm worth it ♪
Get it!
‐ ♪ Baby, I'm worth it ♪
♪ Come on, I'm worth it ♪
‐ Whoo!
‐ ♪ Baby, baby, I'm worth it ♪
♪ Give it to me,
I'm worth it ♪
♪ Come on, I'm worth it ♪
♪ Give it to me,
I'm worth it ♪
My gosh!
She just karate kicked him!
♪ Give it to me,
I'm worth it ♪
‐ My goodness!
You are definitely worth it
and working it.
‐ Fierce, baby.
‐ Wow!
She went all ninja.
That was unbelievable.
It was like a weird episode
of "Angry Birds"
just watching you guys.
But I gotta tell you,
both of you guys are hilarious.
I thought you both
sounded awesome.
And, Sherri,
I hope you make it through.
My gosh!
That penguin got happy feet.
We just went from
"March Of The Penguins"
to twerk of
the penguins up there.
- ‐ She was dropping it low.
- Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
And, Eagle,
I'm completely thrown.
The first performance was
giving me, like, a rich tone.
And for some reason, I was like, "If
Jeff Goldblum was an eagle on this show,
maybe that would be him."
But the tone changed a little,
so I don't know.
I'm here for both of you.
‐ Both birds. ‐ All right,
now, panel, enough talk.
Time to vote.
Who will win this smackdown
and keep their
secret identity from us?
And who's heading home
to someplace
that's probably pretty sweet?
We'll find out
after the break.
The winner who gets
to keep it on is...
‐ ...the Penguin!
‐ Yes! Yes!
Congratulations, Penguin.
You're still in this thing.
Go ahead
and strut your stuff
back to the South Pole‐‐
wherever penguins live.
Penguin came for Eagle.
She's a fighter, man.
She is a fighter.
‐ And she's funny.
‐ I get comedian, definitely.
Eagle, we're sorry
you are going home.
But we are super excited
to see who you really are.
But first, panel, again,
any guesses
of whose famous face
is about to be revealed?
‐ This was a tough one for us.
‐ Yeah, tough one.
‐ I have no idea.
‐ I'm kind of just stuck
on the listening
to people's stories,
finally telling my own.
So that makes me think
of a talk show host,
a radio host.
I came up with Howard Stern.
Then the other side of me
said Adam Carolla.
I am so lost, but if
I'm gonna throw it out there,
I'm just gonna say
Adam Carolla.
I agree. There's a few
things that stand out,
like the, you know,
had a recent health scare,
listen to people's stories,
has a rock star type
of personality.
Howard Stern is definitely
one of those kind of people
and recently went through
a health scare.
And then I thought
Montel Williams,
who is also a talk show host
who recently struggled
with MS.
But because of the height
and the rock star,
‐ I'm gonna go Howard Stern.
‐ Wow.
Ken, you look like
a mastermind.
You look like
an evil villain up there.
He is.
‐ You know exactly who this is.
It really‐‐ just trying to put
all the clues together,
obviously a talk show host
with a great stage presence,
great charisma.
Someone who's really got
incredible comedic chops.
I'm just gonna have to
double down on Craig Ferguson.
He's doubling down.
‐ On the Scottish man.
Why would a Scottish man
pick an American eagle?
Will you just shut
your hole, Robin?
Miss Scherzinger? ‐ I‐‐
first, going off of the obvious,
the red bandana
and the health scare
and the classic rock vibes,
I was thinking Bret Michaels
from Poison.
‐ Rock on, Eagle. ‐ But then on the
smackdown, the tone changed a little.
‐ It did change. ‐ And I was
feeling Jeff Foxworthy.
- Which isn't bad.
- Not a bad guess.
Studies show most people
in bandanas are named Jeff.
Nice.
‐ That's a medical fact.
‐ A medical fact from the doctor.
‐ Fact, guys. Fact.
And, Eagle,
you're welcome to give
any of these guys the bird.
That's all. Just saying.
We needed one more pun.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Okay, panel,
you've made your final guesses.
Now let's see
if any of you are right.
And I'm dying to know
who this is.
Eagle, show us
who you really are.
Take it off.
‐ Yes!
Take it off! Take it off!
‐ ♪ Who, who, who, who? ♪
‐ Take it off! Take it off!
‐ ♪ Who are you? ♪
‐ Who is it?
♪ Who, who, who, who? ♪
‐ Take it off, Eagle!
‐ ♪ Who? ♪
‐ ♪ I really want to know ♪
‐ My gosh! My gosh!
‐ ♪ Who are you, you, you? ♪
♪ Are you? ♪
It's Dr. Drew!
‐ No way!
From "Loveline."
30 years, Jenny!
From one doctor
to another doctor!
Didn't see that coming at all.
I did not see
this coming at all.
‐ I was so close. I was so close.
‐ I know!
You've spent
a lot of your career
talking to rock stars,
helping them out.
How did it feel to finally
become a rock star on stage?
‐ Very bizarre.
‐ We're doctors, man.
Ken, how about you used to
fill in for me?
I filled in for you
on "Loveline."
You did. ‐ But how about
Jenny getting Adam Carolla?
I know!
‐ You got so close.
How did I not‐‐ so close.
I actually thought
"Loveline," Adam Carolla.
I never thought Dr. Drew
as this rock and roll performer.
‐ There he is! Dr. Drew!
‐!
‐ You are so sexy, Drew.
‐ Yeah.
I'm serious.
You look amazing.
Well, you should have
put me through!
I can't believe it.
The artist formerly known
as the Eagle, Dr. Drew!
♪ I would do anything
for love ♪
♪ Anything you've been
dreaming of ♪
♪ But I just won't ♪
♪ Do that ♪