The global singing
phenomenon is back.
Can you guess the celebrities
behind the masks?
Our secret stars have
42 Grammy nods, 140 films.
They also have 29 children,
28 tattoos, and 8 divorces.
Yeah, that's great.
Sensational performances...
♪ Baby, I'm sorry,
not sorry ♪
‐ Come on!
‐ That's the way to win a show.
‐ ♪ Do you wanna go ♪
‐ ...tougher clues...
The queens of the world
taught me
how to be a lady.
‐ I'm more confused than normal.
‐ Wow.
...and a crack panel
of celebrity detectives.
‐ Who is it?
‐ I have no idea!
Why am I even asking you?
Because I'm out of my mind!
♪ This is the greatest show ♪
Each week, the celebrities
compete to stay anonymous.
‐ Whoo! ‐ Jenny: I have no
idea who the heck you are,
but your voice
is unbelievable.
The weakest performers
are eliminated...
‐ Take it off!
‐ ...and unmasked.
‐ My God!
‐
Last week, Egg and Ice Cream
were eaten up
by the competition.
Olympic figure skater
Johnny Weir!
Gamer, Twitch superstar,
and YouTuber!
- ‐ It's Ninja.
- It's Ninja!
Tonight, the saga continues
with group C,
Black Widow versus Leopard
and Flamingo versus Panda,
and another famous face
is revealed.
Your favorite
musical mystery starts...
‐ Martha Stewart.
‐ ...right...
‐ Rick Springfield.
‐ ...now.
This is even harder
than last year.
♪ Who are you? ♪
♪ Who, who, who, who? ♪
‐ Whoo!
♪ Who are you? ♪
♪ Who, who, who, who? ♪
‐ Who is it?
‐ Wow!
Come on.
Welcome to the hit show
that keeps the whole world
guessing who are you,
"The Masked Singer."
‐ Whoo!
I'm Nick Cannon,
and some of my best
celebrity friends
may be masked singers
because this season
they have 42 Grammy nominations,
21 platinum records,
35 number one hits, and are
worth a reported $287 million.
Wow!
Give or take some change.
So how are we gonna figure out
who they are?
We have some help
from our famous panel.
‐ ‐‐ Ladies and
gentlemen, Nicole Scherzinger.
Yes!
‐ Dr. Ken Jeong.
‐ Whoo! Yes, sprinkle.
‐ Jenny McCarthy Wahlberg.
‐ Hey.
‐ And Robin Thicke.
‐ Hey!
Thank you, guys.
All right, after an amazing
season premiere, we are back.
Tonight we got four more stars
trying to keep
their identity a secret
and a brand new flashy floor.
You see this? Look at that.
Yeah, flashy floor!
That's what happens
when you get a hit show.
You get a nice new floor.
Look what it does.
I look like I'm standing on
a waterfall right now.
My God. That's so‐‐
Or a field.
Whoo! Whoa!
Or maybe I want something thick
like Robin with wavy hair.
Yeah. Yeah.
Whoa! Whoo!
‐ That's where it all started.
‐ I like that look.
All right,
let's get off of Robin
‐ and get on with the show.
‐ My God.
Tonight, we will see four new
celebrity singers perform two by two.
After each face‐off,
the studio audience and panel
will vote for their favorite
performance,
and the winners will get
to sing another day.
The loser of each face‐off
will perform again
in the smackdown.
The panel will then decide
who they want to see again,
and the loser will be unmasked
and sent packing.
Are you guys ready for
our next group of weirdoes?
Tonight we've got Black Widow
versus Leopard.
Then the Flamingo
versus Panda.
‐ Watch out.
‐ Watch out, man.
Enter the Black Widow.
♪ I'm gonna love you ♪
♪ Until you hate me ♪
♪ You should've known better ♪
- Wow!
- Whoa!
My God,
that is incredible!
♪ I'm gonna lie to you ♪
‐ ♪ I'm gonna lie to you ♪
‐ Like a black widow samurai.
♪ Like a black widow, baby ♪
‐ Wow. ‐ She has dancer
legs, Robin, doesn't she?
‐ She's got dancing legs.
‐ All right, free the Leopard.
♪ Free your mind ♪
♪ And the rest will follow ♪
Wow!
Man,
she's gonna be a pro.
Wow.
‐ ♪ Don't be so shallow ♪
‐ She's tall.
‐ ♪ Free your mind ♪
‐ ♪ And the rest will follow ♪
‐ I love it.
‐ ♪ Be colorblind ♪
‐ Very elaborate.
‐ ♪ Don't be so shallow ♪
‐ Wow, look at that costume.
♪ Free your mind ♪
All right, let's see if
we can free some clues
from the spider's web.
I'm the Black Widow
because like me,
they hide in plain sight.
And when they strike,
you know it.
Frankly, I've been packaged
my entire life.
I think a Sagittarius?
Is that what that sign was?
And after years of living
in the public eye,
you're in my house now.
Welcome to my empire.
Mwah‐ha‐ha‐ha!
Empire? Is it Oprah?
And now I get to be here to share
the real threads of who I am.
So consider this
the director's cut of my life...
Director's cut.
She's an actor.
...where you'll find
I'm a little edgier, darker,
and more alien
than you know me to be...
She's a lot edgier, so it's
probably a fluffy persona.
...maybe what you'd find
in the deleted scenes.
You better believe
on this stage,
I'm gonna be good as hell.
‐ Looks like Sherri Shepherd's
voluptuousness. ‐ It does.
That was the first thing
I thought.
♪ Clock strikes upon the hour ♪
♪ And the sun begins
to fade ♪
♪ Still enough time
to figure out ♪
♪ How to chase my blues away ♪
♪ I've done all right
up till now ♪
♪ There's a light of day
that shows me how ♪
♪ And when the night falls ♪
♪ My lonely heart calls ♪
♪ I wanna dance
with somebody ♪
♪ I wanna feel the heat
♪ Yeah, I wanna dance
with somebody ♪
♪ With somebody who loves me ♪
♪ Somebody who ♪
♪ Someone who loves me ♪
‐ Whoo!
‐ ♪ I need a man ♪
♪ To take a chance ♪
♪ On a love that burns
hot enough to last ♪
♪ And when the night falls ♪
♪ My lonely heart calls ♪
♪ I wanna dance
with somebody ♪
‐ Whoo! ‐ ♪ I wanna feel
the heat with somebody ♪
♪ Yeah, I wanna dance
with somebody ♪
♪ With somebody who loves me ♪
♪ Don't you wanna dance,
say you wanna dance ♪
dance ♪
Yes! My God!
You killed it!
I think I've been bit
by the Black Widow.
What a great way
to open the show. Come on!
Wow. You
rocked the stage, Black Widow.
Jenny, talk to her
about her performance.
I am so blown away. This is
the first time this season
I've gotten the chills
all over my body.
That's how amazing
your voice was.
The fact that you came out
with your first song
and choosing
a Whitney Houston song says,
‐ "Listen, I know what
I'm doing." ‐ Yes.
‐ "This is what I do
for a living." ‐ Yep.
‐ "And I am here to win."
‐ Whoo!
This season has been
absolutely outstanding
in terms of the quality of performances.
This is so strong.
I'm just completely
blown away.
Amazing job.
Are you picking up on any clues from
the performance or the package?
Definitely from
the clue package.
I saw a film slate, so that makes
me think she is an actress.
So I tried to connect some dots
and thought maybe a actress
that can sing like that.
Maybe from "Glee."
Amber Riley possibly?
- ‐ Amber can sing.
- That's a good guess.
Ken, you pick up
on any clues, doc?
I don't need
no more clues, Nick.
I know exactly who this is.
- ‐ ‐
- Okay, think about this.
You are an actor.
You played many different roles.
This may be one of
my castmates from "Community,"
- ‐ the first TV series I was on.
- ‐
My good friend,
Yvette Nicole Brown,
who was never able to express
her range on "Community,"
and everybody on the show
knew she was an amazing singer.
So, well done, Yvette.
I love you.
I'll see you at the aftershow.
That's a serious guess
from Dr. Ken.
I'm serious this year, Nick!
Well, Robin, we know that your
always in tune with the clues.
‐ What do you think? ‐ She moves
very nimble and very, you know, ‐‐
She just‐‐
‐ Dang. She be dropping it low.
‐ The masked squatter.
Yes, Nick! Come on, Nick!
Come on, Nick!
Whoo! ‐ Maybe it's
Cardi B after that move.
But no, the one thing
I got from the clues
was the darker and edgier
than we're used to,
so it might be somebody,
you know,
who's usually bubbly
on television‐‐
That's Yvette Nicole Brown, Robin Thicke.
That's what I said.
Last year we thought somebody
might have been
Sherri Shepherd for a while.
‐ Yvette Nicole Brown.
‐ And maybe she heard how much
we were saying her name
on the last year
and wanted to come on,
so, who knows?
‐ Yeah, exactly. ‐ Nick: That
is definitely a good guess.
All right, well, we should probably
hear from the Black Widow herself.
‐ Yes, please.
‐ Whoo!
‐ Yes!
‐ Yes.
What makes you
the Black Widow?
I like to hide
until it's time to feast.
"Hide until it's time
to feast"?
‐ I got nothing.
‐ That's Yvette Nicole Brown.
She'd play
hide and seek as a kid.
‐ And then‐‐ guys, it all makes sense.
‐ There it is.
Ladies and gentlemen,
one more time
for the Black Widow.
Our panel thought
one of these celebrities
might be under
the Black Widow mask.
Who do you think it is?
I was a little
nervous coming into it,
but to be able
to stand on stage,
nobody know my face and perform
like I've always wanted to
has brought me utter joy.
Coming up...
‐
‐ This is someone big. ‐ ...three
more electrified performances.
‐ Who is it? ‐ You look
so handsome, young man.
Leopard is hitting on me.
‐
‐ And later...
The time has come for
our masked moment of truth.
Take it off! Take it off!
No!
‐ My God.
‐ We totally got tricked.
‐ Love you, too. ‐ Aww,
she's got a crush on you.
I love you!
I love you, Mom!
‐ She said Jenny.
‐ I thought you said Kenny.
‐ Come on, come on.
‐ I thought it was a "K."
I hear what I want to hear.
I'm calling you Kenny
from now on.
♪ Who is that? ♪
We're back
on "The Masked Singer,"
where we meet the craziest
characters,
and I'm not even talking
about our panel.
Black Widow just went wild
with "I Wanna Dance
With Somebody."
Now let's all look closely
for any revealing spots
on the Leopard.
I am the Leopard
because I am adaptable
and can survive anywhere,
even under
the harshest conditions.
And I know what it's like
to be at the top.
In my career,
I've been a heavy‐hitter.
No one could catch me.
"Catch me"?
Are they a runner?
So, was a big star
at one point.
But now all anyone wants
to talk about
is the celebrity aspect.
Yeah, scandals.
You know, I really don't care
what they say about
what I'm wearing,
or even my relationships.
‐ Ooh, like a Katie Holmes. ‐
What about, like, Gwen Stefani?
Yeah. ‐ But now I'm
stripping away the headlines.
and everything that has come
to define me.
Behind this mask, I will show
the world why I have been
and will always be
the Leopard.
‐ Leopard is so tall.
‐ I know. She's an Amazon.
‐ This is someone big.
‐ Someone major.
Go, girl!
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, each morning I get up,
I die a little ♪
♪ Can barely stand
on my feet ♪
‐ ♪ Take a look at yourself ♪ ‐ ♪
Take a look in the mirror and cry ♪
‐ That's a guy!
‐ That's a man.
‐ Yeah, that's a man.
‐ That's a guy.
♪ Lord, what are you
doing to me? ♪
♪ I have spent all my years
believing you ♪
♪ But I just can't get
no relief ♪
‐ Beautiful.
‐ ♪ Lord, somebody ♪
‐ ♪ Somebody ♪
‐ ♪ Can anybody find me ♪
‐ ♪ Somebody to love ♪
‐ Yeah!
‐ It's amazing!
‐ ♪ He works hard ♪
♪ Every day ♪
♪ I try and I try
and I try ♪
♪ But everybody wants
to put me down ♪
♪ They say I'm going crazy ♪
♪ They say I got a lot
of water in my brain ♪
♪ I got no common sense ♪
♪ I got nobody left
to believe ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Find me somebody to love ♪
♪ Find me
somebody to love ♪
‐ ♪ Somebody ♪
♪ Can anybody find me ♪
Who is it?
♪ Somebody to ♪
♪ Love ♪
Yes!
‐ Come on!
‐ That is amazing.
I think we've all found
somebody to love.
It's the Leopard!
That was lovely.
‐ That was awesome.
- ‐ That was awesome!
- That was awesome.
You look so handsome,
young man.
Leopard is hitting on me.
‐ Nick, we totally got tricked.
‐ Really?
We thought it was a female.
It's obviously a man.
- It's a Leopard.
- ‐
‐ Rawr. ‐ Nicole, one Pussycat
performer to another.
With a voice like that,
there's somebody major
underneath
that Leopard costume.
Like, that was just so regal.
Your presence is so strong.
‐ Right. ‐ Darling, flattery
will get you everywhere.
Your voice is like‐‐
it's soulful.
‐ It's mature, it's seasoned. ‐ Keep
it coming, darling. Keep it coming.
Don't stop. Don't stop.
Robin, you're picking up
on clues.
‐ I know that look. ‐ Well, there's
a couple of things going on here.
At first, you know,
before I heard the voice,
I heard "heavy‐hitter" meaning
somebody who might have had
a lot of hits.
And now it's about,
"What am I wearing?"
So, I'm kinda catching,
like, a Billy Porter.
‐ Nice. ‐ Extra fashionable, like,
king of the Met Ball fashion.
And he likes to hold the mic
with two hands like that.
‐ ‐ Ken, you picking
up on any clues?
I know exactly
who this is,
as I always do.
Dr. Ken is in the house.
I think this is an obvious
pop star who has had many hits,
who's had celebrity scandal.
It might be someone from, like,
Take That in Britain.
It could be a Robbie Williams,
who had a lot of hits
and has had a resurgence,
been on Broadway,
‐ is an amazing actor, and I
see‐‐ ‐ Okay, hold on, Nick.
Well, you guys have talked about that
this person is a huge celebrity.
- ‐ But Robbie Williams is a huge celebrity.
- No, Robbie doesn't‐‐
‐ Sorry, Robbie. ‐ My idea of a huge
celebrity is like a Jamie Foxx.
Someone who's funny, who controls
their voice, who wants to trick us.
No, that's not Jamie Fo‐‐ Everybody knows
Jamie's favorite animal is the platypus.
Jamie would never go anywhere
near a leopard outfit.
All right, Leopard,
what makes you the Leopard?
Well, darling,
isn't is obvious?
Leopards can be fierce,
and yet, so divine.
‐ Fierce and divine? ‐ Wow,
you're a great help, Sherlock.
‐ So divine.
‐ I've got nothing.
‐ That's definitely Jamie Foxx.
‐ That didn't give you anything?
‐ Jamie Foxx is not that tall.
He's a friend.
He's not that tall.
How you you know
everyone's height, Ken?
'Cause I'm a doctor, Nick!
I'm a doctor.
All right.
He likes my tux.
You don't have‐‐
‐
‐ See?
‐ It's definitely Jamie Foxx.
‐ Thank you.
Keeping my distance
from this Leopard.
Get someone
from the zoo in HR.
Either way,
whoever you think it is,
we definitely know
it was an amazing performance.
‐ Amazing job, amazing job.
‐ Ladies and gentlemen.
You're a superstar.
Our panel thought that
one of these celebrities
might be under
the Leopard mask.
Who do you think it is?
All right, it's time for
our panel and studio audience
to decide who won
the first face‐off of the night.
Vote for your favorite now.
The winner will keep it on
and sing another day.
The other will get a second
chance in our smackdown.
‐ This is hard.
‐ It is hard. It's hard.
Okay, the votes are in.
And the winner
of this face‐off is...
Before the break, our panel
and studio audience voted
for who they want to see
sing on in the competition,
the Black Widow
or the Leopard.
The votes are in,
and the winner
of this face‐off is...
Black Widow!
♪ Black widow, baby ♪
Whoa!
Black Widow,
you get to keep it on.
Come on!
Black Widow, get outta here
before the Leopard attacks you.
Go back to your lair
and twerk later.
Black Widow was twerking
right now.
All right, Leopard,
it's not over.
You got some smackdowning
to do later.
I'm sorry, Leopard.
You'll sing for one last chance
to keep your mask on,
but for now, go back to
your spot backstage.
And now,
the most colorful face‐off
in all of
"Masked Singer" history.
Whoo!
The Flamingo
versus the Panda.
‐ Whoo!
‐ ‐
It's like "National
Geographic" up in here.
Straight out of a lawn somewhere
in Florida, the Flamingo.
♪ They call me Hell ♪
♪ They call me Stacey ♪
♪ The call me her ♪
♪ They call me Jane ♪
♪ That's not my name ♪
‐ My God.
‐ ♪ That's not my name ♪
♪ That's not my name ♪
♪ They call me quiet girl ♪
♪ Always the same ♪
♪ That's not my name ♪
‐ ♪ That's not my name ♪ ‐ I
don't even know how to do this.
♪ That's not my name ♪
They have such a cute little body.
Get it together, Ken!
I don't even know how
to put these things on.
Flamingo got a lot of sauce.
All right, free the Panda.
♪ Panda ♪
♪ Panda, panda, panda ♪
♪ Panda, panda, panda, panda ♪
♪ I got broads in Atlanta ♪
‐‐Robin!
My God, it's amazing!
Panda! Panda!
- Get it, Panda!
- Yeah.
‐ Whoo! ‐ My gosh.
The Panda's so cute!
‐ Yes, Panda!
‐ I want to hug the Panda.
Pay close attention. Here are
some clues about the Flamingo.
What's up, everyone?
Welcome to my ZooTube Channel,
‐ "Bird's The Word."
‐ ‐ZooTube.
Where I'm going to tell you
the real story of becoming
a flamingo.
I'm gonna let you in
on all my tips and tricks
from beauty to fashion
to life advice.
It could be a famous YouTuber
that does makeup.
Who's into beauty?
Is it a Kardashian?
Listen, I know what it's like
to feel trapped in your career.
‐ She's been controlled.
‐
So, I left.
Now I'm here to take back
control of my destiny.
- ‐ Okay, destiny. Maybe a Destiny's Child.
- Could be a clue.
‐ Kelly Rowland.
‐ It's why I chose the Flamingo,
because they represent
new beginnings.
It's about damn time
this badass birdie
got to show
her feathers again.
There's so many YouTubers
out there right now.
Yeah, I wouldn't know
where to start with that.
This is gonna be tough.
♪ We go together ♪
♪ Better than birds
of a feather, you and me ♪
♪ We change the weather, yeah ♪
♪ I'm feeling heat in December
when you're 'round me ♪
♪ I've been dancing on top
of cars ♪
♪ And stumbling out of bars ♪
♪ Baby, you know it's obvious ♪
♪ I'm a sucker for you ♪
♪ Say the word
and I'll go anywhere blindly ♪
♪ I'm a sucker for you ♪
Whoo! Whoo!
♪ I've been dancing
on top of cars ♪
♪ And stumbling out of bars ♪
♪ I'd follow you in the dark,
can't get enough ♪
♪ You're the medicine
and the pain ♪
♪ The tattoo inside my brain ♪
♪ Baby, you know it's obvious,
I'm a sucker for ♪
‐
‐ ♪ The subliminal things ♪
‐ ♪ No one knows about you ♪
‐ ♪ Yeah ♪
‐ ♪ And you're making ♪
‐ ♪ The typical me ♪
‐ ♪ Break my typical rules ♪
‐ ♪ ♪
♪ It's true,
I'm a sucker for you ♪
‐ Great job. Great job.
‐ That was really good.
All right.
Still shaking it.
Flamingo! Flamingo!
Nicole, tell her
about her performance.
Fla‐min‐go.
I am here for you, Flamingo,
and your snatched body,
your "ma‐chest‐ic"‐‐
‐ "Chest‐ic"?
‐ "Ma‐chest‐ic..."
- ‐ voluptuous curves.
- All right, all right.
You sounded amazing
on that song.
I think that voice
was definitely part of a group,
and we've bought her albums before.
That's what I'm thinking.
That's how good you are,
Flamingo.
Nicole, you picking up
on any clues?
Definitely there's
a youthfulness about her.
She, you know, she‐‐
she backing it up up there.
Ay, ski, ska.
There's the fashion beauty
from YouTube,
so there's obviously someone
a bit younger,
someone from, like,
Danity Kane or Fifth Harmony
or Destiny's Child.
I don't agree with that.
Initially when I saw
the clue package,
I was thinking more,
quite frankly,
a disgraced YouTuber.
Maybe it was someone
who had fallen from grace,
like‐‐ like‐‐
with all due respect,
you know, like Olivia Jade
or something like that.
‐ I didn't know, going on that before.
No way!
Or just forget what I said.
Maybe it's Chuck Schumer.
I don't know these things.
I'm a dummy.
Well, you know what? I think we
should ask the Flamingo a question.
‐ Right, guys?
‐ Yes! Please!
What makes you the Flamingo?
‐ Well, I'm sassy.
‐ Okay.
The flamingos are a symbol
of very luxurious vacations.
So I, my friends,
are your escape.
Yass, queen.
I see the wheels turning
over there
in Robin Thicke's mind.
Yes, yes, that‐‐
I think she just gave a clue.
‐ But I need a second to go through
my research here. ‐ God, Robin!
Wait, wait, wait. What's the clue?
What's the clue?
- ‐ Escape.
- Yes!
‐
‐ Escape?
‐ Ooh. ‐ Yes. One of the
girls from Xscape, I think.
What's the girl‐‐ she wrote hit
songs for other artists, too.
She's very, very talented.
She has a reality TV show also.
That's it, it's Kandi Burruss.
Kandi Burruss.
- ‐ Are you saying Kandi?
- Kandi, yes.
That's interesting.
Height‐wise‐‐
Maybe. I'm just
throwing it out there.
I also thought maybe
just from her attitude,
it reminded me of Tia Mowry
from "Sister, Sister."
No! She
wanted to escape from that.
She's got that same sass I've seen on
the reel. You know what I'm saying?
Okay. We don't know
what you're saying.
This game is hard, man.
Harder than last year.
And last year was difficult.
Well, hey, at least you guys
got something.
Ladies and gentlemen
one more time
for the amazing performance
from the Flamingo.
Our panel thought
one of these celebrities
might be under
the Flamingo mask.
Who do you think it is?
I'm still in
shock that I actually
went out there and did this.
This is so
out of character for me.
They actually thought
I was a professional singer.
I'm in shock and awe, people.
Shock and awe.
♪ Who is that? ♪
Welcome back
to "The Masked Singer,"
where you never know which
famous faces you're gonna see.
In fact,
in our audience tonight
are three of the shining stars
of the new FOX drama
"Almost Family."
Ladies and gentlemen, make
some noise for Brittany Snow,
Megalyn Echikumwoke,
and Emily Osment.
Thank you for joining us.
And guesses so far?
I'm thinking
it's Dolly Parton, for sure.
The Flamingo is Dolly Parton?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, totally.
Dolly Parton swagging
like that?
Yeah.
I love her YouTube show.
Dolly's "ma‐chest‐ical."
All right.
Remember, everybody,
"Almost Family"
premieres tonight
after "The Masked Singer"
‐ right here on Fox.
‐ All right!
But now, we're
smack dab in the middle
of a very dramatic face‐off.
It's time to grin and bear
some very cute clues
about the Panda.
‐ Aww!
‐ Her dad, big influence.
So it's gotta be some symbol
in banging your chest.
An athlete, possibly.
Famous family in the forest.
‐ Match, tennis.
‐ It could be a tennis star.
And cooking. "Cookin' Like
Mama." So mama might be a cook.
So cute.
‐ Do you have any guesses after that?
‐ Laila Ali.
No way. Her body
type is way different.
‐ Maybe not, maybe not.
‐ All right.
♪ You know the bed
feels warmer ♪
♪ Sleeping here alone ♪
♪ Think you've got
the best of me ♪
♪ Think you had
the last laugh ♪
♪ Baby, you don't know me,
'cause you're dead wrong ♪
♪ What doesn't kill you
makes you stronger ♪
♪ Stand a little taller ♪
♪ Doesn't mean I'm lonely
when I'm alone ♪
♪ What doesn't kill you
makes a fighter ♪
♪ Footsteps even lighter ♪
♪ Doesn't mean I'm over
because you're gone ♪
♪ Thanks to you
I got a new thing started ♪
I'm not the broken‐hearted ♪
♪ Thanks to you
I'm finally thinking 'bout me ♪
Hey!
♪ You know in the end ♪
♪ The day you left
was just my beginning ♪
♪ What doesn't kill you
makes you stronger ♪
♪ Stronger, stronger ♪
‐ Come on! Give it to us!
‐ ♪ Just me, myself, and I ♪
♪ What doesn't kill you
makes you stronger ♪
I don't know!
I have no idea right now.
We'll never figure
this one out, man.
Wow. ‐ Panda!
Panda!
Man, Panda,
that was amazing.
Dr. Ken,
talk to the Panda, please.
Amazing performance.
Really, you just‐‐
you just captured the stage.
And there's just obviously
something so likeable about you,
so charismatic,
and honestly,
you're, to me, the sentimental
favorite of the show.
Aww.
All right, panel, are you
picking up on any clues
from the performance
or the package?
Putting up everything with you
having a supportive family,
and sounds like you were
already successful on your own.
Maybe a celebrity cook,
a celebrity chef.
Maybe, and you guys are gonna laugh
at me and I'm gonna ignore it.
‐ We will. ‐ You know,
maybe a Martha Stewart type.
She does hang with Snoop Dogg
now, so there is some edge to her.
She does hang with Snoop
Dogg, Nick, you know?
That doesn't mean
she's as tall as Snoop Dogg.
She's three times the size of Nick?
I don't think so.
Well, everybody's three times
the size of Nick.
He's the shortest host
in TV history.
He's 5'1"!
- Miss Scherzinger.
- I mean, Nick,
they threw in "match"
and talking about their father
being a strong influence
in guiding them,
so I was thinking
maybe Venus Williams
only because she talked
she talked about Papa Bear.
Nice. I don't hate that answer.
I actually like it.
But these are the clues
that really stood out for me.
Strength, fighting,
match, winning.
So definitely an athlete,
so I immediately went to,
like, wrestling, MMA.
Maybe Ronda Rousey.
Well, Ronda Rousey
doesn't look like that.
How do you know?
She's dressed as a panda.
If it's Ronda Rousey,
she's gonna beat your butt, Ken.
You know, I'm sorry.
Ronda, if it's true, I'm sorry.
Well, let's hear from
the Panda directly, shall we?
What makes you the Panda?
I'm loveable, but fierce.
Aww.
Look, everyone knows
I'm the king of wrong guesses,
so I deserve a second chance.
Now that I've processed
everything,
takes me a little longer‐‐
just hearing your voice,
loveable, but fierce.
Something Queen Latifah‐ish
about her?
No. No.
Thank you Thank you. I won.
‐ It's not Queen Latifah.
‐ I think it's Queen Latifah.
‐ Queen Latifah can sing. ‐ That's right.
Queen Latifah knows how to sing.
- ‐ You can sing, too, Panda.
- Stay with my logic.
‐ Queen Latifah, amazing‐‐
‐ The Panda can sing, too.
It's Queen Latifah, who we know can
sing better than that, but she's shy!
No! ‐ So you
think she's tricking us.
Queen Latifah's gonna kick
your butt, too, let me tell you.
Well, one thing we do know,
that was an amazing performance.
Ladies and gentlemen,
one more time for the Panda.
You did a great job,
Latifah. Love you.
Our panel thought
one of these celebrities
might be under the Panda mask.
Who do you think it is?
All right, it's time for our
panel and studio audience
to decide who they want
to see sing again.
Who will live to sing
another day,
and who will join Leopard
in the smackdown
for one last chance
to keep their mask on?
‐ The votes are in. ‐ Panda! Panda!
And the winner
of this face‐off is...
Flamingo!
♪ They call me hell ♪
♪ The call me Stacey ♪
‐ I'm sorry, Panda.
‐ Aww.
‐ ♪ That's not my name ♪
‐ Nicole: Aww, you guys.
♪ They call me quiet girl ♪
‐ ♪ Always the same ♪
‐ Congratulations, Flamingo.
You get to be a part of
our weirdness for another week.
Go back to your trailer
and gloat, madam.
Panda, you're going
to smackdown with the Leopard
to decide if you take it off
or keep it on.
‐ That's right, Panda!
‐ Come on, Panda!
But for now,
we're gonna see you later.
Keep it going for the Panda.
If the TV was on and I was
cleaning the living room
and I heard that voice,
I'd be like,
"Yeah, it's so and so."
But for some reason
in the Panda costume,
it's throwing me.
It's driving me nuts.
♪ Who is that? ♪
Welcome back
to "The Masked Singer."
The two singers in jeopardy,
the Panda and the Leopard,
now get a second chance
to stay in the competition
in the smackdown.
They both sing,
our panel votes,
one moves on,
and the other will be unmasked
right before our eyes.
Whoo!
This is the smackdown‐down!
In this mouth,
straight outta China,
and all pumped up on bamboo,
the Panda.
‐ Come on, Panda!
‐ Go, Panda!
Panda's so sweet.
Panda! Panda!
And in this mouth,
ready to pounce,
the Leopard.
Yes, Leopard!
Leopard! Leopard! Leopard!
All right, you two animals
know the rules.
We want a good, clean fight.
Panda, you're up first.
Let the smackdown begin!
‐
‐ Nicole: Come on, Panda!
Come on, Panda.
‐ Whoever it is is funny.
‐ Wow.
♪ All I do is win, win, win,
no matter what ♪
♪ Got money on my mind,
I can never get enough ♪
♪ And every time I step up
in the building ♪
♪ Everybody's hands go up ♪
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
♪ And they stay there,
and they say, yeah ♪
♪ And they stay up down,
up down, up down ♪
♪ 'Cause all I do is
win, win, win ♪
♪ And if you going in,
put your hands in the air ♪
♪ Make them stay there ♪
- Whoa.
- Wow.
‐ Come on. ‐ Female comedian,
maybe, the Panda is.
Maybe. ‐ A winning
mentality from the Panda.
Leopard, you up next.
Let's step over here, Panda.
Wow!
♪ What you want ♪
♪ Baby, I got it ♪
♪ What you need ♪
♪ You know that I got ♪
♪ All I'm asking ♪
♪ For a little respect
when I get home ♪
♪ Hey, baby ♪
♪ When I get home ♪
♪ R‐E‐S‐P‐E‐C‐T ♪
♪ That is what
you mean to me ♪
♪ R‐E‐S‐P‐E‐C‐T ♪
♪ That's what, that's what ♪
♪ That's what it means to me ♪
Bravo!
Wow. It's gonna be tough.
Mr. Robin Thicke?
I loved it.
I'm gonna really be sad
to see either one
of you guys go
'cause there's
so much personality,
and you both have such
loveable outfits and personas.
Panda, for you to be shy
and to come
on a stage like this
‐ and "bear" your all...
‐ Get out, seriously.
There it is.
What a confidence boost
this must be for you
to even overcome this obstacle,
and a wonderful job.
Great job.
Okay, panel, enough talk.
Time to vote.
This is hard.
All right,
who will win the smackdown
and keep wearing
a sweat‐drenched costume
while lying
to their friends and family?
And what secret celebrity
is going home unmasked tonight?
We'll find out
after the break.
The time has come for
our masked moment of truth.
And the winner
of this smackdown is...
The Leopard!
‐ ♪ Free your mind ♪
‐ Nicole: Wow.
‐ ♪ And the rest will follow ♪
‐ Panda looks so sad.
- ‐ All right, Leopard.
- Congratulations.
You can keep it on
and head back to the lair.
♪ Free your mind ♪
♪ And the rest will follow ♪
‐ ♪ Be colorblind ♪
‐ Just got kissed by a leopard.
Could it be someone tall
like RuPaul?
RuPaul's a pretty good guess.
‐ That's a good guess.
That means, Panda,
I'm sorry,
but you're leaving us.
Aww.
‐ I feel bad for Panda.
But we can't wait to see
your famous face!
‐ Keep it going for Panda.
‐ Aww, the Panda.
- ‐ Panda! Panda!
- Panel,
it's time for you guys
to give us some final guesses.
I have never been
more confused on this show
than right now with Panda.
I've gone from Ronda Rousey,
because of the athlete,
all the way to Wanda Sykes,
being like a comedian,
'cause you make me laugh and you've
got a lot of attitude and sass.
So I'm so lost, but if I'm
gonna throw it out there,
I'm just gonna say
Wanda Sykes.
No. That's an amazing
wrong guess.
I am going to double down
and say this is Queen Latifah
because she is likeable.
Hear me out, guys!
Stay with me.
Not known for singing,
but can sing,
but did disguise her voice.
‐ She is known for singing. ‐ Had a
supportive‐‐ I know, but she's disguising it.
She can't sing as well.
Just love my logic,
if not my choices!
I got an idea.
So after watching the smackdown,
this has to be somebody
with a comedic background.
I think Loni Love
from Chelsea Handler's show.
‐ Yes.
‐ Also from "The Real."
‐ I'm going Loni Love.
‐ That's a good one.
Ooh.
‐ Miss Scherzinger,
who do you think it is?
I think maybe they
come from a famous family.
And she said "match"
in the clue package,
so I am going with
Venus Williams.
We are all over the place.
Okay, panel,
you've made your final guesses.
Now let's see if any of you
are right.
I'm ready to see my queen.
Show us who you are, Panda.
‐ Come on, Panda.
‐ Take it off!
Take it off! Take it off!
♪ Who are you? ♪
‐ Come on, Loni!
‐ ♪ Who, who, who, who? ♪
‐ Come on, Venus!
‐ ♪ I really want to know ♪
♪ Who? ♪
♪ You, you, are you? ♪
I knew it!
Undefeated boxing champion
Laila Ali!
‐ I said that as a joke.
‐ No way!
- ‐ You said Laila.
- Author, TV star,
and of course,
daughter of the greatest boxer
of all time, Muhammad Ali.
I knew it was you.
I can't believe
you guys didn't guess.
‐ You didn't know!
‐ How did you know?
When you were joking about
singing and she punched me...
- ‐ I was like, "Ooh!"
- Yeah!
‐ ‐ "That gotta be
Laila right there."
So what was it like
being the Panda?
My God, it was crazy.
Just the suit being hot,
just singing
through this mask.
It was, like, I feel like
you couldn't hear me.
So it was a lot of fun.
I've always loved to sing.
Always been shy with singing,
but it was fun to be able to
perform without anyone knowing.
As a joke,
I said your name,
but the padding
on the outfit comple‐‐
I know your body type. I was like,
"That is not her body type."
‐ So it totally fooled me.
‐ Now it makes sense.
Athlete, family, winning.
Nick, I think we can cut out
all that Queen Latifah‐‐
I only mentioned it once.
We can cut that out of the show.
I don't think
she's gonna know, guys.
I will say
this is the first time
I've ever lost
something like this.
Right. ‐ So my
heart‐‐ yeah, I was like‐‐
‐ She's undefeated!
‐ My gosh!
She's an undefeated boxer!
It was very humbling,
but it's been fun.
Aww.
‐ You're amazing!
We know you're
not used to losing,
but you're still
a winner in our eyes.
Ladies and gentlemen, one last
time performing for us right here,
give it up for Laila Ali.
♪ What doesn't kill you
makes you stronger ♪
‐ Come on!
‐ ♪ Stand a little taller ♪
♪ Doesn't mean I'm lonely
'cause I'm alone ♪
Next week...
‐ Whoo!
four new undercover
celebrities battle it out...
‐ That voice is so legendary.
‐ Fierce, baby.
as we all try
to figure out...
‐ Jennifer Hudson.
‐ Mariah Carey.
...who is under the mask.
I did not see this coming.
"The Masked Singer,"
all‐new
next Wednesday on FOX.