Look Bequer, I bought this hat in Paris.
It´s been many years.
It´s a very elegant design.
Don´t you like it?
You don´t understand a thing
about fashion, Bequer.
What a pity, Bequer...
There´s no way to stop this plague.
Look my flowers...
Remind me to put the insecticide tomorrow.
Blacker than the night
Come and drink your milk.
Bequer, where have you been all day long?
If you don´t come when I call you,
there´ll not be any snack for you.
Do you understand?
Bequer,
don´t be such a naughty cat.
Behave yourself.
- Hi. When did you arrive?
- Just now. Who´s that in my bedroom?
- What?
- Oh, forget it.
Hey you lazy, get up.
It´s too late.
- What a surprise!
- No. You gave me a surprise.
Can you tell me who´s sleeping in my bed?
She´s a cousin of mine,
poor girl she didn´t have a place to stay.
- I don´t know what´s happening to men. She´s going to stay?
- If you don´t have any problem...
- Where is she going to sleep?
- Any place, on the sofa or here with me.
- Besides, she can help us with the bills. She´s model.
- That argument convinces me. Come on, get dress, let´s go!
Everything was ok with Octavio until yesterday
when I opened the door and I saw...
- A woman!
- Two! His wife and daughter.
- What surprise may he had!
- Just figure, he had just his slip on!
- What happened?
- I don´t know. I just grabbed my things, acted naïve and left.
- Did they give you any recommendation card?
- Not even a single one.
And I didn´t do it so badly.
Well, just forget it. What´s important is you already
have a place to sleep. Ofelia agrees.
- I really don´t know how to thank you...
- Don´t worry, we´ll charge you every forthcoming.
The rules of the house are:
The first one who enter to work has the right to use the bathroom.
I´m late.
- See you later. Bye!
- Bye!
By the way, Ofelia.
You didn´t tell us anything about your trip.
The bad news are that it´s over now
and I have no plans.
- Ofelia, you´re an actress?
- Well, it´s supposed...
- What do you do?
- I work as divorcée.
As vampire, she lives with money
stolen from his ex-husband.
Here, I´m the one in charge of
the administration of the house.
If that´s the case, bring me
another cup of coffee and put it on my check.
Hi. What are you doing here?
I need to talk with you,
come with me.
- Something wrong happened?
- I´m not sure yet.
Look what they sent me.
It´s a solicitor´s citation.
- You just´ve to go and find yourself.
- I want you come with me, this things scare me.
I´m scared too.
The house and all it properties, will keep after my death
in charge of my niece Miss Ofelia Escudero.
- An inheritance?
- A considerably sum of money.
It´s an old house but has a lot
of land and many valuable objects.
But... I can´t understand why
aunt Susana chosed me.
- I´m aware that you were the only family she had.
- So, it was by default.
Oh, it doesn´t matter!
What´s important is you inherited, like in a soap opera!
One moment. This things always get
weird with strange terms and conditions.
- Like marying someone you don´t know or adopting a child.
- Well, that´s half true.
- See? I told you... - It´s not as serious as you think,
it´s not even a condition but a beg.
As an exchange for this legacy,
I just wait from my niece´s humanitarian feelings...
... to accept the custody of the living being
I loved the most in my life...
...and kept me faithfull company for many years, my unforgettable cat Bequer.
A cat?!
As an exchange of a house,
I can´t see the problem.
- Who´s this aunt Susana?
- She was my mother´s cousin.
I barely remember her.
I was afraid of her, she always scolded to me.
- Then, there was a family fight and I never saw her again.
- You don´t remember anything about the house?
Yes.
There was a big chandelier in the saloon.
And long stairways.
I slid down the handrail when I was a child.
There was a big clock somewhere.
I loved hearing the clock´s strokes.
The entire house had a strange
damp and spikenard´s smell.
And it was always silent.
What impressed me the most,
was aunt Susana´s portrait on the saloon.
- Not very modern, isn´t it?
- No, but it must have many bedrooms.
- That means servants, isn´t it?
- Why not? With the money we saved, we can pay for them.
Good afternoon.
I´m Ofelia Escudero.
- I´m not sure if you know that...
- I know.
Come in.
- These are my friends, they´ll live with me.
- Like you wish.
- We´d like to see the entire house.
- My pleasure.
This is the main saloon.
That´s the reception room.
That´s the famous picture?
- What a cool aunt!
- She was a very distinguished lady, if that´s what you mean.
Yes, that´s it.
- So many weirds things!
- Did you see this eyesore?
That eyesore was a present from
the Persian´s ambassador to Madam Susana.
- I was just saying it´s weird.
- Don´t worry Miss. I understand your point of view.
Modernism, has distorted people´s taste.
- Do you want to see the living room?
- Why don´t we check the bedrooms?
Yes, much better.
Do you want to know when I´ll go the Persia?
Never!
This is your aunt´s bedroom,
where she died.
The notary told me she died of a heart attack
while she was kitting in the saloon.
That´s true but she was still alive
when we brought here.
Everything is exactly as it was
before she dies.
- What´s in the box?
- Your aunt´s ring, the one she always used it.
Put it on.
No.
- We should keep this room closed
out of consideration for your aunt. - Yes, I think that´s ok.
What?!
And waste this bed?!
She died here.
- Then, she died very comfortable.
- Why don´t you keep this bedroom?
- I´d love that but Ofelia is her niece and she should stay.
- No, it´s yours if you really liked it.
If you want to,
you can check the other bedrooms.
This junk is quite comfortable.
- Did you see this? A collection of junk!
- Watch out, it can be from the Turkish ambassador.
- Did they scold you, huh?
- Lousy broad...
Girls, I found an incredible treasure up there.
The bathrooms are full of white clothes
and towels.
- We´ve inherited many things.
- I want to know if we´re going to keep that horrible servant.
Be careful cocky girl, the mummy can hear you.
Did you see the kitchen?
What a fancy oven!
- I´m going right now, that´s my especiality!
- Wait a moment, something important is missing.
- Where´s Bequer?
- Of course, the cat!
I have no idea where it can be.
Since your aunt´s death,
it acts very strange and it´s usually hidden somewhere.
Well, I don´t care.
I hate cats in general.
Tell me something, Sofia...
Is it pretty?
Your aunt said that it wasn´t
anything better in the world.
What colour is it?
Black, blacker than night.
Blacker than night...
- Corny old woman. All this solemnity just for a lousy cat.
- Don´t complain, thanks to it you have this house.
Oh! Listen to the prince consort.
You´re going to defend that cat just to please Ofelia.
And I like it a lot.
The problem is you suffer from urophobia.
What?!
Urophobia. Uro is urine, phobia is fear.
Fear of the cats.
If that´s the case, we´re two.
I hate cats.
Except for the husband,
there isn´t any other ungrateful animal.
- What are you doing?
- Saving me the stairs.
Martha is downstairs waiting...
What happened?
I get tired of waiting.
She´s a weirdo! Everything is in the car now.
Even a needle won´t fit.
- I´ll have to do another trip.
- Take this, there´s a place in the seat.
Don´t touch it!
How you dare to put your hands on my canary?
- Oh c´mon, it won´t die!
- Yes, it can. Look, now it´s trembling.
Did the witch scare you?
Come with mommy.
This is cornier than
Christmas with the family.
Isn´t he lovely?
Yes, I hope Bequer get
both of you married.
You may not believe it but
Bequer´s absence have me worried.
- I hope it gets permanently lost.
- Don´t say that, they´ll take out our inheritance.
The testament didn´t say that.
But I feel morally responsible.
Ofelia... what if instead of living in this museum,
you sell it.
- Cool! You could buy a condominium!
- And lose this? Never.
In the future, when there´s more money
I could throw it and start a modern house.
I leave you with your engaging projects,
I go to sleep.
- Me too. I carried boxes like a longshoreman.
- Ok, session´s over.
- Hey, the testament force you to keep the mummy?
- No, but what can I do?
Embalm her!
- Curtains will look nice up there.
- Still awake, Sofia?
I have the habit of turn off the lights
and wound up the clocks every night.
- You´ll tell me if you want I keep doing it.
- No, no... It´s ok.
Good night.
- Sofia, did Bequer shows up?
- Don´t worry Miss. The cat´ll come back.
I think this moving,
it´s going to complicate yourself.
Because of Roberto?
I´ll phone his office tomorrow to tell him where I´m living.
- For a divorced couple, you´ve a quite good relationship.
- Not at all, my dear.
I´m interested in him sending my money.
- Admit it, you still want him.
- Yes, in the bottom of the sea with a stone on his neck.
If I were you, I´d patch things up.
You´re complicating life with stupidities.
What´s wrong?
I don´t know,
something strange in the air.
- Don´t you notice?
- I feel a spikenard´s smell.
It wasn´t so intense in the morning.
Don´t start with your imagination `cause
you won´t be sleeping.
Can you turn off the lights?
Good night.
Good night, Madam.
- Did you hear that?! - Who screamed?!
- Pilar!
Oh...it´s Bequer!
That´s why you screamed?
It scared the shit out of me!
Damn cat!
Be careful, it can scratch you.
- It´s scared.
- And with a good reason, he found Pilar in the dark.
Very amusing.
- Something´s happening?
- Yes, this indecent cat entered to the room!
It still feel this is her master´s bedroom.
It has always slept in that rocking chair.
- From where it came in?
- From the window. It´s open.
Madam Susana ordered to take off
the grills for Bequer wander around freely.
I´ll fix that tomorrow.
- I´m not going to sleep every night with a cat!
- Not every night but tonight you don´t have choice..
Will see...
Get out of here! Get out!
I don´t recommend you do that.
It´d spend all night meowing at the door.
She´s right.
Forget about the cat, lie down and get to sleep.
- It won´t be easy but...anyhow.
- Let ourselves sleep. - Please.
- Good morning! - Good morning!
- Enjoying yourselves, huh?
- You were sleeping like a log and I didn´t want to wake you up.
- With last night´s little party I could hardly sleep.
Think what you want but
I´m happy we found Bequer.
- I don´t think it´s funny.
- Me, for instance, I won´t sleep in that bedroom anymore.
Ok, I take it.
We´ll change places later.
- Now I want some company to go through the cellars.
- They´re cellars?
- Huge and apparently full of old junk.
- I love seeing pieces of junk!
- Whereabouts is the entry?
- There´s a door at the back of the house.
Sofia gave me the keys.
Did you see this?
I can´t understand how could they
dress like this in the streets.
- I can´t understand how could they cover their bodies so much.
- Being virtuous was meaningless. Where´s the joke about it?
Sure.
Just imagine to undress one´s clothes!
- This fashion suits you very well, Pilar.
- I guess it´s the habit.
These dresses are just like
the ones my husband bought me.
Hey, your aunt sure knew about business.
Check this!
- That´s why your aunt didn´t get married? - She didn´t want to.
She had a romantic story waiting for his first boyfriend.
She has never wore that coat?
What a waste!
Will you dare to go out dressed like that?
Yes, some tuesday´s carnival.
Why not?
- That´d be cool! We can do a masquerade party!
- Pilar and Sofia should go without mask.
- Shut up! Those are malicious words.
Hey, that´d be for the front page
or just for the cancan?
- I think this is Lucía´s sunday dress.
- No, hers are more cheerful.
- You look like my grandmother with that hat!
- Yes but the way she´s now in the grave!
Girls, look what I found!
- I´m sure something especial is in there.
- I´ll find out.
- Damn cat! It scared me a lot!
- Bequer, get out of here. Don´t be a nuisance.
Get out!
- Be careful, it´s furious!
- Like if that box were itself´s. - It´ll pay for this!
- Please don´t hit it!
- Of course I´ll! - It´s leaving now.
Quite friendly cat, huh?
Did it hurt you?
Nah, it just took it to heart.
- Let´s see what´s in that box, ok?
- Ok.
- What a gorgeous dress!
- It must be my aun´t wedding dress.
- Didn´t you tell us she wasn´t married?
- Yeah but it seems she had it prepared.
Maybe you can fix it and
wear it in your wedding.
That´s true.
It´ll cost me a lot to buy a dress like this.
They say wearing something old
is good luck!
That´d be done if you show up
as the maid of honor.
- I´ll go to my room and try on!
- Come on!
Bequer.
Bequer, what are you doing here?
Come here, my dear.
Stop playing pranks. Come here.
Can we listen something more quiet?
- No, that´s why I brought my records. Do you prefer those from the aunt? - Did she own?
- Of course she owned!
Bach, Chopin, Bethoveen, Wagner´s opera,
Vivaldi. She was totally out.
- I´m thinking on keeping the dress the way it is now.
It´s ok? - I think is great.
- Did you like the idea of her wearing that dress?
- Of course.
Of course, he saves himself
buying a new one.
Did she see you with your dress on?
That´s bad luck.
It also means being one step ahead of the wedding.
We don´t like that, little boy. These two mothers in law are watching you.
Bequer!
Come here, Bequer!
Someone´s in the garden.
- What are you talking about?
- Someone´s calling Bequer from the garden!
- Did you see something?
- Yes, looked like the shadow of a woman.
- Watch out, people. Aurora loves making jokes.
- No! I swear it´s not a joke, I heard a voice in the garden!
- I want to be sure about this.
- I go with you.
You´d better not joking about this.
No, I swear I´m not!
Nobody´s here.
- I already knew that.
- Let´s go back, it´s very cold.
This is the first time they leave us alone.
I´m not going to waste this opportunity.
Did you hear that?
Yes and very close.
- Wait here. - Don´t go. It´s Sofia.
I don´t know why I didn´t think of that before.
Thank goodness...
I was getting the chill down my spine.
No, no Miss. It wasn´t me.
- I´ve been in the kitchen all night.
- But we heard you, Sofia!
I assure you. You´re wrong.
Besides, there´s any reason to call Bequer.
It always stay in the garden during the night.
Unless we´d called it earlier because
the clouds looked threatening.
Rain?
In this season?
I´m just giving a report
of this house´s custom.
Ok, you can go now.
With your permission.
I´m sure it was her!
- Crazy old woman, I can´t stand her!
- The good part is we´re in good company.
She´s right about one thing:
There´s a lot of noise in this house!
Oh, you didn´t hear nothing yet!
Let´s dance, Pedro!
I don´t understand why she
said she wasn´t in the garden.
- You know...? I´m not so sure if she was that voice.
- Who else´d be? - I don´t know.
I´m not superstitious but...
... it frightened me a lot
when I heard that voice.
Can you believe this?
It´s raining.
Who´s there?
Of course it was her!
Neither of us could do it.
I can´t believe it.
How this woman dare to enter in my bedroom?
Believe it. This old servants feel they´ve the right to do it.
The fact that they see us as intruders...
- Did you want it to see me, Miss?
- Yes, Sofía.
Tell me...
What did you burn there, last night?
- Me?
- Look Sofia, I want you tell me the truth.
Yesterday, I found a wedding dress in the cellar.
Someone took away from my room and threw it in the fire.
- Your aunt´s wedding dress?
- Yes, that one.
I burned myself.
That´s inexcusable!
How did you dare!
Your aunt adored that dress.
It was something very beautiful for her.
I don´t think you´ve had such love for an object
to the extent of treat it as something untouchable...
... and sacred.
- That didn´t give you the right...! - Of course not, Miss.
I beg you to forgive me.
- If you want I can leave...
- That´s not the point, Sofía.
We´ll talk later.
With your permission.
Why didn´t you fire her?
I´m not sure.
Poor woman, she really loved my aunt.
She´s an hypocrite!
Did you see her innocence face when you asked her?
She almost convinced me.
- But who else could be?
- Of course.
But...
How did she know that the dress was in my bedroom?
He looked so handsome!
Bequer!
Yes!
That damn cat did it...
Bye darling, thanks for everything.
Can we have lunch tomorrow?
- I don´t think so. I call you at the office.
- Ok, bye. - Bye.
Let me close for you.
Bequer, where are you?
Who´s there?
It´s me, Miss.
I´m looking for Bequer.
I didn´t see it all day long.
It didn´t eat and that worries me.
- Don´t worry, it´ll come back.
- No. It won´t if I don´t call it.
- It´s scared.
- Why?
Bequer knows when it behaved badly.
Today, it made something terrible.
It killed Miss Aurora´s canary.
Poor little darling...
Marta! Wake up!
What happens?
Listen...
I don´t hear anything.
Already stopped.
- What happens, Aurora? You´re trembling.
- Marta, those sobbing were horrible.
- C´mon woman, you just had a nightmare.
- No.
I heard ´em, I was awake!
Then... I went to the corridor and...
Someone´s was crying in the saloon.
- We can go see if you want to.
- No!
No matter what, I won´t go downstairs.
I´m so scared!
So scared...
- Good morning, Sofía.
- Good morning.
Sofía...
Did you hear something weird last night?
- Weird? Like what?
- Like a crying.
A crying?
No. I didn´t hear a thing.
Thank you, Sofía.
- I´m sure it was the sound of the wind, Aurora.
- No, not at all.
- What I listened was a crying.
- But Pilar and Ofelia didn´t hear anything.
Yes, that´s very strange.
Why only me?
You better give up, I´m on fire tonight.
Ok, I give up.
- You´re not happy. What´s wrong?
- You´ll make fun of me if I tell you.
- Bequer.
- Yes.
It didn´t come back, not even for eating.
It´s been 4 days now.
- I think we definitively lose it.
- Don´t worry. It must be out there living a passionate romance.
How wonderful animals are...
He had a feeling he´ll be scold after killing the canary.
- It´d do any good if I get a new cat for you?
- No.
- I´ve became very fond of it. He was very pretty.
- And blacker than night!
- Don´t make fun of it.
- No, I´m truly sorry.
- Do you want to come in?
- Do you want?
I´m coming in!
Sofia´s bedroom is at the back
of the garden but I...
- What´s happening?
- We must tell you something. You ain´t going to like it.
What?
- We found Bequer.
- Oh, I was scared! Where is it?
In the cellar...
Dead.
How could this happen?
We didn´t notice and we let it locked.
It couldn´t get out
because of the barred windows.
It died of hunger.
Poor thing...
Don´t get distress about it.
I know it´s sad but it´s nobody´s fault.
It´s urgent we take the cat out
and throw it far from here.
Throw it? Certainly not!
We´ll buried it in the garden.
- Ofelia, that´s nonsense!
- I don´t care! I´d feel very bad if I didn´t do it.
We never treat it respectfully.
Ok. If that calm you down,
we´ll buried it tomorrow.
I feel so guilty.
- He must´ve suffered a lot.
- Don´t think about that. Let´s go.
Ok. Fortunately, Bequer´s problem is finished.
Damn cat!
Not even dead I´ll forgive it about my canary.
Let´s go, Marta.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I´m thinking what aunt Susana´d do if she knew it.
Who is it?
Who´s there?
What can I do for you, Miss?
- How did you dare to bring this here?
- Bring what?
This!
Don´t try to deny it!
- It seems cruel to leave it in the cellar,
this was Bequer´s favourite spot. - You must be crazy!
- Just for this night.
- Take out this junk right now! Do you understand?
Yes. Yes, Miss...
Done. Something else?
I suppose you´re not expecting
we put a gravestone, right?
- Don´t make fun of me. I couldn´t just throw it in a trash can.
- Ok, we already did it. Now, please forget about Bequer.
- I´m very sorry, Sofía. I didn´t take proper care of Bequer.
- The house´ll be very different now.
Personally,
I won´t notice the difference.
I assure you, you´ll notice Miss.
Why did you give her explanations?
- She loved Bequer. I don´t want she hold a grudge against us.
- Hold a grudge? She hates us.
The way she looks at us.
- Does that utter nonsense ended?
- Let me tell you, my dear, that you don´t have any feelings.
You´re a bunch of hypocrites!
You´re as happy as me with the cat´s dead.
You are just making a good impression on Ofelia.
- I can´t understand how no one listened it miaowing?
- Yes, it´s weird that a cat die of hunger so quietly.
Enough!!! I´m fed up with the cat!
You´re going to drive me crazy!
- There´s no other subject to talk about?
- What´s the problem, Aurora?
I can´t stand this! It´s been a week since you only
talk about Bequer! This is too much!
What´s wrong with her?
Bequer.
Who is it?
- It´s me, Miss.
- Come in.
What´s that?
- As you didn´t eat this afternoon...
- Thanks. Leave it there.
Do you feel sick?
Yes, I´m a little bit nervous.
Did you hear those voices again?
No.
You must think I´m crazy.
Why?
Because I´m a modern woman liberated of all
those nonsenses...
... and suddenly I´m listening voices at midnight...
...but I heard them, Sofia!
They we terrifying, long and bloodcurding.
Horrible.
If you had listened to them.
I did.
Sofía, help me please. Help me!
You´ve lived in this house for so long,
you know all the noises...
...it has to be an explanation.
- There is one. Do you believe in the afterlife?
No. Of course not.
If so, you wouldn´t understand me.
If you listen to them again...
... stay in your room.
- You´re going to stay much longer, Miss Aurora?
- No, José. I´m finishing.
You didn´t read any book, don´t you?
- Why it worries you? You never read them.
- At my age? When I´d finished them?
- It´s not about reading all of them but the important ones.
- Much worst would be reading all of them, just imagine trying all these!
- I´m in the office if you need me.
- Thanks, José.
Drink it, Aurora. You´ll feel better.
I saw her. It wasn´t my imagination.
Believe me.
- You just said that the caretaker checked the library
and didn´t find anyone. - But she was there!
And then I saw the walking stick.
I´m still watching it in my mind.
I didn´t recall about the stick!
Of course you do, you see it
every day in that picture over there.
No, I saw it.
It wasn´t the same.
It was very clear.
It´s silver hilt shined.
That stick never was in the library,
I´m going to show you right now.
- It´s in the house?
- Naturally.
- It´d make you feel better if you saw it?
- I don´t know.
Maybe.
All is a product of an obsession. Since that night when you
heard the voices, you can´t stop thinking about this.
- Tell me, Miss.
- Sofía, can you please bring us my aunt´s walking stick?
Don´t look at us that way!
- We want the one she used in her portrait.
- But... that´s not possible.
- She carried with her.
- She carried? How´s that?
The day we buried her,
I put that stick in her coffin.
- What should I put first?
- The sauce first, then the almonds.
- Who taught you this dish?
- My grandmother. It was Madam Susana´s favourite dish.
You really loved her, right?
She was a wonderful person.
Every person who knew her,
became very fond of her.
However, she never managed
to get along with Ofelia.
She was very strict, Miss.
If someone made a mistake, she never forgot it.
She didn´t know how to forgive.
You rest, Sofía. I go.
- You?
- Hi. Can I come in?
Yes, of course.
What message did you gave to the caretaker?
He didn´t explain me very well.
- One of you´ve inherited a house or something...
- Ofelia. This is her house.
You´re planning to stay here with your friends?
I don´t have to tell you about my plans.
Damn! Don´t be so agressive.
It just worries me you live here, as if you didn´t have a home.
That´s the truth.
You have ours, don´t you?
You never show up there.
Well... that was before.
I promess that if you come back with me,
all will be different.
Look... I´ve though a lot about us.
You were right.
- Keep your hands down!
- I made many mistakes.
- I admit I left you alone because of my friends.
That´s over now. - Please, Roberto.
Also, I admit I spent money when you
needed clothes and other things but...
Roberto, they can see you...
Listen... we´re not going to let
nobody intercede in our lives.
You know? I´m still in love with you.
Roberto, they´ll see us...
I can´t live without you.
I need you.
I promess we´re going to be very happy.
- And we´re going to have a child.
- But not here.
- Look... It´s Ofelia.
- Yes, it´s me.
How weird, isn´t it?
Ofelia, what a surprise!
- What a miracle...
- How are you?
He came to talk with me.
- Then, I won´t interrupt.
- No! He was leaving.
But you didn´t answer yet.
- I need some days to think about it.
- Ok, like you want.
- See you, Ofelia. And congrats, very nice house.
- Thanks a lot, Roberto. - Bye!
- Ofelia, let me explain to you...
- It´s not necessary, my mother did it many years ago.
- Don´t think that I was...
- Pilar, is your life and you can do whatever you want.
We´re going to miss you a lot.
I´ve not decided yet.
I don´t know what to do.
To start with, you can button up.
José!
José, is it you?!
Answer me!
What are you doing, José?!
Turn on the lights, please!
Is it you, José?
Answer me!
LIBRARY
- It´s closed.
- She works until late.
- Good night, Miss!
- Good night, I came to see Aurora. She´s still here?
I think she´s gone, there´s nobody inside.
That´s not possible. I just finished to talk
with her and she said that she´d wait for me.
Ok, you can come in if you wish.
See? She isn´t here.
It´s been quite some time since I turned off the lights.
Look! That´s her purse.
She´s still here.
She must be in some of the warehouses.
I´m going to check.
What a place!
Where may be the lights?
Aurora!
Marta.
What are you doing here?
- Nothing.
- Why don´t you come with us? I don´t want you be alone.
- I can´t stop thinking about Aurora. What could happen?
- What they told: the heart.
Yes...
...but do you know what makes one´s heart stop?
- The Fear.
- What are you talking about? Fear of what?
He had that fear for a long time,
since that night when she heard those voices.
- And then the woman he saw at the library.
- That was pure imagination.
You saw Aurora´s face after her death.
Those fixed eyes, opened, full of fear...
...I´ve been many hours here,
I keep asking myself...
What could it be the last thing she saw?
Sofía, Pilar told me you wanted
to talk with me.
- Don´t you think it´s quite excessive to put
flowers on a cat´s tomb? - Why?
- That´s what they do in all the tombs.
- People´s tombs - It´s the same.
They are lovely beings that we´ve lost.
Your aunt thought the same way.
Ok. What did you want it to talk with me?
- This´d be the last week at your service, Miss.
- Why Sofía?
- Perhaps you don´t understand my reasons.
- Tell me, I´ve right to know.
I knew Bequer´s death would brings disgrace.
- And you already´ve saw what happened with Miss Aurora.
-  What does that have to do with the cat´s death?
No with the cat.
- I meant, with your aunt...
- My aunt is dead!
- Your aunt is here.
- Please, Sofía!
I don´t know how you didn´t realize earlier.
Your aunt´s presence is in every corner
of this house...
I´ve heard her crying through the nights
for Bequer´s death...
I´ve seen her wandering in the corridors,
looking through the windows.
You must be out of your mind.
I knew you wouldn´t understand me.
But when I left, you´ll continue
to find flowers on Bequer´s tomb.
- Why does she wants to leave?
- She gave me some silly reasons. I think we don´t like her.
- I knew it, I already imagined this.
- I asked her to stay until we find a new maid.
I don´t want to put such weight on Pilar.
- By the way, why did you take me out when Roberto arrived?
- They´ve to talk alone.
- Do you think he´ll convince her?
- I don´t know but I assure you, he´s trying.
No, Roberto, no!
This ain´t all right...
- I can make it better if you let me.
- Don´t make fun of it.
- You know what I´m talking about.
- What´s wrong with that? You´re my wife, didn´t you?
- Your ex!
- Nonsense!
What´s more,
you agreed to come back to the house today.
No, don´t rush me.
I only promised to think about.
But I haven´t decided anything yet.
You can´t do this to me. I had everything arranged,
I even put flowers in all the house.
The guys are arranging a party tomorrow
at Daniel´s place.
I´m really sorry, Roberto.
But...
I want to be sure.
Ok, like you want it.
At least you can come with me
to the party.
They´ll be pleased to see you.
- Well... It´s possible if you promess to act formal.
- Of course!
- We´ll remember our old times.
- No way. I said act formal.
Do you remember?
You were a pain in the ass.
But you loved me.
And you love me.
Would you like something, Miss?
Nothing, Sofía. Thanks, you can go.
Don´t you prefer I wait for Miss Ofelia?
- Maybe she wants to dinner when she come back.
- No, she went with Marta to the theater.
- I´m sure they´ll dinner in some place else.
- Do you wish I make you some company?
- Can I ask why?
- It´s very late, you´re alone...
...and you could be scared.
No, Sofía. I don´t believe in ghosts,
if that´s what you mean.
Excuse me, people usually have fear
of these old houses.
Good night.
Who is it?!
Who´s there?!
Sofía, is it you?!
Sofía!
Miss, what are you doing here?
No, I didn´t see anything but...
It was her!
I´m sure!
- That´s not possible, Pilar.
Did you see anything Sofía?
No, Miss.
But I didn´t enter in the cellar.
Why don´t you want to admit strange
things are happening in this house?
- Of course I admit that but please
try some logical reasons! - It was her!
- Right, Sofía? You know it was her!
- It´s not me who you need to convince.
Why don´t you listen to me and go
to sleep? You really need it.
- Go with her, Sofía.
- Yes, Miss.
Do you know what´s our problem?
- Aurora´s death have us very nervous.
- Yes, maybe.
The good thing is Roberto will come tomorrow.
He´ll take out to a meeting and everything´s forgotten.
What´s wrong?
Nothing. Why?
Did you realize I´m here with you?
I´m sorry. I was distracted.
Thinking about your ghost?
- If you´re going to make fun of me...!
- It´s just that you haven´t thought about nothing else all night long.
Damn! I never thought I´ll be
jealous of a ghost.
You take things lightly`cause you don´t
have to return to the house.
What a boring couple!
Why don´t you dance?
Do we?
- No, Roberto. I´m not in the mood.
- C´mon, don´t be like that.
Like the old times, come on...
Follow her, you idiot!
Follow her!
Pilar!
What happened?
You´re the same as always.
You don´t care about my problems.
There isn´t any problem!
If you don´t want to come back to that house, don´t do it!
Come with me and that´s the end of story.
I don´t know...
I don´t know!
Listen... I know I made things wrong.
But, what do you prefer?
Spend the night with a ghost or with me?
You fool...
- Let´s see Ofelia´s face when I tell her!
- Better... you better see it tomorrow with more light!
- I must let her know so she doesn´t worry.
- You should´ve called her by telephone.
What?!
- I won´t be long...
- Ok...
Bring all your clothes!
What happened?
- I don´t know...
- Let´s carry her upstairs!
Don´t get close.
She´s dead.
Did you want something, Sofía?
No.
I just wanted to see this bedroom one last time.
It´s ok.
Believe me. It´s not easy.
This is the house where I´ve lived for many years.
It´s full of memories...
It´s a part of myself.
- You don´t have to leave. Nobody is forcing you.
You already know my reasons.
- You´re really convinced that Marta and I, are in danger.
- Yes. That´s what I think.
Sofía.
- Do you think it´s appropiate to leave us at this moment?
- Miss Ofelia, I´m the first to regret what will happen here.
But nor I or anybody can help it.
Hello?
Yes, Pedro. It´s me.
What happened?
Oh, I see...
So..?
Ok...
- No, no... Why I would be angry? Kiss, bye.
- He won´t be coming?
- He doesn´t even knows when. He´s in a meeting business.
- Well... It´s not so terrible news, isn´it?
I already had the ilusion he´d take us out to dinner.
I know what we´ll do.
We´ll arrange a party the both of us!
- Are you crazy? - No at all. We have alcohol, some sandwiches, put music,
let´s prove men they´re not indispensables.
Sofía is a woman with strong ideas. She took her things and left.
- Yes, she said goodbye to me.
- She seemed scared.
- I don´t regret it. She was influencing us with her strange ideas.
- Now the house is very lonely.
- That´s why I wanted you to come with Pedro and me.
That´s silly. You can´t keep me company every night.
Well, at least until...
I´m not sure...
A change, some days pass... or...
- Or aunt Susana kill one of us.
- Marta!
- Why don´t you admit it, Ofelia?
It wasn´t a heart attack or a fall
what killed Aurora and Pilar...
It was the fear.
What about? A ghost?
- Both of them saw her.
- That´s what they believed.
They saw her because she´s
here among us.
This house is full of her perfume
and her cryings...
You sound like Sofía.
Yes...
Because I feel like her the
presence of this woman.
I feel her in the dark threatened us...
Watching us with her cold eyes...
Stop the nonsense, Marta!
Aunt Susana is dead,
no one ever come back from there.
What happened?!
The lights turned off.
There´s nothing to be worried about.
I´m going to light some candles.
I don´t like it this way.
Let´s flare up the fire!
We´re going to have a beautiful fire!
- What if there´s not enough wood?
- This won´t take too long.
- Of course! I should have known. I´m going to check the switch.
- You´ll get soaking wet.
I won´t take long.
Rain almost stop.
- What happens?
- Is her! Is her!
- Who?!
- The old woman is there!
How this got here?
- It wasn´t here!
- Do you believe me now? - Did you see her?
I saw her hand, she had her ring.
Can you see how you´re imagining things?
The ring is in my bedroom, inside the box!
Are you sure?
No! Don´t go to that room,
She´s in there...
We´ll see about that.
There´s no one here.
And, of course, the ring is...
Isn´t there...
- Do you believe me now?
- Yes...
But... I can´t understand.
She´s taking revenge for Bequer´s death.
That´s the most unfair thing I´ve ever listened.
Bequer´s death was an accident, a distraction.
Nobody wanted to hurt him.
And now she wants to claim with 4 women lives.
Now I know what aunt Susana was...
... and old, twisted and cruel woman.
Ofelia, listen to me.
Tomorrow, I´ll throw that portrait in the fire!
I don´t want to see it ever again!
Ofelia, there´s something you must know...
...Bequer´s death it´s our own fault.
- I know that! But you didn´t know about the cat locked inside.
No...
That´s what we told you for you
don´t get angry with us.
It was a lie.
What are you saying?
The day Aurora found her canary dead,
she had a fit of rage.
We couldn´t stop her.
She took a poker and search for Bequer in the entire house.
Finally, she found it in aunt Susana´s bedroom.
She attacked and beat it many times.
Bequer mew in a horrible sort of way.
Suddenly, it trew over her.
Aurora screamed, terrified.
Pilar and I tried to help her.
Fear seized us.
I took the poker from the floor.
Pilar took the candelabra...
Bequer didn´t die of hunger.
We beat him to death.
How could you do it?!
I´ve regreted it a hundred times. I swear you.
Everything happened so fast.
- No! That was a crime!
- I know. You have nothing to do with it.
She´s taking revenge on us.
- I´m the only one left.
- You´re in danger... We must leave this place!
What for?
There´s nothing we can do now.
I´m marked.
Maybe if we get out of this house!
Aurora died in the library.
Far from this house.
Pedro´s here!
Let´s go, Marta! Let´s go!
It´s all useless, useless...
I go to get Pedro.
He´ll protect us!
Pedro, I can´t open!
- What happens!?
- I can´t explain you now! Jump the fence!
- But, what happens?!
- Marta is in danger! Jump!
Marta!
Marta, where are you?
Pedro!
Take me out of here, Pedro!
Subs by pepe
Exclusively for Cinemageddon