Robbery. Don't move
Be quick, you fool
Careful
Six consecutive robberies
in Nathan Road
The gang escapes...
towards the border now
Stand still, or I'll shoot
Inside Chinese territory at last
What can you do to us?
See you after 1997
Robbing 6 shops in 13 minutes
Clean methods
They used Viet automatic pistols,
and Soviet V3 grenade
Can they be our cadets?
School dropout maybe
Superman, what do you think?
Surely win, except Nanny
Nanny?
I'm waiting for you guys only
No guns this time
To seize them within 1 3 minutes, OK?
No problem
See who'll lose
Wait for me
Why it swings?
Damned. I'm too heavy
to jump...
such high fences
Bastards' idea
Some motorbikes coming
Run
Superman, join forces?
I'm OK on my own
Leave me
Goodnight
You'll lose for sure
You cheat
Boomerang
Ferocious gale. Shit
Try my archery skills
Flying Dragon Kick
If you can avoid me,
then I can't be Archet Tiny
Blazing wheels
Bear in mind, I'm Dragon
Eighteenth dragon kicks
Shao Lin Monk at your service
Another fool
Don't move
Go away, fatty
Calm down, your hands shake
Your mouth is parched,
hands sweating, weak limbs
To hold a gun like this
It is dangerous
Listen to me. Go and confess
Put down your gun
Shut up and go to hell
Want a fight?
Dare to shoot Nanny,
the best doctor of China
Thunderous thrust
Spinning
Snake moves
Watch my fist
In 3 minutes, I like breaking records
Stay. It's grenade
Move and you'll die
Who are these guys?
Who bind them?
Report to headquarters
Yes sir
As the Special Force Squad
We always emphasize impartiality
Any offense will be penalized,
even when stationed abroad
Steelbar, according to military rules,
I'll use level 3 penalty. Any objection?
I'm betrayed
That's slander
We've always been good pals
Don't make excuses
Execution
Superman, you have guts
Monk, you're cruel
Don't throw so hard
Tiny, you spiteful chit
No wonder you're single
None of your business
Nanny, give me back $5000
Superman, I won't forget this
A durian for you
You'll have your retribution!
Ha! In the water
Durian brings you bad luck
Girl bitten to death in Tai Po
Please hurry to the spot
In Chun Fung Street shopping centre
a man...
Can I have some peace?
Are you really a monk?
I'm taking out the spikes
I'm helping you
But you're tearing my hair
Just checking your scalp too
Come and taste roasted pork
It's really delicious
It's hot
Eat
It's real good
For our future restaurant
We all depend on this dish
Remember to pay the instalments on time
Don't sigh while you eat
Let me give you a puzzle,
see who've got the highest IQ
It's one of the human organs
Listen carefully
Pa, Mum can touch but not sister
Brother can but not sister
Grandma, can, Granny can't
Make a guess
I know
Stop! It's disgusting
What're you thinking?
There
Leave me alone. You're dirty
Fei, can you guess
Lips
Excellent! You're our leader indeed
Lips?
Whose lips?
Pa and Mum can touch,
but sister and brother can't
Fat Nanny,
Fat auntie can, uncle can't
Right
Fat Auntie can, uncle can't
Jacky Cheung can't
Mimi can touch twice
Funny
Nanny, more please
Someone's here
Move
Dragon, yours
Monk, yours
He's quite good
How do you know?
Let's give him a treat
Good
No more fooling around
Chief?
Colonel Yim,
what do you think of them?
Thanks God you stop them
Let me introduce comrade Yim
Colonel of southwestern army
He'll explain your mission later
They're...
HK based Special Forces Squad
Salute
Come on in
Here we go
Yeung, Major of SW army
He plots with US ammunition suppliers,
selling arms to terrorists
Last week he arrived in HK secretly
Planning to make another deal
Your duty is
to arrest Yeung
and to get all their bank cards
So, we can go to Bank of Switzerland
and open the safe deposit box
There're diamonds worth of $1 20 millions
It belongs to our country
How about our roles?
I've made arrangements
To be the beggars again?
You want to be the governor?
What about these suppliers?
They've got close ties with FBI?
No
It involves two competing governments
Use your assumed roles
Don't ever disclose your true identities
Sit down
Dragon, some news for you
You'll retire soon
Why?
We've found your mum...
in China
My mum?
Really?
Congratulations!
You're not orphan anymore
Chief, what's she like?
I've not seen her also
I know
Same as fat Nanny
What's bad about me?
For Dragon and Colonel! Cheer
Cheers...
Ready?
OK
Let's play
I'm busy
Could you stop playing?
Listen
Look for a good position
For hiding and retreating
Don't play. I'll check over there
Yes sir
Hurry up. Is it OK?
Higher, a little bit more
What's bothering you?
Careful, miss
Look out!
Help! I can't swim
How can you try to save me?
I forgot I can't swim
Sure that I can?
Anyway, save me...
I don't have my swim suit
Bye!
My God
Answer me
I've got you
I thought you're smart
but tricked nonetheless
You're funny, I like that
You flirt girls often like this?
Only this time
Looking for you?
Yes
I must go
Go and flirt more girls then
Brother, you swam?
What happened? You're wet
Come here
I tested these currents just now
Swim away,
if thing get worse tomorrow
How could he think so?
Why can't we take a boat?
It's more expensive
Let's go
Is it expensive taking a boat?
I make it
A balloon for you
Please support Arts Festival
Any special programme?
Give your support please
Steelbar, suspicious persons
Leather coat,
sun glasses and mobile phones
They're behind you
Can you see?
Any others?
Yes, 2 men in suits
They look evil
It look there's much danger ahead
Are we exposed?
Attention! Some changes!
Forget the man in leather coat
He isn't our target
The 2 men had exposed themselves
They're blinds
We're in a good situation
What happened?
Nanny? I can't hear you
Brat, I'll kill you
What? Who to kill?
Kid, get lost
Stop playing with kids now
Situation is under control
Attention! Target appears
Where?
It's moving...
towards centre
He finds his confederate
Attention
Move to the left side of dragon head
Ready
They meet
Standby, everyone
Too many balloons block our sight
We can see now
A lady, long hair, dark glasses,
dressed in red
Let's go
Verified
Attention! "A shark is coming" Accidents
It's going to the "target"
Tsun
Why killed Yeung?
Raise the dragon
Come later
What happened
Tiny's ready to stop him
Get off
Untie strings
Where we go?
We don't know
Stay
Gigantic leap
Dragon spits
Dragon tail flies
Go to hell
Nanny raise dragon
Get it
Go
Flying dragon
Where to go?
It's you?
Surprise?
You like me, so! Chasing after me?
Give me the card
Get down
You're an obedient girl
I'm not free today
See you next time
Why killed Yeung? There's no such order
Our heads also want his share
They're afraid of a breakup with Chinese
So it's left for me
I did for the group only
They've a good reputation
You're cheated by those old devils
I've seen through their pretence
I don't want to argue
How you explain to Sun without the card?
I don't need to report to anyone
I know where it is
What about yours?
Ying, think about it
If we've those diamonds,
we'll be rich
You know what you're saying?
We'll have our babies
Get away
Keep in mind, we're only partners
What's mine is mine
1 died and 4 injured
Police suspected triad feud
Unbelievable, we as triads this time
Without those guys,
police may have traced to us
Nanny, gentler please
Stay
Don't twist
Even steps please
I've seen the design, no good
The kitchen faces west. Unlucky
As we rely on it for our livelihood
Let's tear it down
Nanny?
I don't mind,
do what you say
In catering industry,
relationship is what counts
Thus the post of manager
It should be mine
No, it's too much work for you
A double bonus for you. OK?
How about a good-looking secretary
It's all arranged,
3 days work only
Working hour are 1 0 to 4
It can be changed,
if you are not satisfied
Does it sound great?
It sounds too good to be true
What are you discussing?
Brother, is it done?
Sure
What's up?
Anything I shouldn't know?
Do you want to know?
Pay this month's instalment first
What a good memory
Help yourself. It's in my pocket
You always take the advantage
It's paid. What's up?
Nanny, tell him
We sold the shop
What? Sold it?
How about the money?
For Dragon to bring home
Our money goes for nothing,
and he takes all our money home?
It's unfair
He has a mother. So what?
I'm back
Shut up, Dragon's back
Help out
Good son, you bought so many things home
Isn't it great? Crazy shopping
How nice, a family reunion!
And we...
Shut up. You big mouth
Big mouth?
He's out of mind after dragon dance
Don't mind him
Dragon, we've something for you
What a coincidence! Me too
I want to take all my pension fund
to pay for the shop
To show my appreciation
Are you crazy?
Save it for rainy days
Get up. Stop complaining now
It sounds better
I thought that we'll have nothing left
But it's not that bad
The shop is our dream
If you do this
I won't be grateful and happy
Everyone has contributed
the shop will be opened somehow
Come and help us in your spare time
Right, we'll pay
Good. It's settled now
As you said. I'll be the manager
With double bonus
Lovely secretary
1 0 to 4
It's fixed
Who made this promise?
Not me
I don't know. I didn't say anything
Keep the words. Hey...
I promise you
Throw him into the water
A 7 years old girl lost in Kwun Tong
Anybody get it. Please report
Time's up
Suicide in 1 2 Ho Man Tin Road
Please go to the location. Over
How do you know I'm in good mood today?
We have the same mind
Aren't you waiting for me?
As we understand each other so much
Let's sit down and talk business
Good. Come over
Liar
Go? Our business isn't finished
Here's more comfortable
Try my whip
You're wonderful
So is your figure
Filthy
Go into the water
Not bad but it can be better
Let me pull you up
Show me
Your pose is awkful
Teach me then
Let us make a deal first
A big deal? Can we talk ashore?
No. You're cunning
Here is safer
OK, go ahead
Give me the card
We'll share its contents
AIright
Give me yours. I'll call you later
No sincerity
Take it out
You think I'm that dumb?
To hide the card here?
Name your conditions
Tell me first
How do you know our place?
Well. It's a trade secret
Exchange it with the card
Nothing to lose
I don't like to lose
What's your name? Dear client
Ying and you're Fei
It's my business name only
When are you free?
Wait until I'm in a good mood
Brother Tsun
Tsun,
the group appoints you to get the card
I don't care how you work it out
But I've to scrutinize your work
You know, certain things are laboo?
What I've done?
As the legal consultant of company
if you're charged of trafficking
We'll ignore you
We have our plans here
1 99 7 is coming
All quarters've their eyes here
We must consolidate...
our position
Is it worthy it
for such small sums of money?
Cocaine is found in his possession
He's your man. He's left to you
O.K.
Brother Tsun?
You know what to do?
Yes. I won't be that dumb
to have you stepped on my goods
What happened?
I've reserved...
a table for us
I've business with Sun
Be quick. I'll wait for you
What happening?
It's dangerous to appoint him
He did the cocaine business
Yes
What's your plan?
After you get back the cards
I'll have him transferred to US
He's out of control here
He's a mad dog. Be careful
So do you
Chief, our place has been searched today
They're fast
I suspect there're spies
Be more careful
I know
I've got details...
about these 2 Chinese
We've to get their card soonest
Of course you want to get away
So you don't have to bear with us
Chief have pity on us
Find us some relatives
You all should plan for your future
You're going to open a shop soon?
You've checked us also?
Not on purpose
I just admire you all
You wait for me
I'll hand this card to messenger
Dragon, go along with Chief
I'll be safer
I'll call you if anything happens
Chief, you like to join our venture?
I can't afford it
Messenger?
He's shot
Chief, it's dangerous here
No one should know about our coming here
Be strong
Run with the card
Chief
Don't go
Dragon
Dragon, where're you?
Dragon...
Fei, what's up?
Who are you?
Why are you handcuffed
Where's Dragon and Chief?
Dragon's injured by my shot
Chief is dead
You shot Dragon
Calm down
Listen to him
Sergeant Cheung is
in charge of this case
I'll take the suspect
Yes, sir
Who are these guys?
Friends of the suspect
Tell them to leave
Or handcuff them as well
Get off
Stay
Where are you bringing him?
I don't need to explain
Take them along
Stop
Sergeant Cheung?
China News Agency!
Who's Sergeant Cheung?
I am
Agent of HK Government
They're members
of Chinese Security Bureau
This case is closed
Endorsed by the Commissioner of Police
All evidence will be transferred
to the Chinese
Hope your subordinates'll behave
We shouldn't always have
to clean up the mess
That's our business
Be smarter next time
You won't be needing us if you're smart
You're all talk!
Shut up! You're all under suspicion
Take Fei away
Yes
Let's go
I want to see Dragon
Suspect has no right to request
Colonel Yim
Grant him 5 minutes
I'll guarantee him
Wait for you outside
Open his handcuffs
Why was he beaten?
What's it to you?
He's shot before I hurt him
Dragon, wake up
Fei, you're in a messed up situation
If you don't tell the truth
I can't help you
I want to know too
Only Dragon has the facts
Still, you shouldn't have shot him
You think I hurt him intentionally?
You accusing me?
Monk, you judge
Amen
Damp
Amen? Shit
So you trust me?
I trust you
But the Superiors won't bend
Fei'll be charged
with stealing national secret
It'll be treason
But he's got no chance to plea
We work hard to you
I'll resign if you take him
We will too
As a Chinese security enforcer
One must obey the rules
Colonel, I'll go with you
Fei
Brother
Take care of Dragon
Fei
Too rash just now. Sorry
I know your temper
We'll think of something
When are we leaving Hong Kong?
We're nearing that border
Those scums
The truck's stolen
You thieves
What?
Nothing. Go to hell
Brother. Let's go
Fei
I don't plan to leave
You kidding?
After your play-acting in the hospital
We acted our parts well
I saw you making signs
Now the container is blasted
if you don't go
your charge'll double...
Someone is coming
Let's go
Leaving me so soon?
OK. I'll come with you
We're pals
Hurry to the hospital
Dragon's in deep danger
What happening?
Wheel him out
Use the back door
Unfortunate encounter
Let's separate
So you hasten your end
Brother
Be careful!
Don't fall for the trap
The two fools are over there
After them
Ready
Dash
Give way
A million arrows
Shaolin kicks
Where're you wheeling the patient?
He's recovered
I'm taking a leak
No more fooling around
Move over
Catch him
Run
They've escaped
Abbot, sorry for disturbing you
Not at all, Amen
The monastery welcomes all
because of your generous support in past
Please feel free here
and make yourselves at home
Thanks
Boiling water
Is the medicine ready?
Yes, but he's still unconscious
Warm it then
Nanny? How is it?
Will he awake?
Sure
He's got a blessed face
good forehead
Bright eyes
You can tell even with his eyes closed?
When'll he get up?
Ask him
Shit
Wake up soon, or I'll curse you
Sleep?
Our first priority...
is to get the gang's card
Then the lost card'll be useless
Don't waste any time
or we'll stay indefinitely
Attending to Dragon
Focus on the fellows in the hospital
Shadow them
Seize the chance
Fei, give up on that woman
What woman?
I'm worried about you
You're falling into their trap
What trap?
Right in front of you
Don't make guesses
I'm concerned
About what?
Beware of whom?
Have you nothing else to do?
Go on with your business
Let's eat
Better than being scolded
After Fei and his pals escaped
They carried off Dragon
No news yet
They'll focus on the gang
Cancel that region's arrest
Let's seize the real culprits
Shadow the pair
Call it off in 3 minutes
I taught you guys
I'll be waiting
Don't fail me
Thought it out?
Want a deal?
I brought the card
How do I know it isn't a trap?
How can I trust you?
I've got the card on me
It depends on your guts
This is my place
You ain't afraid of me using force?
Force?
You've seen my powers
It's crowded. Let's talk outside
There's a fly in here
Call them
The card?
Follow me home...
So you want me and not the card
I want the truth about the coliseum
You've come to the wrong place
Are you hurt?
Move...
Mommy
Don't fire
Get down
After them!
Shut down all exits
Follow me
Our man's here
Go south. You're rescued
Thanks
Fei
Take the gun
I thought you wanted the card
If I did,
I wouldn't be helping you escape
Take care
Be on your guard
Those aren't my men
They're from Security Bureau
Come to catch me
but they won't let you go either
Disgusting
You're surrounded
Don't resist
It'll be easier if you surrender
You've got no choice
Come out!
Fei, I know you're here
Don't resist
Come and surrender
It's crowded in here
Only one of us can stay
You're a smooth talker
but good-natured
I don't mind you staying here
If we stay longer,
you may grow fond of me
No excuses
To be truthful
I don't want to leave
Take this gun
Fei
The coliseum wasn't our fault
I didn't harm your friend
Teach me diving sometime
You lose
And you win?
Do you think you can escape?
You like to win by outnumbering
Pass the card
The penalty could be lighter
Discussing conditions already?
Afraid of me?
You want to fight with me
OK. Take the knife
Don't forget my Kung-fu
You embarrass me
I wasted my efforts
Stop
A gun's enough
No need for Kung-fu
Why'd you come back?
I thought of some new moves
What moves?
None of your business
Let him go
Leave the gang
Now I'm the boss
Tell your people to get off
Fire then
I don't want your life
I need time
To catch the killer
I'll bring the card too
Good. Let me see
My best student at work
I'll give you 48 hours
Let them go
Practise your new moves
Coach. I promise
After learning it
I'll show you. Let's go
Thanks for coming to my rescue
I'm also helping myself
Let's separate
You're hurt. Want my support?
I'm alright
I'm afraid of losing face
Which of us go first?
Both, I hope
But I've only got 48 hours
Bye, then
Bye
Remember to teach me diving
Fei
Dragon's awake
No kidding?
Brother is back
Brother...
Where did you go last night?
You're late
Fei, you're hurt
and bleeding
Just a scratch
You alright?
How's Dragon first?
Good....you're with us
I had a dream. You were...
...all killed
You weren't dreaming
While rescuing you
We were shot
We got you here
Incredible that
We come to this
Is he really conscious?
Remember how we became Special Forces?
Ever see "Pao, the Judge"?
Watching "Superman"?
Remember my mum?
Just like me
Nanny, I'm not dumb
We're alive
Have to get the card
Where?
It was dangerous
The killer covered me
I put the card in a seat
Row H No. 53
In between the lining
Let's go
Hold on
I've got something to tell you
Coach's here
Coach?
His proteges?
I met them last night
You escaped unharmed?
I'm lucky
Is it the one in the hospital?
Who?
That's...
Keep it a secret
I'll tell you later
Go and get the card first
Nanny
I'll look after Dragon
Prepare for victory
Be ready in 1 0 minutes
OK OK
Colonel
Dragon is awake
They're going to get the card
Keep in touch
They're ready
Good work
Enjoy yourselves
Tsun
What is it?
I've something to say. Follow me
OK. You stay
The company's decided to let you go
A plane leaves
for the U.S. this afternoon
You're keeping me from making money
Ying'll take up your duties
She knows nothing
I'll tell her
Anything else?
You can go
Right, Sun
Go to hell
I'm boss now
He did it on purpose
Go after them
Got the card. Don't make a scene
No one can outdo Superman
I'll chase after him
Look after him
All by yourself?
You ain't qualified
Let me deal with him
You know...
we've been trapped?
This could be your grave,
satisfied?
I'd consider...
sending your corpse to U.S.
Your mum must an idiot
with such dumb kids
I forgot you're orphans
You mum must be illiterate Indian
You shouldn't say that!
You bet!
Just watch how
See how the Indian in war
The game is not over yet. Stay!
I won't let him go easily
Superman, don't chase
Watch out!
Run
Superman!
Hang on
I will
Superman...
How're you?
Pull him out
On my bike
Superman...wake up...
Wake...
Don't push me
You promised me the manager's post
OK
Tiny
I'm here
You promised a pretty secretary
I've already advertised
Superman
Monk, promise me...
I'll promise anything
Brother
What?
Finally I can...
...be the leader
But it's a difficult position
I promise, if I...
...survive this, I'll follow your orders
Superman
Wake up!
Superman...
He's returning to his origins
Don't ask. Don't talk
We understand each other
Wrapped in the candlelight of the moment
Let's spend it quietly
Don't wave. Don't turn
When I sing this song
I'm afraid I'll weep
Hope my laughter will stay in your mind
To share with you every season
Grief and misery
Life is full of sorrows
It's after you've lossed that
you treasure
Hard to make you stay
But when we part
Every memory will remain
Hope my laugh will stay in your mind
To share with you every season
Farewell is coming
Hope our reunion is near
Chance may throw us together
We'll meet again someday
Tiny said you released the enemy
I don't care what your relationship is
We've got to avenge Superman's life
I won't trouble others
He called me Brother
I must do something
How many do you need?
Twenty is enough
You got it
Anything else?
Let me introduce
Colonel Yim
Colonel's my best business partner
My girl, Ying
Nice to meet you
Hi
Our deal's almost done
When Fei meets Colonel at the pier
I'll kill him and get his card
How about celebrating afterwards?
Got to finish off his partners too
Maybe a party at night
What do you think?
Does Sun know?
I forgot to tell you,
I've killed him
Well done
Your next move?
It'll be our big day
Congratulations! A perfect match
I know
Excuse me
Miss Ying's coming towards the lobby
Let her go
Yes
Miss...
You can leave me once
But you'll always be mine
I want to see Fei
Steelbar
What do you want?
Calm down
Fire then
Let's see what she's got to say
I'm harmless
Tell Fei
If he met Colonel tomorrow,
he'll need an extra life,
or a coffin
I want your life now
Save yourselves first
Even I know your hiding place
You think you're safe?
Whatever your relation with Fei is,
I'm taking revenge for Superman
If I wanted to kill you
You wouldn't be speaking here
You arguing with me
Why help Fei?
Who're you?
I'm not his girl
But why'd you help him that much?
We were both betrayed for the card
In helping him
I also helped myself
Understand?
Go to Kau To Shan
Maybe he's there
How'd you find me?
Ying told me
Don't meet Yim tomorrow
He's the spy
I must go, for Superman's sake
Where's our hiding place tonight?
Where are they?
They're gone
To where?
I don't know
After I finished the call...
Shit!
Wah...
Who?
Come out
What's up?
Come
Where can we hide?
To the stable
Over there?
Follow me
Be careful
Take care...
It's a roof over our heads
Careful
Cold?
Yes
Take the clothes
You may catch a cold
Hang on
Colonel, you killed chief,
injured Dragon for these diamonds
Want me as a substitute?
It's a serious offence
I can sentence you to death
Plenty of opportunities in this age
We should all plan for future
Even if we're honest
You think
the money'll be returned unopened?
You cops are crooks
The officials are cheats
With people like you, life is hard
What about our lives as soldiers?
You're always complaining the government
What's your contribution to the country?
Your life?
I salute you
You're bad
Don't count us in
Stop moving your head
and hands
And me
Brother...
Why do you come?
You haven't paid this month's instalment
Buddies, relax
You come here for money
We can't lose you after Superman
I'm still alive. Disappointed?
Only a matter of time
I'll visit tomorrow
Plan on it
Good. I'll prepare a death game
With fabulous prizes
Apart from the card
Our lives
Are you in?
I'll come
Good
Don't be scared
Climax's coming
Miss, careful
Take care
You're a smooth talker
but good-natured
I don't mind you staying here
If we stay longer,
you may grow fond of me
Mum
Come over here
It's cold
Give me a kiss
Let Pa carry you
Monk, are you mad?
Why're you holding a wooden fish?
Let me show you
Worship'll bring God's blessing
Worship me then
I'm the Gun God
I'll come with you
No. Wake us up tomorrow instead
I can still shoot
We know, but no
You stay and open the shop
Despite the number of us returning
The shop must open
I don't want to live here
Here's without any possessions
I promise
Promise me too
For the shop, come back on time
Of course!
Even if they don't, I'll
Lucky to all
Just kidding, sorry
Don't forget
The deadline's in 48 hours
Coach'll come anytime
We can't choose
Try our best
Ready
Go
You plan it?
What do you think?
You decide
Are we smart today?
Very. So I'm dressed up
Go
Good morning
You look refreshed
and prepared
Don't be nervous
I'm the host, welcome to all
Ying
You also interested in this game?
The prizes must be attractive
But I'm fair
You got to obey the rules too
There's still time to change your mind
My ring's still yours
Come over
Your death is looming
Leave the ring for your burial
Is your show over?
Brought the card?
Can't you see?
Prizes are on the 60th floors
but whether you can get it...
I want nothing
but you, bastard
Game starts
Flying dragons
Dual dragons
Dormant dragon strikes
Marble spill
Dragon phoenix dance
Come over here
The ground is cleared
Let's split
Where's security?
1 0th floors
We'll meet on the 30th floors
If we come out alive
What's your plan?
Back to U.S.
You promised to teach me diving?
February is too cold
But I've heard by then
The Great Wall's Scenery is much better
I want you to take me
Fei went in 1 0 minutes ago
He's now advancing
We've closed down nearby streets
OK
If I don't come out in 30 minutes,
blast the building
Yes, sir
6 fools following me
They's here
Where?
Dragon butt
Two grenades for you
Boss, security's bombed
Coming to climax
You continuing
Yes
Fei, say hello to your pal
He won't submit
You don't want to see Dragon?
Set him free and the card's yours
Sharp
You'd demean yourself for a card
You the killer in the coliseum?
Am I a good shot?
You're so damn proud?
You've no right to criticize me
He confessed. Over to you
You can try
Dragon
You nearly fooled us
I told you before
It's you who see me as a handicap
This makes 7 at us
Fei, I've come
Coach, you're late
Don't worry
We'll meet soon
You take care
I miss the others
We'll hold a graduation dinner
Enjoy yourself
To gain time, we'll stay
You two catch Tsun
OK?
Well deserved
Next party
Fei, you're worse
48th floors took you 20 minutes
You failed this exam
I respect old man only
Which floor are you on?
Want my help?
I'm always on top of you
Fei, what happen?
He's taken to gondola by Coach
Hurry
So at ease?
Coach, get it?
Take my hand
Who's this bald-head?
He's interrupting our game
I can't join in, no fun
Let me finish him off
No
Why?
You don't want to play with me?
Give me the card for safe keeping
I'll be the judge for you two
Don't think of escaping
If I don't get out in 1 0 minutes
They'll blast the building
So I save much work?
Thanks!
Bald-head, you're quite something
Better than Fei
I'm a little aversed to see you die
Fei, give me the card
Only I can order you
You can't
If you weren't so stupid
You wouldn't be reduce to this
Release me first
I'll get out myself
The prize is drawn
Game's finished
Prepare to die
Wait! Another player
Want to continue?
Wonderful
Wait!
Continue by yourself?
One more time
All for this guy?
I'll play anyway
Hold tight
Are you crazy?
All for you
Ying
Give me your gun
I'm falling
Hold my leg
Your shoes won't fall off?
3 minutes before the blast, over
Retreat
Yes
Fei, I've lost contact with them
This building will blow up in 2 minutes
Tell them to retreat
Or it'll be too late
Listen, all lifts have stopped
Try to...
get down in 2 minutes
Give the walkie-talkie to bomb experts
or we'll die
But we're on 52th floors
I'm on 58th floors
See you
Hurry
Dragon, how's your leg?
Fine. Hurry
40th floors? Let's try our luck!
I want to know something
What did the girl teach you?
I won't tell the others
Really want to know?
Tell me
Teach you after I learn it
Count down to explosion
1 0, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5...
4, 3, 2, 1 ...
Wait
Take it
Coach has something to say
Coach?
Whoever you're, stop the blast
Amen
You should jump earlier
I'm breathless!
You're lucky
to have escaped death
Fight next time
Take out the card
Ask my gun first
Fei
Bye
Blast this lift!
Fei's in life no. 3. It's sinking
Damn! How to save him?
He dies this way?
God'll come in
Buddha's spirit
A million Buddha
How'll it be?
Ying, give me your hands
Hold tight
Don't go...
I'm cold. Don't leave me
The cord's about to break
Your hands...
Save me in the end
You don't want me to die
Come over here
Get away
Coach, blow up the building?
Shit! I'm the only one in here
Send someone to help
Ying
Our present to you
No harm
An invitation
to our restaurant's opening
Wait till the shop opens
Are you going to change jobs?
Why don't you join us?
Too nice an offer
Wait till...
I settle my affairs in U.S.
Bye
Brother, we tried our best
See her off
Success depends, go
You all want me to go?
Shamming?
I'll see you off
Giving me the card?
What about your boss?
Stay, if you can't leave me
Which do you want, card or me?
Both
Greedy pig!
Card? She wants me
If works!