Yeah, dudes. Welcome to your Dumb Ass
Show. l am your Sky Commander Winky.
- And this is the beautiful Captain Dare.
- Yeah, baby.
- The biggest dumb-ass l know.
- Thank you, Sky Commander.
Captain Dare will show you
what a dumb-ass he really is.
But be forewarned. Only a stupid dumb-ass
would neglect to take every safety precaution
in the stunts you are about to witness.
Now, the physics alone took
almost five minutes of calculation.
Yeah, dude. Fire when ready.
Oh, mother... What the...
And that's a dumb-ass.
Oh, right in the...
Natalie, come here.
How about a kiss for good luck?
- Bill, why are you doing this?
- His name's Captain Dare.
And he'll be famous one day for
going where no dudes have gone before.
lf you won't give me a kiss,
how about throwing me a magazine?
That is it.
There it is.
That is a dumb-ass.
l'm the man.
What up? Come here.
You want some dirt on you?
And now the awesome Captain Dare
will make Dumb Ass history
in the scientifically modified
shopping cart of doom.
Rolling down this hill, hitting the launch
ramp at an estimated 24.6 miles an hour,
sailing just over
the scrumptious Natalie Gordon,
who will be holding
this flaming torch in her mouth.
- l didn't say l was going to do anything.
- This is the money shot. Captain, tell her.
What could go wrong?
You mean besides landing on me
and crushing my head?
lt'll be killer. The Captain will jump,
her torch will set the cart on fire.
And our daring hero rolling on
to salvation in the pool of life, triumphant.
Natalie, come on.
Just do it for me. Please?
You're gonna freakin' fly, man.
This is gonna be big. You can do this.
- You are the man. Show 'em, dumb-ass.
- l'm the man.
l'm the man. Captain Dumb-Ass,
comin' down. What up.
Bill!
Now that's a dumb-ass.
Come on, Bill, get up.
- Thanks for coming so quickly.
- You the medical examiner?
l'm Dr Fountain.
You're the experts from the FBl?
- ''The experts?''
- l was told you were the experts.
We work on the X-Files.
Our expertise is the unexplained.
- We were told you had an unexplained death.
- You're the experts. You tell me.
Why don't you explain what happened?
Well, l can't. That's the point.
- You can't tell us anything?
- l'd prefer not to go on record.
- Why is that?
- The kid's parents are suing everyone.
- For what?
- Everything.
The county for making the street too steep,
the shop he stole the cart from,
the company that made the helmet he wore.
Off the record, what the hell has that
got to do with a supermarket shopping cart?
- You familiar with The Dumb Ass Show?
- The Dumb Ass Show?
A cable TV show where
kids act like dumb-asses.
- They tape themselves doing stunts.
- This was an accident?
l'd prefer not to get sucked
into a legal nightmare.
You investigate the unexplained.
How about you explain it to me?
Dr Fountain, do you see this?
- What the hell is that?
- You're asking me?
- Thanks for coming so quickly.
- You said ''urgent.''
- What am l looking at?
- Maybe you can tell us.
ls she the expert?
What do you think?
Well, l have to say that l have never
seen anything quite like this before.
Something killed this kid.
Judging from the amount of insect feces
in the ear and nasal cavities,
they fed at such a furious rate that it caused
the boy's skull to collapse from the inside.
His helmet protected his head during
the crash. There is no impact trauma here.
You're saying flies killed him?
Of all the kids at the scene,
flies choose to attack this boy. Why?
Maybe they acted
for reasons we're not seeing.
What if somebody put something
in his helmet? lnsect pheromone.
Spanish Fly, that stuff you see advertised
in magazines that guys use to attract girls.
l glance at 'em for amusement.
l may have to brush up on my Spanish Fly,
but l don't think the science works that way.
Before we look for an MO, l wanna find out
what kind of fly would act that aggressively.
The musca vetustissima Walker,
the Australian bush fly.
lt craves protein so much, it will crawl
into your nose, mouth, ears, even eyes,
to feed on blood and moisture.
The New Zealand screwworm fly
often kills its victims in mere moments
by burrowing into an open wound or cut.
l'm sorry. l'm Dr Rocky Bronzino.
Hi. Rocky Bronzino.
Hello there. Rocky Bronzino.
Field entomological expert,
Rutgers University, at your service.
- Dr Bronzino...
- Rocky.
Neither of these flies are
indigenous to America.
Are you suggesting a virulent foreign vector?
No. Your specimens
are your garden-variety calliphorid,
harmless as, well, flies.
- What are you suggesting, then?
- Nothing.
Dr Fountain brought me in for my scientific
expertise and l must say l'm glad he did.
Dr Bronzino, you should know
we may be looking at a murder.
A murder? Are there any suspects?
Natalie Gordon, the lady in Captain Dare's
short life and the last person to see him alive.
- Leave me alone.
- lt's for the memorial video.
For a fallen hero.
A few words for Captain Dare.
You want a few words, Winky?
You're ajerk, and so's your brother,
for making Bill do those stupid stunts.
Captain Dare died doing what he loved,
pushing the envelope.
Maybe if you weren't such a...
Hey, you. Freaky-Deaky.
You want your own memorial?
You wanna be in Dumb Ass?
Just leave her alone.
l'm talking to you now, freak.
David Winkle. ln my office, right now.
Typical. Lokensgard's gonna have
his mommy stick up for him.
Baby.
That is it. There it is.
l just solved this case. This kid had
crap for brains. The flies couldn't resist.
- And you were a choirboy growing up?
- We were stupid, but we didn't know it.
This isn'tjust stupid, this glorifies stupid.
These kids take pride in being sub-mental.
That's why they call it Dumb Ass.
- Mr David Winkle.
- Sky Pilot Winky.
Just the man we wanna see. Come on in.
- Very entertaining, Sky Pilot.
- Sky Commander.
You can call me Sheriff John
as l haul your dumb ass to jail.
- What are you talkin' about?
- We have a recent email you sent,
offering the video of this death
to the Fox network.
No, l wrote all the networks.
Fox were the only one who were interested.
l don't think you understand.
You think l killed him?
You think l'd kill Captain Dare
to make money? My best friend?
You were the last person
to have contact with him.
You gave him his helmet at the top of the hill.
l think you put something in it.
- Sit down, Sky Commander.
- l can't. l'm being attacked.
Oh, God, it's happening to me.
Now that's a dumb-ass.
Where you been?
Dinner's been on the table an hour.
l'm not hungry.
Then you sit down here until you get hungry.
Dylan?
l have something to talk to you about.
l'm glad you're here. We got our first break.
- What'd you find?
- lt's what Rocky Bronzino found.
The flies that ate at the brain and skull
of the victim are all female. Every one.
- Exactly how is that a break?
- What are the chances of that?
You mean the absence of males suggests
a reason for the attack, behaviorally?
Something biological - hormonal or chemical
- caused these bugs to attack.
- Or a need to express themselves.
- Say what?
The kid known as Sky Commander Winky.
Agent Reyes and l were interviewing him
when this happened.
Paramedics treated him
for an aggressive attack of body lice.
Lice are not uncommon
in a school environment.
But these are better spellers
than most of the kids.
- So is this just another Dumb Ass stunt?
- That was my thought.
But he was too freaked out
to make me believe he'd staged this.
Which makes me think that while
you're right about this being biology,
someone is directing the biology.
How does one direct bugs?
l don't know, but we've been
running down a long list of witnesses.
A loner who was at every Dumb Ass stunt. He
had a run-in with Winky before the lice attack.
His name is Dylan Lokensgard.
We'll talk to him.
He's just not well. He's unable to talk.
Dylan, l wanna have a talk with you.
Honey, can you come out here?
- Where are you going?
- To school.
l know where you're going.
- What did Natalie want?
- Stay away from her. She's no good for you.
We've been friends since we were kids.
But you're not kids any more,
which is why we need to talk.
Your body is going through changes.
You don't understand anything.
l don't wanna talk to you.
l wish Dad was still here.
You know nothing about me.
Honey, l want what's best for you.
Dylan, come back here.
So many flowers, so little time.
- Excuse me?
- Pheromones, Dr Scully. Heavy in the air.
Nature's natural attractants, driving
the insect world to go forth and pollinate.
l'm aware how pheromones work. According
to this there are no pheromones here.
That can't be right.
The sensor is an actual fly antenna,
over which the pheromones pass.
l modified the EAG
to measure in picograms,
making it sensitive
for a mile in any direction.
l still don't see why pheromones might cause
a harmless fly to attack a human, Doctor.
Rocky.
Bugs are small-minded
and therefore very predictable.
They don't have moods.
They react to circumstance and stimuli.
They have been doing it for millennia.
So what do you suppose
they're reacting to out here?
lt may be the bugs are being
somehow driven crazy with desire.
They say we humans
respond to pheromones too.
- l agree with that.
- Women's dormitory syndrome.
Pheromones are the reason that women who
live together share the same menstrual cycle.
Fascinating.
When a male and female calliphorid fly mate,
they are joined for up to one and a half hours.
One and a half, Doctor.
Rocky, l'm a mother.
Mothers are women too.
- Big hit.
- What is it?
A high concentration of C-13 calliphorone.
lncoming.
- Are you all right?
- l'm fine.
- What about your bike?
- l'll get it later.
- l came by your house to see you.
- Really?
Your mom said
something was wrong with you.
Me? No, l'm fine.
What did you want?
l wanted to apologize about
what happened yesterday at the cafeteria.
Winky can be such ajerk.
l was just worried about you.
What did l say?
Nothing.
No one understands.
My mom and dad think
it's just gonna go away.
What l'm feeling.
You mean about Bill?
l wish you could just turn back time.
l wish you could just make everything
go away, and start all over again.
l know, like when we were kids.
Remember that night
we played hide-and-seek on your street?
Manhunt.
We hid in the tree together.
Our names are still carved in it.
l'm gonna be late.
Dylan Lokensgard?
Can you come with us, Dylan?
And now the awesome Captain Dare
will make Dumb Ass history...
- Why are you showing me this?
- What do you think of it?
- You mean The Dumb Ass Show?
- That and the kids who make it.
l know 'em.
You ever have contact with Bill,
the kid who played Captain Dare?
You have anything against him?
Do you think it's strange that
he was attacked and killed by insects?
Who wouldn't?
- What's going on?
- We're talking to Dylan.
No, you're not. Dylan.
No one interrogates my son in my office
without my permission.
- Calm down.
- He's not a part of that crowd.
- What are you accusing him of?
- We're just asking what he knows.
- He doesn't know anything.
- He was at the crime scene.
So were a lot of kids. Dylan...
Too late, gentlemen. The bugs are gone.
Bugs are all gone.
Whatever.
- How is he?
- He's unhurt, apparently.
Not so much as a single bite on him.
Mrs Lokensgard,
we haven't finished talking to Dylan.
Yes, you have. We're going home.
l've said it before. This case is attracting flies
because somebody's full of crap.
l think what we just saw was a show.
Dylan made the bugs attack him to make
himself look like a victim, not the perpetrator.
OK, but how?
This guy's a horse whisperer for bugs?
l don't know how he's doing it,
but l may know a way to find out.
- Where did you get this?
- Dylan gave it to us in his interview.
There's not a lot to be found
in a teenage boy's sweaty Kleenex.
You want pheromones.
Aren't they in adolescent sweat?
Yes, it's what causes BO. But obviously
it's not all that attractive - to anything.
l've got a reading going right off the scale.
Holy Toledo.
We got pheromones coming out the
Yin-Yang here. C-13 calliphorone, and how.
- What happened?
- l think my electroantennogram tilted.
- What's C-13 calliphorone?
- lnsect pheromone.
- Where did you find this mother lode?
- A boy, Dylan Lokensgard.
That specimen came from him.
A boy secreting bug pheromones?
That's impossible. Preposterous.
You're the expert, Dr Bronzino.
How else do you explain it?
Rocky?
A boy is a boy, a bug is a bug.
You can't have it both ways.
He's going through puberty.
Maybe his body chemistry is going crazy
and his raging teenage hormones
are attracting insects.
What if it's more than chemistry
or hormones or biology?
Dylan's notjust attracting bugs.
He's using them.
Yes, but against what?
- We saw him talking to a girl.
- The one in the Dumb Ass video.
Captain Dare's girlfriend.
- What are you doing?
- l need to talk to you.
You have to be quiet.
My mom's gonna hear you.
l'm coming up.
What? No.
- You're gonna break your neck.
- l needed to see you.
l haven't been here in so long.
Since fourth grade.
After school.
lt was a Wednesday in April.
''A dream in a mist of gray.''
That's from a Syd Barrett song.
- How do you know all these things?
- My dad told me.
Syd Barrett, he was in the band Pink Floyd.
He was this brilliant guy
that nobody understood.
Kinda like you.
Me?
l never said l was sorry when
your dad disappeared, Dylan.
l never said a lot of things.
But l wanna say 'em now.
l know you've always cared about me.
We've grown apart,
but l haven't forgotten you.
And after we talked this morning at school,
l realized how special you really are to me.
l can't believe this.
After what happened to Bill,
l realized how important it is to have
someone who does understand you.
l want us to do this.
That was amazing.
What was that?
What was what?
Your tongue.
There's something wrong with you.
No, don't say that.
- l need to go.
- Natalie, please don't.
Just stay. Let me talk to you.
Natalie, listen to me.
Natalie, please.
Hey, Bug Boy.
How about we go for
a little buzz around the block?
So, Lokensgard, how'd you do it?
How'd you kill him?
- Bugs killed Captain Dare.
- Yeah, bugs that do what you say.
You wanna know how l did it?
l'll show you.
Maybe you should get your camera ready.
- What are you talkin' about?
- l just have to open my mouth.
What the hell... Oh, God!
l'm getting a reading here.
Trace levels inside the house.
l guess that's probable cause.
Dr Scully?
This is so exciting.
l've never had a partner before.
l have.
l think of it as a hymenopteran relationship.
Two scientists reaching higher
than either of them could reach alone.
lf l may say so, Doctor,
you complete me.
- l got upstairs, you take down.
- All right.
Oh, God.
David Winkle, is that you?
- Now that's a dumb-ass.
- lt wasn't a stunt.
lt was Dylan Lokensgard. He attacked us.
- He attacked you?
- The dude's a freakin' bug.
He chewed right out the back window.
You stay. l'll see that Dylan
didn't head to that girl's house.
Where are you?
l'm with Rocky at the Lokensgard house.
Nobody's here.
l'm afraid the kid's on a tear.
- He's caused an accident on Glenhaven Road.
- How'd he do that?
Better see for yourself.
C-13 calliphorone. l got a reading up here.
Dylan's bedroom's up there.
Unfortunately he's not in it.
- Where are you going?
- Kid's on a rampage.
You got my number, partner.
- Natalie?
- Whoever you are, leave me alone.
l'm Monica Reyes, with the FBl.
l'm here because l need your help.
- lt's about Dylan.
- Don't say that name.
lt's important.
You may be the key to stopping him.
Dylan Lokensgard is a freak.
l thought he was the normal one.
l think Dylan was normal, like any other kid.
This is to do with what he's becoming.
- He kissed me.
- And it's probably what he's living for.
lt's probably why he attacked
David Winkle and his brother.
- He attacked Winky?
- They'll be OK.
We just wanna make sure
he doesn't hurt anyone else.
Come with me.
- Why did you run from me?
- What is wrong with you?
l'm different. lsn't that what you wanted?
Somebody different from Bill and Winky.
- You killed Bill.
- To keep you from being killed.
- And now you're coming with me.
- Stay where you are, Dylan.
Don't try and stop me. That little talk
you wanted to have, it'll have to wait.
- Where do you think you're going?
- We're going, me and Natalie.
- l'll be taking the car.
- You won't.
Don't cross me. l'm not
a kid everybody can kick around any more.
You think l don't know what you are?
lt's what l've been trying to tell you,
to save you from what you are about to do.
These are the things l couldn't tell you,
the things l couldn't tell your father.
You are not like the other kids.
You never will be.
Monica.
Holy Mother.
Monica, hold on. Can you hear me?
Can you breathe? Monica, talk to me.
- He's got the girl.
- Where'd they go?
- To Dylan's house.
- That's where Scully is.
She lost phone contact
with the entomologist Bronzino.
Where are they?
Help me.
Four bodies were found in the attic,
including that of Michael Lokensgard,
Dylan's father, long reported missing.
He, like the others,
fell victim to Dylan's mother,
who, in Dr Rocky Bronzino's expert opinion,
was neither human nor insect,
but something in between,
a biological anomaly
whose difference from the rest of humanity
could be hidden only for so long.
However strong
Dylan Lokensgard's yearning to fit in,
to win acceptance, to love and to be loved,
he could not defeat the unseen forces
which direct behavior.
ln the struggle between our desire
to determine what we will be
and the identity which biology defines for us,
there can only be one outcome.
But even in victory, there are
forces biology cannot defeat.
The stirrings of the soul,
the mysteries of desire,
the simple truth that
the heart wants what the heart wants.
Visiontext Subtitles: David Van-Cauter
US ENGLlSH