(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(m ITALIAN)
(GASPS)
What the hell
are you doing to me?
(PROTESTING IN ITALIAN)
What are you doing?
Goddamn it! Where am I?
A boat! A fishing boat.
You were in the water.
We pulled you out.
What water?
You were shot. See?
There are the bullets.
Look, there is a number for a bank.
Why was it in your hip?
My hip?
My hip.
Yeah, in your hip
under the skin.
Oh, God.
What are you gonna
do with me?
You need to rest.
Wait.
Please. Lie down.
I'm a friend.
I'm your friend.
My name is Giancarlo.
Who are you?
What's your name?
I don't know.
Oh, God.
Lie down.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
It's been confirmed, sir.
Mission failed.
(BOURNE SPEAKING FRENCH)
(BOURNE SPEAKING DUTCH)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
If you want to eat, you'd
better get in there.
You know, based on these charts,
I think I may have been
closer to the coast.
What is this?
You tie these knots?
So, it starts to
come back?
No, it doesn't
start to come back.
The knot's like everything else. I
just found the rope and I did it.
Same way I can read.
I can write. I can add, subtract.
I can make coffee.
I can shuffle cards,
set up a chessboard.
Yes, it will come back.
No, it's not coming back, goddamn it!
That's the point!
I'm down here looking through
this, all this shit!
For two weeks I'm down here.
It's not working. I don't
even know what to look for.
You need to rest.
It will come back.
What if it
doesn't come back?
We get in there tomorrow,
I don't even have a name.
It's not much, but it should
get you to Switzerland.
Thank you.
(COPS SPEAKING GERMAN)
(m GERMAN)
All right.
No, I don't...
I don't have any papers.
I lost my...
(m GERMAN)
(ORDERING IN GERMAN)
(WARNING IN GERMAN)
These people have threatened my family.
My babies.
So I'm telling you,
when the evidence is clear,
I will have a nice story
for you to read about.
And all my friends out there,
you will read about yourselves.
'Cause if you want to
play this game
after I have been reasonable,
I will show you.
That's Nykwana Wombosi speaking in
Paris the day before yesterday.
He was an irritation before he
took power, he was a problem
when he was in power, and he's
been a disaster for us in exile.
He's writing a book about the
Agency's history in Africa.
He's going to name names.
It's basically a shakedown. He's
demanding the Agency's help.
He wants us to put him back in
power in six months, or else.
This interview, and I'll make the
tape available to whoever wants it,
he goes on to claim that he's just
survived an assassination attempt.
He says it's us.
He says he's got proof.
The Director wants to know
if there's any shred of truth
in this accusation.
I've already assured him there's nobody
that reckless on my senior staff.
I was recalling a conversation
we had some time ago.
Talking about
Treadstone.
I seem to remember Wombosi's
name might have come up.
I'm not sure
what we're talking about.
Someone tried
to take him out.
Tried and failed.
Was this Treadstone?
You're asking me
a direct question?
Yes.
I thought you were
never gonna do that.
What happened?
Well, we lost the
communication with our man.
This was almost
two weeks ago.
We've been working around the clock.
The whole unit.
We've been
sleeping down there.
We're doing
everything we can.
And you don't
let me know this?
You never wanted
to before.
You never made
a mistake before.
(m GERMAN)
Yes, I'm here about
a numbered account.
If you just enter
your account number here,
I'll direct you to
an appropriate officer.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
My name is Jason Bourne.
I live in Paris.
(MEN CHATTERING)
(m GERMAN)
(PHONE DIALING)
BOURNE: Yes, in Paris.
Do you have the number
for a Jason Bourne?
OPERATOR: Yes, sir. Would
you like me to connect you?
Yes, please.
BOURNE.' (ON ANSWERING MACHINE)
This is 46990384.
Leave a message at the beep.
(REPEATING MESSAGE IN FRENCH)
(AMBULANCE SIREN BLARES)
(TRAM SOUNDING HORN)
(POLICE SIREN WAILING)
I'm an American.
Okay.
Hold it.
Wait. You have
no jurisdiction here.
Hold it there.
Okay?
MARIE; No.
Excuse me. No. This is not
my current address, okay?
This was my address
until two days ago,
when I started
standing in line.
Now I lose
my apartment, okay?
That means no address, no
phone, no money, no time.
And I still have no visa!
Miss Kreutz, please.
I'll have to ask you
to keep your voice down.
MARIE: Excuse me. I mean, but where's
the guy that I talked to last week?
Every week it's a new person.
How am I supposed to...
I don't know who
you saw last week.
Well, let me help you. I'm sure I have it.
Wait. Hang on.
Could I have your
attention for a moment?
I have it right here.
Just look at it.
You staged an effort to circumvent the
immigration laws of the United States.
This is
a student visa now.
It's not about a green oard anymore.
It's completely different.
It's not a menu, Miss Kreutz.
You don't...
MARIE: I brought
all this proof.
DISPATCHER ON RADIO:
Potential suspect...
Help in assault incident.
You! Red bag!
The red bag!
Stop right there!
Put your hands up!
(PEOPLE GASPING)
(ALARM SOUNDING)
I'm on it.
SECURITY CHIEF:
Move it! Now! Now! Move!
Alpha Unit, take the back stairs
and work your way up. Bravo...
Move in! Move in!
Okay, clear!
The suspect is...
BRAVO LEADER: Bravo Unit. Moving up
staircase. Proceeding to second floor.
SECURITY CHIEF:
Alpha Unit, you're clear.
Move! Move!
Alpha, Bravo Units,
target may have a radio.
Go to Code 77. Over.
Code 77, copy.
The floor! Down!
Clear!
Go. Move up. Move up.
He's in Zurich now?
Right now?
Yes.
It just came in.
But they're sure?
They're sure it's him?
Yes. He went
to the bank.
Our source at the bank,
that's who called.
Come on.
But he's got to assume we're
watching the bank, right?
I don't know. Come on.
I mean,
he cleaned out the box.
He left a gun.
What does that mean?
I said I don't know!
I liked it better when
I thought he was dead.
(CURSING IN GERMAN)
What are you looking at?
I heard you inside.
What?
The consulate.
I heard you talking.
I thought maybe we
could help each other.
How's that?
You need money. I need
a ride out of here.
I'm not running a car service.
Thank you.
I'll give you $10,000
to drive me to Paris.
(m GERMAN)
(BOURNE SPEAKING GERMAN)
What is this, a joke?
Some kind of scam?
No, it's no scam.
And I'll give you another
$10,000 when we get there.
(POLICE SIREN WAILING)
Jesus.
Is that for you?
Look. You drive, I pay.
It's that simple.
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
lgotenough
trouble, okay?
Okay.
Can I have
my money back?
CONKLIN: All right, go.
Keep going.
Go.
There! Wait!
No, it's got to be
near the end.
Come on, folks! We caught a break here!
Let's go!
Okay, I'm UP-
We're getting grids. Airline,
train, hotels, hospitals.
Who's getting
the address? The street?
Gemensheidt.
Here we go. I got it.
I think I got it.
ZORNI Is it him?
TECH 1: Unreal.
This is 38 minutes ago.
Zurich police are looking for an
American carrying a red bank bag.
He just tore up the embassy and he put
two cops in the hospital last night.
Get everybody up. Do it now.
I want them all activated.
Wait. All of them?
At the same time?
You heard me. I want Bourne
in a body bag by sundown.
All right, let's get a map up here!
Come on, folks! Let's work it!
The grids
are getting updated.
(BLEEPING)
MARIE: ...which was fine
with me because I was ready.
After six months in Amsterdam,
you're not sure
if you've been there 20 minutes or
years, if you know what I mean.
So I went. And I took all the money I had.
And I went in with friends,
and we took over this cool surf shop
outside Biarritz, right by the water.
It was amazing.
It was just amazing for about three
months, until it turned out that this
jerk who had fronted us the lease was
actually shining everyone on and...
And what?
What do you mean "what"?
Listen to me.
I've been speed-talking
for about 60 kilometers now.
I talk when I'm nervous. I mean, I
talk like this when I'm nervous.
I'm gonna shut up now.
No, don't do that.
I haven't talked to
anybody in a while.
Yeah, but we're not
talking. I'm talking.
You've said, like, 1 O words
since we left Zurich.
Well, listening to you,
it's relaxing.
Ihaven%
slept in a while and...
And I've had
this headache.
It's like a constant thing
inside my head
and it's just starting
to move to the background,
so keep 90mg-
Really, if you want,
please keep talking.
Okay.
What kind of music
do you like?
What do you like?
Come on.
You know what?
Never mind.
(TUNING RADIO) No, it's fine.
Tell me.
What do you want to
listen to?
I don't know.
Come on, it's not that hard.
What do you like? Tell me.
I don't know.
Who pays $20,000
for a ride to Paris?
FUCK it.
I can't remember anything that
happened before two weeks ago.
Lucky you.
No, I'm serious.
I don't know who I am. I
don't know where I'm going.
None of it.
What? Like amnesia?
Yes.
Amnesia.
Right.
And that's the best angle
of the courtyard?
That's the only angle.
What do they have of the streets?
Or, you know, the area?
They must have
something.
Hang on.
What is he doing?
Is it a game? Is he warning us?
Is it a threat?
Sir? Look at this.
What's that?
It's an angle of the street,
a sort of alley.
Just enhance it.
Now, who the hell is that?
TECH:
Marie Helena Kreutz.
She's 26, born outside Hanover.
Her father was a welder.
He died in '87.
We still don't
have the mother.
The grandmother,
she's still in Hanover.
It looks like she's the anchor for
this little domestic disaster.
And there's a stepbrother.
It's tough.
The girl's a gypsy.
I mean, she pops up on the grid here
and there, but it's chaotic at best.
She paid some electric bills
in Spain, '95.
Had a phone in her name for
three months in Belgium, '96.
No taxes, no credit.
I don't like her.
I want to go deep.
Get a phone log for Granny
and the half-brother.
Anybody we can cross-file.
I want to know every place she's
slept in the past six years.
Have Paris get these out
in the field.
BOURNE:
I'm not making this up.
These are real.
Okay.
Who has a safety
deposit box full of
money and six passports
and a gun?
Who has a bank account
number in their hip?
I come in here, and the first thing I'm
doing is I'm catching the sightlines
and looking for
an exit.
I see the exit sign, too.
I'm not worried.
I mean, you were shot.
People do all kinds of weird and
amazing stuff when they are scared.
I can tell you the license plate
numbers of all six cars outside.
I can tell you that our
waitress is left-handed
and the guy sitting at the counter weighs
215 pounds and can handle himself.
I know the best place to look for a gun
is the cab of the gray truck outside.
And at this altitude, I can run flat out for
a half-mile before my hands start shaking.
Now why would I know that?
How can I know that
and not know who I am?
Hey.
I slept.
I can't believe it.
Yeah, well,
you were tired.
I haven't slept.
Oh, here. For $20,000, I
like to throw in breakfast.
Did you stop for gas?
You were
pretty out of it.
So, do you think there's, like,
a family waiting for you?
I don't know.
I've thought about it.
MARIE: Is that it?
104.
Yeah, that's the address. No,
no, keep going. Keep going.
Okay. Where?
Just take a left.
Pull in over here.
Okay.
So, this is it, right?
Yeah, I guess.
God, I don't recognize
any of this.
Okay. I should go.
Jason?
Oh, God.
The money. Right.
Yeah.
Here.
Thank you. Okay.
Thanks for the ride.
Anytime.
Well, you could come up.
I mean, or you can wait here.
I can go check it out.
But you could wait.
Oh, no, no.
You could wait.
With you, you would probably just
forget about me if I stayed here.
How could
I forget about you?
You're the only person I know.
Yeah. That's true.
I guess you're not home.
(RATTLES DOOR)
(m FRENCH)
(CHURCH BELLS RINGING)
Hello?
Are you sure
this is all yours?
I guess.
This is my kitchen.
Any clues?
I think I'm in
the shipping business.
So it's all coming back?
Do you mind
if I use the bathroom?
Sure.
Okay.
(SHOWER RUNNING)
(PHONE DIALING)
(BEEPS)
(WOMAN SPEAKING FRENCH)
Yeah. Hello? Hello?
Yes, sir, Hotel Regina, Paris.
How may I direct your call?
Yeah, you're in Paris?
Yes, sir.
I'm looking for
a guest there.
A Jason Bourne.
One moment, please.
Thank you.
I'm afraid I have no one by
that name registered, sir.
Okay. Thank you.
Wait! No, no.
Are you there? Hello?
Sir?
Can you check another
name for me, please?
Here, bear with me
one second.
John Michael Kane.
Kane with a
One moment, sir.
Thank you.
MANAGER: You call about Monsieur Kane?
John Michael Kane?
Yeah, that's right.
You are a friend of his?
Yeah.
I have some very bad
news for you, sir.
I'm sorry
to tell you this,
but Monsieur Kane has passed
away almost two weeks ago.
There was an accident.
On the motorway.
Apparently,
he was killed instantly.
Really, I'm terribly sorry to
be the one to tell you this.
When they came for his things, it
was made known for us, you see?
Who came?
His brother.
Did his brother leave a number or
a way to get in touch with him?
I think not.
No, I'm sorry.
Jason?
There's no hot water.
It's freezing.
I'll go try the water
in the kitchen.
Why don't you just stay in the bathroom?
I'll see if I can get it hot.
Yeah, it's really cold
in here, too.
The water is still cold.
Yeah, it's cold in the kitchen, too.
I got it running, though.
So...
What?
Nothing.
Are you okay?
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah.
What is it?
Something wrong?
(MACHINE GUN FIRING)
(GRUNTS)
Jason!
Open that. Open that.
Tell me what's inside.
Who are you?
(BOURNE SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
MARIE: Oh, my God.
God.
BOURNE: Answer me!
Who are you?
He's got my picture!
All right.
Just hang on.
This is Zurich.
It's yesterday!
No, no, don't...
I don't know.
Where did you get this?
Hang on.
Stay there.
How did you
get my picture?
Where did you
get this from?
How did you get my...
My God!
I'll do this! You stay there.
Stay there!
(CAR TIRES SCREECHING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Where are your shoes?
Get your shoes.
Sure. Yeah, sure.
He went out the window.
Why would someone do that?
We can't stay here.
It's not safe.
I can get us out of here, but we got to go.
We got to go right now.
Okay, look,
you can wait.
You can wait for the cops.
It's okay.
You just wait for them to get here.
But I can't. I got to go.
Marie?
BOURNE: Quiet. Be quiet.
Don't look.
(AMBULANCE SIREN WAILING)
MAN: Code in.
Alpha 37509.
(PHONE RINGING)
Yeah.
Hang on.
Bourne. He went to Paris.
He went to the apartment.
We got him? Tell me.
NICKY: He killed our man.
What? In the apartment?
Yeah.
Well, you got to
clean that up.
No, I can't clean it up.
There's a body in the street.
So?
There's police.
This is Paris.
Put up the scanners. Get as much
radio information as you can.
Okay, you stay here.
I'm gonna go find a place for this money.
I'll be back in 1O minutes.
(WOMAN ANNOUNCING ON PA)
Hey, I told you
to stay in the car.
Jesus Christ. I told you
I needed a drink. I didn't think
you would come back anyway.
Look, you got to
go to the cops.
Right now. You got to go
before this gets any worse.
By myself?
It's gonna be okay.
You're gonna take my passport, okay?
You show this to them.
You have that picture,
you have the $20,000.
You tell them everything thathappened.
They'll believe you.
They have to believe you.
Marie, you can't just sit here.
It's not safe here.
Safe? This is from
inside the embassy.
Who can do this?
This is from yesterday.
I don't know.
How can they know
we're together?
I'm trying to do
the right thing for you.
That's all I'm trying to do.
Right?
How will you make this right
by sending me there alone?
You think I want you to go to the oops?
That's good?
You want to go, fine.
If you go, I run!
You go tell them
what happened!
I don't know
I don't know who this guy
was or about that picture!
I don't know who I am!
Look, I'm...
You act like
I'm trying to burn you.
I'm trying
to do the right thing.
Nobody does the right thing.
Look, I can't run with you.
I can't.
We run, I got to
live like this. I got to...
I don't even know
who I'm hiding from.
These people
know who I am.
Yeah, I got to stay here.
I got to figure this out.
So figure it out.
You take care
of this car?
What do you mean?
The tires felt a little
splashy on the way over here.
It pulls a little
to the right.
(CHATTERING ON POLICE RADIO)
(POLICE SIREN WAILING)
Last chance, Marie.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ON RADIO)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
So...
What?
We got a bump coming up.
(EXCLAIMS)
(MARIE SCREAMING)
Turn your head away.
(SIREN WAILING)
We can never come back
to this car.
You understand?
Okay, we're gonna
clean it out,
and I'll wipe it down,
and we walk away.
That's it.
Okay.
Okay. And I'll find a place for us to rest.
And I got to think.
Do you have a hat or
a scarf or something?
For my hair?
Yeah. Just until
we can change it.
Yeah. Sure. Okay.
Okay.
(CHILDREN GIGGLING)
(MAN SHUSHING)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
It's not him.
(IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
(PHONE DIALING)
(PHONE RINGS)
CONKLIN:
What do you have?
NICKY:
Wombosi went to the morgue.
He saw the body.
He didn't buy it.
Where is he now?
I told you,
I'm not staffed for this.
Where is he now? Right now!
Where's Wombosi?
They were
leaving the morgue.
They just left.
Sir, what do you
want to do?
(BEEPING)
I need to
get the bottle.
Hey.
You already
cleaned the room?
I wiped the whole place down
for fingerprints.
Can I walk around or is it
gonna leave any footprints?
You can walk around.
It's no problem.
But we'll just keep track
of everything we touch.
I think it's better
if we leave a room,
that we're not gonna
leave a trail.
Why? Where are we going?
I need to go to the hotel where
John Michael Kane stayed.
The Hotel Regina.
If I was him, then they're
gonna have some records.
We need that hotel bill.
Okay.
It gets slightly
complicated, though.
Because you're dead.
Right.
(WATER RUNNING)
BODYGUARD: Sir, please.
If they want war, then
we'll give them war.
If they want to kill me, they
better kill me the first time.
They better kill me dead. They
better kill me when I'm in my sleep.
Nykwana, listen to me.
We need these people.
It's hard enough getting people
that we know to help us.
We need to be careful.
We?
No, you.
You need to bring me back
that bastard kid's head,
put it in the front
of this house,
and show them the war
we're fighting.
But that is precisely...
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
BODY GUARD'. Nykwanw.!
We'll give the watch a
reference check before we go.
Okay.
What's the
pay phone number?
616-2468.
Exits?
There's three.
Service at the back, side goes
to the street past the shops,
front is the best.
If I think I'm being followed, I walk out
with the bag over my right shoulder.
And if there's no taxi?
I keep on walking, don't look
back until you make oontaot.
What?
We need this, right?
Okay.
BOURNE: I need distances.
You walk in, you pick a spot.
Some midpoint in the lobby.
I want you to count your steps to that
spot, and then remember that number.
Because after I call you,
I can get you moving.
You understand?
I also need a head count.
How many people from when you walk
in until you get to the desk.
How many hotel employees are there?
And obviously security.
And it might not be that easy
to see who they are.
So I'll call you, you give me the
layout, and we'll take it from there.
OPERATOR: Regina.
(m FRENCH)
(PHONE RINGS)
(KNOCKING)
What happened?
I...
Did something
go wrong? What...
I've got the records.
He, this guy at the front
desk was smiling at me.
So I thought, you know,
all this trouble,
maybe it's easier to
just ask for them.
You have the bill?
He made me a photocopy.
You just asked for it?
I said I was Mr. Kane's
personal assistant.
Oh.
Okay.
That's good thinking.
Sir, can I...
No.
Wombosi was assassinated in his
house in the middle of Paris.
Yeah, we just heard.
It's him. It's Bourne.
We're almost positive.
He had an assignment.
He failed.
He obviously felt compelled
to finish the task.
Jesus.
We think he'll come back
in now.
I mean, it's routine.
It's like
behavioral software.
He's following a protocol.
Now that he's completed the mission,
we think he'll come back in.
They always do.
When?
How long
till he checks in?
Twenty-four hours.
Twenty-four hours?
Yeah, it's usually
something like that.
Then what?
I told you
we'd clean this up.
It will be clean.
Yeah, I understand you're a dive
shop, but where are you looated?
Marseilles?
(PHONE DIALING)
(MAN CHATTERING IN FRENCH)
(TURNS UP VOLUME)
What specifically does
your company supply?
MAN: I am sorry. What did you
say your name was, monsieur?
OFFICER: (IN FRENCH)
What?
Paris police
found the vehicle.
(BEEPING)
RAWLINS: You've reached the
office of Simon Rawlins
at Alliance Security,
Maritime Division.
Paris office hours are
from 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m.
I got a lead in Paris.
The rest were Marseilles,
and two out in Southampton.
In Paris?
It's what?
Alliance Security.
Simon Rawlins.
I got a machine.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Mr. Kane?
Mr. Kane!
How are you?
I'm good. I'm good.
Mr. Kane. Come right in.
Please have a seat.
Thank you.
So, this is the
Palmer Johnson tri-deck.
I'm assuming you're still in the market.
It's still the same vessel?
Yes.
So I'm Kane.
They“.
I just had a meeting as Kane.
They said...
No. I'm definitely Kane.
I just had a meeting as Kane
and he knew me as Kane.
So I'm definitely Bourne. I'm
also just definitely Kane.
It's all just boats.
I got blueprints and cameras
and security systems.
I just found
John Michael Kane's body.
In a morgue here
in Paris.
But if you are John Michael
Kane, whose body do they have?
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
What was the name again?
Kane.
John Michael Kane.
Kane. It's number 121.
I want to see the body.
Our boss could come back. We
are not supposed to do that.
Come on.
Is this it?
I mean, where is he?
I don't know.
(m FRENCH)
Who are you?
What's going on here?
Where's the body
that goes in here?
I said someone
came last night.
I know. Where'd
they take the body?
Look, this is not
a carnival, okay?
People call, they make an
appointment, follow the rules.
Everyone signs in and out. This
is a serious place. Serious work.
It's not just to come in
whenever you like!
You're right.
We didn't sign in.
Get the hell
out of here.
Fine, fine. No, I'm
just gonna go sign in.
Okay, go.
Is this it?
Slow down. You can't
just take the book.
This is it?
It's okay. There's a pencil in here.
That's fine.
Honey, why don't you go
wait outside? Here it is.
We can't have...
Okay.
Jason, what just happened in there?
What are you looking for?
Nykwana Wombosi.
Wombosi went to the
morgue to visit Kane.
See?
So?
Solook, he's in the
Alliance Security brochure.
Same 911V-
This guy knows.
(SIREN WAILING)
(MARIE STUTTERING)
My French sucks. I can't... It
says something about a boat or...
I don't understand. Vvhatdoesitsay?
You read it. Tell me. What?
It says that 3 weeks before he was
killed, Mr. Wombosi told police
that a man came onto his yacht, five
miles off the coast of Marseilles
and tried to kill him.
It says that he chased the man off the
boat and shot him twice in the back.
It says I'm an assassin.
(POLICE SIREN WAILING)
(m FRENCH)
MARIE: What's going on?
What the hell
are you doing?
BOURNE: Go. Go.
What are...
DRIVER: (IN FRENCH)
We're blown. Come on.
Blown?
What is "blown"?
Keep walking.
What do you think they're doing back there?
They're on to the hotel.
No. You don't
know that.
Trust me.
Just keep walking.
(ALL CLAMORING)
Are you crazy?
What are you doing now?
Jason!
This is blown.
Marie?
Get away.
Marie, stop right there.
Get away from me.
What are you gonna do?
Kill me?
Marie.
Is that what's next?
Listen, stay calm.
Stay calm.
Whatever we do,
we have to do it together.
We have to be...
We?
The only thing
we had in common
was that neither of us
knew who you were.
We've passed that now.
Listen to me!
The police will find us. The people
who took that picture in the embassy
who killed Wombosi, they're
gonna come here and kill us.
The people who you work for.
I will take you
wherever you need to go.
I'll take you there.
I'll leave you there.
You can do whatever you want.
You never have to see me again.
But not here. If we
stay here, we die.
Boy, great police work!
Really brilliant!
Why don't they just hang out a
banner that says, "Don't come back!"
Jesus Christ! What is the
French word for "stakeout"?
Okay, this was 16 minutes ago.
This is our starting point.
They can't fly. Trains are risky.
Nicky?
NICKY: Here.
I need to know everything Paris's
finest is doing on this.
I'm on it.
ABBOTT: You said 24 hours,
and he's not back.
No. But we got a good idea
where he is.
You've got a black ops agent
who's off the reservation.
He's trashed
an American consulate.
He's on the run
somewhere in Europe.
You don't know why. I got to stand
before an oversight committee.
What will I tell them
about Treadstone?
You're worried about
a budget meeting?
We don't take care of this, we
don't make it to the men's room.
Now, is that clear enough
for you?
We will burn for this.
We will both of us burn.
All right, I want two teams.
Daryl, Ray, stay on the grids.
Brian, Harris, Steve,
I want to work on this girl.
Where about this
residency pattern?
We started it.
Get it out.
TECH 1: We cross-referenced numbers
from the grandmother, stepbrother.
When we found convergence,
we took the numbers,
back-checked them,
ran a search merge with other
data we had, which wasn't much.
Pins. These pins.
These are all the places we think
she's lived in the last six years.
One, two, three, four, five.
That's our pool.
No answer.
How many times
you let it ring?
Look, if you don't
want to go, I'll hitch.
I said I'd take you.
Those are the targets.
Beg, borrow, hack, tap,bypass!
I don't care what you do!
I want to know everything you oan tell rne
about what's going on at those looations.
BOURNE: How do you know
he still owns this?
Eamon always had money.
He would never sell this.
(CURSING IN GERMAN)
Marie?
What?
We got to go.
(CURSES IN GERMAN)
(CAR BRAKES SQUEAK)
I thought it would...
Oh, shit, that's Eamon.
I'll talk to him.
We're leaving.
Eamon. Surprise.
It's me, Marie.
Wow, God,
there's a really
good reason for this.
There bloody well
better be.
Daddy!
Hang on. Hang on.
I had no idea
you would be here.
Well, why would I be here? It's
only my bloody house, right?
Yeah.
Did she get you
into this?
It was just gonna
be for a day.
Daddy, Alain has to go pee!
All right, all right, come on.
Here. Get out of the car.
Okay, in you 9°-
Come on, Alain.
I'm sorry. I...
I thought it would be okay.
But I guess I was wrong.
Let's find Mommy.
Mommy?
Mommy is away for two days,
thank God.
You've got yourself
all tied up here.
Okay.
What's he do
for a living?
He used to be
in shipping.
Is he good for you?
Are you happy?
You know me.
I try too hard.
Here you go.
Sleep well.
Good night.
I'll sleep on the floor.
This was when?
11:45 a.m.
Which is definitely within
the driving range of Paris.
The call came from a highway
rest stop, southbound side.
Yeah.
What's this yellow pin?
She spent a couple of
months there in 1997.
Closest town is Riom.
We took her family's phone records and
collated the international calls.
They were in Paris
at 2:00 a.m.
They can't fly.
The train's too dangerous.
He knows better than to go
anywhere we might track him.
So this is our best guess.
What are you
doing here?
The kids. I was worried.
I couldn't sleep.
You're gonna wake them up.
We got to go.
I don't want to know
who I am anymore.
I don't care.
I don't want to know.
Come on.
We'll talk about...
Everything I found out
I want to forget.
It's okay.
I don't care who I am
or what I did.
It's okay.
We have this money.
We can hide.
Can we do that? ls there any
chance you can do that?
I don't know.
Come on.
CLAUDIA: Here, boy!
Here, boy!
Morning.
Christ.
You were up early.
Bless you
for making coffee.
One night.
You weren't kidding.
For a change.
He's not there either.
EAMON: And you looked
by the car?
He's not anywhere.
All right,
let me get dressed.
Who?
EAMON: Bloody dog's
gone missing.
Does that happen a lot?
What? That mutt? Miss his breakfast?
Not a chance.
It's always
something, right?
Get in the basement.
What?
Get everyone
in the basement now.
What the hell
are you talking about?
You're in danger. Your family's in danger.
I don't have time to explain.
Wait a minute. What the...
Eamon.
You should go.
What the hell
have you done?
It's not her.
It's me.
You need to get out of sight and in
the basement as quick as you can.
Daddy.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
The phone is dead.
Yeah.
Jason, who's out there?
Who is it?
(CURSING IN GERMAN)
What are you doing?
Oh, no.
We should never have come here.
I... These children...
That's not gonna happen.
(GUN FIRING)
(GUN FIRES)
(BIRDS SCREECHING)
(GROANS)
(GROANING)
Where is it?
Where's the weapon?
Who else is out here? Who else?
How many you got with you?
I'm not gonna ask you again.
I work alone. Like you.
We always work alone.
What do you mean?
Who are you? Rome?
Paris?
Treadstone, both of us.
Treadstone?
Which one?
Paris. I live in Paris.
You get the headaches?
Yeah.
I get such bad headaches.
You know at night
when you're driving a car?
Maybe it's to do
with the headlights.
What is Treadstone?
Treadstone said pills.
They said go to Paris.
Is Treadstone in Paris?
Look at this.
Look at what
they make you give.
All right, all right.
All right, Claudia, get in the
front and put your belt on.
All right, we're just gonna
put you in the back.
All right, get in
the front, Claudia.
I'm not waiting, Marie.
One minute, Eamon.
I'm not waiting!
Please!
Take it.
I took out $30,000.
The rest is yours.
That's it?
That's all I got.
No, that's not what I meant.
This is not gonna stop, Marie. You
got to get out now. Away from rne.
You got to get out.
You got to start running.
You get low,
you stay low.
No more friends.
Nothing familiar.
There's enough in there for
you to make a life. Any life.
EAMON:
I'm out of here, Marie!
Hey!
Get in the car.
You got to go.
What are you gonna do?
I'll end it.
Go ahead.
Please.
(BEEPING)
(PHONE RINGING)
(RINGING)
Code in, please.
Code in.
BOURNE.' Who is this?
Who the hell are you?
The man you sent is dead.
So whoever this is,
you better start talking.
CONKLIN.' Hello, Jason.
So, what are we into now?
It only goes two ways. Either you
come in and let us make this right,
or we'll have to keep going
until we're satisfied.
You mean
until you kill me.
I can't fix this if I don't
know what the problem is.
Tell me what we're into,
and I'll do the best I can.
Why don't you talk to
Marie, Jason?
Let's ask Marie
what she wants to do.
Actually, I don't think
she gives a shit.
She's dead.
I'm sorry to hear that.
How did that happen?
She was slowing me down.
Jason, all we've been
doing right from...
Enough.
5:30 p.m. Paris.
Today. Pont Neuf.
Come alone, you walk to the
middle of that bridge.
You take off your jacket.
Face east.
I'll redial this number.
Jason, wait!
First flight out. Tell Nicky I'll call
from the car. Tell her to find Picot. Go.
So...
What are we gonna do?
I told you I'd clean this up.
That's what I'm doing.
Can you really bring him in?
I think we're past that,
don't you?
Do you have a better idea?
You've given me nothing but a
trail of collateral damage
from Zurich to Paris.
I couldn't do much worse.
Why don't you go upstairs
and book a conference room?
Maybe you can talk him
to death.
MAN 1: The bus, the
tour bus, secondleveL
MAN 2:
Negative on the target.
Position one?
Negative.
Position two?
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
MAN 1: Position three,
motorcycle.
MAN 3: Negative.
MAN 4: Negative.
(RADIO STATIC CRACKLING)
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Jason?
I told you to come alone.
lguessthat was too complicated.
So try this. I'm gone.
Fuck.
CONKLIN:
Get Nicky on the phone.
(PHONE RINGING)
(VIBRATING)
Yeah?
CONKLIN: How long does it take to
wipe the room down and move it?
Get rid of everything?
Yeah.
Two to three hours.
All right,
well, get started.
Listen, no breaks.
Two men outside, oneinthelobby.
And keep your eyes open.
MAN: Keep the truck?
CONKLIN: Yeah, keep the truck.
I'm gonna close this unit down.
We'll move the gear in the truck.
They were covering Spain,
Malta, Morocco.
Yes, all local police
radio traffic.
No, for northern Europe we need
an authorized direotive. Yeah.
Okay, they're on it. We'll have a
satellite download in 30 minutes.
(CAR ALARM SOUNDING)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Where's your field box?
It's right there.
The whole system's
gone haywire.
That's this window
right here.
Dining room window?
I don't get it.
Dead.
The phones are dead.
It's Bourne,
isn't it?
Just quiet.
(CLATTERING)
You move, you die.
Bourne.
Gun down.
In there.
Okay, so what
do you want...
Treadstone.
You better take a look around.
There's not much left.
Are you Treadstone?
Am I Treadstone? Me?
What the hell are
you talking about?
He's lost it.
You better start
filling in the blanks here!
'Cause I thought
we were on the same side.
Whose side is that?
You don't know what you're doing, do you?
You don't have a goddamn olue!
Who am I?
You're U.S.
government property!
You're a malfunctioning
$30 million weapon!
You're a total
goddamn catastrophe!
And, by God, if it kills me, you
will tell me how this happened.
Why are you trying
to kill me?
What happened
in Marseilles?
You sent me
to kill Wombosi.
Kill VVombosi? Yeah, we can
do that any time we want.
I can send Nicky to do that,
for Christ's sake.
Mr. VVombosi was supposed
to be dead three weeks ago.
He was supposed to have died in a way
where the only possible explanation was
that he'd been murdered by a
member of his own entourage.
I don't send you to kill.
I send you to be invisible.
I send you because
you don't exist.
I want to know what
happened in Marseilles.
I don't remember
what happened in Marseilles.
Bullshit! This is
unacceptable, soldier.
You hear me? You failed!
Unacceptable?
You failed!
You failed and
you're gonna tell me why!
I can't tell you!
I don't remember!
You brought Kane to life. You put
together a meeting with Wombosi.
You found the security company.
You broke into the office!
For Christ's sake, you picked the
yacht as the goddamn strike point!
CONKLIN: You picked the boat.
You picked the day.
You tracked the crew.
The food, the fuel!
You told us where.
You told us when.
You hid out on that boat
five days.
You were in, Jason.
You were in!
It was over!
(GUN FIRES)
No, you do remember.
Don't you?
I don't want to
do this anymore.
I don't think that's a
decision you can make.
Jason Bourne is dead.
Do you hear me?
He drowned two weeks ago.
You're gonna go tell them that
Bourne is dead. Understand?
Where are you gonna go?
I swear, if I even feel
somebody behind me,
there is no measure
to how fast
and how hard I will bring
this fight to your doorstep.
I'm on my own side now.
(RADIO CRACKLING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(MAN SHOUTING)
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
It's done.
Shut it down.
ABBOTT: The Treadstone project has
actually already been terminated.
It was designed primarily as a
sort of advanced game program.
We'd hoped it might build
into a good training platform.
But quite honestly, for a
strictly theoretical exercise,
the cost-benefit ratio
was just too high.
It's all but decommissioned
at this point.
All right,
what's next?
Okay, this is
Blackbriar.
Blackbriar is a joint DOD
communications program
that we really feel
has good traction to it.
It's got legs.
It'll run and run.
It combines elements of proactive
and reactive fields of security...
This your store?
Yeah.
It's nice. It's a little hard
to find, but...
Think I could
rent a scooter?
You have ID?
Not really.