Damn it.
I waited too long.
Please, come on,
do something!
Come on, do something!
Do something!
Couldn't have saved her.
It's your choice
if you wanna go back on drugs.
You think
I can fix myself?
I just need to know
if you and I can work.
Let me see.
It's okay.
It's gonna get infected.
Hey, you're not gonna...
You are.
Don't--don't--
It's okay.
I love you.
So now what?
♪ House 7x01 ♪
Now What
Original air date on September 20, 2010
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
Everything's good.
We don't have to
talk through it all.
No, I meant it
literally.
Now what?
We could make breakfast.
We could go bowling.
We could stay here.
I have to go home
and get dressed
and go to work.
So that's it?
I'm hoping this is
the beginning of it.
Yeah.
Your assistant's new.
It's a 50/50 chance
he just...
Can't find
the light switch.
Hello?
Dr. Cuddy?
No, this is
Dr. Cuddy's nanny.
She's, uh, feeling a little
under the weather now,
so she won't be
coming in today.
Oh. I hope
she's all right.
Would you mind
asking her if--
No. Can't do that.
I'm afraid she's locked
in the bathroom.
Terrible bug going around.
What's the problem?
Well, I'm sorry
to disturb her,
but it's Dr. Richardson.
He must have
the same stomach flu.
He threw up
in the O.R.,
and I'm not sure
how she'd want me to--
hold on a second.
I've talked to Dr. Cuddy,
and she would like you
to do three things:
One--send him home,
two--sterilize the O.R.,
three--use your own brain.
See ya.
It's about puke.
That's what's
so important.
Puke.
Well, I guess I don't
have to rush back in.
But whatever "now what"
we do decide on...
It comes after
you take a bath.
Here's one.
"25-year-old man
"with numbness
and tingling in his legs
and a speech disorder,
three--"
anybody see House?
It's 10:00 A.M.
I'd be worried
if he was here.
"25-year-old"--
he was in pretty bad shape
yesterday
after his patient died.
House has lost
patients before.
We all have.
He's a big boy.
You didn't see him.
Best thing
we can do for him now
is find him a new
puzzle to solve.
Thus bringing us back
to my 25-year-old--
yet you're
the only person here
without a potential case
in front of you.
I haven't found
the right one yet.
Oh. I-I thought
maybe it was because
you were asking for
a leave of absence
and wouldn't have time
to see a case through.
I didn't say anything.
He didn't...I saw
an envelope on House's desk
with your name on it,
so naturally, I...
Steamed it open.
What's wrong with you?
You steam an envelope
to keep it secret.
Which is why I just ripped it.
You gonna tell us
where you're going?
Sure sounds like a no.
There's glass everywhere.
Couldn't you have just put
the mirror down nice and gentle?
I was in a mood.
I'll be right back.
Don't get that.
It could be important.
This is important.
Right now,
we are more important
than what's going on
at the hospital.
So...I say we turn off
our phones
and...Give the morning
to us.
Okay.
I'll go turn it off.
Thank you.
You're distracted.
I'm not.
Yeah, you are.
You turned off your phone
but you're still wondering,
"what could it have been?
"What emergency
will bring down
"the entire hospital
if I decided
to take the morning off?"
I'm sorry.
The clinic is facing reduced
funding from the state.
Nurse Jeffrey is filing
his 12th H.R. complaint.
Richardson
is threatening to quit
because he's basically been
a prisoner at the hospital
for almost a week.
Richardson?
The Neurosurgeon.
He's the only one
I have right now,
which means he has to stay
on the premises
at all times,
or else the hospital
technically isn't
a level one Trauma Center.
Which means?
I'd have to shut down
the E.R.,
transfer all of the patients
out of the ICU...
Okay, stop.
Turn around.
Why?
'Cause you need to relax.
Where are we going?
I am going to make you
a magical bath
with a lot of bubbles
and eastern spices
and blue diamonds,
green clovers...
Transformative powers.
But I must have solitude
to focus my creative energies.
Hello?
Interesting factoid.
Did you know
that if we don't have
a Neurosurgeon
on the premises,
all the puppies in the world
will choke to death
on all the babies?
Yeah.
You got a note
from Thirteen.
So how come we don't have,
like, five Neurosurgeons?
Well, we had three,
but Kapur retired,
and then Nichols just took off
for his daughter's wedding.
I've got good news.
For the next 16 hours,
you are the new Neurosurgeon.
I'm not a Neurosurgeon.
Which would matter
if you actually had to do
some neurosurgery.
House, it's a hospital...
The odds of having to do
neurosurgery are higher
than in most places.
If an EMT calls in
with a brain or spinal trauma,
just divert them
at the nearest hospital.
All you gotta do
is stand around
and keep the E.R. open.
It's an administrative problem,
not a medical one.
House, where
the hell are you?
Great. Glad you're on it.
All systems go!
Why are you going to Rome?
I found the flight
information in your locker.
I love how everyone
thinks it's so quaint
and childlike of me
to expect a modicum
of privacy around here.
Your flight's tomorrow.
What's so urgent in Rome?
I hear they want
to tear down the Coliseum
to build a karaoke bar.
The Buona Speranza
Medical Center in Rome
is doing
a Huntington's trial.
Seriously, I live to sing.
I know that they've been doing
fetal neural transplantation.
I also know
that their subjects
have increased risk
of intracranial hemorrhage.
This isn't the time
to join a trial.
This research
is in its infancy.
So's your condition.
You read my note.
You go through my locker.
And then you decide
you want to round it off
by lecturing me
on my life choices?
I'm worried about you.
Oh. Well, that makes it
all right then.
So what, exactly,
is this?
It can still be open
and casual
and fun if you want.
Open?
You think I want to see
other people?
Well, last night
was emotional for you.
We both lost that patient.
We watched people die.
I came back here
and I went for the Vicodin,
and you...Dumped your fiancé
and you came here.
Which I don't regret.
I'm not saying you do.
I'm just saying
it was an impulsive move.
Don't do this.
Why do you have to
analyze things to death?
Why can't you just...
Let it be nice?
You're right.
That was very
anti-secret bath.
House.
Yeah.
The secret bath is...
Burning my lady parts.
How do you think
my anus feels?
Burning means it's working.
Can we get out now?
I was so waiting
for you to say that.
Could I speak to
Dr. Jankowski?
No. I don't need
to disturb him in Bermuda.
Everything okay?
Dr. Cuddy's phone keeps going
directly to voicemail,
and I need to get
a Neurosurgeon
to replace Dr. Richardson
for the day
or else she's screwed.
I'm a Neurosurgeon.
No. You're not.
I've cut into people's
heads more often--
you did a residency
in neurosurgery
at the University
of Melbourne,
but you were never
board-certified.
You've worked here two days.
How--
Dr. Cuddy's first assignment
was for me to get to know
everything about
Dr. House's team...
And not to believe anything
any of them told me.
I'm...Not
a Neurosurgeon?
And...Voila!
The first course,
I flaked some tender
young ears of corn
on the side of assorted
exotic breakfast meats
in a Chile sauce reduction.
And the...
Second course?
A single grape.
To cleanse the palate.
Which is kind of a waste,
'cause there is no third course.
I'm glad we stayed in.
This is actually...
Pretty good.
I can always tell
when you lie.
I mean always.
I slept with
my freshman roommate.
A lie.
A truth.
You have a tell.
What is it?
First admit
that you were lying.
Fine. I was lying.
My sexual history
is boring and predictable.
What is my tell?
Are you kidding?
If I tell you your tell,
you'll get rid of it,
then I won't be able
to tell.
Well, then you have to
tell me something
I don't already know
about you.
Even though, technically,
you didn't tell me something
that I didn't already
know about you.
Quit being so damn logical
and just tell me.
I used to have
an intimate relationship
with a photograph of you.
Well, actually,
a sock and a photograph.
I know.
I was lying.
The photo you took of me
as sleeping beauty on Halloween.
Why else would you
take that picture?
I have to pee.
Ha! You can tell.
'Cause actually,
I have to poo.
What?
Cuddy's assistant decided
to use his own brain.
Who put that idiot idea
into his head?
Perhaps you could
follow the same advice.
He notified DPH that there's
no Neurosurgeon on the premises.
Said he legally had to,
which he legally had to.
Sounds like you got
the situation under control.
No. I don't.
You know I don't.
When DPH shows up,
they're gonna shut down our E.R.
This can't be fixed.
It is what it is, House.
Great. I've got
every faith
in your ability
to solve the problem.
I have called
every Neurosurgeon
within a 45-mile radius--
nothing.
I think House
is just testing us.
He's always
testing us.
Test or not,
it's a problem.
It's not our problem.
Why the hell is it House's
problem?
Where the hell is Cuddy?
We either report this,
and half the hospital
gets shut down,
or we cover it up
and run the risk
that the entire hospital
gets shut down.
Or we get Richardson.
He's sick.
And we're doctors.
We get people better.
Fing fong fooey?
Ohh...
Can I open them yet?
Just a second.
Okay.
Hold out your hand.
Oh...
I always wanted
to open a bottle of champagne
with one of these things.
You might wanna
stand behind me for this.
Okay...
Oh!
Yeah!
Mm, I think I might have...
Got that slightly wrong.
Well, good thing
I got a case.
House, open up.
We need to talk.
Just let him in.
No.
House!
If we just ignore him,
he'll go away.
House!
I think he finally left.
But just in case he hasn't,
what can we do that does not
involve talking?
You turned on my ringer!
I know you're in there.
I can hear your
cell phone ringing.
Just let him in.
No!
He's like a stray...
He'll eat everything,
shed all over the place,
and crap on the floor.
Hi.
This is Gregory House.
I can't take your call
at the moment.
Please leave a message.
If this is Wilson,
I'm fine, not suicidal,
not on drugs,
coping very well with the loss
of my last patient.
So feel free to go about
your day without worry.
Beep!
House...
You can't just
not show up to work.
What's Cuddy gonna say?
If this is still Wilson...
She gave me the day off.
And tomorrow.
Okay, maybe not tomorrow.
But today.
I'm fine.
Now, go away.
Beep!
If you're not in tomorrow,
i'll be back.
Look, you're the only
Neurosurgeon we've got.
You have to suck it up
and go back to the hospital.
We're not asking you
to operate, just to be there.
Unless you can transport
this t-toilet with me,
I'm not leaving
the room.
I'll get a bucket.
You're missing
the point.
I ate bad Sushi.
I'm sick. Go away.
We can give you promethazine
for the nausea.
Already took it.
And trimethobenzamide.
Maybe this isn't
food poisoning.
Whatever it is,
it must have damaged
the lining of his stomach.
Till that heals,
nothing's gonna work.
So we need to treat
both that and the nausea.
And whatever's
wrong with him.
We give him ondansetron
and prostaglandins.
And whatever's wrong
with him.
Neither of those will treat
any possible
underlying condition.
Who cares?
He's not our patient.
The hospital is.
I can...Hear you.
You're pretty miserable,
aren't you?
Would you be willing
to take a...Fairly risky drug
if it would make it
all go away?
Ah!
Why didn't you
let him in?
You were
thinking about Wilson
while we were having sex?
That's so cool!
So was I.
You were hiding me
from him.
Why?
I was not hiding you.
I was protecting
your privacy.
Wasn't sure if you were
ready to go public
with the whole...
"Us" thing yet.
Why would I be
doing all this
if I wanted it to be
private?
Ohh...
Oh. I never even asked.
Maybe you're not ready yet.
Have you read the list
of side effects on those drugs?
We could crash his BP.
I haven't heard a thump,
so I assume he's still
quietly puking.
We could be
making him worse.
Bigger picture--
we're making
the hospital better.
We can test for whatever
you want to test him for
once he's stable enough
to get back to the hospital.
Now, stop being a girl
and move.
So you gonna ask me
about this Huntington's trial,
and by ask, I mean
give me your opinion?
No.
There is one thing,
though.
Will you have sex
with me?
What?
Well, this trial means
you're leaving right away.
I was playing
a long game.
Deadlines
have been moved up.
Wow.
That stuff is good.
Think you can make it
back to the hospital?
Uh-huh.
That lamp is shiny.
I mean,
the way it shines is...
Shiny.
I take it this is one
of the side effects
of the drugs.
Who cares?
Let's go.
What are you doing?
You think I'm afraid
to go public?
I'm gonna prove you wrong.
With a tripod?
With a sex tape.
We'll send it to Wilson.
It's a win-win.
We get to do it again,
and...He might actually
learn something.
It sounds like someone's
trying to break in.
It's probably nothing.
Stay here.
Hey.
Stuck?
Bummer.
Looks painful.
Chamomile
or English breakfast?
Would you stop
being an ass
and pull me out of here?
You didn't get
my message earlier?
Yeah. But as someone
once told me,
everybody lies.
I'm fine.
Just staying home,
chill-laxin'.
Your patient died,
you ignore my calls,
and you won't open the door.
I don't think you're fine.
I think you might be
throwing away a drug-free year.
Or...I'm ignoring you
for a different reason.
Sex with my girlfriend.
Hmm.
Will you please just--
please let me in?
Thank you.
And since when did you
start referring to hookers
as girlfriends?
She's not a hooker.
What are--wha--
really?
Begins with "C",
ends with uddy.
How many Vicodin
have you taken?
I'm serious.
Cuddy and I
are now Cuddy and I.
There's an "I"
in Cuddy.
House...It's okay.
Almost all addicts
relapse a few times.
She's in my bedroom.
You're hallucinating,
House.
Honey buns!
We got company.
Pupils are normal.
Pulse is normal.
Better than that.
They're both
totally awesome.
I'm not on drugs.
So...Why did you lie
about Cuddy?
To make a point.
Probably something to do
with shutting you up.
It's my go-to idea.
You do seem okay.
You want me to stick around?
I could do my usual thing
of pretending I like
watching monster truck rallies,
if that would
make you feel better.
No. You go.
House...You could have
died.
You had a patient
who did die in your arms.
You shouldn't be alone.
I know.
That's why I called a hooker.
Now, go away.
'Cause...
You'll be extra.
Are you really okay?
Are you gonna
break in again?
You checked my pulse.
You checked my pupils.
I'll mail you
the urine sample.
How come I've never
even met you guys?
Y-you're like the greatest...
Guys. You know
fluorescent lights
flicker at the same frequency
as the human brain?
You know the human brain
doesn't flicker?
Doesn't take a brain surgeon
to figure out
that he can't perform
brain surgery.
What's wrong with him?
High...Blood sugar.
He'll be fine as soon
as we rehydrate him.
That's a relief.
Thank God.
DPH guy will be here
in 20 minutes.
What is wrong with him?
High blood sugar.
You just said so.
Chase is running labs.
Right now the top two
contenders are hepatitis
and peptic ulcer disease.
So...Is today really
your last day?
Flying out tomorrow.
How long a leave
are you taking?
Depends.
On the drug trial.
Sounds risky.
Yadda, yadda.
You don't think
I should do it.
Message heard.
No. I approve.
Living fast
and dying young is crap.
If you have a chance
to get better...
I say good for you.
I brought Wilson in here
specifically to go public,
just like you requested.
I pressured you.
Wilson coming through
the window pressured you.
If you're forced into this,
it's not gonna work.
Do you have any response
to that?
Game on.
Is he better?
Yep.
You're lying to me
again, aren't you?
Yep.
Then we're screwed.
Don't we have
to tell--
oh! Damn.
Dr. Richardson's
prepping for surgery.
Yeah. I need to talk
to him.
He's prepping for surgery.
So you said.
I just need to confirm
he is who you say he is
and that he's
a licensed Neurosurgeon.
Well,
here's his paperwork.
His hospital I.D.'s
right there.
You can...See it's him.
Yeah. I should
still talk to him.
They've already scrubbed.
He'd have to be re-sterilized.
The patient's anesthesia
would have to be adjusted.
Why did you report
he wasn't here?
I must have...
Misunderstood.
Oh...Why...
Why...
Why is it so...
So hot in there?
Oh!
Ahh.
La-dee-dah.
Woodstock, baby.
Is he stoned?
No. We're pretty
sure he's got--
oh, I'm sure you have
an explanation,
but I don't care.
See, you need to have
a doctor on the premises
who can actually do
neurosurgery.
Tell the attending
to divert all ambulances away
and start calling
other hospitals
and see who can take
your stabilized ICU patients.
Those departments
are shutting down.
"Design" for five points.
Got it.
"Hear."
Both versions.
"Love."
You didn't see love.
Wow. I didn't think
you'd take
my lack of board game skills
so personally.
Why didn't you tell me
you loved me?
Didn't a wise woman
once say--
and by once,
I mean two hours ago--
"why do you have to analyze
everything to death?
Why can't this
just be nice?"
I told you I loved you.
You didn't tell me
you loved me back.
You don't think that should
give me cause for concern?
No. 'Cause words
don't matter.
Actions matter.
You're really gonna
take a stand here.
You can't say--
nope.
Why?
Because...
I forgot to grab a "v."
Lobe.
Gets you one point.
One.
Labs show he's negative
for everything.
I'm guessing at least
one of them is wrong.
Who cares?
The E.R. and the ICU
are half-empty and the place
is crawling with suits.
It's over.
You do know we still have
a sick patient here.
Right?
He's the guy sitting
right behind you,
taking off his clothes again.
Uh, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
Uh, why don't you
just sit down
and take it easy?
He should be coming down
by now.
And yet...I'm not.
What if his behavior
isn't a side effect
of the ondansetron?
What if it's a symptom?
Thank you.
What causes delirium
and nausea?
He's been stuck here
in the hospital a few days.
Nobody else is sick,
so it can't be environmental.
Not exactly stuck.
I snuck out.
Freedom is my birthright.
Where did you go?
The Seafood Festival at the Convention Center.
We're screwed.
Seafood Festival has stuff
from all around the world
in combinations
nobody every thought of.
We could be here
all year.
You had shrimp?
Uh-huh.
And crab?
Lobster?
Uh-huh.
And...
I ate whatever
looked good.
Did you eat any roe?
Little tiny eggs?
Nummy!
Toad eggs will cause nausea,
and they can get you high.
If I'm right,
the antidote is fast-acting.
If we can get him to keep
his clothes on long enough,
he can pass
as a functioning Neurosurgeon.
Um...
France.
And not Paris or the Rivera,
but there's this place
in Normandy.
It's on a...
A tidal island.
Everyone who's not staying
in one of the small inns
has to leave
before the tide comes in.
You have this 900-year-old
fortress all to yourself.
It's called...
Mont Saint-Michel?
That's it.
Have you been there?
Nope. But I got a pretty
good idea what it looks like.
H-how did you know?
You used to have a picture
of it as a screensaver.
That was years ago.
I guess
it's a memorable place.
Now, unfortunately, we can't
fly straight to normandy,
but the layover in London's
only a couple of hours.
What are you talking
about?
It's all there.
All you gotta do
is click confirm,
and we're eating croissant
and being insulted
by stinky people
this time tomorrow.
Don't worry.
I used Wilson's credit card.
I can't.
I'm kidding.
I used your credit card.
House...
The hospital
does not need your body.
I do.
So does my daughter.
Well,
she can come too.
Or to grandmother's house
she can go.
This is crazy.
So...You break off
your engagement,
but you won't adjust
your schedule.
I can't.
Not...Tomorrow.
But...Two weekends
from now.
If Rachel's gonna
stay with my mom,
I'm gonna need a little
bit of prep time.
Okay.
What if it doesn't work?
What if I stay this way
forever?
The antidote works quickly.
If we're right,
you should be back
to your old self in no time.
My old self was boring.
Can't we keep the new self?
Just lay down,
and stop unbuttoning.
I'm sorry
that I read your note
and looked in your locker.
You get used to that
kind of thing around here.
Do you have anyone going
with you to Rome?
Is that your
passive-aggressive way
of asking me
if I'm seeing somebody else?
I hope you are.
I mean...I hope
you have someone with you.
If I'm scared about this,
I can't imagine
how you must feel.
You shouldn't be alone.
If you want...
I could fly over
for a few days.
Friends.
I appreciate that,
but I think I'll be okay.
I guess we took
the long way around
to being friends, huh?
I guess we all did.
Thank you.
For everything.
You're welcome.
I'll see you tomorrow.
I really do have to leave.
I know.
What's the problem?
This isn't gonna work.
That's it?
You can't just...
Say that and shut up.
It's just
a statement of fact.
It's not
a debatable proposition.
Right. Because you can
see the future.
No. But I can see
the past.
And you're gonna remember
all the horrible things
I've done,
and you're gonna
try to convince yourself
that I've changed.
And I'm gonna start doing
those horrible things again,
because I haven't changed.
Then you'll realize that...
I'm an insane choice
for someone who has a kid.
And from there,
it's a short step
to the inevitable conclusion
that all of this...
Was a mistake.
Tell me any of that
isn't true.
Mercy doesn't have
enough room in their ICU
to handle the overflow, so--
Don't worry about it.
I believe you wanted to talk
to Dr. Richardson,
our Neurosurgeon?
I'm sorry that we met
under such trying circumstances.
I hope you restore our rating
as a level one Trauma Center
and reopen the E.R.
and the ICU immediately.
An accidental case
of poisoning.
Dr. Richardson
has been treated
and is ready to resume work.
Hmm.
Touch your nose
with your index finger
and tell me how you treat
a cerebral contusion.
Uh, I-I-I would watch
for edema
and transtentorial
herniation.
Good enough.
Turn it around.
You're gonna be up late.
Next time...
Avoid responsibility.
Cake?
Taub thought we should
have a little party
to see you off properly.
He gets sentimental
about these things.
I never should have
flashed him.
Speaking of which...
Earlier today
I asked you about...
Having sex.
You gave me a look
that almost certainly
could only mean no.
However, on the other hand,
I'd be remiss if I...
Didn't follow up
and confirm.
See? It's the same look.
So if it didn't mean no
the first time,
then...
No.
No. No, no.
Okay.
No pressure.
Does that method
ever work?
At least once.
Mm, I'm, um...
Getting mixed signals.
See you at the cake.
The only time
you're afraid
is when you're happy.
You just don't
expect it to last.
'Cause it doesn't.
You don't know that.
I've done
horrible things to you.
And I'll do horrible
things again to you.
But because of one
stupid moment
with a dying girl
and a pile of rubble...
You think I can change.
Tell me where I'm wrong.
I don't want you
to change.
I know
you're screwed up.
I know you are always
gonna be screwed up.
But you're the most
incredible man I've ever known.
You are always gonna be...
The most incredible man
I have ever known.
So unless you're
breaking up with me,
I am going home now.
I love you.
♪ Oh, yeah, and later on ♪
♪ we took a southbound train ♪
♪ yeah, and it was cold out ♪
♪ yeah, it was freezing
down rain ♪
♪ yeah, and it'll let up ♪
♪ if we all screamed
for the change ♪
where's Thirteen?
I don't think
she's coming.
What's going on?
She's not going to Rome.
You mean
she changed her mind?
I called
the hospital in Rome
to see when she was
schedule for surgery.
Why would you--
doesn't matter.
Point is, she's not
even in the trial.
Never heard of her.
She's been lying to us
all day.
Well, have you tried--
both her phone lines
have been disconnected.
She's just gone.
♪ No, no,
just the good days ♪
♪ yeah, yeah,
it's gonna be great.
Yeah.
♪ Just the good days ♪
♪ ♪