♪ Teenage Mutant Ninja
Turtles ♪
♪ Heroes in a half-shell
Turtle power! ♪
♪ They're the world's
Most fearsome fighting team ♪
♪ They're heroes
In the half-shell ♪
♪ And they're green ♪
Hey, get a grip.
♪ When the evil Shredder
Attacks ♪
♪ These Turtle boys
Don't cut him no slack ♪
♪ Teenage Mutant Ninja
Turtles ♪
♪ Splinter taught them
To be ninja teens ♪
LEONARDO:
He's a radical rat.
♪ Leonardo leads
Donatello does machines ♪
That's a fact, Jack.
♪ Raphael is cool but crude ♪
Give me a break.
♪ Michelangelo
Is a party dude ♪
Party!
♪ Teenage Mutant Ninja
Turtles ♪
♪ Heroes in a half-shell ♪
♪ Turtle power! ♪
[♪♪♪]
MICHELANGELO:
Dudes, I have to admit,
The 47 Loyal Ronin Go Hawaiian
is a modern classic.
DONATELLO:
Oh, yeah. I mean, it's certainly
one of the best surfing samurai
movies ever made.
Say, did anyone see
a tank go by?
A tank?
What would a tank be doing
on a city street?
I don't know,
but one's been here.
And they're wet.
And they're coming
from the water front.
Ah, it must be one of Shredder's
amphibious modules.
We better follow it while
the tracks are fresh.
Come on.
Hey, April.
We may have a hot story for you.
We're on 6th Street,
heading north.
APRIL [ON RADIO]:
Thanks. I'm on my way.
LEONARDO:
Light-Foot Heavy Industries.
They must have gone in there.
Well, it's a cinch
they ain't robbing that bakery.
Come on.
ROCKSTEADY:
Say, Bebop,
when we get done
pulling this heist,
let's hit that bakery
next door.
Huh-huh, yeah.
I could really go for some
between meal sweets.
I hope your dentist
knows about that big cavity
between your ears.
The turtles.
[YELLS]
[YELLING]
[♪♪♪]
Huh.
Whoa!
I wish I had a pizza
for every blaster
I've taken away from you goons.
[SNORTS, GRUNTS]
H--Hey.
Where'd everybody go?
[YELLS]
Ha-ha, boy this is the life,
huh?
Throwing dough around
like there's no tomorrow.
Whoa!
[YELLING]
And now for the icing
on the cake.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Mm.
I had no idea that defeat
could taste so sweet.
ALL:
Turtle power!
Come on.
Yeah, let's get out of here.
[ENGINE STARTS]
Wow,
what a fight, guys.
I'd say our ninja skills
beat them again.
Yeah, either that
or the sugar shock.
KRANG:
Those incompetent mutants
of yours failed me again.
So, what else is new?
But I must have the parts
to build my new
thermal generator.
It should produce
enough energy
to run the Technodrome
forever.
Yeah, yeah.
That's nice, Krang.
I'm programming the computer
to come up with a plan
to finally defeat those
insufferable turtles.
KRANG:
Oh, this is hopeless.
All Shredder can think about
is getting revenge,
the Foot Soldiers are incapable
of independent thought,
and those two mutants
couldn't steal a free sample.
Ooh, oh, good help is so hard
to find nowadays.
What I need
is someone who's clever,
and sneaky,
and fiendishly brilliant.
Someone like me.
That's it.
[BUBBLING]
[MACHINE HUMMING]
It's working.
I've done it.
Six exact duplicates of myself.
Hey.
What do you mean, "duplicates"?
I'm unique.
Oh.
No, I'm not.
But what am I doing here?
I sense this is not
my natural environment.
Well, I'll say.
It's already smoothing out
my beautiful wrinkles.
This is the dreariest place
I've ever seen.
Heh-heh.
I should be warming myself
by a nice hot volcano
in Dimension X.
For what reason have I suddenly
been summoned into existence?
To do my bidding.
And why, pray tell,
should any of us do that?
Because I made you.
I am your master.
You ain't the master
of anything.
We could blast you to pieces
with all the firepower
in these gizmos.
Ah, but I control the gizmos.
KRANG:
I can take you for a spin.
Or freeze you up.
Or even cause you
to blow yourself to bits.
I-I guess we have
to take his orders.
A wise decision.
Now, head to the city in one
of our amphibious modules
and steal the items
on this blueprint.
And no tricks.
I'll be watching you.
SHREDDER:
Blast!
This stupid computer
can't even come up with
a halfway decent scheme
to eliminate those turtles.
The attempted robbery took
place just half an hour ago.
Here's how it looked.
Every time
the turtles defeat us,
April O'Neil is there
with her camera
to record our humiliation.
Of course. That's it.
Bebop, Rocksteady.
Meet me at the launch bay.
We're heading up to the city.
Thanks for the story, guys.
Our pleasure, April.
BURNE [ON RADIO]:
April. What are you sitting
around there for?
Some weird alien brain
is breaking into
the A1 Scientific
Supply Company.
Get over there and cover it.
Go, go, go.
LEONARDO:
That sounds like Krang.
APRIL:
Come on!
Hey, fellow dudes,
look down there.
Isn't that one of Shred-Head's
amphibious doohickeys?
It sure is.
You check it out,
Michelangelo.
We'll see what's going
on in the building.
Why should I take orders
from that idiot?
I'd tell him where to get off,
if I had a body.
KRANG [ON INTERCOM]:
Well, you don't have a body,
so shut up
and get back to work!
It's Krang.
All right, Krang.
Drop that stuff.
You're coming with us.
Leave me alone,
you frog-faced freaks.
What the--?
Nice night for a robbery,
huh, Krang?
Oh, I wouldn't say so.
Whoa!
Did you find Krang?
Yeah, and he's packing
some serious artillery.
Dudes, dudes!
You'll never guess
who I just saw.
Don't tell me.
The Easter bunny.
No. It was Krang.
Michelangelo,
that's impossible.
We just nearly got blown away
by him in there.
BURNE [ON RADIO]:
April. That alien brain
just robbed
Light-Foot Heavy Industries.
Get over there!
Man, that guy must have
turbo-charged his bubble-walker.
He's everywhere.
Well, either that,
or maybe there's more
than one Krang.
RAPHAEL:
I'd say that's
a distinct possibility.
Dudes. Our troubles
just multiplied.
LEONARDO:
It's a half-dozen Krangs.
Yeah, as if one
wasn't bad enough.
If they're all as well-armed
as that first one,
we don't stand a chance.
Then I suggest we execute
a bold, daring ninja maneuver.
And retreat.
KRANG:
All right, all right,
now get back to work.
There's something annoying
about having to take orders
from a guy that looks
exactly like us.
LEONARDO:
We've gotta come up with a plan.
APRIL:
And I've gotta file this story.
Wait for me in my office.
So would someone explain to me
why there are six Krangs
running loose?
Oh, it's obvious.
Krang cloned himself.
Yeah, but why?
And what's all that
scientific-type stuff
they're stealing?
I'm not sure,
but if Krang's involved,
it's gotta be something bad.
[♪♪♪]
Ooh, ooh. There is is.
April O'Neil's TV camera.
Quick, open it up.
VERNON:
Hey, you there.
What do you think you're doing?
Huh? Oh. Uh, well, y--
I, uh...
Uh, we're from the Department
of, uh, uh--
Uh, Snacks.
The Department of Snacks?
Uh-huh.
Uh, we're here to investigate
a potential vending machine
malfunction.
You're putting me on.
Hey, buddy.
This is a serious
junk food emergency.
Uh, okay, okay,
but quit hanging
around the news van.
It's filled with highly
sophisticated equipment.
Hm.
At least they didn't
steal anything.
We better take care
of this candy machine.
Uh, Rocksteady.
We ain't really here
to fix the machines, you know.
I know,
but I'm hungry.
LEONARDO:
I've been thinking.
Those Krang clones
would be totally helpless
without their
bubble-walkers.
If we could sneak up
on them one at a time,
and disable them...
Great, let's do it.
I don't know if you
should come, April.
It could be dangerous.
Hey, danger is my middle name.
MICHELANGELO:
I thought your middle name
was Harriet.
KRANG CLONE:
There they are.
Prototype high
energy capacitors.
[CRIES OUT]
Quiet, you half-wit.
What's the matter?
I've got hands.
Fascinating.
My tentacles
are changing as well.
Heads up.
I think one of them's coming.
[SINGING INDISTINCTLY]
RAPHAEL:
Grab him.
Why?
Cut it out, you guys.
That tickles.
We've gotcha now.
Oh, oh.
I wouldn't necessarily say that.
Tell me I'm not the only one
who saw that.
Hang on, guys.
Let me get a shot.
Man, how much weirder
can this show get?
[HUMS, ZAPS]
Leonardo!
Does that answer your question?
Well, like,
where'd he go?
Did my camera do that?
[HUMS, ZAPS]
DONATELLO:
April!
[ELEPHANT TRUMPETS]
Well, well.
Miss O'Neil.
I was hoping the teleportation
device I put in your camera
would bring me all four turtles,
but one will do.
You won't get away with this,
Shredder.
The others will
come for us and--
And we'll be ready for them.
RAPHAEL:
Somebody please explain
what just happened.
Okay. When she pointed
it at Leonardo,
he disappeared,
and when she pointed
it at herself,
she disappeared.
You supposed somebody
put some kind of teleporter
in April's minicam?
I don't know,
but if we don't scram-ola,
we are gonna disappear too.
DONATELLO:
Oh, man, here we go again.
So much for them.
Now. May I please have
a show of hands?
Just as I thought.
We all seem to be growing.
But why is this
happening to us?
Without sufficient data,
I can only speculate
that it has something to do
with the cloning process,
but whatever it is,
one thing's certain.
We're free.
KRANG [ON INTERCOM]:
What are you up to?
Get back to work.
Dry up, Mr. Nobody.
We're through taking
orders from you.
You ingrates!
How dare you disobey me?
The bubble-walkers.
They aren't responding.
What's going on?
So. What do we do now, huh?
We'll never get to Dimension X.
We're stuck here.
Then I say we take over
this stinking city.
But this place
is so depressing.
It's d-dark and cold
and spooky
And it's simply ruining
my lovely complexion.
Ah, but we now have the means
to make this world
more like our natural
environment of Dimension X.
We-- We do?
We have all the components
to make a massive
thermal device.
We can assemble
it underneath the city
and really turn up the heat.
MICHELANGELO:
I don't get it.
How come those clone clowns
are growing bodies?
Yeah.
Krang doesn't have a body.
Not now,
but he used to have one.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
It was taken away from him
when he got booted out
of Dimension X.
Uh-huh. And the clones
have that data in their DNA.
So they're growing bodies,
the way some lizards
can grow new tails.
Well, we can't grow
a fourth turtle.
I've nearly got a fix on his
turtle com's homing beacon.
[RADIO BEEPS]
SHREDDER [ON RADIO]:
Attention,
you miserable turtles.
You've got 30 minutes
to come get your friends.
Before it's too late.
Don't panic,
I think I found them.
What in the world?
It's a huge concentration
of intense heat
coming from the sewers.
And it's getting hotter.
Well, that's nice.
Now, can we please rescue
Leonardo and April?
No, Raphael,
you don't understand.
If those clones have built
a thermal device,
the heat that it generates
could destroy the city.
We've gotta shut it down
while we still can.
Then we'll rescue the others.
How are we gonna do all that
in 30 minutes?
Tell ya how:
really fast.
KRANG:
My clones.
Where did they go?
Why aren't they answering me?
What's going on up there?
MICHELANGELO:
Man, it sure is toasty
warm down here.
I knew it.
A thermal device.
Oh, no. It's melted
straight through the ground.
So? It'll be buried and we won't
have to worry about it.
Uh, not exactly.
See, if that thing melts
into the Earth's magma,
it'll turn the city
into one big volcano.
We've gotta get that thing
out of there and shut it off
while there's still time.
Holy guacamole!
It's the invasion
of the...Krangazoids!
[KRANGAZOIDS GROWLING]
Dudes? I don't think
these Krangazoids
are gonna let us
get to that thermal thing.
Bingo.
In a few short minutes,
it's going to turn
this entire city into a more,
shall we say,
hospitable environment for us.
And in the meantime,
you three runts will
make a delicious snack.
Tails?
[KRANGAZOIDS GROWLING]
Oh, a wise guy, huh?
Why, I ought to--
Dudes, we better split.
Now all we have to do is wait
and when this city's been
turned into an enormous volcano,
I shall be absolute ruler.
What do you mean,
you'll be absolute ruler?
I should be absolute ruler.
[ALL ARGUING INDISTINCTLY]
Well, that didn't work.
We better go rescue
Leonardo and April.
Yeah, and time's running out.
You do realize, of course,
that we'll be charging
head-first into a trap?
I know, but we've gotta get
that teleportation device
of Shredder's.
Dudes, what we need
is some serious firepower.
You know,
the kind those Krangazoids
were packing
in their bubble-walkers.
Michelangelo,
you're an absolute genius.
Totally righteous, huh?
I am?
It's been nearly half an hour.
What's keeping
those stupid turtles?
BEBOP:
They always show up
to rescue their friends
just in the nick of time.
BEBOP:
Oh, boy, is this gonna be easy.
DONATELLO:
Oh, I wouldn't be
too sure about that.
Whoa!
There you go, amigo.
wretched reptile,
I'll fillet you!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Drink blazing photons,
robo-scum.
Oh. Always wanted to say that.
[GRUNTS]
DONATELLO:
All right.
There's the teleporter.
And this must be
the teleportation receiver.
[GRUNTING, SWORDS CLASHING]
Hyah!
[SHREDDER CRIES OUT]
ROCKSTEADY:
Come on, boss. We're losing.
He shoots, he scores!
RAPHAEL:
They're getting away.
With all this artillery,
we could have finally
caught those creepazoids.
But I want them to get away.
You do?
Yeah. It's all part of the plan.
Excuse me. We have a plan?
Of course.
Come on.
Hurry. We haven't much time.
[APRIL SCREAMS]
What's going on?
[EXPLOSION]
The Krang clones are making
a volcano under the city
and we've gotta stop it.
You better stay up here, April.
It'll be safer.
Yeah. But for how long?
[BUBBLING]
Hang on, guys.
This is gonna get hot.
Now, how are we gonna cool
down that molten mountain?
With those.
[YELLING]
[GROWLING]
DONATELLO:
The minicam.
We've gotta get it back.
Leave it to me, compadre.
Guys, back off.
Say cheese, cheese-heads.
[ZAPS]
DONATELLO:
The valves. Come on.
SHREDDER:
At least those wretched reptiles
can't do anything
to us down here.
KRANGAZOID:
Who are you calling
wretched reptiles, bum?
LEONARDO:
Come on, harder.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Come on, come on.
[VALVE SQUEAKS]
That'll douse the volcano.
Yeah. Not only that,
but we're getting
a supremo sauna.
Say, Donatello, where'd
you zap those Krangazoids?
Well, with any luck,
straight to the Technodrome.
Ha. Now they're Krang
and Shredder's problem.
KRANGAZOID:
So you thought you could
boss us around, huh?
We shall be your masters now.
No. Wait.
I can send you home.
To where you belong.
To Dimension X.
KRANGAZOID 2:
Oh. Our homeland. Oh joy!
Did you really send them
to Dimension X?
And have six of me
running loose there?
Are you out of your
cotton-picking mind?
I sent them
to the dimensional limbo.
Hey. This ain't Dimension X.
Oh, I'll say.
It's h-horrible.
It's even more
wretched and depressing
than that planet Earth.
It's some kind
of dimensional limbo
and we're trapped here.
This is all your fault.
My fault?
Well, pretty boy here
is the one who went
through the portal first.
RAPHAEL:
Yeah, you guys,
let's make a mental note
to smash that cloning machine
of Krang's
next time we visit
the Technodrome.
Good idea.
We can't afford
to have him making
any more duplicates.
DONATELLO:
Can you imagine what might
happen if he made six Shredders?
MICHELANGELO:
Yeah, or six Rocksteadys.
Or worse yet,
six Vernons.
Oh, come on.
That wouldn't be so bad.
VERNON [ON TV]:
Sources say that the volcano
was put out
by the Teenage Mutant
Ninja Turtles,
but frankly, this reporter
doesn't believe it.
On second thought,
that would be pretty horrifying.
[♪♪♪]