you can tell me.
You know you want to.
I don't want to.
You're afraid.
Or you justcan't do it.
No,I'm not.
All right,I'll give it a shot.
Hold on.
Ooh.
Uh! It's a boy!
No,wait a minute,it's a girl.
Oh,twins.
Twins,walt.
Hey,hey,hey,what's going on here?
I thought we were
gonnakeep this a surprise.
What's happening?
I'm justteasing johnny.
Hey,J.J.  ,Let's go.
We got a lot to do today.
Yeah.
What do you say to johnny for
making us breakfastthis morning?
Thanks f ***kitchenis torn up.
Well,J.J.,I'm excited to seeyour
band tonight,buddy.
The bass playerbroke
his wrist snowboarding.
The new guy learned stuffthis week.
But he sucks,so don't expect too much.
I'm glad reverend purdybrought
back the faith heritagewinterfest.
Yeah,rememberwhen we were kids,we had
the sleigh ridesand the snow fights.
Hot chocolateand pie-eating contests.
Now it's justanother opportunity
for stillsonto make a speech,man.
Well,I don't careabout the speech.
I'm all aboutthe pie eating.
Yeah,me too.
Johnny,you hear the namewe
made up for the baby?
Don't even know if it's
a boy or a girl yet.
Gretzky bannerman.
The great one.
Gretzky bannerman?
-I like that.
--I was kidding.
That's good,though. I like that.
Bannerman.
Hey,yeah.
Hey,J.J.,Do me a favor. Take this,please.
-Yeah.
-Thank you.
One second,sarah. Be right back.
Hey...is everything okay?
Yeah,sure.
You're not mad that I
didn'ttell you about the baby?
I mean,I could.
We don't have to tell walt.
I'm not so sure walt careseither way.
Come on,of course he does.
Yeah,I know.
It's just he's beenso busy lately.
Well,work,a new house,right?
No,it's not the houseor work.
It's something else.
I saw him emailingon the computer the other
night and when I came in,he turned it off.
I don't know,think he has a girlfriend?
Oh,sheriff walt?
A girlfriend?
Come on.
Why don't you just
ask himwhat he's doing?
You thinkI haven't tried?
all right,let's get going.
Time to set upsome bingo.
And,hey,on theirst encore,I want
to hear layla,got it--remember?
What's layla?
Oh,man!
And I don't thinkyou guys are getting
any preferentialbingo treatment.
This is gonna be a clean game here.
And you,john,no visionsabout
what number's next,huh?
sometimes fate deals us a strange hand.
On the day of the
faith heritage festival
,a day when normally we
would celebrate community,
the people of cleaves mills lost one of
its most beloved citizens-- walt bannerman.
Walt.
Hey,come on,bingo waits for no man.
I,H... I just had a vision...
that you're gonna die.
Come on.
What,are you serious?
Today.
You're gonna die.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: Max  ÏûÉùÄä¼£
The Dead Zone
Season 6 Episode 1
Heritage
you sure you're notworking anything dangerous?
I'm sheriff,john.
Every day's dangerous.
What happened to me?
I don't know.
In the vision,purdy says that it
happenedthe day of the festival.
All right,well,I'm workinga bingo booth.
How dangerouscan that be?
Well,we needto take this seriously.
John,after allwe've been
through,I do take this seriously.
I can also take careof myself,you know?
All right,but todayyou have no choice.
I'm sticking to you close,like glue.
All right,well,do me a favor.
Don't tell sarah.
Got it?
All right,we got nothingto
worry about,right?
Nope.
Hey,johnny,maybeyou can ride with walt.
Okay,I can help himset
up that bingo booth too.
That sounds fun.
Come by and visit us.
We'll have the pest
prizesat the festival today.
I got the best prize right here.
What is that look?
Nothing.
I'm just thinking thatyou
get prettier every day.
I look more likea
bowling ball every day.
J.J.  ,Let's go.
Like glue,huh?
All right.
What could be betterthan
goldfish for best prize,huh?
I don't know,kittens,puppies?
Your best bottleof tequila.
uh-oh...there's stillson.
Morning,johnny,walt.
Little chillyfor these guys,isn't it?
Yes,it is,mr.Vice president.
That's got a nice ringto it,doesn't it?
I would have thought
washingtonwas keeping you busy.
I always enjoy comingto cleaves mills.
Back to my roots.
Thinking of making
itmy own kennebunkport.
And I've always got thefaith heritage satellite
feed to keep up with all the beltway action.
Gonna be thereat the speech tonight?
Yeah,I wouldn't miss itfor the world.
I welcome the opportunity to give
something backto faith heritage,
after everythingthat reverend
purdy has done for me.
Walt,I owe youa congratulations.
I heard the newsabout you and sarah.
Thanks,greg.
It's wonderful.
Children can besuch a blessing.
Gentlemen,tight schedule.
Always a
pleasure--yes.
Great to seethe two of you.
Pleasure to see you,mr.Vice president.
Always a pleasureto shake the
hand of a man with such vision.
Stillson'sa heartbeat away
from becoming president.
Nothing can stop him.
I'm gonna need a hotdogand
a cappuccino,if you will.
Nonfat.
Thank you.
Malcolm.
A hotdog?
Next you'll be buildinga snowman.
How can you standbeing here?
Oh,I like maine.
It's where I startedmy political career.
Would you likea hotdog,malcolm?
Don't allow yourselfto
get distracted,mr.Vice president.
I know what you're doing.
No,I knowwhat you're doing.
You're giving a speechtonight
on the faith heritagesatellite.
Subject matter:Global warming.
And you will beprepared.
You underestimate me,malcolm.
No,sir,that's one thingI never do.
I've made some changesto your speech.
Please look them over.
The vice president has reconsidered.
He won't be havingthe hotdog after all.
bobby,I'll take one with extra relish.
 here
you guys go,congratulations.
Look at that,huh?
I'll give you botha fish,how's that?
What's the deal with youkeeping
eagle eyes on walt all day?
Who says I'm doing that?
Well,zero reactionwhen I
mentioned my job offer earlier.
Job offer?
You got a job offer?
My point exactly.
It's a great gig.
Sports trainer for all
kindof professional athletes.
Sweet paycheck.
Congratulations.
It sounds perfect,man.
Almost--it's
out of state.
Listen,if it'sa good opportunity for you---
come on,and let youfight stillson by yourself?
I'm not leaving you alonewith
armageddon out there.
Walt!
whoa,whoa,whoa,hey.
You wanna see what the
insideof a jail cell looks like?
Keep that up.
It's a really good way to find out.
Come on,let's go.
Faith Heritage
University
we didn't support faith heritage,
give you money,a satellite,
a bigger audience than ever for you to throwa
carnival for cleaves millscountry bumpkins.
You should be concentratingon stillson.
Fundraising for hisfuture
run for the presidency.
That's our objective,not sipping
hot cider,or making s'mores.
I have been thinking lessabout stillson,
admittedly,and more about faith heritage.
I'm not sure I'm comfortable with the
directionwe're headed in these days.
Who are you to makethat decision?
The founder of faith heritage.
You have a short memory,gene.
Remember?
I put you backon your feet.
I've decidedto take faith heritage
back to where it used to be.
A churchfor the community.
Not a global interestthat
serves politicians.
Did johnny smithput you up to this?
Johnny has nothingto do with this.
Your agenda isat cross
purposes with god's work.
You don't understandanything,gene.
"And these will waragainst the
lamb,and the lamb willovercome them.
" "O-66.
" Clickity-click,66.
"O-66.
" bingo,I got it!
Oh,we have a
winner--come on up here.
Hey,buddy,can I get a hotdog?
Thanks.
Give me the money!
Hurry up!
Give me the money.
Stop!
Stop that man!
I've been robbed!
Walt,come back!
stop!
Stop that man! I've been robbed!
stop that man! I've been robbed!
Heads up! Watch out!
Don't move or you'll
feela whole lot worse.
I think I owe you one,john.
"We fix our eyes not on
what is seen..."
well? It's not over.
So what's going on?
A guy with two strikes looking
at someserious jail time.
All in a day's work.
But what about the phone
callat the house this morning?
Walt,I'm not letting goof this.
All right,I am working on
somethingoutside of work.
Well,that doesn'ttell me much.
Look,john,we've been friendsa long time.
You help me with my
stuff,I help you with yours.
But you've gotta trust meon this one.
It's not dangerousand it's not
something that sarah needsto know,a'ight?
I'm still keeping my eye on you.
Fine.
Where are you going now?
I'm goingto the bathroom.
You wanna follow mein there too?
Now really.
Okay.
Come on.***
***
-Drop it!
-walt,watch out!
I'm gonna kill you!
Don't know if I can
handlea whole day of this.
Yeah,you and me both.
No.
Well?
I got nothing.
Which means what?
I didn't see anything.
Okay,good.
Now you can stopbothering me
and I can go to the bathroom.
Yeah.
Look at this guyup there,huh?
Hey hey!
What have you twobeen up to?
Oh,the usual.
Wow,he's gotyour musical talent,huh?
He's good.
He's a big ham,like you.
Oh,stop.
Cut it out.
Bannerman.
***
He'll be back.
Excuse me.
I'll see you thereat
the park in ten minutes.
Okay,thank you very much.
Listen,I gotta run,okay?
I gotta see somebody,but
I'll be back really soon.
You're leaving?
I'll be back shortly,okay?
Walt.
Look,it's nothingto worry about,sarah.
No,I am worried.
The way you'vebeen acting
lately-- hiding things.
Have you noticed?
I'm having a baby.
And your son isexpecting you to
come congratulate himin a minute.
I wouldn't be doing
thisif it wasn't important.
More important than J.J.?
You know,the pastcouple of weeks,your
family's beencoming in second place.
I'll make it up to you...and J.J.
Really?
I mean,you're not
listeningto me anymore.
I feel like I'm speakinga
different language.
Je t'aime.
Very funny.
Well,it used to be when we learnedto say
"I love you" in eight differentlanguages.
I'm too mad to playthat game right now.
I want you to stay hereand see J.J.
I've been waitingfor
this lead for a long time.
I gotta go deal with this
nowand then I'll be back.
Ti amo.
So,gene,what'd you thinkof
the new introduction?
It's not gonnabe necessary.
I'll be making the speech.
I wasn't made awareof this.
Well,I decided thatit's more
appropriate for me to deliver the speech.
After all,this isn'ta political rally.
It's the faith heritagefestival.
Gene-
-mr.Vice president,with all due respect,
I used to believewhat you stood for.
But now I havesome serious
concerns about the peoplebehind you.
Don't you?
Where'd walt go?
He didn't tell me.
You didn't see anything?
Visions about walt.
I mean,you'd tell me,right?
Yeah.
I haven't seen anything.
What do you think?
Did you like my song?
Well,I know the bass playerwas
off tune,but otherwise,was it okay?
You were great.
The solo was awesome!
Where's dad?
He had some business.
But he'll be back as soon as he's done.
What's that?
Oh,it's a gift card.
Reverend purdy gave itto us for playing.
We get to buy mp3 songs.
on the day of the
faith heritage festival,
the people of cleaves mills mourn the
loss of one of our most beloved citizens.
sheriff bannerman,do you know
how longI've held on to this?
If this is true...
john
smith's in fora big surprise.
If you don't believe
me,ask reverend purdy.
this is reverend purdy leave
a message after the tone.
Gene,it's johnny.
Do me a favor,get back to
meas soon as you can,okay?
It's important.
Thank you.
Are you gonna actually tell
mewhat's going on with walt?
Listen,I had a visionthat walt died.
I thought I stopped it.
Now I thinkI put purdy in danger.
Have you seen him?
Not in a while.
But we'll find him.
Let's split up.
Good job.
Here you go.
Well,congratulationson the,uh-
- bowling ball.
That's what my mom calls it.
J.J.
wow,you threw that just like a girl.
Ahem.
Sorry.
Girls can throw great.
Especially my mom.
Yeah.
Yeah,I'm sure she can.
-Oh,you were closerthat time.
-So here's the deal,J.J.
If I miss this thirdand final shot
I will give you a rideon air force two.
Or air force one,if
you wait a couple years.
How's that sound?
Wow!
Oh....
That's all right.
We can pretend I
missed.How's that sound?
If it's okay with your mom,you
pick a weekend,I'll take you up.
so what's my prize?
Here you go,Mr ***.
enough sweet.
well,thank you very much.
good seeing.
also
I get to ridein air force two.
****
Hey,have you seenreverend purdy?
I left just a while ago.
What did he say wherehe was going?
We're about readyto
broadcast--he's gotta come back.
He left his notes.
Let get set up ***
What up,john?
walt,listen to me.
I just got a bad
vision.Purdy's gonna die.
You know the chapel at faith heritage?
There's a stained glassof st.Michael.
It's gonna explode.
I'm meeting him hereright now.
You're meeting him
-Walt.
-oh,my god.
Walt.
janus.
Oh,my god.
Come on...come on.
He's not responding.
He's gone.
Walt,no.no..
no....
There's my man.
How you doing,buddy?
Okay.
You need some help?
No,I got it.
That's the tricky part right there.
The guy that came upwith
that,I wanna smack.
You got it now just pull the big part
over the top.
Down--drop it
through there.
Perfect.
You did great.
Okay,watch me.
There you go.
See that,you're
alreadyin the homestretch.
And voila.
-Perfect.
-Dad!
******
I've never really done
itby myself before.
My dad used to do itfor me.
You're doing fine,J.J.
He was gonna teach mea
lot of stuff this summer.
He was gonna teach me howto water ski.
He was gonna let me
ride the atvon the lake.
But we weren't gonna tell mom.
You won't tell her,will you?
No.
We would always joke about howhe was gonna
have to teach me to shave pretty soon.
"None of those electric
blades,"he'd say.
A real blade.
That's what a real guy uses.
I just-- I can't
believe he's gone.
Hey...
Me either.
People are startingto show up.
I don't wantto see anybody.
I'll just tell people
you're not feeling well.
I haven't cried yet.
Isn't that weird?
I mean,what will people say when
they seeI haven't been crying?
First I lose you and now I lose walt.
I must have banked
upsome really lousy karma.
It's not karma.
Then what the hell is it?
Can you explain it to me?
Because I don't understand it.
And can you explain how
you with all your visions
never saw this coming?
I mean,how could you miss this one?
Sarah,whatever happenedin the chapel...
whatever he was doing...
I'm sure that he died doing
something that he always did.
Something heroic.
That really doesn'tmake
me feel any better.
Walt tried to save someone and
so now I don't havea husband
and J.J.Doesn't havea father.
You know,our last
conversation was a fight.
And I think thatthat's the hardest part.
You know,the thought that he died
thinking that I was mad at him.
I never got to say good-bye.
And it's just somethingI'm
gonna have to live with.
And there's nothingyou
can do or say to help me.
We should go.
Man,I can't believe it.
Oh... never misses an
opportunityfor a photo-op.
never misses an
I'm sorry.
It's a terrible tragedy.
Yeah,it is.
If there's anythingI can
do for you or the family
anything at all... let
me tell you something.
-If I find out you had anything to do with this
-his wife is pregnant with their child.
Walt was a good man.
We're all gonna miss him.
Certainly no one's
gonnamiss malcolm janus.
Agreed?
I'm not the man you think I am.
Sometimes fate deals usa strange hand.
On the day of the
faith heritage festival
a day when normally we
would celebrate community
cleaves mills lost oneof
its most beloved citizens
walt bannerman.
Cherished husband of
sarah,devoted father to J.J.
walt faced danger every day
with courage and con...
conviction.
We will never allow ourselvesto
forget walt bannerman.
We will not forget his sacrifice.
"There fore,we do not lose heart.
"Though out wardly we are
wasting away,"yet inwardly
we are being ren ewed "day by day.
"For our light and momentary
troubles "are achieving for us
an eternal glory "that
outweighs them all.
"So we fix our eyes not on what is seen
"but on what is unseen.
"For what is seenis temporary
but what is unseenis eternal.
" Lovely eulogy,reverend purdy.
Thank you.
Gene.
Walt,is that you?
You denied stillson
the satellite feed and you thought
there wouldn't be consequences?
That is very braeof you,gene
I'm doing what's right.
Stillson is moving forward
ard and you will make that happen! -no!
You can keepleading stillson astray.
It stops right now with me.
I in tend to reclaimmy church!
Your church?!
It doesn't belongto you anymore!
No--unh!
I am reclaiming my church!
Gene,we gotta go.
Get the hell out of
here,get down--go,go,go
You were there.
Walt died saving you.
I still think you need
to goto the authorities
and just tell them what happened.
That I killedmalcolm janus?
In self defense.
The police will neverbelieve me.
I left walt there.
I saw what happenedat the chapel,gene.
There was nothing you could have done.
I'm responsible for
the deathsof two men.
How do I go aboutforgiving
myself for that?
Why was waltat the chapel?
He said we had to meet.
Why?
Something about you.
Me?
What about me?
I don't know.
I have to leave.
-To go where?
-I have no idea.
Ashes to ashes.
Gene.
I'm gonna turn downthat job offer.
Why?
Janus is dead.
Armageddon's over.
Take that job.
Try something new.
It's not gonna be the same,you know
having a psychicin my back pocket.
You know whereto find me.
Where am I going?
There's still somethingyou're
not telling me.
I saw gene die.
I called walt.
He went in to tryto save purdy.
-But if I hadn't done that...
-you tried to save
no,no,no,you know what
you did save him...twice.
What are you saying,that
walt was fated to die?
People maketheir own destiny.
Walt tried to save purdy.
He was doing his job.
-That case that walt wasworking on
-let it go.
I just feel likeI need to tell sarah
that I saw walt's death,you know?
I couldn't do anything.
Sarah does not need to know.
-Trust me on that.
-She deserves the truth.
-No,what sarah doesn't know
-would be a lie.
J.J.Said you were here.
What are you doing here?
I thought if I looked around,maybe I'd
... find out something.
I don't know...
maybe explain things
if I had justmade him stay.
It was his decision,sarah.
This mysterious case
walt did what he always did.
He put other people first.
But why did he cometo the chapel?
No one will tell me what happened.
All they did was give me his effects.
This is all I have left.
sarah...
what do you see?
Sarah...sarah...
he's saying your name.
No,you're--you're
just making that up.
Tell J.J.That I love him.
I've been the luckiest manalive.
Ti amo,sarah.
Ti amo.
Oh,my god,you saw him.
What else did he say?
To tell J.J.How muchhe loved him.
And that you made him feel
likethe luckiest man in the world.
Did he suffer?
No.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Sync: Max ÏûÉùÄä¼£