BROUGHT TO YOU BY RAMEN SOUP SUBS!
[Before taping]
[JongShin at Inki Gayo rehearsal]
[On the stage you can't find a trace of his sickly demeanor]
I have a lot of fun watching Family Outing
Ah we need to have Minwoo come out
I'm getting a phone call
Hello?
Hello Family, this is Yoo Jaesuk!  This time we'll be going to Nonsan in the South Chungcheong province.
Please meet at Ihmegol's village hall by 9:00AM.  Dispatch over.
I understand
[New Family member Song Chang Eui]
Hey! They said I'm going to Nonsan.  I guess I'll be going.
[Tells the 200 Pound Beauty Musical family the news]
Come back alive!
Family Outing, here I come.
[On our way to Nonsan]
[In front of the village hall]
[As always, the first to arrive, Sooro]
[Chunhee arrives too...]
Did you just come from Russia?
[Russian officer?!]
It's Hyori
Why do you keep doing body gags (physical comedy) lately?
Hi oppa!
[Jongkook is here, too!]
Oppa, hi!
[Yejin arrives]
[As well as Daesung]
[One person still hasn't arrived]
Who's the one not here?
Jongshin hyung!
[Jongshin is running late today]
Let's just go on ahead then
[At this moment]
And do what?
[Anticipating]
Changeui!
[Tender and charming golden boy, song changeui]
[Hyori enthusiastically greets him]
JS: Do you know him?
-HR: Nope!
[An intimate hug with Sooro]
Sooro hyung was just saying that the two of you (Chunhee and Changeui) went to the same school.  But that Changeui lived like a prince
Actually, while I was at school I wasn't friends with Chunhee.
Oh really?
[Confused]
So you were a friend he didn't know existed!
But we were in Room 5 together!
No, we were close.
Hyung, here's the map
[Confirming the grandmother's map]
Okay let's go
[Ditching Jongshin and on our way to grandma's house]
[Last night's frost covers everything in white]
[The famous delicious dried persimmons]
[The peaceful Ihmegol village]
[While Changeui is leading the way]
Oppa!
[The elderly Jongshin arrives]
[Changeui comes to greet]
[Changeui leads everyone inside]
[Arriving at Grandma's house]
Hello!
[Kim YoungWoo, Grandfather /The 15th Outing / Seo YongSoon, Grandma]
[Happily welcomed]
On our way here I saw dried persimmons...
Yes we have very delicious dried persimmons here
Has it been a long time since you've traveled?
This year is really a commemoration for us
What kind?
This year is his 60th birthday
Wow! It's your 60th birthday!
Since we're in the country we can't really travel, so we really love this opportunity.
So this worked out really well for you guys
[Since it's Grandfather's 60th birthday, there's a warm feeling for this vacation]
Bye!
[The grandparents that haven't traveled in a long time]
[Off to make warm and lovely memories for his 60th birthday]
Oh the things to do
[List of chores!]
Make mehju
Prepare persimmons to dry
Grandma said she already put the soybeans on the stove
Oh she did?
-HR: We can't let them burn so we should hurry
-JS: That's right, let's go fast
But what are we going to make for dinner?
There's a reservoir here
-JS: Then hyung, let's catch some fish
-SR: Okay
We'll go fishing and make maeun tang (hot spicy fish soup)
Sounds good
But since the soybeans can burn someone has to stay behind to stir it
Ok we'll play rock-paper-scissor, and the winner can choose someone to stay with them
Since we're playing with a lot of people let's just do it so that the people doing the least used hand is dropped from the game and not care about who wins in each round.
Rock, paper, scissor!
This is kinda weird
Ok whoever has rock is out
There's 4 of us left now
Okay now it's just us four playing
[People left, Sooro, Chunhee, Hyori, Daesung]
What happened? Am I out?
[Hyori is out]
[Chunee is out]
[Sooro wins]
Our strongest family member is going to stir the beans!
Can I can pick 2 people instead so I can go fishing?
[The winner doing whatever he wants]
Ok, ok, ok
Okay I'll do that.  I pick Hyori and Jongkook.
[The Awkward couple get picked]
I don't wanna!
[Both of them are fiercely resisting]
Sooro Hyung!
[But the rest of the family thinks that Stepmother Kim made an excellent selection]
[The awkward couple stays behind to stir the fermented beans]
[So that little by little they can get friendlier]
[Irked]
Oh my stomach, my stomach!
[Repulsed]
[Jaesuk is about to die from laughing]
This is too funny!
I think this is the best thing I've done on Family
(Given up) Kim Kookjong, get over here!
[Will the Nation's fairy be controlling this time?!]
Get over here!
[Dominated and insecure, One Man]
Do you want to have a staring contest? Ok, come here!
Why that?!
What do you think you're doing?!
Do it for 5 seconds! 1, 2, 3!
[The awkward couple doing a staring contest for the first time]
[Delaying the staring contest can only lead to]
[Even if just a little, can they get closer]
[Can't even do it for 1 second]
[Looks away]
No!
Does he like me or something?
Huh? Hey, do you like her?
Jaesuk hyung!
[Bewildered]
These two are good
That's right.  Just stir the pot together.
[The awkward couple has to spend time together for the first time]
The abusive language is just how she is
[What will happen with these two]
[Family's To Do List
1. Make mehju
2. Prepare persimmons to dry
3. Watch the house well and clean]
[Chapter 1:/ Jongkook and Hyori, the awkward scandal]
[Awkward]
Stand closer together, you guys are going to stay here anyways.
They're standing more than shoulder's width apart
Wait, but why are all our moods so bright?
[They're all very delighted]
Hyori looks like a new bride
Hyori unni, stand like this with Jongkook oppa.
[It's even more awkward like this]
We can make it even more awkward saying goodbye
We're on our way after playing well
[A farewell towards a married couple from houseguests]
We'll come visit again!
[Awkward newlywed couple?]
Visiting the newlywed couple was nice
Go inside already!
[The surprised remaining people]
[The One Woman who doesn't know what to do]
Let's go
[The embarrassed and awkward One Man]
Okay
[To the kitchen to stir the fermented soybeans]
[The fermented soybeans that Grandma left on the stove needs to be cooked for 2 more hours.]
Here it is
[Tip: Keep pouring in water every now and then and keep watch over the fire]
Wow!
I think we have to cook these until they're practically crumbling
-JK: We have to keep watch over the water?
-HR: Yeah
Oppa, the fire...
[Staring hard]
How is it?
(stuttering)
If you do this you can save the fire
Oh, it's okay now
[If only the two can huk! burn away their awkwardness]
[10 minutes have passed]
[Awkward silence]
[Hyori, absorbed in thought]
[Wooden spoon?]
(What is she going to do with that...?)
I played this with Chunhee before where we played rock-paper-scissor and the loser gets hit on the cheek by this.
[On the cheek?!]
[Will the awkward couple be able to get closer by hitting each other on the cheek?]
Rock, paper, sci-
Hold on a minute! Let me think about this.
It's just a game
No, it's just that this happened really fast
[Should I play, or not play?]
Rock, paper, scissor!
[Hyori wins]
(This can't be...)
Were you trying to hide?
How can I not move when you're doing that?
[A proper hit]
Since it's just a game, play it cool.
[The two try to play it cool]
[This time Jongkook wins]
[Uneasy about hitting her hard]
[Will Jongkook play it cool since it's a game?]
You're letting me off the hook?
[Hyori wins]
Hit this side
(She did it again...)
It's funnier if you hit hard during games
Even playing games is awkard..
It hurt a bit though
Did it?
[Embarrassed]
[After 30 minutes]
(Ca)mera, hi!
Today I'm feeling awkward because this one person is here.
But since you're here as well, I'm happy!
[The One Man is also in front of (ca)mera.]
-HR: Are you looking at your reflection?
-JK: No!
[Even so their luck seems to blossom~]
Talk to it
Mera... Mera, hi.
You're really good friends with Hyori, huh?
I'm making an effort to get to know her too.
But since you're here, I feel more comfortable.
Please be good to Hyori.  Tell her that...
I don't hate her.
It just seems that way since it's awkward.  Talk to you later.
You did a good job
Oh did I?  Good.
[Even so... there's still a gap between them]
[The family members that went fishing]
I haven't done it with real fishing poles before
I've done it twice
Oh really?
A long time ago
[Arriving at the fishing spot]
Wow~
It's really nice here
[The still and expansive reservoir]
We have to put bait on here
but the bait is worms.
I don't think Yoo Jaesuk will be able to touch the worms.
You did it once before though
[Opening the can of worms]
The worms...
[Extreme fright]
[Dumb and dumber cause a commotion]
They're alive, they're alive!
[The worms for bait]
How can they just spring out right when I open it?
I think they gave us snakes
Put the hook through the thickest part of their body
I don't think I can do this!
[Dumb brother making a fuss]
[Dumber little brother as well]
(What's there to be scared of?)
Oppa, do I push it through the middle?  Behind the neck?
[Savage Yejin appears]
(The rumors are true that she's a scary woman...)
Ok hold the pole in your left hand.
[Jongshin gives instructions]
When you push in this part, it'll unreel on it's own
Throwing it is the most important part
I know we don't know what we're doing, but you've only gone two times before.
So this will only be your third time.
When the pole is over your head release your reel
Give it a shot
If you release it later, it'll just crash to the ground
Alright, here I go.
I'm uneasy about this.
What if he falls in with the pole?
[Here I go]
[Huh?! It didn't even unreel!!]
[His explanations were so precise and it still came out like this]
What is that?  Seriously, what is that?
Hey, give me a second
[Suddenly very quiet]
You gave us instructions for like an hour
This is irritating
Do you think what we learned was right?
[Jaesuk's turn!]
[The line went out very far]
[Feels like an ace for a moment]
Wow you did everything I taught you well!
You are my handiwork
[Yejin's turn!!]
[Hers went out the furthest!]
I think I'm a natural at this!
[Anticipating Changeui's ability]
[Drops to the ground]
[In case someone says I'm not Chunhee's friend]
[The bait fell off his hook]
-Chunhee: Ever since we were in school he wasn't really good with these kind of things.
-Jaesuk: Really?
[Clumsy Chunhee's shabby friend]
Whenever you're friends come on, they're all...
Oh Jongshin hyung, be careful
-PD: Make sure the reel is pushed in
-Changeui: What?
You have to push it in, he says.  Push.  This, push this in.
[Clumsy Chunhee scolding his friend]
Should we switch poles?
That's not the reason.
Take a look at your pole.  One of your rings is facing up.
Are you going to catch any fish like that?
[Clumsy Chunhee makes a good point?]
You just.. hold it like this
[Chunhee is still nagging]
And throw it far like this
Alright!
[Changeui can't hold it in any longer...]
Chunhee hyung just stop lecturing him and come over here
That jerk with his one ring facing up
Chunhee, take care of your own pole first.
Yours is all wrong, too
Changeui, just watch your friend do it.
[How good does he think he'd be, even moving to a different spot...]
Changeui, watch me!  Just do it like this...
[Gets caught in the tree!]
[He'd do something like that...]
Hey, hey, hey!  I said that you'd do something weird, didn't I
[Even in the new year he's still Clumsy Chunhee...]
We just have to wait now
It's done?  Is this fishing?
What do we do now?
Should we play a game?
No just pick a spot and wait there
Usually you just sit quietely when fishing
If you talk too much the fishes don't come
I wonder how Jongkook and Hyori are doing
I'm kind of worried about them
I think they're not even talking to each other since they're so awkward
I know, huh
But you don't know, they can also become close too
True
[They spent the next 30 minutes awkwardly]
Since I'm here I didn't get a chance to work out
Can you be my personal trainer?
[Workout in the kitchen]
My backside is the area I want to focus on
The back?  You have to do pulling motions to exercise the back
I guess..
You can just have me pull you
What?
I can pull you
[Awk~~ward]
Ok, pull me
No, no, we can't do this
[Embarrassed]
Why? This works well
[Trying it again]
Ok, pull me
Wait a minute.  Let's not do this.
No!  My back is really important!  I have a lot of problem areas in my back.
People can become closer with common interests
-Jongkook: You really enjoy exercising
-Hyori: Yes
I think it's really attractive when women have toned thighs
So you must look at a lot of women's thighs?
No, it's just that... when I look at female celebrities...
When you look at female celebrities you stare at their thighs
[They were just barely getting closer with their exercises]
[And still it ends up awkward]
No, I look at their eyes
Oh, their eyes?
Where do you look when you look at a man?
Me?  Their butt.
Their butt needs to be firm
When it's sagging it's not attractive
Yours seem firm
Oh, I didn't do my butt exercises
You do it like this?
So what?
You can do it like that, but your waist..
Then how should I do it?
Face down like this and fold your knee in
Oh this is the first time I've seen it done that way
Yeah just like that.  No bring your knee all the way in to your chest
Where do you think you're touching?
I was just guiding your leg!
[One minute their cooking and now...]
Stretching it out is the most important part
UP!
One more time!
Now the other leg
Did your pants rip?
No, it was my bones
Ok hold it!  And slowly bring it down.
[It looks like they just came from a health club]
Oh this is good
We can make a work out tape together
[Hit! Awkward Couple's Workout Video!]
Everyone please follow along. Now, 1...
[If the Awkward couple knew they could speed along their friendship like this...]
[Stimulating workout]
[If there's an awkward moment, try exercising together]
Oh! Oppa, this can be a workout!
[Pot lid workout!]
Don't just go halfway
Use your strength
This is a workout, too!
Stretch me out more.  Raise your hips.  Oh this is refreshing.
Wait, I'm not your servant am I?
How should I pour the water?
[During the workout, they pour in the water so the beans won't burn]
In a circular motion
[The fermented soybeans cooked by the Awkward couple that have grown closer.]
Mera-ya.  Kim Kookjong...
[Can he hear through the earmuffs?]
I think Kim Kookjong really likes me.
He just pretends to be awkward around me, but I think he's fond of me.
I can hear you!
What? No.. I was just..
I can hear you! And Hyori, that's not it!
I was just kidding around!
[Becoming close very quickly, the Awkward couple]
[And the quickly cooked mehju beans]
[Drain the water]
[The family have been fishing for 1 hour]
[Bored]
[Tedious]
[Listless]
If we can't catch any fish, do we really just have to eat rice?
No, that can't be
We have kimchi
We have 6 fishing poles, how can we not possibly have one fish
[Someone is singing?]
[It looks like he's really bored]
[They can't seem to catch anything even when they're quiet]
[They wait for so long but the fish do not come]
[Rather than waiting, Hyori and Jongkook go]
Oppa!
You scared me
We finished
-Jaesuk: Really?
-Daesung: Did you get closer?
You guys should have just talked to one another.
No it's just that so much time has passed
Where's the fish?
In the water
We should just cook the whole reservoir
It's because I wasn't here that we couldn't catch even one fish
You need someone looking over you, huh?
If we can't catch any fish, what are we going to do about dinner?
Just ask one of the staff members to watch the poles
Ok, let's go play a game
Did you put the worms on and everything?
Yes
Who?
Nowadays I can do it all
[The Family leaves the reservoir]
[While the youngest assistant stays behind alone]
[Lonely]
[I'll guard the fishing poles]
We should have caught fish, but what can we do?
We have our youngest PD watching the poles.
He came here to be part of production but we have him watching fishing poles instead.
We should have sent the PD that talks too much
Then the fish wouldn't come
Why aren't the fish coming?
Hurry up and come!  Come and bite!
Hi Hyori!
[The Family are able to imitate their PD's personality]
We're going to play a game in this empty rice field
We'll spin around five times doing the elephant trunk
hop over those bales of hay
and then break through that plastic wall
and whoever breaks through first wins.
-Hyori: We have to break through that?
-Jaesuk: Yes
This reminds me of our first episode.
Hyori's body gags in that came out in full force
We shouldn't do that now though because the ground is frozen
Yes, we should be very careful
I can't really jump over these
While you're trying to break through the plastic, you can pull each other away
Jaesuk: Okay
Hyori: Of course
[Jaesuk vs Hyori]
Ready...
Go!
[These two will be unsteady this way]
[Wow, Hyori's moving fast]
[Hyori sets her mind to win]
[Hyori is the first to arrive at the plastic wall]
[But it's not easy to break through]
[Jaesuk comes from behind]
[First he pushes Hyori away]
This isn't working!
[It broke!!]
Where do you think you're going?
[Pulls her away at a crucial moment]
[The always fighting Nation's siblings]
[Jaesuk's now able to push his leg through]
[Hyori will lose if he goes through]
[Hyori makes a mad dash]
[Who will come out the victor?]
[Hyori hops over Jaesuk's back and touches the ground first]
[Hyori wins]
I won!
Hyori wins!
Hey, Jaesuk's the one on our team
[Hyori is the best at game strategy]
[Chunhee vs Changeui]
Hey Chunhee, Changeui has a lot of room to win with you so just...
I have room too
I feel bad about this
You have to do this right.  Jump over each one correctly and break through right.
[Why is Chunhee nagging during a game]
Alright
You have to do the elephant trunk.  Do you know how to do the elephant trunk?
Just worry about yourself
You've never done anything like this before
(And you call yourself a friend...!)
Chunhee, he said just to worry about yourself
Ok, ready
You have to shout out how many times you turn!
Get set.. go!
[Chunhee's the only one enthusiastically yelling out the turns]
[Where?]
[Clumsy Chunhee, where are you going...]
[How can you mess up like this when you were just scolding him earlier]
[Changeui is the first one at the plastic wall]
[Changeui was able to pierce through but]
[What kind of behavior is this for two grown men]
[Chunhee's shoe]
[Trying to catch his breath]
[The two friends trying to defeat each other]
You can't win
Let me just win one time!
[Chunhee's real intentions revealed]
No!
[Changeui widens the rip]
[Chunhee stubbornly jumps through Changeui's passage]
[But Changeui was still the first one through]
I came out first
How can you be like that Chunhee?
[Changeui still gets Chunhee's shoe for him]
[Miserable]
Is our team all losers?
We just need ONE person to win on our team
(I must get my revenge...)
Yejin's turn
I want to go against game slump, Kim Jongkook oppa
This is the kind of existence Jongkook oppa has with us
This isn't it
Just show us for real today
Yeah show us
Even if he wins against me do you think he'd gain confidence from that?
Since I'm playing against a woman I'll turn 7 times
Just do the five turns!
We're not in first place right now!
No since he's playing against a woman he should have said he'd turn ten times,
but he said only 7.  What is that?
How do I jump over this?
Just run and jump, it's okay if you knock it over
[Lady Yejin sweetly jumping over the hay]
Jongkook!  Just run through it
[As expected, it's harder for the women to break through the plastic]
Translator: suebee
Timers: swtsrwlove, warunee123, melijay
Editor: swtsrwlove
Encoder: melijay
Uploaders: melijay, maryys, Shannice, swtsrwlove, kaflom
You can try again!
Hey! What's with the charms?!
Just go!!
We have to win! What are you doing?!
He's just having Yejin break through
so he can go through easily!!
Ooh, it ripped!!
Oh my, take a look at him!
[Jongkook was the first one through,
a win for Jaesuk's team]
I won!
[A ceremony for Jongkook~]
[Dumbfounded]
1,2,3! Cheer~!!
Oppa, how could you do that as a man?
That was a hard opponent, really
Really, he went up against a hard person
Should we do a relay this time?
And the last person goes through the plastic
We'll run and come back but have to put back
the bales we knock over
Alright, let's go
Jongshin hyung, you go first.
Jongkook is a little uneasy, so you go second.
Hyung!
Looking at it, I think you should go second too
Our team is just like that
[Jaesuk's team:
Jongshin->Jongkook->Jaesuk->Jongshin->Chunhee]
Don't be so burdened!
Even if you mess up,
we're behind you to catch up.
I usually feel burdened when playing games though
Just look over here, you're either
going to play against Hyori or Yejin
Jongkook, just make it so that
people won't change the channel!!
You just have to press your face against it
[Jongshin vs Changeui]
Ready, set...
Go!
[The first two to go do it easily...]
[Touch the plastic wall once and come back!]
[Jongshin puts back the bale he knocked over]
[2nd person up, Hyori]
[2nd person up, Jongkook]
[The outcome is still unclear]
[Jongkook is the first to break it!]
See, he's in a slump!
I haven't touched it yet?
[A firm grasp...]
Jongkook what are you doing?
See, I told you he'd be like this
We have to win
[Hyori first puts back the bale of hay]
[and knocks over the other team's hay!!]
Hey!! What is going on?!
Oppa, let me go!
Hey! Do you guys like each other?!
Huh?! What is up with you two?!
I knew it! I knew you'd be like this!
Now I have to catch up
[The eldest brother is fast!!]
Hey! He's our ace!
[Who will win?]
[Sooro]
[Chunhee]
[Whoever is first through the plastic wall wins]
[Sooro advances!!]
[He breaks through in one try!]
Jongshin: That's Chunhee for you!!
We were too concerned over Jongkook...
The ace was you, Jongshin hyung!
Chunhee's not our ace!
Do you think we caught any fish?!
Jongkook, it's raining only over you
See, take a look.
It's all thunder and lightening.
You should be more concerned over the games
and get over this slump.
He used to do so well on Dream Team
Jaesuk: This is such a huge slump.
Hyori: Oppa, let's go...
Jongshin hyung, you're seriously the ace now
[By your side at times like these, Hyori]
[Still haven't caught even one fish...]
[Chapter 2, Family makes mehju]
What's this?
A fashion show?
Since we couldn't catch any fish
the mood here is really...
[Since there's no fish everyone is feeling disappointed]
What are we going to eat?
Should we first make the mehju
like Grandma asked us to?
Yeah, let's do that
How? Do you know how?
[Chunhee is going to look it up in the internet]
Oh the antenna gives me better reception
[Fixated]
Hyung, why are you staring at something
Chunhee is holding way up here?
[Hanging off Chunhee's shoulders like crow's feet]
I can see the switch from down here!
What's it say?
First wash the beans.
We already boiled it
[1. Wash the fermented soybeans and boil]
[2. Pound the beans and mold it and let dry]
It says you can't move it while it's drying
So two people go inside and get
the fermented soybeans, and Changeui..
Changeui should be doing something.
That's right, Changeui we should find
something for you to do
Let's all start working on making mehju
[The well cooked fermented soybeans]
[Place in bamboo basket before washing]
Oppa! Do you want to try
some of the cooked beans?
Kim Gookjong, wanna have a taste?!
[Absurd/Nonsense]
It's yummy~
Excellent skills!
Jaesuk: Hey, my glasses are fogging up
[Place in mortor to pound]
Chunhee: It looks like he's waiting sunglasses
[A sunglass wearing grasshopper?]
Oppa, back up a little
- Hyori! I can't see anything right now
- Back up a little!
[Jaesuk is feeling irritated]
I have to be able to see to know what I'm doing
Jongshin: Your sunglasses look nice
I wanted to avoid the sun~
Ok put the basket behind you
I keep telling you I can't see anything.
[Still giving orders to the blind Jaesuk]
I can't go forward or backwards~ right now!
This has a good feel to it
Oppa you have to do this with a bit of rhythm
[Jongkook and Hyori joining forces to pound grain?]
[Developing a steady rhythm]
Sooro: Good job! You have to do it more
Chunhee: Get every nook and cranny
Chunhee, give it a shot
[This time it's Chunhee and Changeui]
Watch carefully!
You have to pound it like this
so that all the beans...
[Chunhee acting like a know-it-all again]
Jaesuk: There he goes again
Hyori: Watch out it's going to fall
[Clumsy, clumsy]
Jongshin: Do it carefully so it doesn't fall
Why can't you do it with more rhythm!?
I think it's better if only one person does it
Sooro: Chunhee, let me try.
Jongkook: Grab that tightly.
[Today's bean pounding king!]
[I'm going to crush them all!]
It's better with Sooro hyung doing it by himself
Of course
[Pounds practically all of it by himself]
The mehju factory owner is scooping it out
[Scoop out the crushed beans from the mortor
with a wooden spoon]
[Mehju factory owner?]
Aren't you the lady that made
the kimchi last time?
Kookjong! Go and help Hyori
I don't wanna
- Get over there!!
- I don't wanna!
- Just go. Hey Game Slump, go!
- I don't wanna! I don't wanna!
Why are you doing this to me?
Just get over here!!
[Immediately going...]
Hey it's been awhile since I've seen Jongkook
trying to end a relationship
Just listen to me
[Jaesuk pounds the leftover beans]
[Molding the pounded beans]
[Hard stare...]
Oppa! The mehju has to be in a rectangular shape!
I was going to do that
[Immediately making it into a rectangle]
Jongkook, how's mine?
Ah! It looks like a loaf of bread
Yours should look more like that
But this looks more like mehju. Speak honestly.
- No seriously, it should look more like that.
- Yah! Jongkook ah~
In the end you're going to do
what Hyori wants anyways so what's the point
You should make up for how bad you were
during the game by doing this well
Quit making your own version of mehju!
[The two friends still pounding beans
in the mortor]
Chunhee: Get out faster!
Changeui: I am~
[Is Changeui getting irritated?]
Changeui! You're not mad are you?
You're not mad are you? It's okay.
DS: For a moment I felt a gloomy force above me
No, no.
You guys are wearing matching clothes
in black and white
Are you making a heart-shaped mehju?
Yes.
To give to whom?
To myself
[Yejin's sweet heart mehju]
Changeui should try making mehju, too
[This time Changeui and Chunhee will make mehju
Sooro: Just grab it and throw it down
This isn't too much?
No, that's fine
Can't you tell how much to scoop out
by looking at the one next to you?
[Chunhee's scolding starts again]
Alright~
Changeui's been irritated since before
Why don't you just make mehju next to him
Chunhee, show him how it's done
[Clumsy Chunhee as an example?]
Let's have a mehju making battle!
[Lee Chunhee vs Song Changeui, Mehju Battle]
Chunhee, yours isn't any better
Changeui's mehju's shape isn't coming together
It seems right now that Chunhee's leading
Will you let yourself lose against Chunhee?
Chunhee is?
[One phrase provokes his pride...]
[Will you let yourself lose against Chunhee?]
[With man's pride on the line, Mehju battle]
We are here at the Mehju Battle
One contestant here is Song Changeui
And he's quickly forming the shape
Forming the shape quickly with his hands
But leading ahead is Chunhee!
Lifting it with his hands!
[When it comes to making mehju, I am not clumsy!]
[Musical mehju]
[Entering the second half of the battle
by urgently using their hands]
3, 2, 1!
Alright, stop! Will the two of you please stand.
We'll have our judges inspect the mehju
The mehju inspector today is...
Kim Boo Jong
[Mehju Factory's Kim Second-in-Command]
[Which one will Kim Second-in-Command choose?]
Oh, it's stuck to the board.
It shouldn't do that.
[Stuck and unmovable, Changeui's meju]
Chunhee's is the better one
[Chunhee gets 1 vote!]
[2nd judge, Kim Sooro]
[Turning it over to inspect]
Turning it over I can see that
Changeui's is well formed
[Changeui gets 1 vote!]
[3rd judge, Yejin]
[Softly touching the mehju]
This one is more solid
[Changeui gets 1 more vote!]
[Earnest]
[4th (idol) judge, Daesung]
Jaesuk: Oh he's checking the temperature
[On his knees to take the temperature?]
I pick this one
[Chunhee gets 1 more vote]
Our Mehju battle is at a tie 2:2
Our next judge was originally
the president of a kimchi factory,
but has now changed it to a mehju factory.
Jongshin: Yes, from U-Go's Mehju, Hyori
The decision of President Hyori can make
a big impact on this battle
[To smell it?]
[Tense]
mehju-meh meh meh girl
[Which one will Hyori choose?]
Hyori: I think this one is the better one
[Changeui gets 1 more vote]
[Joy]
[Sorrow]
If you use too much beans like this one
you can't make any profit!
[The choice was made because of money?]
Just use an adequate amount
and it can be delicious and profitable
After considering many aspects,
President Hyori has chosen Changeui's mehju.
Ok, so that we can have the results
of the Mehju battle, Judge Jongshin please.
Jongshin: Uhh...
PD: Changing tapes!!
[Of all things...]
[After a moment...]
Judge Jongshin came to his decision
during the tape change,
so we'll proceed immediately to the results.
Please step forward and have a seat.
And close your eyes.
The winner of today's Mehju Battle
will get a kiss from Hyori
Hyori, please come up
Yes.
You guys can't open your eyes
Hyori, you're ready to go right?
Yes.
Are you okay with this?
Well it's just like a business kiss~
Please tightly close your eyes
And, go!
[OMG! Jongshin...]
Congratulations!
[Changeui has no clue]
[He's so happy he fell over!]
How do you feel?
I feel good~
[Because you got a kiss from the elderly?]
Did you see his bright smile
when he got the kiss from Hyori?
[Can you get any happier than this?]
I think it was good for me to come out here
Have fun watching this episode later!
[He might be traumatized
after he sees the broadcast]
Let's make dinner now!
We should see what they have in the house
There should be something that
Grandma already made
[Chapter 3:/ Timid Dumb & Dumber]
Tofu!
We found tofu~
[The tofu Grandma made for the Family]
We can cook kimchi and tofu and make tofu kimchi.
Sounds good!
I heard they have a strawberry field
in the greenhouse
Us three can get the strawberries
Then Daesung and I will start the fire
Strawberries, strawberries, strawberries
[They're already excited thinking about
the delicious strawberries]
We have to pick the really red ones
that are all the way out with big, thick bodies.
And...
It must be something like this.
Looks good, huh?
[No problems eating it right after plucking...]
The juices are..
Huk!
You guys should try one
[Changeui and Chunhee both try one...]
How is it?
[In wonder]
It's really sweet and juicy.
If we're too greedy with this all
the strawberries will fall out.
So only pick the prettiest and reddest ones, ok?
Hurry pick it up.
[Changeui picks one...]
(abusive) That's not a red one, Changeui!
[Chunhee has become abusive too!]
Chunhee: It should be like this shade
Turn it around. See it's not ripe on this side
[It looks the same...]
Alright~ Just hurry up and pick!!
Don't just pick at random,
we have to eat this you know
Changeui~
I got it!
Why do you keep bothering me?
[Chunderella is a stepmother today?]
It's because I'm worried about you
Sooro hyung. This is a good strawberry, right?
Yes, that's a good one~
You saw that right? Like this one.
Changeui! Like this one, like this one!
I got it!! Just pick your strawberries!
Chunhee. Whenever I watch you on this show,
you're the one getting abused.
So why are you yelling at me?
It's not that I'm yelling at you
You've been yelling at me all day
I just understand Sooro hyung's intentions now
When Sooro hyung is scolding me,
it's not that he's really scolding
Sooro: No, never
He just values me and is concerned of me
Because he loves me he talks to me like that
Don't look after me then!
I'm regreting this
Sooro hyung can do that,
but you can't look after me
You just don't understand where I'm coming from
Sooro: That's right
After filming this,
you guys shouldn't see each other.
Alright Chunhee, let's keep picking.
That red one right there
[Looks delicious]
[At the house, Madam Lee and Dumb and Dumber...]
The bonfire feels good since it's so cold
Peel the sweet potatoes
so I can make sweet potato rice
Can't you just do it?
Yeah why don't you do it?
You always make us do it
That's right! Today Hyori ah~
Daesung: Yeah, you do it
Jaesuk: Why don't you peel them!!
[Oh~ Dumb & Dumber rebelling?]
That was funny, huh?
Of course we'll peel them~
We improved a lot, huh?
Very good
You were scared for a second, huh?
Oh! Oppa, the fire went out!
Jaesuk: Oh did it?
Daesung: Already?
[Abruptly]
Just wait one second
It's been awhile since I've worked with you two
Yeah it's been a long time
How does it feel Daesung? After the long time?
Daesung: It feels g.. good..
Jaesuk: It feels good, huh?
Being here with Hyori feels comfortable
Hyung, do you really feel comfortable?
Jaesuk: No~
I know, huh?
Seriously though, if you hadn't said we were
just playing around we'd be in big trouble!
I know
She had this "why you little~" glare
Do you know how many times I get that glare?
I was grateful for your reaction
Oh it's so warm
Oppa! I told you to peel the potatoes
and you're just standing there?!
No it's not that, we literally just lit the fire
Hurry up and wash the rice
You want us to wash the rice?
How do you expect us to wash the rice
when you want us to peel the sweet potatoes?!
Dumb, sweet potatoes; Dumber, rice!
How'd you know that Dumb & Dumber
were two people?
What are you going to do?
I have a lot to do
Why do you want us to peel the sweet potatoes?
Because I'm going to make sweet potato rice
Oh really?
[Dumber washing the rice]
My hands are cold
- Hyori ah~
- Huh?
I'm not saying this is the way it should be,
but shouldn't I be doing that
and you be doing this?
You should throw away that way of thinking of
a man should be doing this and a woman be doing that.
I was just going to quote a phrase
And stop texting me phrases!
Hey! When did I ever?
I'm just saying don't call me
when we're not filming
Just accept it one time!
I did it because I got ten of them!
Hey! I got ten of them
and you only get one and you're..
Am I nothing to you?
And what's up with having not talked you in so long
and you suddenly asking me
for someone else's phone number?
It's because I needed it and I forgot what it was
Oppa, the fire went out. Light it back up!!
It went out again
I really...
What? You have something to say?
Nope~
Daesung ah~
What?
Are you going to wash the rice all night?!
Yeah
Hurry up and get out here
Do you really think the fire's going to light
back up with you fanning from up there.
You should be doing it down here
Bring me some paper
Oppa~ peel the potatoes!!
You told me to do this?!
[Daesung comes out after washing the rice in cold water]
[Forgets everything and is touched...]
Faster! Faster!
I think it's completely out
Faster!
Oppa, faster!
I said faster!!
Oppa, faster!!
It won't happen like this!!
[It's...]
[It's... an all out war now...?]
[It won't happen like this!!]
Dinner won't happen like this!
I have to light this fire fast!
Oh no, we won't be able to make dinner!
Hyori! I have to quickly light this
so we can make dinner!
Of course, if we light this we can eat
Really, I really...
We're going to put those big chunks of
sweet potatoes in the rice?
- How is this big?
- Oh yea, you're right
We should roast these
Yeah, let's roast them!
Why are you being so agreeable?
Oppa I'm not the kind of person you think I am!!
No, you are~!!
Daesung ah~ in your head,
you have to say those things in your head
Oh no, I didn't know
You have to be careful!
Make sure what you're thinking
doesn't pop out of your mouth.
You never know
when Hyori's intentions will warm up~
Yeah, I get that feeling too. Whenever I'm burdened
you're always there by my side.
Spinning lies!!
I'm just kidding, it's a joke
Where do I put this?
Over there.
Excuse me! I said over there!
Why is it when you're with Hyori...
You take the route furthest away from her?
Are you saying that in the show I'm a bad person?
You're talking nonsense
No, tell me!
If you want me to express it,
I want to say you're like constipation
Constipation?
Even when you try to let it out you can't...
So you're saying I'm like poo?!
I'm sorry
He just wanted to look good to you
Daesung you just compared Hyori to constipation.
What am I like to you?
If I say this you might get overwhelmed
Coffee
Coffee?
Why?
You bring a warm feeling throughout the nation
[Excited]
Oppa, can you help me?
With what?
Hyori, this is really basic~
- It won't close
- The gas might be in wrong place.
It's because you try to fix everything
with your strength!
Did you do it? It's fixed?
It's not closed!
Let me just bring it down a little
Then we can slowly close it!
Hey, why isn't this working?!
I told you!
Yeah
[Getting ready to cook the Tofu Kimchi]
[Jaesuk bringing the tofu over one by one...]
[Following behind with the whole tub...]
[In situations like these, Daesung seems smarter...]
Daesung, I think you can put it down now
What'd you do now?
Nothing, nothing
This looks like cheese!
Do you think this might be cheese?
(Chee...se)
[In true Dumb & Dumber style]
Cheese~
What are you guys doing?
[Suddenly]
[Hyori preparing the vegetables for the Tofu Kimchi...]
[1. Slicing healthy foods like green onions,
carrots, and onions]
[2. Pan fry vegetables with kimchi]
[3. Add a bit of red pepper powder]
Where you going?
To go get something
Should we just try a bite?
Should we?
It looks like it'd be so good
It smells good. It's a work of art.
Look at the kimchi
[They're been caught]
It's not ready yet
I didn't eat any~
- Daesung ah!
- Mmph
Ok we just had one bite
How does it taste?
It's a work of art~
- You should try a bite
- I should, shouldn't I?
Nuna, it's seriously a work of art
Just give me one bite
Hold on, I'll give it to you later...
I'll give it to you now!
No, later!
Now!!
Are you going to give it to me or not?
I'll give it
How does it taste?
Umm~ It's yummy!
The kimchi tastes so good
It's really delicious
[The family members that went to pick vegetables:
Jongshin, Jongkook, and Yejin]
Wow~
This is like a house of sesame leaves
Because of the greenhouse you can even pick
sesame leaves during the winter
This sesame leaf smells so good~
Ever since I was little...
I've always had a need to eat meat!
Why is Jongshin oppa talking to himself?
Jongshin oppa...
Who are you talking to~?
- I'm talking to the camera
- Oh, Mera!
I said hi to it earlier.
I was telling it how much I wanted to eat meat~
Do you know who I am?
I am Yejin's little sister, Yeji
Hello
Are you by any chance Kim Jongkook oppa?
Oh yes, I am
I've heard so much about you from my sister
- Ahh, Yeji.
- Yes.
I didn't recognize you with your sesame leaf hair.
What do you think of my sister?
Your sister? I like her, of course
I like her and everything but when
she's with Hyori they start acting the same
Oh no~ Oppa!
You're telling my little sister weird things
Who are you?
Do you know me?
It's Jongkoo!
I'm Jongkoo~
You guys look so much alike~
You work out a lot too, huh?
Of course
You're embarrassed, aren't you?
Not everyone can pull this off~
You guys, we have peppers and sesame leaves,
what else do we need?
Meat
You're still talking about meat?
Do you have any money?
I'll buy as much meat as I can
with the money I have on me
Hyung, will you be able to find a store?
I think I'm going to have to suffer a bit...
Just hurry and go
and if they don't have any come back home
Alright! I can't stand this
You can't stand this?
Are you going to fight someone?
Will he be able to find it in the dark?
Whatever happens his will to live
will guide him back home.
Wow~
This is seriously a prairie...
Oh! dog.
There's only the sound of dogs barking
But I have to eat meat!
Are there no stores?
Is there a store here~?!
Auntie~
Store owner auntie~
I have to keep going
How many km have I walked?
Oh! It's a store!
Grandmother, hello!
Welcome. How can I help you?
We're trying to make stew and...
We don't have anything you can make stew with
You don't have canned meat?
We don't
Oh! It's right here
It's past the expiration date.
You can't eat it.
Jongshin: This one too?
Grandmother: yeah
Grandma, it says it expired in 2005!
We had it up there to sell but no one bought it
so it's just sitting there~
So it's like interior decorations
Oh that means I can't buy it
But we need to make stew
We don't really have anything for that
Then how much are the sausages?
60 cents
60 cents?
Oooh
You're going to use that?
Yes
If I squeeze this wouldn't the oils come out?
Why don't you try cooking it with this?
What is it? Dried fish?
How much is the dried fish?
8 dollars
Thank you! Goodbye!
How are you going to boil that?
Happy New Years~
Woohoo~
[At the same time...]
The tofu.
Oppa, take one out
Ok, here you go
Daesung: It looks so soft
[Hot water and all...]
Oh that looks so good
It does
They're coming!
That's Dumb & Dumber's walk!
Look at the strawberries
Hyung try the tofu we just made
Hyung, it's a work of art
Chunhee: Stand in line.
Changeui, you have to stand in line!
How is it? It's a work of art isn't it?
It's seriously a work of art!
- You guys are waiting in line?
- Yea
Changeui~ You have to stand behind me!
Is the rice ready?
- Ah! rice~
- It's still cooking, oppa.
- Oh so just leave it?
- Yeah.
In my life I get to eat sweet pototo rice...
This is the first time I've eaten this
Me too
Oppa, we have to put in the anchovies
Sooro: Put them all in?
Jaesuk: No, just 3 of them.
[Kimchi juice]
[Green onion]
[Leftover tofu...]
It might tastes weird because there's no meat
But we have tofu though
??: How is it?
It's short by 2 percent...
- You're here!
Hyori: Are you guys closer now?
Oppa give me the sesame leaves
We still have to wash them
Jaesuk: Hurry up and wash it
Chunhee: Changeui will wash them really well
How come no one is asking where Jongshin hyung is?
There's no concern for him
Look, no one even cares
Oppa, where have you been?
It's sausage!
Yeah.
Do you know what I went through to get these?
You did really well hyung
- But do you usually put these in stew?
- Of course.
Even if a little we need to bring the flavor out...
Is that so?
Can we really put those in?
Hyori, it's okay to put dried fish in right?
Dried fish?
Just put it in. I'm certain about this.
It'll bring the flavor out.
Whatever we could possibly put in we did!!
See. Compare it to before we put the dried fish in.
The sesame leaves make it taste really good
That's the dried fish you're tasting!
- The sesame leaves!!
- The dried fish!!
No, it's the sesame leaves!
Chunhee: If you want to eat a lot of tofu let me know
Sooro: Jaesuk, come and eat
Jongshin: It's tasty, really tasty
It really tastes like meun tang~
It's because of the dried fish and sesame leaves
Is the sweet potato rice delicious?
Yeah
Everything tastes good today!
Even though we weren't able to catch any fish today,
- This is all good.
- That's right!
Jongkook oppa, you should say if it tastes good or not
Jongkook: It's really delicious
[Chapter 4/ Say it, friend!]
Today we're going to be calling up friends
and try to have them say a phrase
without telling them the exact wording.
Alright, shall we each choose one? Yejin's turn.
This is hard!
"Yoon Jongshin is manly"
Call up anyone of your friends!
Jaesuk: Who are you going to call?
Yejin: (Jo) YuJung Unnie
[Will Yejin be able to get YuJung to say that
The Elder Jongshin is manly?]
- (Hello~)
- Hi, what are you doing?
(I'm watching a movie)
At home?
(Yeah)
(And you?)
Me? I'm taking a break
while filming Family Outing
(It's really cold isn't it?)
Just a little...
But earlier it was really cold and Jongshin oppa
took off his jacket and gave it to me!
- (Really?)
- Like that would ever happen
- (Did you hug him?)
- What?
(Did you hug him?)
You can do that if you want...
I think the image I had of him
before filming is different
Sometimes when we have to do hard things
like moving wood he says he doesn't want to
But when he's by himse
lf he just carries it right away
(But his body is so weak...)
He eats like 3 spoonfuls of rice at once...
(Really? Is he tough?)
Of course
(You've totally become a fan of Jongshin oppa!)
Oh~ and...
He also farts a lot
(That's the most sexiest!)
(Yeah he seems so manly...)
(He seems so manly...)
Success!
I'm actually filming right now
(Hahaha...)
- (Oh so that's why you kept talking about Jongshin oppa)
- Yeah
Seriously when would Jongshin oppa ever
take off his jacket? And carry wood, whatever.
I had to hear from you that Jongshin is manly
Oh what do I do, it's going to broadcast that I said he has a weak body
What's there to do?  It's the truth and you were only speaking honestly
Hold on a moment
Sooro hyung, why are you grabbing the phone?
Yuhjung! It's Sooro oppa!
Oppa!
Yuhjung-ah!!
I miss you!
I miss you too, so much!
You're doing well, right?
I'm having a lot of fun watching the program
I'm doing a play in 2 months!
When I do the play you better come and watch
I'll call you another time!
Yes, bye!
She's really cute!
Should I try it now?
Yoo Jaesuk is so handsome
That doesn't make any sense
Who are you going to call?
(Park) Myungsoo
Good good! I like him
What?
Hyung, it's me
Sorry, I just drank a bottle of alcohol
Hyung! I'm calling from Family Outing right now!  Where are you?
You don't need to know!
I know I don't need to know
I'm out having dinner with friends
Oh you are?
Yeah
Hyung, how do you think I look?
Depressed
I'll just call you another time
Don't call me. Hang up!
Ok now it's Chunhee's turn
Chunhee would make the best husband
That seems alright
I think he'd be able to get someone to say that
I'm going to call Park GunHyung
Chunsoo~
What are you up to?
At a shoot
Where are you?
Naju
Is it cold?
It's sooooo cold!
Oh sorry I should have left you a jacket or something
It's seriously cold
Lately since filming Family Outing I have a lot of people coming up telling me good things
How do you think women look at me?
One that suffers.  To me at least.
No to women.  You look at me and see someone who suffers, but women
They see me being nice and looking out for Hyori and Yejin
Women should see something in that, don't you think?
Why are you being like this?
How do you think I'll be once I'm married?
Huh? I don't know because I will not marry you
No like what kind of qualities would I have as a husband?
You're being weird, what's wrong with you?
Park Gunhyung!
I'm filming right now
What kind of shoot?
Family Outing
All you had to do was say I'd be a good husband!
Jaesuk hyung wants to talk to you
Gunhyung, we have Changeui on our set as well
Changeui's there?
What's he doing over there?
We're filming our show right now
Hold on there's someone that wants to speak to you
Hey Gunhyung!  Why don't you ever call me?!
Let me see your face
-In 2 months I'm going to be doing a play
-Stop it!
Come see my play!
We'll go to each other's plays
Ok thank you Gunhyung!
Oh this one is hard
Sooro is the sexiest guy
It can't just be Sooro is sexy, it has to be Sooro is the sexiest guy?
Yeah
(Kim) HyunJoon
Hello?
Is this Hyunjoon's phone?
No it is not
I'm sorry, sir!
I was wondering why his voice sounded so strange
It's because I haven't called him in so long
Now it's Kim Sooro's turn
[Hyori is very feminine]
Why did you give me the hardest one?
Oh you're calling that person?
It's a work of art
I really like this person!!
Hello?
(Ha) Jongwoo! How have you been?  It's been awhile hasn't it?
Yes it has
You mentioned you like watching Family Outing?
It's a lot of fun
What do you think of Hyori?
She's very beautiful
We were just saying how Hyori is like a guy to us and like a little brother
But you know, you could think differently
To someone like you, how do you see her?
Because she's like a guy to us
Out of all the female singers, isn't she the best?
But she's a guy to us.  What do you think?
She may seem like a guy, but she also seems feminine as well.
Success!
I told you, everyone else thinks of me like that.
-Is that by any chance Ha Jongwoo?
-Yes, it is
-I really like him! The Chaser!
Hey, Big Bang's Daesung says he's a really big fan
Just talk to him for a bit
Okay
Ah! What do I do?
Hello?
Is this Ha Jongwoo?
Yes
HELLO!
It's nice to meet you
You're still doing The Chaser right?
I'm really anticipating it, and once it comes out I'll be the first in line
All he said was yes
Thanks Jongwoo, bye
He's got a lot of charisma
I got to talk to him and everything
Yejin is very loveable
Hi Jongshin
Yes hyung
Yes yes yes yes
(Kim Gookjin) Hyung, what are you doing?
I'm just sitting here
How come you're always doing nothing?
I'm only doing nothing half the time
Do you by any chance watch Family Outing?
I do
You know Park Yejin on the show?
Yeah, yeah, Lady Yejin
What do you think of her?
Huh?
What if he thinks he's trying to set up a date?
She's got a good color to her
And she has charisma since she's an actress
And she's good at sucking it up
She comes off as very innocent
Without any flaws
As a woman, how is she?
good
You seem to have watched her a lot on the show
I did, because she just sucks it up
Hyung this isn't a dating program
I'll put Yejin on the phone
Hello?
Hello? Who is this now?
It's me!
It's Jaesuk!
Wait, so you guys are filming right now?
Yeah
Oooh
You didn't know we were filming? Is what you said the truth?
I thought Jongshin was just calling me for no reason
Hold on a second I'll put Yejin on the line
Hello I'm suck it up Yejin
Oh I really like watching you on the show
Hyung, I had no idea you liked her so much
No it's just that.. it's just.. who doesn't like Yejin on Family Outing?
Thank you for liking me on the show, I had no idea you had so much feelings for me
No, it's just.. you.. I saw it on TV
Sorry for calling you out of the blue.  I'll give you a call another time, thank you!
Daesung, you seem smarter than Jaesuk
I'm going to call President Yang (head of YG Family, Yang Hyunsuk)
I don't really call him usually
You should call him every now and then
Should I do this? I'm really nervous
Ah, it's our song!
Hello? Who is this?
Hello?  Hello!
What is it Daesung?
My IQ is 110
What?
My IQ is 110.  And Jaesuk hyung is 114.
Uh huh
Have you ever wondered if he lied about his score?
Yoo Jaesuk?
I think you're score might be a lie, too
No actually it should be higher.  Because I can't have a stupid image.
Watching Family Outing, how do I seem to you?
Because lately I've been trying to seem more smart
Who am I smarter than?
Oh in comparison?
Uh.. Yoon Jongshin
Hyunsuk-ah!  Why are you being like that?
Ok, failed!
I'm sorry, did we wake you?
Oh I was just taking a nap
Why are you sleeping at this hour?
Daesung told us once that you told him he can't ever have a stupid image
I did.  I think he became like that after hanging out with you
Changeui and Hyori seem good for one another
Did Changeui write this himself?
It seems like everyone that went to this school likes Hyori
And when he got kissed by Hyori earlier
He must really like her
I'm going to call Oh Jiho
Hello?
Hello
Oh who could this be?
Hyung, do you know Family Outing?
Yeah
I have to go on that show
Do you know who Hyori is?
Of course I know who she is.  Is there anyone that doesn't?
Imagine me and her together, what do you think?
You guys don't go well together
Think about it carefully!
Even carefully considering it, it still doesn't seem right
Failed!
Oh Jiho, hello!
Oh hello!
Are you guys filming right now?
Yes
Hello everyone, I am Oh Jiho
Since I told him we're doing the show he even introduces himself
I was just wondering why you thought they didn't fit together?
Because Hyori would be at a loss then
But looking at these two it seems alright to me
Well if Changeui wants it that's good for him
and I guess if Hyori doesn't mind, then .. ahh.. it'd be alright
His voice changed
out of the successes, we have Park Yejin in 4 minutes
and Kim Sooro at a minute and a half.  Kim Sooro, winner