BROUGHT TO YOU BY RAMEN SOUP SUBS!!
Chapter 1
Sun, rise up,
Family, soar high!
Are you ... 6th?
-Here...
Wow, it's been a while since I've been next to Daesung.
Daesung must not be used to it because it's his first time being in last place.
Daesung, are you okay?
Your ending the year cool.
You're sleeping with Jwa (left) Jaesuk and Woo (right) Jong Shin...
Should I turn off the lights?
Should we?
Oppa, what's going on?  Saying you want to turn off the lights immediately...
I also...
Am very tired today.
Jong Kook oppa!  In the black bag above you, in the front pocket, can you please take out my cellphone?
I'm comfortable now that Jong Kook is here.
Oppa!  I would like to go there myself, but because I danced too much back there, my back hurts.
-It's right above you, so please take it out for me.
-Where?
Right above you.  The black bag.
You were going to anyway!
Get up!
-Your phone?
-Yes.
Would you like to use my phone?
No, no.
-Where?
-The front pocket, yes.
Oppa, pass!
Thank you~
She has great pronunciation.
Good night!
Oppa, thank you!  Good night!
Hyori speaks English well, doesn't she?
Good night.  Everyone worked hard today.
Daesung, there's no strength in your voice.
Is it your first time being last?
Yes... last place...
I'm your sunbae at being last...
I'm the champion from last week!
Just say first place.  What's with 'champion'?
Hey!  Being first place is being the champion!
Hyuk oppa, please tell us a funny story.
Tell her no thanks.
You were like a girl just then, oppa.
Jong Kook also gets very sulky.
Ah.. It's really tiring today...
He finally says something now...
-Hyuk!  You're better than Cha Tae Hyun!
I want to see him again.
Jaesuk oppa's voice is cracking.  We have to be quiet now.
Good night~
[Like this, the last night of 2008 deepened...]
[Current time: 05:20]
[Until sunrise:  1 hour and 50 minutes]
[Must wake up the Family to see the sun rise...]
[First, wake up Jaesuk...]
[Because of the cold weather outside, the camera lens became foggy]
[It has only been two hours since they've fallen asleep...]
[Still ringing the Siren of Horror in the New Year!]
[Also very noisy for Jaesuk...]
[And the new year hasn't changed the love between Stepmother Kim and Chunderella]
[8 degrees under zero - Kang Won Do daybreak]
['One Man' out the door first...]
[Falling asleep again...]
Come out.
(It's cold.  Let's go quickly...)
Oppa.  We're going to see the sunrise of the new year and you're going to go wearing that?
[Pajamas for loafing around...]
Did you turn on the air conditioner?
Where is the wind coming from?
It'll be all right if you can go to see the sunrise by yourself.
Hyori...
It's cold..
Ye Jin...
You're not supposed to comb your hair in the morning.  You have to make morning feel like morning like this...
I have no other pants...
[The grasshopper who is cold and sleepy from the beginning of the new year]
(Inside...)
Hyung, go wake them up quickly.
-Wake them up!
-They'll come out~
Hyuk came when it's the most tiresome.
Let's go.
We're already very late.
Let's go, let's go.
Hyung, let's just go to see it!
Jong Shin hyung didn't have to duck down when coming out...
You can't do something like this on the first day of the new year?
Ah, it's done.
Why oppa?  Do you have something you want to say?
No, it's just that I woke up right after I laid down...
Really?
-It's January 1 of 2009, right?
-I came here to take it easy...
[The hardest Family recording so far]
That reminds me of what Hyuk said before we went to sleep.
[It's really tiring...[
Jang Hyuk oppa, with me...
It's our second annual sunrise.
That's right.  The end of 2008 and you're starting 2009 together.
Soo Ro hyung is 40~
[Welcome to 40~]
Jong Shin hyung, 41~
Hyori 31~  Ye Jin 29~
Ye Jin, 29 passed by as swift as an arrow.
Anyway, it's been a long time since I've seen a sunrise.
Jaesuk oppa's lips don't stop in 2009 either.
I might suddenly...
The day my mouth stops...
Is the day I'm not in this world any longer.
That's 'never stop'.
Never stop!
-Never stop!
Never give up!
Timing is now!~
You remember, right?
A day has passed since I learned 'Timing is Now'.
A year has passed...
Is your face still burning from embarrassment?
I've brought the hwanggi!
Who ordered the hwanggi...?
That's what we...
-That's what becomes memories.
[This man who regretted it like that...]
I've watched your appearance in Family Outing with enjoyment.
Thank you.  Yoo Jae Suk hyung gave me private lessons in gag.
I've learned to make people laugh.
The hwanggi is here!
We need to air the place out...
[Note:  Pun on word 'hwanggi']
I learned up to here.  Next week...
Why am I so...
Why am I getting the chills after hearing that...?
[Note:  Pun on words - hangi (chills) sounds like hwanggi.
I think I'm getting used to variety shows.
Hyori put her leg up on Kim Jong Kook...!
[Glanced and pretended not to see...]
Jong Kook can't say anything, I told you...
Jong Kook, she's asking you to massage her leg.
You've already been oppressed for two years.
Oppa, you're now my food.
The new year of 2009...
-First well-wishing remark
-First well-wishing remark.
[Oppa, you're now my food.[
Kim Jong Bab (food).
It's Kim Jong Soup though...  (Note: Kook is soup in Korean)
Everyone, how can we be like this on the first day of the new year?
Will be okay how doddering we are?
Oppa, should we take a nap, too?
Hyori, I'm going to take a nap.
I'm going to take a nap until we get there.
Stay quiet and sleep.
Good... Good morning...
[Confused because still not fully awake]
The first day in 2009 has gotten brighter...
But because of the clouds, we're not sure if the sun will rise or not.
We need to see it.
Right now it's very red.
Right now, on the other side...
There's a slight red feeling as if the sun is going to rise, but...
Because there are clouds in the sky....
Has the sun risen already?
It's slowly rising right now.
It hasn't risen yet, right?
The light will.... @#$%&
It's like that.
It also has been a while since I've seen the sunrise...
I think it has been covered
-By the clouds...
-I think it's covered by the clouds.
Hyuk, you were in the military here in Kang Won Do.
Has the sun risen yet?
This isn't sunrise.
It's not?
Hyuk says it's not sunrise yet.
It rose?
The energy doesn't come up like that, but comes from underneath and spreads up.
Then hasn't it been covered by the clouds?
It's supposed to come up from there, isn't it?
Wow!  The sun is up!
The sun that has been covered by the clouds...
Ah, this is ...
Because the sun has broken through the clouds...
It's dazzling.
The first sunrise of 2009!
The new year of 2009 has become bright!
[Having sent 2008, the year they first met under the name of Family]
[The similar small eyed brothers]
[And The serious man who is with them for the new year]
[And the elder who is always looking after his health and the national star who now needs to look after her health]
[With Jaesuk, who always throws his body for the Family]
[And Chunhee who throws his body without knowing it]
[And Soo Ro, who always gives the family much energy]
[And lady Ye Jin who gives everyone sweet dreams]
[All standing in a row in the same place]
[Like the rising sun, holding onto swelling hopes]
[They are meeting the new year, 2009, together]
The new year of 2009 is bright.
Everyone will state their resolutions
And expectations for the new year.
In 2009
My family
And our Family Outing members
I wish them all to be healthy
And that everything they do succeed.
Happy New Year!
And this year...
The work I used to do
And my movies and dramas, I wish will do well!
Chun Hee, fighting!
Because he's an actor...
I wish him the best and that he can be in a good movie or drama.
Soo Ro hyung.
My fellow citizens!
2009!
Are you campaigning?
They say that the world economy is on hard times!
You must be having a hard time as well!
On Sundays at 5:10
While watching Family Outing
I wish that your troubles would be washed away.
And, even though it's hard
In 2009
Let's show everyone that we can do it!
And I wish that Kim Soo Ro's movies would be hits!
Please love Kim Soo Ro's movies
And I humbly ask that the viewership ratings of Family Outing rise to over 30%!
I just wanted to say that we should keep going straight.
Hyori.
In 2009
After meeting a cool guy, I want to get married
And have the work I'm doing now do even better
And release another album that will receive a lot of love
And I will completely control Jong Kook oppa so that he feels timid!
Okay, next is...
Jong Kook.
Jong Kook's thoughts
Please speak in a thick voice please.
In 2009
He's conscious of it.
I wish that everyone I love and everyone who loves me all stay healthy.
I may have come into the Family late, but like a real family, I'd like to be more comfortable with them and
I would like to become someone who works harder.
And... I will never be controlled!
Please don't worry...
You've already been had oppa!
It's just that... because she's like a cute hubae
[Note:  hubae = someone in the industry after you]
I will look after her...
I will look after Lee Hyori...ssi...
What will you be looking after?
Don't worry.
I will look after her well.  And I wish my albums do well
I wish the economy would revive and that everyone becomes wealthy.
I wish you become wealthy!
Don't become timid yourself.
I'm okay!
And next is Ye Jin.
In 2009
I wish that my body and heart stay healthy
And that there are results that match my efforts
And that Jong Shin hyung will be in less pain
And I wish that there will be many cool guests who come this year!
It is 2009!
That's the same tone as 'It's Daesung'!
It's 2009!
Everyone, health is the most important!
I wish that everyone's work goes well
And that we don't forget to laugh.
And that I also don't forget to laugh
And stay healthy
With good music
I wish that I will become someone who is loved by more people!
And this year...
I will not cross the line!
You're not going to cross the line anymore?
-You're saying that to idols, right?
-He's saying that he's become a man?
Yes, do that.
Yes
He's now an adult.
Now, Hyuk.
In 2009
I wish we become a better country
And personally
A good family...
I wish I can have a good family!
Please stay healthy!
Um...
It's supposed to be, personally I wish to be a good head of the family for my family.
But because he said 'a good family'... he forgot.
In 2009
I wish that my whole family including La-ik stay healthy.
The Family has to be healthy as well.
And my remaining...
I have a few loans remaining...
I wish that I'd pay them all back.
In 2009
I wish they'd develop a new medicine
That will let people over forty
Continue to grow!
(Me too...)
Now that we've all finished
In 2009, everyone have a happy new year!
We will work hard to bring more laughter to more people.
I wish this year will be a year full of laughs
Everyone!  Many blessings to you in the new year!
Ah, I feel good inside.
Let's go now.
No!
Why?
We have to do what we got to do before we go.
If we go now
The people who have to make breakfast will make breakfast...
Everyone else can rest while breakfast is being made.
Do it here?
Let's do it here!
We will do our 'wake up mission' here.
Okay, first...
We'll start with Jang Hyuk-ssi and Jong Kook-ssi.
First spin five times doing 'elephant nose' and go quickly
To bring back water in your hands, but whoever is faster wins.
But, you can't have no water in your hands.
Understood?
Okay, sta...
It's the first competition between friends in the new year.
[Here] [There]
He can't do the 'elephant nose'...
He can't do it because of his muscles.
Just try... Now sta...
Start!
One
Two
Three
Four
Five.  Go!
Okay...
Be careful of your feet...
Your gloves!
Your glove in the water!
Glove!
Hyuk, your glove!
Because he wants to be Jong Kook...
Jong Kook...
There's water.
Success!  Win!
Water, water, water!
Kim Soo Ro, win!
Hyori and Ye Jin
If we're talking competitive, then in Family Outing...
There's no one who can follow these two.
I want to win and go to sleep.
Ready!
[Careless Chun Hee, not fully awake yet]
Okay, st...
Start!
One.  Wait, Hyori-ssi.
How can you start in the beginning of the new year?
Why?
You have to bend down.
Ready!
Because we played so hard last night...
Start!
One
Wait, Hyori-ssi...
You have to do it correctly.
Let's start again.
Are you okay, Ye Jin-ssi?
I did bend, but you couldn't tell because of the clothes.
No, you can't do that...
Okay, start!
One, two
Three, four
Five!
There has to be water remaining and you have to come quickly!
There has to be water remaining!
Ye Jin, where are you going?!
Hyori came first.
There is, there is!
There is.
Hyori, win!
Oh, the amount doesn't matter?
-The amount does not matter
-What did I hear before...?
Well, it's now me, Jong Shin-ssi and Daesung.
Hyori-ssi, please be our referee.
Ready, start!
How many turns has it been...
How many turns has it been...?
Run!
[Because no one wants to make breakfast, running like it's life and death]
Be careful!
Why isn't Daesung coming?
Oh there's water!
-Ah, it's all destroyed.
-Jaesuk oppa, win.  Ah, Daesung lost.
[Lost the game, and...]
I wanted to take care of the boots Chun Hee hyung bought us...
Ah because you wanted to save the boots.
(You can wash it...)
Now, the last game to find who will be in charge of breakfast.
The defeated!
We will go into a repechage.
Lee Chunhee, Daesung, Ye Jin and Hyuk, all four of you together.
Ready!
It's the last.
The males will make 10 turns, and Park Ye Jin will be 7 turns.
You're all ready, right?
Sta...art!
One, two
Three, four, five
Six, seven!
Ten!
[Tumultuous confusion]
Ye Jin!  Be careful!
Oy, Daesung...
[But Daesung again, trip~]
[Daesung, 2009, first breakfast duty decided?]
Daesung, come quickly!
Hyuk, there's no water...
There's water here.
Water.  Pass.  Pass!
Hyuk had no water...
Hyuk, there was no water!
Pass!
Hyuk had no water...
It's sad, but Jang Hyuk-ssi has
Lost the game.  He did come in early, but...
He had no water left.
Please pick two people to make breakfast with you.
[As always... averting their gaze]
Please say something nice to me...
Since it's the new year...
The sun might be out like that,
But I only see Hyuk in my eyes.
Jang Hyuk-ssi's look and expression
Is very clear.
It's very genuine.
Did you see his eyes when he said, 'I've brought the hwanggi' yesterday?
In one area of my heart, always...
There is a bright someone who I always think of.
I would like to call him Hyuk without hesitation.
I think you'll be picked immediately.
Hyuk oppa, choose someone you think will be comfortable and easy to make breakfast with.
I'll pick the knowledgeable ones, Jaesuk and Sooro.
I have to make breakfast again.
Let's go.
[Here begins the first meal of 2009 cooked earnestly by three guys]
I'm sorry that I don't have much to say to you, brothers.
I didn't know that my one phrase will turn out like this.
It's already in the past, don't be so burdened Hyuk ah!
Having to cook breakfast again in the new year makes me very happy.
Actually, going back to sleep in the morning doesn't seem quite right.
Don't feel burdened, Hyuk ah!
Ever since you came, if you were to cook, I will *huuk* feel like doing it too.
Everyone only slept for two hours, so tiring. What's more, there's an elderly.
By elderly, you mean...? He will hear you. That hyung's ears are very sensitive.
Let's do a good one.
Coming to this village, only two things come to mind.
What are they?
Co-op center, and bean curd.
Where are we going to get those?
In the village, there are grandmas who are famous for their bean curd.
Really? Oh~
-Then we should go and have a look.
-Let's go.
Let's go to the co-op center and get bean curd.
Coming out so early in the morning, the feeling is great.
Hyuk, are you in a good mood?
Of course.
Hyung, you're doing the dance with much feeling.
Hyuk, what are you doing?
Hyuk is still a little reserved.
Just do whatever you feel like doing!
It's here...
It's grandma's house.
-Hello.
I'm sorry, you were doing a facial... The chief told us to come here..
Bring over the pot straight away.
We're really thankful. Just a little bean curd will do... was this made in the morning?
Yes, this morning.
What time did you wake up to make this?
I woke up around five in the morning to do this.
It smells wonderful.
It's so fragrant.
It's the smell of the soy.
Do you make this fresh every morning?
No, not every day.
Is there an occasion today that you made this for?
No, I just wanted to keep some.
Oh, to keep some.
This bean curd is really smooth.
Thank you so much.
Grandma, how should we prepare the bean curd soup to make it delicious?
Just add kimchi.
I'm salivating...
Can we eat it as it is?
Of course you can, try a little.
This was freshly made.
It's really good, try some.
I thought it was milk, really, really.
I'm really surprised. I'm having this kind of bean curd for the first time.
Hyung, it's like milk, right?
It's strange...
I'm sorry, this is my first time having such bean curd.
Have you have this before?
Hang on, let me try a little more.
This is bean curd, grandma?
It is bean curd.
It's really good.
There's no need to make soup.
We can just eat it on its own.
Like grandma said, just add kimchi on top, we don't need to add anything else to it.
It's already so good.
I really wish you a happy new year, and good health, grandma.
We will eat it well, thank you very much!
This was made from scratch without preservatives.
Since we have this kind of bean curd, we don't really have to do much for breakfast!
[3 men totally sold on this delicious bean curd]
-To describe such good bean curd in words is quite a feat
Is this the co-op center?
Yes, I saw it yesterday
When was that?
Yesterday when we were turning again and again
These are rations that have been stored up by the villagers
This one, and this one
Hyung, you're too greedy!
-That's enough..this is exactly right
[JH is still blissfully happy, unaware of what's going to happen next]
[The 3 men are home]
They are still sleeping? (dissatisfied)
You're saying that because you hate them?
No, it's not like that..
So, you're just asking in passing, right?
I made a long trip to get here yesterday and this morning, had to wake up early to catch the sunrise..
In just such a short time, I could feel the depth of our friendship..
..I got to know everyone all over again.
Learning to handle the hardship.
If we do anything, we all have to do it!
Even when guests are selected to cook, go to the kitchen..get the vegetables..pots..and bring them out here
No, No.
Don't misunderstand..I'll work as well
Eversince the CTH episode, things are a bit different
It's not that I don't want to work..
You have also changed quite a bit in a day
People will change?!
[Speechless...]
That's right, people do change.
Yesterday after picking the herbs, he wasn't even like this!
It's not that.I'm only saying this now..
Whatever it is, I feel sorry towards you for yesterday!-
Hwang Yi, really! I said that when I came through that door, right!
Is he really the kind of person who harping on stuff?
The Hwang Yi incident..I can understand
So..i guess I'll have to go in and get all the stuff!
Yes. yes.
He'll feel appeased if you do it
We didn't lead hyung to do it, you want to do it out of your own will..
That's right! It's not like I'm doing it just because you said to. It has to be brought out anyway.
Thanks, hyung!
Chopping well..
That's the way..
You two make the pancakes, I will make the soup
Hyung..can you really do it?
Do we have to chop up the kimchi as well?
Hyung..chop evenly
As if I don't know I have to chop evenly?
Hyung, for this, I just have to keep stirring?
Yes..mix some more
[Serious]
[What's he doing?]
Aiyaa!..Hyuk ah
I know, I know..I didn't add oil
It's not whether you have added oil or not, the fire isn't even lit
Ah I'm going crazy..Jaesuk, look at this
You've got to turn on the burner before adding the mix
-Ya, whats the matter..
It's ok without the oil, but the fire isn't even lit
This is really my first time, hyung!
Even if this is your first time with making a pancake, with no fire how can you cook the pancake!
Ya, this is so simple
Nobody would want to use the sun's energy..
Use the sunrays from above to heat it up?!
It's not shining from this side. It's from the other side.
[It is this 2% insufficiency that led to the first incident]
Aiyo..really love this scent
Ya, the bean curd soup
No,hyung. Look at the kimchi
Look at the bean curd..
[ After awhile, it's back to bickering ]
I won't let you eat this then
I was the one who got this, why aren't you giving it to me!
Have a look at my kimchi
Can you shoot this way?
Cameraman, look at this! It's as good as at dinner time!
Ahh Jaesuk-ah! How can you fry it on its own like that? You have to fry it with sesame oil
I was just about to say that
What do you mean?
[After JH, now it's JS's turn..What's happening today~]
JaeSuk! really..
Put this first. Then this, then mix them together
Have to put this later? Can't put it now?
Do you have to fry the kimchi again?
[ With such good bean curd, nothing can really go wrong. Today's breakfast will be a good one]
How do you open this?
[At this moment, finishing off the remaining bean curd]
Hyung,stop eating!! We have to eat together.
These have gone bad..bad.
Then just leave it there, why are you still eating it
I'm afraid it'll get into yours
Oh, really
Hyung..can you do this?
where are you going?
You want me to do this?
I'll fry this.
why is this kid so curious about everything
No. The fire..is it on?
[It's really the insufficient 2%]
It really smells good
Hyung, You go over to your side.
Just for a little while
We can still eat the kimchi, just cut it. That should do.
we have more.
No..
Hyung..what are you doing now?!
[First, stuff Jaesuk's mouth to shut him up]
Hyung..why are you eating so much
Ya, is my mouth not a mouth?
[Jang Hyuk gets angry!]
Hyung..why don't you just leave it there. Why you keep going back and forth
[Appeased after eating]
I think it's about ready
[Sesame Oill]
You're not thinking of using this oil to fry the pancake, right?
I was trying to be funny!
That's right, trying to be funny?
Hyuk ah, look and listen carefully..
There are 2 kinds of oil, sesame oil and vegetable oil. What did I use when frying the kimchi?
Sesame oil!
Then what should we use to fry the pancake?
vegetable oil..seasome oil?
Pick one out of the two
[Eventually, picked the sesame oil]
[Afterall, it's the insufficient 2%]
This is usually how it's learnt the first time..
it's ok if you don't make it that big
[Again, busy eating]
[He eats more than he cooks]
Hyung! Stop eating.
Jaesuk ah..
What?
There's no flavor to it..
[Such good bean curd with no flavor?]
Grandma gave us good bean curd
Let me try
Why does it become worse after putting in the rest of the ingredients?
-It was really good just now?
-We still have the pancake
You guys aren't giving me a spoon!
Ok..try it, try.
Hyung, this is really too much.. this...
Hey, we already added everything... what else is there?
Besides adding those ingredients, I didn't do much to it! It's not salty..it's not spicy..
Is this salt?
I don't think adding salt will solve the problem here
It's not good to add too much salt
Let's try improving it with salt..even if it's not good, there should be some flavor to it
[Seems the outcome is not too favorable]
Now, are your hands a little itchy? Said we shouldn't use that thing... but we have already tolerated it for so long…
[The 2 men got tempted]
[This guy is oblivious to what's going on..]
Be gentle..
I's too thick
[Looking at the pancake, there is not much hope]
[Suddenly, he picks up the fried kimchi]
You're not flipping the pancake?!
If I flip it, it'll tear..it's not time to flip it yet
Have you seen the female fox coming in search of her food yet?
I've seen the old fox looking for food
[Totally engrossed]
Is this how it's done?
It has to be good
[Even the color changed]
Give me a bite too
It's here..!
The taste is here..
It's good..add a bit more
It's a lot better than it was just now
The flavor grows on you
Yes..definitely..
[Eating ramen flavored soup from elderly?!]
[Whatever it is, they are relieved about the soup]
What are you doing?
I'm trying to wrap this up..
It's not like that..
[2% insufficient JH makes a mistake again]
Hyung, I'll do a good one for you to see..
What are you doing?
Initially, we wanted pancake but I see it's not possible now..
How is it?
Be truthful
We have to save this with the 2nd pancake..
Is it really that serious?
It's not good, right?
Don't reprimand him, hyung..let the guest feel more welcome..
If you're nice..it's good?
I can be more frank..
Don't be too frank..
This is my first time having such a hard time eating this type of pancake
[Sad]
Let's not talk about this, let's talk about our soup
Hyung, try this..you can't be like hyung and make stuff all nice and delicious?
I already failed..
Hyuk, how is it?
Oh! This taste..is good..
[Forgot his sadness, there's even life in the way he speaks]
The flavor of all soups can be enhanced..
Let's not make pancake..
Hyung, you do it..
Can't boil the soup for too long; if it stands for too long the flavor won't be as good.
Get the table and cutlery from the kitchen and arrange them..I'll do it quickly
Fry more?
It's ok..
[A gentle touch]
[Looks like the real thing]
Hyuk ahh..I'm sorry..can you cut up more kimchi?
You don't have to chop it finely..like this will do
Hyuk looks quite disappointed with the pancake..now that it is unsuccessful
He was humbled.
It's possible that he was hurt
You ah..look alive!
[Speechless]
Hyung, it's not easy, right?
[If Sooro succeeds, Janghyuk will lose face..]
[Well done!]
[What should I do…]
[Sooro looks for a plate for the pancake]
There's a new plate here..
Janghyuk is now so obedient..suddenly..a change of attitude
[Finishes it easily]
Look at this..the most-difficult-to-make kind of pancake
When should we do this..?
Now..
This is also my first time doing this..
How should we wrap this up and eat it?
Hmm...this is the taste..it's really good
[This is the pancake!!]
[Satisfied]
[On the other end, speechless]
Well done, hyung
[Finding a space to sit]
I'm getting better and better at it
Hyuk ah..why are you looking on so forlornly? You had a confident look just now
See that? Writing?
The origin of food comes from men
[I've seen through you!]
Hyuk..smile! The pancake is going to burn because of your intense gaze..
Ehh..beautiful!
[Feeling sad while looking at this..]
Let hyuk try it once..
Yes, you try it once..
[Nearly dropped out of the pan]
You scared me!
[Sad again]
Janghyuk: I really can't do this...
It's the first time I broke into a cold sweat
[Pancakes are getting better]
I really did well today
I did the soup well..did the pancake well..
[The breakfast is done..]
Today's breakfast is all thanks to teacher Sooro's hard work..
Today we went through lots of incidents, from when the soup didn't taste good to making it good..let's hear a little about the pancake..
The hardest part about making the pancake was..
The beginning part was very difficult..
Yes, later on..after gaining strength from the Family, the final product was a success
I would like to say that teacher Sooro has the highest skill in making pancakes among the family members
So now, we complete our soup and pancake breakfast!
Ok, hyuk has now finished scooping the rice..let us begin..
Let's first have his interview
Let's do a short interview
What are your feelings today? Please answer simply
Initially, I thought I could do it..thought that with a competitive streak
To cook breakfast with me, that was a good choice
No matter what, the breakfast is done..now 3 of us, let's shout "Long Life!"
Soup..Long Life!...pancake …Long Life!...breakfast..Long Life!
We'll do this…Janghyuk, you go wash up and wake up the rest
Yes..put the soup on the table
Breakfast is ready..wake up please
[Now whenever he speaks, he'll carry the same tone as when he said the hwang yi had arrived]
Why are you so quiet? Why are those 2 so noisy?!
Oh..so stuffy..
What's this?
It's a pancake..
Yejin, look at this..
Oh..it's a pancake..
[Not expecting much]
It's a root veggie pancake..
Now we have the person who's responsible for it here..this child..really..
You guys are really noisy!
Onnie..looks like it..
Really?
[Disheveled]
Had a bad dream?
Oppa..it's really good
[This way, can only see his back]
Oppa..it's ok..better to see only the back..
Now..he really feels like crying
The soup is good, right?
Soya is good for the body
The pancakes are yummy!
[Closes the door after it gets blown by the wind]
[It's actually the cameraman!]
[It's the cameraman in the room]
[Jongshin and Janghyuk also have to be in the shot]
Oh..you're taking shots of both of them first?
Out of all the soups we've cooked, this one is the BEST
[Food expert wasn't able to detect the extra ingredient: Soup Flavor]
It's not cold anymore…it has become warm
It keeps changing..from yesterday to today..from today to tomorrow
[Together they sing JK's song]
[3 tasks to be completed by Family: 1. fertilize the ground well
2. Dig up bellflower roots
3. roast a turkey
[3rd topic: Family is lucky!]
[Climbing up the mountain to dig up grandma's flower roots]
It's very fragrant..can you smell it?
The fragrance of the roots?
Oh..it's really fragrant..
We have to dig up some roots...
Grandpa and Grandma will be back soon..
How do we dig these up, Sooro shi?
There's an opening, just start from there and go further down..
[Harvesting roots TIP: just slowly remove the top, grab and remove it]
You'll see the soil, rake further and then you'll see the root... dig for awhile..there should be plenty since this is herb land
Really? Ok..let's quickly do this..
First..we have to remove the film?
Is this it?
Got one here!
[The rest of the family starts to find the roots as well]
This is really herb land
Just wash it a bit and you can eat it
Soak it awhile
There are no insects
Have it with this!
When did you have this?
From my home
[Daesung discovered the King Root!]
The roots here are 2 years old
[Hyori carefully peels the root]
Oppa..you try it.
Got to wait for another year, then it'll be good..then it's 3 years
It's sweet
[One bite Daesung..one bite..Chunhee]
It's sweet..good
Can eat it like this..just like a fruit..it's really sweet
Hyori..give Jongkook a bite..also to Sooro. Also, please look after our guest..
He's moving back to his spot again.
Oppa..how's the taste?
Very good
[I want to have a bite as well...]
[Who is Hyori giving it to this time!?]
Don't use your hands, you'll dirty them
So, it's Jong Kook?
[He knew it would be like that...]
Come on, oppa!
Jong Kook, eat it!
I don't feel like eating it
Just eat
I really don't like this herb
Ok... no jokes anymore
Eat it quick
I really hate this herb!
Hyori is specially feeding you
Eat it quick
Can you take Hyori away?
I'm serious this time
[Caught!!]
[He finally gets it in one bite]
This is a pity. Now you two should hold hands.
Sooro hyung...
Just by closing his eyes, he can taste the herb
[There's more chilli sauce than the herb]
Hyuk... you're working diligently again..
Soo Roo: Hyuk... you don't have to be like that
Jongshin: He really looks like a labourer
Working hard is good. But!
Even in movies, you can talk to the person next to you
After the pancake incident, I have to revert to my old self
I just picked this one, right?
It is in the shape of a human
Is this not ginseng?
[Collected lots of herb already]
Can you carry it by yourself?
Are you ok?
Ok. Let's go
Now, let's play a game... but you will be covered by the saw dust
When we were kids, we used this to play this. Once you break it, the saw dust inside pours out
[Break it open to let out the luck]
[Throw the sand bags at it until it breaks]
[The team which does that first, wins!]
Since it's the new year, let Yejin and Hyori begin.
In 2008, we started the games with them. In 2009, we will do the same
Sooro: Yes. We all hope to have good fortune.
Breaking it in 2009 will bring a lot of good luck
Not just breaking it, we still need the good luck.
Don't just break it, we also need lots of luck
Bring this to your attention, Yoon Jongshin and myself... you know...
Sooro oppa
Jongkook oppa
Jang Hyuk
He knows how to play baseball
Dae Sung
You 3 should stand in front now
Chun Hee
Aaah! I'm left with these two. What should I do?
How can you say we're bad at it? You still don't understand us
This has to do with ball sense. Aii... really!
I'll give you both of them
[Yejin's team: Jong Shin, Jae Suk, Soo Roo, Jong Kook vs Hyo Ri's team: Jang Hyuk, Chun Hee, Dae Sung]
I have to make this clear. Jang Hyuk is very serious. We can probably see his true nature today
You can see what it's like from the opposite view of making a mistake
I had to handle Jang Hyuk three times in the games
Let's pick who's to go first
Pick 3 representatives. Because this is a game...
[Ye Jin's team 2 baseball experts (?) ]
[Ye Jin's team 2 baseball experts (?) + 1 game king]
Jong Kook shi will be out
I can play too!
Winner is declared on number of hits before it breaks
How about having one member stand under it?
We have already selected the person to stand there!
Then in this case, serious person... let's have another go
Is that ok?
Looks like he's looking at something
Start...
[The first hit by Yoon Jongshin! How will he do?]
Don't just talk... aim properly!
[Looking forward to the 3rd ball by game king]
Three
I used too much strength
[4th ball, Jong Shin again!]
This is already the 5th hit!
why cant you hit it?
[Already 5th ball!]
Five
Six
[The ball could hit...]
Seven
[It's right in front!!]
Are you ok?
Eight
Nine
Ten
Eleven
Twelve
Thirteen
[Stay still... the 'luck' is about to explode]
[The hit of 25th ball]
[About to split]
[Big Hyungnim with full-confidence]
[Now, with one hit... Its gonna be explode]
[A throw by a retired baseball player...]
Both of us, can do it
[Now, it's split!!]
You dont have to throw
[Jaesuk will end this with his 31st ball]
[He used too much strength]
[Finally, this time?]
[The luck explodes!!]
How many balls?
Thirty two
[Yejin team: success on 32nd ball from the Game King]
The one who will sit on the ground will be...
[Hyori team's turn]
[He knows even though she hasn't said anything]
That person...
Kim Jong Kook oppa!
This is not right below... so, sit here!
Really cute, our Hyori hoobae
He said, Hyori hoobae, Hyori hoobae
Why do you called me Hyori hoobae?
Oppa, you have to sit exactly there
I hope Kim Jong Kook oppa will receive the luck well
Exactly there, oppa
Hyori, am I sitting at the right spot?
Hyori: Yes
[First ball is throw by serious guy, Jang Hyuk]
[Hyuk-ah, slowly]
[Second ball, Chunhee]
[Daesung-ah, you...]
Just like Park Chan Ho (Pitcher for Philadelphia Phillies)
[This time Jang Hyuk's jump shot]
[His movements are the coolest]
Park Chan Ho will throw like that
[Again, Jang Hyuk's cool wind up]
[This time also, only his movement is suave]
[Everytime the ball hits, he is shocked]
Sooroo: nice, nice
Hyori: there, there
[Chunhee, 11th ball]
[What a pity... the ball is just flying away]
[What's wrong with Daesung who always hits?]
[This time also with his cool movement]
[Even though he can't hit the luck, he's already tired]
Sooroo: YA CHUNHEE-AH!
CHUNHEE-AH!
Oowwh... what's happening?
[Everyone's got virus from Jang Hyuk]
[Now, 17th ball]
[He will throw again!]
[Finally, is this the one?]
[Indeed, the move is great]
[Hit!]
[Jang Hyuk, he gets a hit sometimes]
[Explode]
Yah, who put the stone in?
[Hyori team success in the 19th ball]
[Chunhee, still throwing the ball]
You are really in a game slump!
I will shower you with luck
[Got showered by all the luck]
I hope all the luck will explode in year 2009
Hyori's team wins
Now, Hyori's team just won, right?
Why?
Kim Sooroo has a secret
[Kim Sooroo's secret]
He said that he has a different way to throw the ball
When you hold the ball like this, ready to throw, you just think it is a radish
Ah!.. think it is a radish?
Like this, oh... it's a radish.. oh, puk, puk, puk, ah, shh... huuuukk
If we saw it properly, we also used radish, not only ball
So we have to feel it's a radish?
[Real radish!]
That's right... Sooro oppa go and sit there, no cheating
Yah... Hyori-ah
Oppa, if you cheat on first day of new year there won't be any luck
I'm about to go and sit... huuuk, sit there
I think the viewers really want to watch Jang Hyuk throwing the balls
Just now, you just said 'hyuk-ah'
His posed when throwing the ball just like in the movie
Here?
Here
Hyori-ssi is escorting him personaly
Oppa, moved a little bit
[I really know that feeling....]
Hyori nuna is too much... how can you push him with your knee?
Like that...
I just made him to sit at the right spot
[Please explode the luck for Soo Roo oppa[ game
[2009, Please explode the luck for Soo Roo oppa Game]
Make a wish for Soo Roo oppa when you throw the ball
Hyung, I wish your movie has a big success
Oh~ good!
2009, Soo Roo-ssi, best movie award, grand award and male suppot actor award
HUK!
Soo Roo hyung, please stay healthy
Seems like he will have some health problems later
Hyung, later you just HUK
HUK!
Soo Roo oppa, huk
Jang Hyuk-ssi
[Finally, will Jang Hyuk hit it?]
Be well
[For Soo Roo hyung's sake, the ball hits good]
Yejin
Soo Roo oppa, in new year, have a good huk-huk luck
Huk-Huk
Have a good huk-huk luck~
[Starts to split]
[Jang Hyuk, even from a short distance, he can't hit it...?]
Ah... oppa, you cant hit it?
Receive this luck~
Chunhee: Let it all out
Yah... it's luck... it's luck...
Please be healthy
Did you guys scare him?
Lets Go!
[These guys!!]
[Cleaning the house before grandpa and grandma return]
[Sweeping the floor roughly, serious youth]
[Praising others while holding a broom]
Stand here for the ranking
[Play the "sleep order ranking" while waiting for grandpa and grandma?]
Will the next week's ranking be in this order?
[Suddenly]
Here they come...
You here!
Did you have a nice trip?
We really had a good meal of your turkey...
Wasn't the trip cold?
No.. I really liked it
What did you do during the trip?
[They had a very memorable trip]
Omoni, omoni... now, it's time for us to go
[Time to say goodbye]
During this cold winter, you guys coming here...
We really enjoyed..
[Happy new year]
[2009 new year special]
Translators: angelyrique, thowysg, amirahd2b
Timers: swtsrwlove, jocelyne03, gyugu, flyingkaratemonkey
Editor: swtsrwlove
Encoder: melijay
Uploaders: melijay, jocelyne03, Shannice, swtsrwlove