Brought to you by Ramen Soup Subs!
[Last week]
[Daniel Henney makes an appearance]
[The Family quickly follows]
[They all come together in Kyungbuk, Yangdok]
[While the Grandmothers go on vacation]
[The Family prepare the squids by hand]
[A Real Man Showdown, Jongkook vs Henney]
[Jongkook's surprise attack]
[A worked up Henney]
[Now a loner, the One Man]
[After 8 months of difficulties]
[Sooro and Jongshin become older/younger brothers]
[But in reality?]
[The younger brother acts like the big brother!]
[Henney shows us how to film a CF]
[New Years Family fashion show]
[Henney's charisma explosion!]
[This is a real runway walk!]
[This is how the Family's fashion show continues]
[How Henney spent his New Years...]
[Ch. 1: The Family goes to Membership Training]
Alright guys, step down already
[The time to pick the sleeping order]
Oh it's this time again
It's this time so why are you all up here?
What can we possibly do now?
So for now, stand where you think...
A moment please?
Before we begin
I brought presents for you guys
Really?
[Really?]
You didn't have to!
[Already a strong candidate for 1st place, and he still brought presents?]
[Uneasy]
Let's see the presents first!
Ok, I'll show you
Show me show me!
You got us all presents?
[Family T-shirts]
I thought he was Superman!
He really is Superman
This is too much
How can he bring presents on top of everything?
[Last week's last place, Seven Jongkook]
What's going to happen to me?
I'm so smart
Jongkook-ssi
[Just a moment ago he was worried...]
He's so responsible
Hyori
[I should have caught it coolly...]
[The surprise presents for the Family]
-CH: There's numbers on the back
-JS: Why does mine say 6?
It's your sleeping rank
[Daniel's estimated sleeping order]
So I'm 6th?!
I'm 5th, I'm 5th!
[Then who is 1st place?]
[Stepmother Kim]
[They're all looking at the sleeping order...]
Hyori's 2nd!
[According to Daniel: Hyori 2nd, Yejin 1st]
-JS: Daniel, what's your number?
-HR: Show us your back
I'm...
[His number is?]
[Just in case...]
He's not humble
[Clever and cheeky?]
Thanks Daniel
[Everyone's thankful for Daniel's sincerity]
My brother
My brother?
My friend
When we were in the room, I noticed Daniel plays the guitar really well
So we're going to gather around like we're at MT with the guitar
Should we sit down and do it?
Yeah, let's sit
I wish we had a small campfire going...
[The quickly prepared campfire]
[The small campfire helps create the atmosphere]
The atmosphere is so nice!
I feel like I'm at a college MT camping trip!
From now on, let's pretend we're in the same class
I'm a freshman!
You can be a freshman, but you're one of those old people getting a late education.
[Class of '99, Old Freshman]
Sooro hyung, you already have a career
You became head of the department
But you're here to learn new technology
[Class of '93 Student trying to keep his job]
He came back from the army
[Class of '88 Back from the army student]
Yeah, you're back from the army
From overseas
[Handsome foreign exchange student]
Foreign exchange student!
Daesung is a freshman
[Class of '09 Real freshman]
Yejin is...
Class president
[Class of '00 Class President]
[Class of '98 Athletic student]
[Class of '97 Clumsy bad student]
[Family Outing University]
We're at a MT for the first time for F.O. University
[Class of '91 Social activities leader]
We can get closer if we share memories
At these things we usually talk about love stories
-JS: That's right
-HR: Talk about our first loves
[MT Conversation Topic: First love]
So let's talk and share our memories
I like it
I'm curious about everyone's first love
When was yours?
[F.O.U.'s Social Activities leader Jaesuk's First Love]
Here it comes.  The emotions are coming!
[Remembering the vague feelings of his first love]
The emotions are rising, right?
Are you sure he's not just sleeping?
It was during high school
It was a 3 on 3 meeting
And I was paired up with a student
We went to Kyungbuk Palace
[Center of attention?]
Her house was in Mapo
This is taking forever
[Letting too much time pass...]
Oppa, sing a song
Hyung, saying that you went to Kyungbuk Palace is pointless
[Everyone's impudent reaction]
What about your first kiss?
On a bridge
What bridge?
Some bridge in Sadang
But you're from there
So yea, on a bridge
She made the first move
Even then...
Even then you followed someone else's lead
When I think of her, all my memories of her surface
And this song comes to mind
[Heeya by Lee Seung-Chul]
[Devoted]
[His memories are awakened...]
[He must really hate it (lyric reference)...]
[The sad grasshopper]
That's enough
[Earnest]
Let's go
It's going up!
[Struggling to catch it]
[But it's going further away]
[His first love leaves him...]
[As well as the camera...]
[They all leave...]
It's leaving you
And this is how I'm left
I'm curious about Daniel's first love
[Foreign exchange student Daniel's first love]
When was it?
When I was nineteen
19? That's pretty late
Principal
Oh yea, that's right.
[The principal's daughter...]
It was a forbidden love then!
Yea, it was a bit dangerous
[Uproar]
So who approached first?
[She made the first move...]
Was it when you played basketball?
Yea
[The popular basketball player and the principal's daughter's first love...]
Why did you and your first love break up?
There wasn't really a reason
-HR: Just because?
-DH: Yeah, just because.
Was it because if you kept dating you wouldn't graduate?
-JS: That's not it?
-DH: No
Joke!
But, even now, I still think of her
[Even now his first love still has a piece of his heart]
Then what about your first kiss?
First kiss?
Um, what kind.. of kiss?
Deep kiss!
[Of course it's deep kiss]
[Confused]
[Embarrassed]
What? I'm sure this is what everyone's wondering about
[So Daniel's deep kiss?]
When I was... fourteen
So it was with someone other than your first love
Yeah
While we were in-line skating
For a moment
In the corner
Oh, in the corner
[Daniel's song choice...]
[Suits this night]
[The sweet guitar melody]
When you go to MT's, there's always that guy that sings pop songs
This is so cool
Even if you wanted to sing along, you couldn't
[A brokenhearted, rough voice...]
[Burning up like the campfire]
[The F.O. students feeling the rising romance]
[All coming together as one tonight]
[Singing as one voice]
[The Family are all knocking on heaven's door...]
[Why is he singing like a mosquito...?]
Why is there a crying animal next to me?
He gave us everything
Even if he hadn't done all this, he'd be 1st place
Seriously, he was automatically 1st
How about Chunhee this time?
[Clumsy Chunhee's first love]
It was during my third year of high school
I liked this really popular girl
That girl was going to go to a performing arts school
So I thought to myself that I should go to a performing arts school
So you got into acting because of this girl?
Yeah.
When we graduated, we couldn't get into the same school
So since we were at different schools, we couldn't really meet up
So in the end, you guys didn't get together?
After a long time, we saw each other again when I came back from the army
Was she your first kiss?
Yes
Where?
Video room...
[A room where you can rent movies to watch; has a seedy reputation]
What is this?!
[The story was going well... until video room...]
What movie did you watch?!
Steven Chow's... Chinese Odyssey
[His first kiss happened while watching this comedy?!]
I thought it was a really good movie
I guess.. so.. your song...
What song?
But his first kiss was in a video room
This song is too pure
It was still his first love though
[Perhaps That by Chae Yong-joon]
[The faint memories from that night surface.. It was probably love..]
The opening crack of the door?
The opening door of their video room?
[Still going on like he doesn't know...]
[Absorbed in his emotions]
[Heart touching midwinter first love]
[Dim midwinter first love... Chunhee's deep lingering attachment...]
[Sad finish]
[My old love...]
But the lyrics are...
The opening door part...
Was the door already open?
It's supposed to be my eyes open from the morning sunlight
[How could the lyrics be so off...]
[The warm atmosphere of FO MT]
It's so nice that we're all together with the juniors and seniors
How about we start dancing time?
Good, good!
Loosen up our bodies?
This is really good! To just let loose and dance with friends
[The Social Activities leader must do Dancing Time...]
You have to really get into it, ok?!
[FOU's first Dancing Time]
[Trying to appear youthful, but past his prime]
Seniors, please don't be like this
Nowadays, nobody dances like this
Time to relax!
[Unbearable]
Do you know the story of my life?
Well do you?!
[Whenever you go to MT, there's always this kind of guy]
[The senior that needs to speak the truth]
Why is he like that?
Please don't be like this
What's up with him?
[Why is he like this...]
It's because Jongshin hyung likes you, stupid!
[The veteran senior student likes the old late education freshman]
[Drunk off of water]
Check it out!
[The attention seeking Sooro Senior]
You guys just need to leave us alone!
Fine
[Wants to get closer despite Hyori's request]
Hyung, just get over here
He's scary!
[This woman doesn't understand his heart...]
Why don't you just take a break
[So this is how they play...]
This area is for the young students
[The depressed veteran student...]
So, you're from America?
[Interviewing the foreign exchange student?]
Wanna dance?
[The two overdoing their dance]
I'm from America
Really? I went there before
Hyori!!
[Dumbfounded]
Hold on
That oppa didn't even pay and he's here
You drink all our alcohol and now you're acting up?
[The scapegoat veteran student]
Oppa you should drink more
-SR: Hyori, you shouldn't...
-YJS: Hyori, you changed!
How?
You changed since Daniel got here
Do you realize you've become more savage?
[Leaving with the veteran student]
[Leaving the young students behind]
[Real dance time!]
[Freshman Daesung first]
[Powerful dance]
[Becoming huk huk hot]
[However the lonely elder veteran student]
[Here I go~]
[Even breakdancing]
[And I'm out~]
Jongkook!
[The One Man starts off with a gentle rythmn]
[Heavy with his physical education speciality?]
[Comic dance]
[The uninvited veteran student making an entrance]
What's wrong with you?
Chunhee!
[Bad student Chunhee participating in MT]
[Showing his dancing skills]
[Only making dirt blow around]
Chunhee, you're doing good!
[Stiff]
[Showing off his true dance]
[Ow, my back~]
Yejin!
[The reserved Class President]
[A sudden change]
[And she said she couldn't dance...]
Henney! Come on!
[The popular foreign exchange student's turn]
[Daniel Henney's first public dance performance]
[Sooro, the old student]
[High quality step]
[He must have danced when he was young...]
[Huk huk~ let's go!!]
[Dancing devil]
[Hitting all four corners, stage manners(?)]
I can do the rabbit dance!
[Careless rabbit dance]
[The Family in a rabbit dance daze]
[Dance time has come to an end...]
[I'm jealous...]
We can't end this night
We're just excited since it's New Years
Let's just stop
We're just going to pick first and last
[Time to pick the sleeping order]
[Anxious]
[Worried]
[They're only picking last...]
[Impossible...]
[It can't be me...]
This is my second time last
You guys aren't really anticipating 1st place?
[1st place most likely Daniel]
Kim KookJong, play it cool
[Maybe me...]
[1st place, Daniel Henney]
[1st place was as expected...]
Let's pick 7th place
[More important, last pick selection]
The rest can just sleep wherever?
Yea, just sleep wherever you want
Today's 7th place...
[7th place selection]
No, hold on
I haven't picked yet
[Already scared he's last, Seven Jongkook]
I've already been last twice!
-HR: Oh, is that right?
-JK: Yeah!
Why am I always last lately?
[Only concerned about sleeping order during dinner time...]
How should I be like towards Hyori?
Just say through your eyes, 'I know you really like me'
[With his Small Eyes little brother]
[Making an elaborate effort]
And if that doesn't work, we Small Eyes brothers can smile with our eyes
[As a last resort, practicing smiling with his eyes...]
[It can't be?]
[The Awkward woman might let him slide this time?]
Actually, you've been last 4 times
No, it's only been 2 times
[Earnest]
I worked really hard today
Ok, last place is...
Do it cool
1, 2, 3...
[As expected?]
[He explained and everything...]
[It's still me...]
[Seven Jongkook is last for the 3rd time...]
But I danced and sang!
Why?! Why me?!
Just be cool.. why are you being like this?
Get off of me!
It's okay
[Gets a hug from Daniel]
You take a hug from Henney?! How can you..
Let's pick the girls now
[Women's ranking]
This is for Hyori, this is for Yejin
1, 2, 3...
[The men vote]
This could have been unanimous
[Unanimous?]
Unanimous?
[Results; 6:1]
Henney will hug first place
That's right, and Jongkook wil hug last place
Why?
No thank you!
Why can't you just be cool about this?
[Firmly upset...]
I said no thanks!
-YJS: Jongkook's eyes got bigger!
-JK: Why?! Why are you bringing me into this?
Oppa, are you upset right now?
You're really worked up over this
Why me?!
[Depressed]
What is it that I didn't do right over this hyung?!
[The veteran student can relate to his frustrations]
[Jongkook not hiding his frustrations...]
Why don't you go and sleep first
Hey! Why are you still treating me like that senior?
[Preparing to receive Jongkook's hug]
[Who's 2nd place?]
1, 2, 3...!
[1st place, Park Yejin]
[About to hug... but pushes instead]
[2nd place, Lee Hyori]
[The Awkward couple starts to fight...]
[Becoming demonic again]
[Will the Awkward couple ever become friendly...?]
[They start to become friendly and then start fighting again]
[The never-ending story of the Awkward couple]
How can you guys be like this when you are family?
Hyori, talk to me!
Talk?
Talk about what?!
That he likes you!
[Sigh]
We just all seem to like each other!
Everyone go inside
[Everyone goes into the room...]
[As soon as Jongkook goes in]
These are Kim Kookjong's huh?
These are Sooro hyung's!
They're Sooro oppa's?!
[Oh no!]
He'll be okay.  He just needs to calm down
I heard you threw my shoes!
No, no I didn't
[Evading]
What's with you?
Those are my favorite pair!
[The Awkward couple causing a scene again]
[Even though they argue and fight...]
[We live as one and love like a true family~]
[Current time; 12:15AM]
Oppa.  With the exception of 1st and last, you guys can sleep wherever
Let's do rock-paper-scissors
[2nd-6th male selections through rock-paper-scissors]
Okay
Winner gets to sleep next to Daniel
And the person we like the least sleep next to Jongkook
Does anyone want to volunteer to sleep next to me?
Sooro hyung says he'll sleep next to you
Thanks hyung
[The remaining people play rock-paper-scissor]
[Jongshin and Chunhee advance]
So it's whether they sleep here or here
[Jongshin wins and gets to sleep next to Daniel]
Let's lay out the bedding
Daniel, did you say hi to Mera?
Hello!
[(Da)niel's first hello to (ca)mera]
-DH: Does it have a name?
-HR: Mera
-DH: Mera?
-HR: As in camera
Ca-mera.. Hello
[The courteous man says hi again after exchanging names]
He's my boyfriend
Oh, it's a guy?
[Since it's a guy, saying hi again in a masculine voice]
[The Family has extreme confidence in saying greetings in English]
We all worked hard today
Henney, is it okay that you're not on a bed?
I like this
It's okay?
I like the hard floor
It really feels like we're camping
I feel like once I close my eyes I'll fall asleep
[Impossible...]
My eyes are closed, so why are my lips still...
Is it because I need to talk a lot?
Why does my tongue wag so?
Talking machine
Hyori... talk to me for a minute
[That Senior is back again...?]
Why do you keep doing that?
Hyori! It's because the senior really likes you, stupid!
No thanks
He's really not my style
Who is your style?
Henney
ZZZZZZ
Jongkook.  I know you don't really speak your mind, but
There's no need for you to throw a fit for being last 3 times in a row
So you're saying I still have to face it in the future?
That's right
[You will be lower than Jongshin and Jaesuk for ten thousand more years...]
You still have a long way to go
See you in the mol(?)~ning
You thought it was Daniel, huh?  It was me!
[Today the Family studied English very hard with Daniel]
[Ch. 2: Big Hit~]
[The next morning at 7:40AM, The village has the beautiful chirps of birds]
[But inside the room, there's only snoring...]
[Without fail, it's wakeup time!]
[The first to open his eyes...]
[Even sleeping, Henney's like a sculpture]
[The grasshopper accepts his fate and wakes up]
[In his usual state...]
[A gourd on top of a seesaw?]
PD: Today's morning mission is to head butt the gourd and break it
With our head?
(Yes...)
[The clueless Chunhee]
[The Elder, as if his head already hurts]
[Thrusting the horn into the room!]
(Oh my God)
[Sooro coming out the other door, away from Jaesuk's damage]
[Daniel trying to attack the megaphone]
That sound doesn't really bother me anymore
We should change it to something sharp and piercing
What am I supposed to do?
Flip the gourd up on the seesaw and head butt it
[MC Yoo enthusiastically directing Sooro]
-SR: Only head?
-JS: Only head.
[Make the gourd fly... and head butt]
[Jongkook is also awake!]
[Daniel isn't fully awake yet...]
[The experienced Family members wipe the sleep from their eyes]
[Put on their clothes and get ready to go outside]
[The Elder is fully equipped]
[The youngest is still half asleep!]
Just jump and break it with your head
[First up, Sooro!]
Start!
[A lot of strength!]
[Try to head butt it~]
[It looks like it'd be good...]
[Sounds like it hurt...]
[Sooro fails!]
[Jongkook's turn]
3 times 6th place.  I'm sorry, 7th place.
[Stiffens]
In case.. you forgot...
[Releasing his 7th place anger]
[A strong head butt!]
[Losing pride, Seven Jongkook]
And he claims he plays soccer...
(He really is in a game slump...)
I think it'd be better without the hat
(My hat...?)
[Next up, Daesung!]
[Lined up to his head!]
[Will he succeed?]
[One try]
I just huk! and hya!
[The Dumb brother immediately following along]
[The Elder Jongshin's turn!]
[The gourd goes flying...]
[Head butts the edge of it]
[The Elder's morning misfortune...]
[Of all things to happen it was that part...]
[This time it's Chunhee's turn!]
[First hits the roof and then Chunhee's head...]
[Perfect timing head but!!]
I like today's game!
[In high spirits]
So good!
[Daniel's first attempt!]
He's a basketball player
That doesn't help here
[Is Daniel familiar with a seesaw?]
So I just step on it like this?
Yes like that
[Even though he hit it, it didn't break and probably hurt]
That gourd is really thick
[Checking the thickness of the gourd...]
Sorry...
[Jongkook's turn!]
Jongkook, do you want to take off your hat?
[In his heart he wants to win]
He can't even break one?
[With just one remark from her]
[It was like a World Cup heading!]
[Breakdown]
He really is in a game slump
But that looked like it was a thin one
[Sympathy pain]
[Hyori's turn!]
The gourds are frozen solid right now
Even if I smashed this on the ground, it wouldn't break
[It's thick]
Sorry.  My feel for the game is a little off
Here's a lighter one
[Hmph, he apologizes and changes gourds]
[With a lot of strength, the gourd flies far]
[When it doesn't break, it hurts more...]
The Hyori gourd broke
It hurts!
It's been awhile, you're a big hit (play on words)
[Jongshin's turn!]
[The gourd flew to his short height, but he fails]
The gourd.. My whole gourd is going to break
[Kim Sooroo's turn]
[A nice and clean win]
[Yejin's turn!]
Let me at least connect with it
[Lady Yejin carefully proceeds...]
[Fail!]
But her last name is 'gourd,' she shouldn't be afraid of it...
(Gourd and Park are spelled the same)
I really tried, why didn't it break?
[Hyori's turn!]
[It didn't break this time again]
[And broke when it hit the ground]
[A streak of rage]
It's irritating, isn't it?
Hyori's alive!!
She's back, she's alive!
Where did the kind Hyori go?
I want to be nicer to you guys in the new years
[She showed everyone a warmer feeling...]
Let's just do everything with a pure heart
[The kind, angelic Hyori...]
She's back!
[In the end, back to her true nature...]
[I liked it then]
[Jongshin's turn!]
[He tried hard last time...]
[How will it be this time?]
[Broken pieces]
Why does it hurt for me?
[Yejin's turn]
[Goes right in front of her head]
[A proper heading!]
[A proper heading! Win!]
[Jongkook, Daniel, and Hyori are the only ones left]
The first one to win out of you three is exempt
Henney...
[First up, Daniel...]
[Will he win like this?]
[Failed, even though he went down on his knees]
[He must really feel the loss to hit the ground...]
Hyori: Where you going?  You're leaving?
Jong Shin: He said he's leaving (god sounds like go)
[Hyori's turn!]
[Head butts the front]
I did it?
[This time again, it breaks on the ground.  Fail!]
It broke because it hit the ground
No it didn't!
What do you mean it didn't?  All the pieces are piled here!
[The Awkward couple dragging out yesterday's fight...]
[Hyori picking the gourd for Jongkook]
[The gourd from before that probably wouldn't break even if it hit the ground]
[First taking off his hat]
[For sure it'll break!]
[You can't!]
[Impossible]
[The One Man head butts with his entire body]
[It broke!]
Cooking today's breakfast: Hyori and Daniel!
[From this moment, the time has begun for Daniel's stunning breakfast preparation]
[Do you know how crabs taste?]
What should we make for breakfast?
Since we're in Young-duk, we can get snow crabs
[Young-duk snow crabs?]
Is that okay?
I've never done it before
[Jongkook coming back from the bathroom]
[Resenting him for being exempt...]
Hyori cooks really well
Don't hate me
Since we're in Young-duk, we have to eat their snow crabs
Oppa, how do you feel about snow crab stew?
Oh! Sounds good
[And so, the two leave to buy snow crabs...]
We're not like the oppas who...
Hold on
It's not that we don't want to make breakfast
Let's just be cool about this
[Hyori and Henny being cool!!]
[The morning sunlight]
[The blinding winter ocean]
[Weaving the basket like a basketball]
[The energetic pajama clad people]
[Looking for the best crabs...]
[Looking for the best crabs... An outing to the Young-duk coast!]
If we go to the boats we can probably buy it cheaper
[Henney doesn't really know about markets...]
If we just buy in wholesale...
You know.. wholesale?
What is it?
Like... one on one
You know?
Understand?
[The clever Henney understood...]
[The small dock where the boats line up]
Hello!
Crabs!
Wow!
[Right away, Young-duk snow crabs]
Are these the snow crabs Young-duk is famous for?
Yes
[Very big]
Are they alive?
Yes, they're alive
We were hoping to buy some
How much for three?
Can we choose which ones?
Yes
[The kindhearted captain even letting them choose]
Let's pick the pretty ones
Here, gloves
Choice, choice
[All they have to do is pick the crabs!]
[Pushing]
Men have to do these things. Are you scared?
[Gentle Henney doesn't want his hands bitten...]
I grew up in Michigan!
So you're scared?
We don't really have crabs there
You're scared right now?!
Yeah, a little
You can't have this kind of image!
Just grab it coolly
Cool?
Show me how
You can do it!
The time is now!
[Making use of what they learned...]
How do I grab them?
You just do it
They don't bite?
They bite
So?
It doesn't hurt that much
[Absurd]
He said it doesn't really hurt
Like this?
[Starts with a bang...]
[Even the perfect man Henney can be like this...]
Fighting!!
[Causing a fuss over one crab!]
Henney, this kind of image...
Shhh! my mind!
Ok
It's looking at me right now!
Then pick another one. One with their back on you
That one, the one without a care
[Absentminded crab?]
How can I do this?
You can do it!
I think that crab is sleeping right now
This is how they look when they sleep?
[They had both agreed they'd cook breakfast cooly...]
No, he's just saying 'Hurry up and grab me so you can cook me.'
Okay
[Will he be able to catch it now?]
That one that one that one, the one in front
Yea like that like that
[Henney's about to die from fright]
[Hyori's just nagging at his side...]
You can't grab his legs or else it'll just break off
The legs of Young-duk snow crabs are the soul!!
The legs can't break off
Get the sleeping crab
Do I just grab it here?
No, grab its body
Yea like that!
[Henney, for now succeeds at getting one]
It looks yummy
Let's get a really big one next for the stew
Him?
[Hesitating]
Catch him catch him
You can do it.  It's just like the last one!
I can do it!!
[It's big]
It's got long legs!
[My legs are long]
He's really big.  Good job!
[Full]
This one is Jongshin oppa, and this one is Henney
That one, that one.  Ok!
[Now just one more!]
[This time he caught it well...]
See, you're a natural!
Captain, can we take these three?
[Acting cute]
Thank you!
Let's go
[Troubles and obstacles in preparing the crabs, coming soon!]
[The quiet morning in the village]
[The rest of the Family still sleeping]
Oh!
Two of its legs are missing
Where did his legs go?
I don't know.  He had them before
[The remaining legs on the crab]
It must have fallen off from the cold
[Tip: In cold weather, crab legs are more likely to fall off]
The legs are frozen
Have you eaten these before?
Like this?
Yeah, fresh
No
How about cooked?  You haven't had them in stew before, huh?
No.  I didn't really get to eat fresh seafood
It's so good!
So, we'll boil the big one and put the little ones in the stew
We have to prepare these with our hands
[Confused]
Me?!
Why?
These are things men should do
[They're trying to push the task onto each other again]
But I was the one that caught them
But catching them is easy
It was hard for me
How? With a knife?
Or with my fist?
No, you grab the end and rip it off
Knife, knife.  Let's use a knife
We don't need a knife, just use your hand
No... Why...
They'll be okay!
How do you know?  Did you ask?
You're okay, right?
No I am not!
Oh, so you're Korean crabs?
[Discouraged]
You said to knock them out
No, it's passed out...
There it is
I did it, huh?
We just need to peel it now
[Clenching teeth]
Grab it like this and...
Like this... like this...
[Madam Lee, good job!]
[Regardless, they have to prepare the crabs by hand]
[Flawless]
Now you try
[Now the rest...]
[Henney's turn to peel]
Rip it off
Rip it!
Rip it off, Henney!
Open it up!
[I did it...]
[Absurd]
The stew ones are done
[The ones for the stew are done]
Let's boil this one
Henney...
Can you find the lid for this?
[Does Henney understand what lid is?]
[Oh! He found it right]
It looks a little big...
[However...]
It's okay
It doesn't fit
[No support for its size]
The size is different
Huh?
Pardon?
[What did he say just now?]
[After a moment]
That looks about right
Right?
[Sure enough]
[Not sure if she really understands...]
Oh, we have to put the anchovies in
[Now, putting in the anchovies for the soup]
Find the stomach
Stomach's here
Yes, now open it
Take the head off first
If you do this right you can meet a good Korean woman
Have you ever had a Korean girlfriend?
I haven't
Do you like Korean women?
Henny: Since I'm not from Korea
How about me?
You'd be good
I'm good, huh?
The U-Go-Girl Hyori you see on TV, compared to me
Are completely different
I'm the same way
You see the Are you gentle? CF guy and then look at me
It's different
Right
So you can end up marrying a Korean woman then?
I could
I want to get married this year
[Madam Lee getting married this year?]
Have you ever dated a foreigner?
Not once
Really?
Because of your english?
[Diplomatic moment?]
My english was never the problem
I guess it was because of the cultural differences
[Defensive...]
It didn't match
It's okay even if you speak english fast
Because I got full marks on the listening exam
Huh?
[Meeting his gaze]
Can you cut this for me?
[This time preparing the radish]
My hands are too cold.  Do you know what this is?
You don't know?
I don't know what it's called
Radish, radish
Oh yea, this is a radish
You don't cut radish with a knife
You cut it with your teeth like this
[Cut with my teeth?]
That's how we cut it in Korea
Really?
Yea.  Watch me
[Hyori gives a demonstration]
[Henney doesn't seem to believe her]
[With more effort...]
[Doubtful]
You have to do it like this
You see the wavy pattern?
So it can be decorative
Doing it with a knife is too boring
I'll just use the knife
No! I'm telling you, it's not done with the knife
We don't use knives in Korea
Why?
The elderly don't really like it
[Quick response...]
[Quick response... the Korean way to peel]
[In the end]
[He fell for it]
Faster, faster
Like this.  Fast
Do it for me
Another demonstration?
[Oh my God]
[One more time!]
Here
Try it
You have to try it!
You look like a squirrel!
You have to try the Korean cultural experience
[In the end, he does it again]
[The Gentle Henney plowing...]
Why am I so bad at this?
You don't use strength for this
It's more about rhythm
[The Nation's fairy... unexpected...]
Like this
I've done this since I was young so I'm good at it
Make it so it comes out like this
[There's something on your nose]
[The radish bit on her nose]
Alright, now let's use the knives
Joke!  You know, joke?
[Of course there's no reason to cut radish like that in Korea...]
Just put it in
[The big snow crab to boil]
Like this.
Grab those legs
[Not wasting the broken legs]
[Hyori preparing the vegetables for the crab stew]
[1. Boil anchovies in water for the soup]
[2. Red pepper powder]
[3. The hand prepared crabs]
[4. Green onions and pepper, and cook]
Henney, you speak Korean well now huh?
Who, me?
Ya
You still can't understand all of it?
Of course
Still?
I'm not good at it now
Then what's this?
[Will Henney know what soy sauce is?]
Traditional formula
[Reading off the company's label]
Just, traditional formula?
Yes
What's inside the bottle?
I'm right
Inside the bottle?
Stuff to use when you're cooking...
Soy sauce
Red pepper paste
[Hyori tells him what everything is]
Soybean paste.
[I got it...]
Soybean paste
Red pepper paste.
Red pepper paste
[The Nation's fairy playing around again]
Soybean paste
Really...
[Huh?]
[Raw green onion?]
What are you eating?
Green onion
You're weird
[Raw green onions aren't that good]
It's not that good eating it like that
It tastes good though
[It arrived]
[He can't say anything because he claimed it was good]
[About to die]
[Regardless, the crab stew is cooking nicely]
It's short by 2%
[The crab stew hits an obstacle]
What else should we add?
I...
Since I've been watching Family Outing a lot lately...
I brought this...
Just in case
[Oh! Ramen soup!]
No we can't!
This isn't good!
You're learning bad things!
It's okay... because... it'll be our secret....
No, the reason why this won't do
This is God made
This is human made
It's okay, it's okay.. it'll make it taste good
No no
Only people like Jongshin oppa use things like these
Just add a little bit..
Cannot
[pleads]  A little bit...
No
No!
Okay, okay. I get it
This is really
[Understanding this from Henney]
These man-made methods that Jongshin oppa and the rest use have really misled these innocent people
[The great influence that food expert Jongshin has brought about...]
Food is not natural like that
Cannot!
DH: Ah really, how can we eat it like that?
Cook it a little longer and it will become more palatable
[Hyori who has a great sense of responsibility to food cannot bear it]
Really?
It will be better after adding some bean paste and chilli paste
[10 minutes later...]
I'll get some salt
[Hyori who goes to get salt]
[Daniel...you wouldn't...]
[Trouble!]
[Thinking of how to clear up...]
[Careful] [Careful]
[Coughs for no reason]
[Destroying of evidence]
[Perfect timing~]
[A little suspicious...]
Asa~ NANTA (musical) was nice right?
Yes
[Secretly changes topic]
How many times have you watched it?
One time
One time?
[Hyori, who still does not know yet]
Let's go together after some time
[Daniel is nervous]
[Just then..]
[Scoops up a lump of ramen seasoning]
[I'm dead...]
You wanna die?
Ah no..no..forehead..
[Stutters nonsense]
It's hot~
What did you do?
Nothing much
HR: You added the ramen seasoning didn't you?
DH: No..no I didnt.
[Obstacle]
I could actually have done really well..
We...
What? That is not a good habit.Henny ah~
I didn't do it. I didn't put it in
You didn't put? But there's a smell, I'm very sensitive to smells
[First, sticks head out to look..]
[Smells] [Smells]
There is that smell
Mucus
It'll become more delicious because my mucus fell in
Look, it'll become tastier now
[The first taste after adding the ramen seasoning..]
It came~ It came!
[Ramen seasoning is still the best!]
Try, Henney
[Anticipation]
Ah can it only be like that?
The mucus, it fell in
[Exclaims] It has even become a little more palatable
[So, Daniel's conclusion is?]
Ke~ha~ha~ha~
It did come didn't it?
[The blend of eastern and western taste]
[The power of seasoning]
That's why I say the oppas cannot escape the lure of seasoning!
[After trying the taste once, it'll be difficult to escape it..]
Ah..looks delicious!
Ah I've become too embarrassed to criticize you
Indeed, I still have a long way to go in the art of cooking
[Thus on the path of every great chef...
there needs to be something...
-by the Food Expert]
[Steamed crabs] [Crab soup]
Ah~ Looks delicious!
[The breakfast which is almost ready in a blink of an eye]
This is too good. It looks really delicious
I'll wake them up
[Henney to wake the family members]
Yeah, go and wake them, I'll scoop up the rice
[Hyori lays the table]
[A ladle and serving plate?]
[What noise is that?]
Hey you guys. Wake up, have breakfast
[Using American english even for the morning call]
[One by one starts to open their eyes..]
[This person...are they open or are they still closed...]
Ah~ This is so much fun!
Everybody please come out
[This time using the megaphone]
[Silently~]
Time. Breakfast time
[Like a dream~] [Not like a dream~]
[The food expert, on his way to the South Pole for breakfast...]
Wow~
HR: Oppa, there are steamed crabs and crab stew
[The exclamations before breakfast]
JS: Woah~
Are we going to eat the breakfast Daniel Henney prepared for us?
Yeah
Yo Baby~
[The crab stew which was saved by the seasoning]
Steamed crabs. Oppa, please serve the steamed crabs
Is that steamed crabs?
[The result of their ambitious selves - steamed crabs]
It's so early in the morning...
This breakfast is really...
It's too sumptuous for breakfast..
Isn't today's breakfast too huk~huk~?
Its really nice
[Indeed, the food expert who has an inborn reaction to the taste of ramen seasoning]
This is different from adding ramen seasoning
Daniel, so what are your thoughts about making breakfast?
[Henney who always eats American breakfast]
I've always eaten American breakfast so I'm really excited
Wow! Look at that
[This huge chunk of crab meat is a treasure]
Come Henney, try this
Hyori is indeed good at making breakfast
Hyori ah, you're really meant for house-keeping
[The praise which is only given after providing them with such tasty crabs]
You're saying that to order me around, aren't you?
[Jaesuk who has been eyeing it]
Wow~ this is really a delicacy!
[The highest level in crab delicacies - crab meat with rice (like bibimbap)]
[Mixing the rice dedicatedly]
JK: Delicious
[Puts it in his own mouth]
Oppa, you were so serious with the mixing just to feed yourself?
[The Nation's Siblings are really...]
Mm~ delicious~
[The Family who got to try such delicacies]
[and adding a guest well-liked by the Family..]
Nice to meet you, we just woke up so we're a little lost
[Hyori's mum and sister who visit Family Outing's set]
Why is the mother....
While travelling we passed by coincidentally so we came in..
[The coincidental meeting on their holiday...]
JS: Is that so?
Mother: We made some snacks,everyone please have some
[Still brought new year snacks for the Family]
Hyung, Hyori's mum and sister
Eh?
[Stunned]
[Just woke up and yet...]
Oh really, they were just passing by on holiday, so they decided to drop by
Chun Hee ah, this is Hyori's mother and sister
[Chun Hee is also in a daze]
CH: Nice to meet you~
Mother: Come let's shake hands..we've been happily watching Family Outing
JS: Hyung, it's the real family
Oh! This is...
[She glances at everybody else...but the only one she likes..]
Jong Kook ah
[Bows]
Jong Kook does like Hyori a little
He bullies me everyday
No such thing~
[Though a very short meeting, it has made the Family very happy]
[Chapter 4 - Let's try the Family's rice cake]
Now, we have to hurry up and cook the rice cake soup which we are going to give to the village families
Yes
Deliver it and offer New Year's greetings
[The greetings and rice cake for the village's old folks]
So, next the wood
Huk! Pour it in! Huk!
[The anchovy soup that Daesung has prepared...]
Yes
Wahh~
So it is because of the anchovy soup that it has this taste
So delicious, doesn't look like much was added in
[The leek is also in chunks]
[The rice cake which was cut yesterday]
There seems to be as much leek as rice cake
[Thinking of the village's old folks]
Okay, pour it in
[Equally careful with the ingredients]
Yejin ah, shall we try one?
[The egg filling to be put on top of the rice cakes is also being prepared]
Looks good
[The Family's sincerely prepared rice cakes are cooking]
Daniel oppa,could you help me to cover the lid?
It's too heavy huh
Yes, it's too heavy for me to lift it up by myself
[Undeniably a gentlemen]
HR: Daniel oppa
YJS: Daniel has done quite a lot
Yejin ah, it's so weird to call him daniel oppa, english names shouldn't add an oppa
That is also...
Just call him Daniel, he'll be so happy
Is that so?
Daniel oppa
Aren't you a noona?
Noona? No!
[Now they just have to wait for it to boil..]
The two of you look like two young masters standing there
The lazy sons
[Family Outing's two sturdy young masters]
Yeah, like the two lazy sons of the house
My younger brother, my cute dongseng
My scary hyung
The pitiful dongseng
Do you feel like getting punched?
Ah, it's only a joke
[Why is he unable to take such a joke...]
Only a joke
Let's try it now, oppa
[Dukkbogi (rice cake) seems somewhat cooked..]
Ah, the smell is out
Try the dukkbogi
[Jaesuk tries first]
-HR: The rice cake might not have absorbed the taste entirely
-CH: The rice cake might not have been fully cooked
It's okay
[Satisfied]
HR: Okay?
JS: Yes, its okay
Henney!
[This time Henney tries it too~]
Oh~ Perfect
It's certainly huk huk~
[Put them in the thermal flask to ensure it does not cool]
Come, let's get the thermal flasks and set off
Huk~ Huk~
[Sets off together to go new year visiting!]
Let's turn left here and go in
-HR: The Chairman's house
-JS: Yes.
[Firstly, they give it to the chairman of the elderly association]
It looks like it's here
Nice to meet you~
Don't stand on such ceremony
Come, let's all go up
First, we'll offer our new year's greeting to granpa and grandma
[Starts off with an official greeting ceremony]
Grandpa & grandma, have a blessed new year ahead
[First, the 3 elderly]
Wishing you longevity
Stay healthy
[Next, Yejin, Jong Kook and Hyori also...]
Have a blessed new year ahead
[Bow their heads~]
We prepared rice cake soup and brought some over
Is that so?
[Brings out the new year rice cake soup]
There's no need to stand on such ceremony..
It's so rare that we get to see Lee Hyori shi
[Full marks for popularity among the elderly]
You know her too right?
Of course, Miss Yejin
Yejin ah!
All of you please eat more
[Carefully adds the side dishes to the hot, steamy soup~]
[Also careful with yesterday's skewed meat]
Oh, we're really thankful..
[The Family's rice cake is served~]
[Touched]
[Will they like it..]
Wow, it's really delicious
Grandpa please eat more, we made a lot
It's really delicious
Is it still to your liking?
[Fortunately, it appears to be alright]
Since the two of you have said it's delicious, we can stop worrying
Grandpa, grandma, please eat while we prepare for a mini performance
Oh really? Let's see it
[Hyori and Daesung (the little bridegroom)]
Hyori, don't be shy
1,2,3,4
[A glance here, and a glance there]
[The cute & amusing grandchildren's party]
[The shy wedding couple]
[Grandpa & grandma have forgotten about their rice cake...]
Grandpa, grandma, please stay healthy!
[Because they still have to visit other elderly]
Have a blessed new year!
[They still turn and leave despite feeling reluctant]
Thank you!
[The two elderly's warm smiles will be remembered forever]
[Now, they split into groups to visit the elderly's houses]
[First group: Jaesuk, Henney, Hyori]
JS: The time is now
Nice to meet you, so it's here
[Grandpa Nam Yeong Shik (72) Grandma Keun Nu Mi (67)]
[Extremely anxious]
Have a blessed new year ahead!
You too
Really nice to meet you, Mr Yoo Jaesuk who often appears on tv
If only the children could see you, they'd be so happy
This is..
[Introduces sister Lee Hyori...]
Miss Lee Hyori
Ah, the wife?
No, the wife is someone else
My wife is at home, this is my younger sister
[The nation's siblings suddenly become a couple...]
I'm not yet married
So, Hyori and Henney will go and prepare the rice cake while I will engage both of you in conversation
[Although it is not much, they still hope that you can eat it well]
It looks really delicious, it's been hard on you
Although we did not do it well, we still hope that you can enjoy it
[The sincerely prepared meal]
Please try it
-JS: How is it?
-Grandma: It's done very well
Not bad?
It's delicious
Really?
-JS: Grandma, please try this
-Grandma: The rice is good too
Grandpa, please try this..
[Hyori offers the meat to Grandma]
Woah,what a big piece
[Jaesuk immediately tries to stop her!]
No...this..
How can grandma eat such a..
No! It's only delicious when you eat a few pieces together
I heard both of you were match-made..
Yes
Was grandpa handsome when he was young?
Yeah it must be
Grandma must also have been really pretty back in the younger days
How can you only mention that grandpa was handsome...
I think I've said the wrong thing again..
[Hyori messes up in front of Grandma again]
It's the new year, you should be careful of what you say
Because we were match-made, we believed in each other
I see
Grandma, why do you laugh...
Grandpa talks and grandma laughs
[The couple who stays loving looks so beautiful...]
Thank you for your visit, I hope you will be able to fulfill your wishes and spend the year in good health
[On the other hand, the small-eyed brothers]
Nice to meet you...
[Grandma Kwon Sang Nam (88) Grandpa Nam Byeong Ju (90)]
Have a blessed new year ahead
Thank you
This is what we made in the morning
It must've been hard
Rice cake soup and..
[Their faces when they taste the food are the most valuable to the Family]
We're really brothers!
Brothers, brothers
Really?
Who is more good-looking?
I'm the older brother while he is the younger brother
[The battle between the brothers' egos]
The older brother is a bit better..
Oh really?
[Happy]
[Even so, the small eye brothers still have a strong relationship]
Why~ I'm in a good mood, I feel happy for my brother
Look at me, grandma, look at me, grandpa, look at me now, look at me
[The performance that the small eye brothers prepared]
Yeah~that's good~
Grandpa, grandma, please stay healthy in the new year!
[The elderly's smiling faces...
give our Family strength...]
Have a blessed new year ahead!
[On one side, the 40-year-old brothers are...]
[At this time, they silently take out...]
You're not giving us red packets, are you?
[It can't be...red packets?]
It's not necessary, grandma
Just take it
Oh, you gave quite a lot
We were actually saving for the grandchildren a while back
[Seeing them as grandchildren~]
We'll take the red packets then
[The 40-year-old brothers get along so well that they each took half!]
Taking the red packets makes me think of my mother
[The afternoon which was spent celebrating the new year with the village's elderly]
[Although the Family only prepared a small table of rice cakes, they received much warmth from the village]
After a while more, the grandmas will be returning soon..
Before picking the onions as the grandmas have instructed, let's play a game
Now the waves are really big
Oh so pretty
[ Today's beach scenery is also pretty...]
Love Titanic
[Love's Titanic: While standing on the other's thighs, with two arms wide open, one must shout out the memorized line below]
[Year 2009, wishing everybody before the television a new year with great health, lots of luck and love, Family Outing fighting!]
[Yejin team: Jongshin Sooro Daniel Chun Hee] [Hyori team Jaesuk Jongkook Daesung]
It's alright
Jongshin hyung, you be the judge
[Full of confidence!]
I will not move an inch from where I am standing
[Both sides are showing off their legs]
Look at us! Look at our side!
Although that team has longer legs, it is weaker
[Short but sturdy? Hyori team]
OK, We are sending out Jong Kook & Hyori
Our side, we're sending out Daniel & Yejin
Jong Kook hyung looks nervous..
[Jong Kook's footsteps seem heavy]
No! This game is specially created for me
Hyori, fighting!
[Hyori, must it be that far...]
Hyori, you know Jong Kook's thigh, don't you?
Hey, you have to step on the thigh okay,it'll be disastrous if you step on anywhere else
Kim Kook Jong, here I come!
You have to step on the thigh! The thigh!
[Terrified]
Why did you run so fast?
[The result of running so forcefully...bumped into each other!]
[Hyori team: Jong Kook Hyori FAIL]
Jong Kook hyung, you can't even bear this?
Why did you run over!
How could you just fall over...
[Should've bore with it for a little while more..]
Can't you walk over?
Are both of you dating? Really!
Ah, you couldn't even bear with that?
[Jong Kook Hyori! It won't be easy to succeed..]
Why are both of you like that!
Look at what happened to the ground as well..
The ground has already sunk in by so much
[Sunk in!]
Jong Kook ah, come over here.
I do want to do well...
[Yejin team: Daniel Yejin]
Daniel fighting!
[Goes barefoot because she's going to step on Daniel's thigh]
Barefooted?
What's with taking off your shoes?
Because I like it.
You could just wear it anyway.
Daniel oppa will be hurt.
[Daniel oppa?]
Great, great!
Daniel oppa, I'm coming...fighting!
Are you that happy?
[Lightly jumps up!]
[At least the titanic look was a success!]
[Now, all is needed is the new year greeting]
[They even captured the right posture~]
You have to say the ment!
You need to shout it out...
[Did she want to do it once again?]
[Even though they failed, it was better than the Jongkook, Hyori couple]
They've really got manners, just like American manners.
Manners guy and girl.
Yejin even took her shoes off, but I still feel relieved that Hyori didn't wear heels.
Are you sticking the stone on?
Kim Kookjong, I'm going!
You don't have to run from so far, slowly... slowly
Ah, really!
Where are you going?
What's wrong with you, don't be like that.
Why did you make her fall?
No, I slipped!!
[These two people, always like this...]
No, it's not Kookjong's fault.
[I want to cry]
Sorry... sorry...
You must step on solidly like me!
[Jongkook, slowly telling her the technique]
I'll do what I should!
She never listens to me, never!
Kim Kookjong, I'm going.
Say it, quickly!
What are you doing?
Are you shooting a movie now?
I think they're dating, they're probably dating.
Make an official announcement that you like each other.
Do you want to play on the ground?
Oppa, we couldn't do it because you don't hold me with enough strength.
That's because you hold my head like that...
Fighting!
I'm going!
In this year 2009, we will be with the viewers' love, happiness and health, Family Outing fighting!
[Daniel, Yejin, success]
[High-five with Jongkook?!]
Then, this time...
Let's do the battle between the 40 brothers and Dumb and Dumber brothers.
Oppa, you have to win.
Don't worry!
The sum of their ages is 81!
[40-year-old younger brother Sooro]
Sooro, you must hold me well.
[41-year-old older brother Jongshin]
I got it.
I'm your hyung!
For~ty brothers!
Forty forty forty!
In this year 2009, with the happiness, love... ah!!
What are you shouting?
I forgot the line!
Daesung-ah!
I'm going, hyung!
Go there! Go there!
Ah, what's wrong with our team~!
One, two, three, forty!
It doesn't work.
I'm going, hyung!
[This time, a bit slower...]
Let's succeed(?) this time!
Forty forty!
Forty nine, party?
In this year 2009, we will be with the viewers' love, happiness, and health, Family Outing fighting!
[3 points for the last battle!]
For us...
Daniel, Chunhee!
-Daniel, Chunhee?
-79 club.
And our team's ace, Lee Hyori and Jaesuk.
You're the ace?
Should I stand there?
No, I do.
Daniel, I'm going!
[So high!!]
It's really scary up there...!
Just wear your shoes, it's okay.
No, oppa.
What are you doing?
Didn't you know, Jongkook-ah?
We're siblings!
Hyori-ah, just wear your beautiful heels! It's okay.
-Oppa, I'm going.
-Okay.
I'm like this for only you.
-Oppa!
-Come on, Hyori-ah!
Going... up...
Where, 'going up'?
Your ment is "Everyone, Happy New Year".
-Fighting!
I'm going.
Everyone, Happy New Year!
Wow, Daniel, success!
Okay, with this, Yejin team wins!
Now we have to pick leek for the grandmother.
Let's pick it, huk-huk.
Let's go to grandmother's leek field.
-This is the field.
-Leek field, leek field.
Oh, the field is...
-It's okay to pick as many as you can.
-We can pick many of these today.
Just grab it and huk, huk, huk!
-Then shake the root like this, right?
-That's right.
And then, take out the dry leaves like this.
This is fun.
Henney, is this fun?
In the past, I did this a lot in my country.
Oppa, do re mi pa~
(Fa is pronounced pa in Korean, pa means leek)
Hyori-yah, shake the root a bit more, get rid of the soil.
Yejin-ah, use a shovel. (sounds like the word for leek)
Ah, I'm so hungry. (sounds like the word for leek)
Oppa, oppa- old school (9, leek, foot)
Papa smurf.
[For a short time time, that family fell into the leek puns gag world]
Hello!
I had a really nice meal, and slept well..
[Chatting about each others' memories]
Did you have a nice trip?
[Family, curious about the grandmothers' trip]
Yes.
[It's relieving to know that they enjoyed the trip...]
Today we also had a nice breakfast, yesterday we went to dry up the squid.
We also ate the squid.
You all gave us a chance to go on a trip.
I will never forget it, in my life.
Grandmother, happy new year and please stay healthy.
Please be healthy.
Yes, thank you!
Goodbye!
Grandmother, be healthy!
Translators: suebee, nxh, amirahd2b
Timers: swtsrwlove, flyingkaratemonkey, aznhoneychik, pekkles
Editors: swtsrwlove, melijay
Encoder: melijay
Uploaders: melijay, sunshinemoon, tiff80