[The day before shooting]
Have you already watched Taehyun hyung's new movie?
Driver: Not yet
Chunhee: Uh? Not yet
Hello?
Everyone, hello. I'm Yoo Jaesuk.
On this trip we are going to Yongdok Gweshi village, Gyungsangbukdo.
Tomorrow at 7.30 am please gather at Gimpo airport. The end.
[Speaking to himself again and hanging up the phone]
Aish, I can't search that movie again
He always calls during these situations
Ok... should I go now?
Let's walk together, oppa
Why do you always get a solo shots?
You know because
The moment when we're are coming out, I really like it.
I like to receive the sunlight.
[Hyori was submitted into hospital due to pneumonia]
Are you ok now?
Yup
[Please anticipate Hyori's participation]
[One man who arrived earlier]
Kim Kook Jong~
Hyungnim
[Followed by Yejin]
What happened to you?
[She seriously suffered from the flu]
[New family still did not arrive!]
I hope a pretty female guest is coming
[At this point]
Oh they're here
[Interested]
[Anticipating]
[Gave them a shock?]
[The greatest romanticist, Daniel Henney]
Aigoo, Daniel
Nice to meet you
Which family members did you want to meet the most?
Honestly, I wanted to meet Yoo Jae Suk.
Why? Why?
I'm his fan
Oh wait, can you hold my bag?
Don't be like this
Oppa, let's go~
Uh! Let's, let's go
Daniel, first~
Are you gentle?
[Embarrassing, really...]
He's really handsome~
We're really surprised that Daniel is joining us
If he takes off his sunglasses he will be more handsome
Like this?
Like that, like that
Seems like he is close to Hyori
Long time ago, both of us went to States and worked together
Our age also same, 3 friend
Friend, friend
CH: Same age, friend
Hyori: Chunhee is also a model
[Model ChunHee?]
Singer
-You are a singer?
-Yes
Excuse me, what time is it now?
Timing is now
You also know that?
Is it correct to say "timing is now"?
No, it's not correct
How should I say it then?
The time to speak is now
The time is now
Do you know this uncle?
Uncle Yoon, Uncle Yoon
How old are you?
Just a baby!
We're going to trip with an uncle and a baby
Can I call you hyung?
Of course!
We're arriving now
I am Daesung
Aw, cold!! Cold!!
It's very cold, aahhh~
Daniel has to find the house according to this map
Daniel go, we follow
Daniel take the lead
You must say ' take the lead' in English too
U-Go-Girl~
Let's go
right, right
Oh! Is he taking the right path?
Is it here?
Oh it's here
Hello~
Thank you for taking us for a trip
No, it's okay grandma.
Daniel also came here to join us
He's handsome, right?
Yes, thanks for coming
Goodbye grandma
[Today's duty]
Dry up the squid
Pluck the spring onion
With our Daniel
Pluck the spring onion, dry the squid
Look after the house, the End
Then we are finished
It's very easy
That's why
It's easy to say
So, let's get ready
[1. Drying up the squid]
[Episode 1: Jong Kook VS Daniel Henney]
We have to do what grandma ordered us to do
Since we are from Seoul
We have to make some dduk (rice cake) soup for the villagers because of lunar New Year
To make dduk we have to soak the rice first
That's right
How do we do that?
Wash the rice and let it soak in the water
Ok, let's wash the rice, since we have to soak it later
Chunhee-aah show us
You also have English name, Chunderella
Don't move, be careful
It swells!
Swell? How are we going to wash it?
Daesung: That's enough. Too much
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Hyori, You get out
It's because she's not feeling well
Here in family outing all the work is done by the males
I heard that rumor
The female members don't do these things
I'm sorry but I will avenge you during the game
Right now we are doing so well.
Excuse me, Henney, would you like to try washing the rice?
Like giving it a massage...
Rice massage
Rice massage please...
Hyori-ah, you're too much
His hands are precious
Then our hands are not precious?
Warm?
Daniel you have to go deep like this
Deeply?
Then, you have to stir it
It is milk
milk... milk
No, no. It's rice wine (makgeolli)
Do you know rice wine?
Why do you roll your tongue to say rice wine?
Henney, have you eaten dduk soup before?
We're going to make dduk to cook dduk soup
'next morning' we'll make it 'together' and 'eating' it
We'll make for 'parents' who live in this 'town'
Make for 'grandfather', 'grandmother', 'father' and 'mother'
Giving to all... giving...
[It's more surprising that he can understand]
Why is his name Chunderella?
You know Cinderella right?
Why?
Since he is always doing the work
Doing work without complaining
He is stepmom
Staff's mom?
Hyori, help me
Help you?
Move a bit, I'm going to help him
[Daniel-Hyori washing the rice together]
Do you know the movie with actor Patrick Swayze?
Ah... Ah... Ghost
I like that movie
[What makes all couples excited]
[Is this scene!]
[They always imitate whatever looks nice]
Oppa, you can't waste the rice like that
Did I ruin it?
Can you lift it Daesung?
Daesung-ah
Hey Daniel
Yes sir
Help me!
Ok great!
Good job, good job!
Okay let's go
We finished all the work here
Let's go "squids tanning"
Squid tanning, right? Ok, let's go party
Oh the squid dries up like this
Is this dried squid?
In this situation, it's good if we eat dried squid
It looks really tasty
Hello
Do we have to dry up all these squids?
Yes
Will you all help me?
Yes!
We will help you
Fighting!
You're already into the work
Knee, knee. Don't step with your knee
That's right, that's right
Be careful
Okay!
Why is mine bigger?
Your black ink pouch exploded
Very well done, Henney!
Should we make Yejin do it?
Yejin must do it, Yejin-ah!
You are the daughter that all mothers will proud of
She is a university student majoring in the use of the knife
Indeed Yejin is doing well
[Perfect]
Oh my, Yejin
It's so clean
[The internal organs done nice and clean in one try]
[Flawless]
Yejin, you're a work of art
[It never looks like it's her first time!]
(It's nothing...)
Oh, I think you already popped it
[Even though the Elder was handling the squid with care...]
[Even before he could slice through the belly he pops the ink]
Are you trying to do calligraphy?
What is that?
Alright so I'm going to be drawing
You guys just cut up the rest of the squid
[Ink pudding]
He must have eaten chocolate
[While getting hit by the cold winter ocean air]
[They are handling the squid together]
[Skillful handling]
[Delighted Elder]
[Going through one by one with sincerity]
Since the guys are doing everything we have nothing to do
What do you mean there's nothing to do?
Hand me a knife
[The women cheer them on by singing Kara's Pretty Girl]
You guys don't know this song
It's not that we don't know it
You don't know Kara?
I wish Kara was here so I could meet them firsthand
[Sigh]
They might come, don't you think?
When do you think Kara would come?
Then I'd have to go buy new clothes...
Why do you have to buy clothes for Kara?
I have to buy a suit
I'll show up wearing a necktie
What song is that?
Ah Kara.
Kara?  Oh, Daniel doesn't know who Kara is
[Because Daniel is from overseas he doesn't know Korean music very well...]
If you want a lover?
[Singing and dancing...]
Daesung!
You sing Kara's song...pretty well
Do you, by any chance, like Kara?
[The speechless idol...!]
So you do like Kara!
Daesung! Is the girl you were texting Kara?
[Where is he going all of a sudden...?]
[Why did I do that...]
[I shouldn't have said anything...]
That's enough, Oppa
I was just about to stop
The time is now!
You heard that right?
We have to put these all in there
[Wash off the cut squid]
[Wash it in ocean water]
[Then rinse it once more in tap water to get it clean]
Good job! Good job! Go! Go! Go!
[The clean and prepared squid]
I didn't know the dried squid we eat was prepared like this
I know right?
[Carrying it over to dry]
[The squid will hang from the wood to dry]
Push it through
[Yejin's squid hanging lesson!]
And then spread out the bottom part
Ok, okay
[Since it's their first time it's awkward]
[They all go through one by one]
[The Family's sincere sweat]
[They hang it well so it will be tasty...]
Whenever I go to America,
The only English I use is when I have to go buy something.
Every english word I know is coming out right now.
I want to learn better English...
[From now on they can only speak English!]
What's 'That's what I wanted' in English?
[So this is how they speak English with Daniel]
[Hanging up all the prepared squid]
Wow we did a lot
So since we finished hanging the squid
Let's go play a game
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you
Take some with you for dinner
Oh, we can do that?
-Thank you so much, sir
-Thank you!
How many can we take?
As much as you can eat!
[Happy because they received the squid as a present]
Our nation's Lunar New Years Day is right before us
So instead of doing a normal game
We're going to have a wrestling match
The waves behind us
They're so cool
It makes you think of old songs
And the wind is very suitable
Suitable?
Today the person who loses, wins.
So Henney and Jongkook will be captains
You guys do rock-paper-scissor
I'm in a game slump
[Daniel wins]
Oh that's right, he doesn't really know anyone
[All of a sudden he broadens his shoulders]
Let's wait and hope then
Jaesuk, why are you like...
He usually does that
I have to show Henney what I'm made of
FYI, Sooro Oppa is really good at games
This side over here is all bad
Why are you gesturing with two fingers?
My friend, Chunderella
Hey, this is a first
[Henney... you have no clue do you...]
[Henney wins again]
This one is seriously in a game slump
[Hyori, by Henney's side since the beginning]
Hyori, you're not on a team yet
You're not picked you know, get over here
You think you can just go with your friends?
Hyori, are you wearing rouge (blush)?
Why are you wearing rouge when we're going to have a wrestling match?!
I've had it on since before
Really?
Yea
Are you sure you didn't put it on to look more lively?
Friends, I'm picking all my friends
[Jongkook wins]
[Trying to avoid being picked]
[Averting eyes]
No matter what, I have to be on Henney's team!
Even if you paid me, I'd still go to Henney's team!
[Jongkook's team: Sooro]
There's no space on Henney's team
[Jongkook wins again]
[Totally averting their gaze]
[Yejin, suddenly pretending she's sick...]
Yejin, please take better care of your body in the new year
[Jongkook's team: Yejin]
Nuna left!
[Jongkook's team: Daesung]
[Jongshin and Jaesuk still have a chance to be on Henney's team]
[Henney wins]
I really like you~
I want to be on your team~
Jongshin hyung
[Jongkook's team: Sooro, Jaesuk, Yejin, Daesung vs Henney's team: Jongshin, Hyori, Chunhee]
Our team's ace, Henney!
Then our team's ace, Jaesuk hyung
[Confused]
(It looks like he'd do really well...)
Since when was I ever an ace?!
Please get on your knees
He's really handsome
-HR: Oppa, compliment each other before playing
-JS: Oh should we?
Say it in English, cool
Yes please, do it in English
That's the best compliment I know in English
Jaesuk hyung.
Meeting you in real life, you seem really cool
Can I do another one?
Inside you, there's me
I'm serious
[Everyone there is embarrassed]
You call that a compliment?
[Did they say to compliment each other or express our love...]
-JS: It's a compliment!
-YJS: If you say so
[Lifting him in a flash the moment she said go...]
[Henney's back is first to hit the ground]
[Henney wins!]
The match can't end this quickly...
What do we do if the match is shorter than the compliments?
It's because Henney doesn't really know how to do variety shows
You have to play with him for a bit
Just play around with him in a mean way
And then just win later
Wait just one second
I can win too!
What do you mean toy with me?
[Another match just to create laughter]
[A big difference in leg length...]
[Jaesuk seems to be giving it all he's got...]
[Playing with him well]
[However it looks like the first match...]
Oh look at me!
Henney, you don't know what to do now huh?
[What will be the final outcome!]
[Jaesuk... Is falling...!]
[Of all places to hit when falling...!]
Camera out!
[Interrupting filming to access situation!!]
[An unspeakable pain...]
[Sorry]         [Sorry]
Are you okay?
Aigo, aigo
Aigo... Henney!
Ok, camera in
[Just think of it that you escaped worse misfortunes for the new year by suffering this one...]
No I'm okay
-DH: You're okay?
-JS: I'm okay
Oppa, you won!
I did?
[An honorable win despite the wounds...]
[Jongkook's team: 1 vs 0 Henney's team]
You won and all, but at first it didn't seem like you would
[Yejin vs Hyori]
For the ladies, you have to win to win
The first person to flip to the ground
Then I'll just flip her over my shoulder
You guys remember when Chunhee planted my head in the ground?
You can do something like that
We have to do the compliments
[It's awkward since they're so close]
Yejin, I hope your drama does really well
and I hope you don't sick
I hope you don't get sick as well
And you stay healthy
And you get rid of your manly image
I don't have that kind of image!!
I'm just hoping you come across softer
Ok, okay
Since the compliments weren't very funny
Now insult each other
[This match should be funnier]
[Hyori makes a move for the back leg]
[Yejin is doing a good job playing defense]
Yejin, you have to keep moving your legs!
[Equally matched]
[This time, Yejin makes a move for the back leg]
[The coaches are causing more of a commotion]
[The women's match is more intense!]
[Yejin makes another move for the leg!]
Just toss her!
[After spinning around, their energy fades...]
The back leg! The back leg!
[Yejin goes after the back leg one more time!]
[But Hyori still avoids it!]
[And.. pushes back?!]
[Hyori has the technique and strength!!]
[Hyori wins]
She's like a strong man!
[Starting the new year with no regrets, the strong Madam Lee]
I shouldn't have won...
[Trying to shed this kind of image this year]
Good job, Hyori you did a good job
Chunhee vs. Daesung!
Chunhee it's okay, you can win this
Chunhee you can't put your hand there like this
What do you plan on doing?
Grab his butt
You can't grab on to his butt
[Clumsily grabbing on to the Satba belt]
Do your compliments now
I'll be satisfied if you shed your clumsy image this year
I hope you will go back to being the smart Chunhee...
I hope that you become smarter than
Jaesuk hyung this year
In my opinion, I think you're smarter than him anyways
What kind of voice is that?
[All of a sudden his voice gets weird]
Let's just play the game!
It's the same voice he had when he MC'ed Gayo Daejeon last year!
[That same extreme voice]
Ok, ready!
[A wrestling match with many variables! Can the winner be predicted?]
Stand up, stand up
[Tense]
You have to lose to win
Start!
[Daesung hangs off of Chunhee right from the get go]
[The Dumb Little brother has similar tactics to his Dumber brother]
(I'm in trouble!!)
[Chunhee trying to drag him back up]
[Squirming around]
[Chunhee's even got his head caught now]
[Chunhee is free!!]
[And now his body is moving back...]
Chunhee! Chunhee wins!
[Daesung's foot...]
Chunhee your back, move your back
From our team, Game Slump Jongkook!
[Now it's the time for the final round!]
He has confidence in losing!
That's right!
[Henney Team's Ace, Daniel Henney]
[The match you can only watch]
For this match, we're changing it up
Instead of losing to win, you have to win
[Burdened]
That can't be
He said he wanted to get closer with Henney, but now...
This looks like it'd be hard
They're just talking amongst themselves
[Finally, the final round!]
[Best body condition, Daniel Henney!]
[Although in a game slump, the muscular Jongkook!]
[The rarely seen big match]
[This time it's strength and technique to win!]
[Jongkook attacks the back leg right away!]
Hold on, hold on!
[Henney's worked up!!]
I didn't hear it!
[What are you doing?!]
[What kind of person are you?]     [You have no manners!!]
[Everyone is criticizing]
[I should have won...]
[It's been such a long time since I've won...]
[...Huh?]
[The worked up Henney quickly chasing after him!]
Daesung: He really must have wanted to win
Jongkook oppa, I said ssi-jam not ssi-jak(start)
When the gentle Henney was like
'Oh~ hold on, hold on!'
[Quickly and fluently speaking Korean...]
Jongshin: That's the first time I saw Henney speak so fast
Alright~
I understand you're going through a game slump.
But you're being tactless!
Hey~ baby one more time~
Henney must be feeling so down right now
[Jongkook makes a gesture to reconcile]
Let's just skip the compliments and go straight to it
[Henney's still worked up over it!]
Even someone gentle as Henney has his moments
You shouldn't try to get out of your game slump like this
[Even though he's won after such a losing streak he's being reproached...]
(This time I won't lose...!)
I'm starting to like Henney more
He seems just like us
Look at how tightly Jongkook oppa is holding on to the satba belt
No!!
No, it's because Henney has a lot of strength
If Henney knew how to play wrestling you think he'd come wearing jeans?
[Henney pushes!]
[Turns him over?!]
[Jongkook flips over the charging Henney...!!]
Hey! How could you use such a hard technique on him!
[Everyone goes to comfort Henney]
[While Jongkook is remorseful again...]
Henney, are you okay?
[At a loss...]
How many times did Henney do this?!
I thought you were (Kim) Heung-gook hyung!
[Still the winner, Jongkook]
Come here...
You won and everything
Let's try again
What for?
Killing him twice is enough
Kim Jongkook, winner!
Hurry up and be a good sportsman
You feeling good?
Jongshin: You like that you won?
He likes it, look at him
Sooro: I don't think they can become friendly
[The two men reconcile with a hug!]
[Henney, joking to the end]
Henney's the kind of person that just holds everything in, too
PD: How about Jongshin vs Jaesuk next?
There's no point
I'm just too...
I can plant him on his head in one try
(What a joke...)
Hyung, I can just toss you like baggage!
I was the wrestling king when I was younger!
You said you ran track and field!
I did it while doing track and field!
[International referee, Sooro]
(Is this how refs usually talk...?)
[However you look at it, it's an evenly matched round]
[They're only making noise...]
[Trying to apply offense techniques, but the leg length...]
His leg can't reach
Oh~ The tensions high now!
[We asked them to fight for nothing...]
[After 10 minutes...]
[And they're still like this...]
[A seemingly endless round...]
Hyori: Let's just go...
Jongshin: Are they all leaving?
Jaesuk: Hey, we'll be done soon!
[Hollow...]
PD: Evacuate! Unplug everything!
[The staff that can't watch any longer...]
Jongshin: Hey, they're leaving!
Where are you guys going?
You have to film us!
My glasses! Hold on a second!
Are you okay?
[Even though there's no one watching]
[The two are having an intense match with themselves]
Jaesuk: Hyung, just fall over!
Jongshin: Can't you just lose this one?
[The outcome of that battle...]
[Is a secret only the ocean waves know...]
[Ch. 2- My dangerous little brother]
With the new year approaching, Hyori's been really generous
Daesung: She must be sick
She gave me chocolate today!
She gave it to me even before I asked her for one
'Oppa, you want a piece of chocolate?'
When she was in the hospital,
she had her ill temper taken out
[Is this slander or praise...]
Nuna, your face looks slimmer
I'm just trying to be nicer to you guys for the new year
I'm not sure if that's a problem that can be fixed in one day
When I got sick, I realized how important the Family was to me
Oh really?
When we cook dinner tonight, since we're all splitting the chores between us
Let's just do it with a pure heart
[That can't be done]
What's with you?~
Nuna, I thought I was in an after school special
In horror movies, the villain always starts off like this~
Oppa, the rice that we soaked earlier,
we have to get it made into rice cakes
Oh really?
Ok, then me, Daniel, and Chunhee..
Right-niel and Left-Chunhee will go
Okay, then get the spring wood and..
Spring wood?
Yeah
It's not even spring, how can it be spring wood!
[Angelic Hyori can't even last a day?!]
(That's how it is...)
Who's going to get the vegetables?
Jongshin: The vegetables? It's been awhile,
why not the small eyes brothers.
[Small eyes brother]
[Small eyes little brother]
[They like it~]
Jongshin: Are they stupid?
Wait so it's Jongshin and Sooro hyung, and you two?
Sooro: Hold on!
Hold on! I wasn't going to say anything, but
Who's going to work then?
You, Jongshin oppa, me, and Yejin
I know, so who's going to be working then?
Daesung: They're all the ones that don't work
No, the two of us are the type that work hard
I think our characters all overlap
This is touchy!
Are we going to get dinner done this way?
When you guys return, there's a chance all 4 of us will be sleeping
Daniel, shall we go?
Let's go!!
Explain it to him, too
Chunhee: We'll be back
[After a moment...]
[Arriving at the town's rice mill!!]
- Hello
We wanted to make this into rice cakes
- Are you the owner? Hello
- Yes
You must have been really surprised!
I wasn't surprised!
But sir, your expression seems very surprised
That we just all of a sudden came in here
It's a pleasure meeting you
Chunhee: We're trying to make rice cake soup
Jaesuk: To give to the elders in the village
Please make them delicious
Should we take out the water more?
I'll take out the water
Is there anything I can help with?
Store owner: To help?
Jaesuk: Yes
It'd be helpful if you just quietly sat somewhere!
He just politely told us to stay out of his way
Daniel: Is it hard to make?
Store owner: This? It's not hard at all~
This is Daniel's first time seeing a rice mill
You put the rice here
And add a bit of salt
Oh you have to add salt
You don't just stick rice in.
Oh it just comes out of there
This is a novelty
Even though it's wet rice
When it comes out, it's wheat flour
Store owner: Rice flour, I meant rice flour
Can I try a little?
It's flavorful
If the salt wasn't added, it'd be...
[Waiting patiently like the owner asked...]
[The fragrance of mushroom boiled water]
You just took a sip and it looked like a coffee commercial
Can you do one for us?
Let's do it together
We'll do it one by one, but show us how it's done
Daniel: Me first?
Family Outing coffee is very delicious
Chunhee did you see that?
How his lip only went up on one side?
Chunhee give it a try
[Somewhat... Rotten Smile]
FO Coffee.
What was that?!
[Somewhat... Rotten Smile]
Chun Hee, what is up with you?
When he first came, he was very suave.
It's hard, isn't it?
I've practiced that ever since I was young.
Oh, really?
You have to do this, like this.
I have another one.
Look at this eye.
-Oh, only one side.
-That, that!
That comes out some times in commercials.
Are you gentle?
Chun Hee, you try it.
Doing only one side doesn't work.
How can only one side go up?
I don't think you can either...
[Stiff face]
How do you only do one side?
Ah, I can't.
I can only raise the right side, the right side.
Why?
The left side, I can't.
[In the time that they filmed the impossible CFs]
[Somewhat well steamed rice cake]
Wow, that...!  Wow!
Oh, look at the smell.
That, when it becomes well steamed, that...
Becomes the stick of round rice cake.
I've never been able to eat anything that just came out, you see.
You can't eat something like this unless you go to a rice mill.
It's really amazing.
It's coming out, it's coming out!
[Here] [There]
I see, at first they take that and do it again.
You always take the stuff that comes out first and put it back.
You have to redo this about three or four times to make the dough.
Ah, the dough.  You make the dough like that...
It's not done in one go, I see.
-Daniel, this is your first time seeing this, right?
-Yes!
-It's so amazing, really
-I think that rice cake will be delicious, too...
You're right.  That looks delicious, too...
Ah, it becomes dough.
Right?
If you stick that in honey and eat it, it's really delicious...
Ah, he's starting now.
The stuff that comes out first... Just a little bit...
Sure.
Look, it's coming out!
This is my first time seeing it.
Wow, this...
Oh, it's warm.  Eat it now.
The stuff that just came out!
Oh, it's really mushy.
-It feels like cheese
-It's really delicious.
It really feels like cheese.
You definitely can't say that you ate this when we go back.
[They're teaching him great things...]
Do you want another one?
There is an ambiance if you eat this round rice cake as if in a CF.
Mm, round rice cake.
That felt sleazy, right?
Oh, so Henney does have different impressions.
Okay, good, good.
I think you'll do it well.
Round rice cake..
I can usually, but...
It's because it's too
That's a sea lion...
It's so delicious.
Oh, but this, really...
We, during the lunar new year, have rice cake soup...
And have food that's made with the round rice cake, but
We've never come to a rice mill and tasted it immediately after it was made like this.
It's extremely delicious.
It's really delicious.
How much is this?
This 10,000 Won.  (About $10)
10,000 Won?
Oh, Henney is..
I should start carrying my wallet around!
I feel weird...
He just... 10,000 Won...
Thank you.
Mr. Owner, thank you.
Mr. Owner, please receive a lot of blessing for the new year.
Thank you.
This is all spinach?
It's like a piece of artwork.  It's grown like this?
Is it okay if we just dig these out?
How do we... Wow, this..
Take a look.
You see, this here is the knife that cuts the spinach.
Since there is some dirt on it,
This had to go into the ground.
So you press in like this and pop.
Wow, this...!
But, I don't think we use the roots.
So we should cut it off.
Okay~
Oh, this color.  So this is how it is.
That color is this.
Because I've always eaten seasoned spinach, I didn't know what they really look like...
Anyway, today... Daniel Henney...
-His life is like a picture.
-Because he was so suave...
His life is a like a picture.
I felt good just looking at him.
It's the first time I felt that a man was suave.
I'm in big trouble today.  These days, I'm always last place!
Hyung, remember how I was first place last week.
You were first?
You don't remember...?
I also saw somewhat recently...
A fan had written
The average ranking of our members for sleeping order.
Yeah?
Guess who took the first place, hyung.
Me, me.  Dumber.
-Me, me.
-You?  You're first?
I'm on average, the first place.
Looking at the margin between first and second place
There was a remarkable difference.
Oh, really?
There was a huge difference.  Like an 'Usain Bolt' difference.
But, really.  What am I supposed to do today?
Daniel Henney... Really...
I do really like him.
Of course, Daniel Henney is a piece of art.
But he can't defeat you in charm.
Haha, you really...
In these times, it's charm.
Daesung!
-It's charm these days!
-You, really...
After standing on stage with me, did you really see my charm?
Hyung, your charm.  You know when you smile...
-Everyone in the area goes crazy.
-Really?!
"Oh, Jong Kook is so charming!  So charming!"
Really?!
Do you know how depressed I've been?
You're supposed to go out and use your charm.
I thought I had gone back to the Turbo days...
Because during those days, only our songs were popular.
I mean, really..
Hearing that only your songs were popular makes my heart hurt, too...
Daesung!
I'm in the same boat as you!
Daesung!  Why are you like this?!
No you're the current trend!  Do you know how many kids live and die because of you?
After living and dying, they must all die, hyung!
When we go back in, what should I do for Hyori-ssi?
Tell me how I should act.
The important thing is... Do you call them to inquire after their health?
You don't right?
What?  You even call them?
Hyung, you have to call them every two days.
-Really, hyung!
-Every two days?!
That's what the ranking is, hyung.  You have to make it yourself.
How can anyone call every two days?  I...
I don't even know their numbers.
You have to create during the two weeks what you film on Monday and Tuesday every two weeks.
Do you have something else?
Hyung, you don't understand Hyori-noona's feelings, right?
She has the heart of an elementary school student.  It's exactly an elementary school student.  I mean, hyung, what did you do when you liked someone when you were in elementary school?
-Ah, it's like that.
-You treat them badly and bother them.
That's why she's been bothering you like this until now.  Because she doesn't want her feelings to be discovered.
Because she doesn't want to be.
You will slowly see the feelings that are half there, and not there.
If Hyori noona sassily says
"why are you doing this, why are you doing this."
Then you go, "All right, I got it~"
The look you give her!
Has to be one of 'I know you like me'
That way, Hyori noona will see this and go
"Have my feelings been detected?"
Well, if it just doesn't work, we the small eyed brothers
At least we have our eyes that smile.
Go to Hyori noona and...hehheh.
[Usually eyes that dust motes can't even get into...]
And laugh?
Laugh without reason.
Like that!  That's us small eyed brothers!
Our smiling eyes.  How cute are they.
-If you do that, it's automatic No. 1.
-Okay, I got it.
Should we start to go now?
If we season this, this many should be okay, right?
I wish I can at least sleep in the middle...
Hyung, the middle...  You are too modest.
Modesty...
It's because I've been last too many times...
No, no.  Your charm will today...
[Jong Kook is going with inflated hopes...  Will he finally leave last place?]
[As predicted]
[Sleeping...]
I think it's about 8 degrees.
Ye Jin has a cold and has to rest.
Then she has to sweat it out.
-By working
-A lady doesn't sweat even if she does work, oppa.
She's already wearing gloves so she can work.
Those work gloves really fit you well.
We're the '40 Club'.
-You unwise 20-30 year olds.
-What '40 Club'...?
Do you understand the world?
For dinner, we can have squid stew.
So it's squid stew?
And since we have to give the elders of the village some seasoned vegetables and rice cakes tomorrow
Jong Shin oppa is the oldest here, right?
-He's the elder.
-He'd be the elder.
No, we're the same age!
Then oppa, make Soo Ro oppa do something!
You're the eldest here!
Why do you act so awkwardly...
Are you just going to lounge about?
And, since it's the new year, stop talking formally to each other.
You keep saying you will!
Then, comfortably
Since the kids are here...
You can talk to me casually.
Well...
We're both in our 40s...
Hyung!
Oh, you don't have to call me hyung.
-Oppa!
-Why are you acting like this when you're all old like this?
I'll start the fire.  You slice the squid.
-The squid?
-Yes.
That cold squid?
Then I'll bring the chopping board and the knife for him and that's it.
Okay?
Why are you only doing that?!  There's so much to do after that!
Say it, don't get angry...
Oppa, do that first...
And there will be more work awaiting you.
-Oh, there is?
-Yes, yes.
The first thing Soo Ro oppa needs to do is bring the knife and cutting board.
-Then...
-And Jong Shin oppa...
You'll be getting the ingredients and tools ready for the meat shish-kebab.
We should do that.
-(Jong Shin hyung's) sounds a lot harder.  I should do my part quickly.
-So the ingredients for the shish-kebab first?
Soo Ro, are you betraying me?
So move quickly as we say it nicely.
Hyori's telling me to do it...
The work we have to do...
Don't I start the fire really well?
Wow, it's already like that?
The squid is really cold...
Oppa, stop talking formally with Soo Ro oppa.
Because you're the older one, you have to tell Soo Ro hyung to talk casually so that he actually can.
If we do, that'd be good for me.  And I'd have another 'younger sibling'.
That's right.  We're family.
Soo Ro-ssi, should I just talk casually?
Oh, please do.
Then I'll talk casually.
Please, talk casually.
I can always call you hyung very casually.
Then...
(Tell Soo Ro oppa to cut the squid!!)
Since I have to cut the squid...
Then, can Soo Ro-ssi cut the squid?
(Tell Soo Ro oppa to cut the squid!!)
Still Soo Ro-ssi...
'Can Soo Ro-ssi cut the squid', what is that oppa?!
You have to say, 'Soo Ro, you cut the squid!' like that!
If you see this face from the front, it's hard to speak casually!
Oppa, you have to break open that wall.
-I have to?
-Yes!
Soo Ro, will you handle the squid?
Why is it that as you go, your words diminish?!
Okay, hyung.  I'll do the squid
And since it's the lunar new year...
In celebration of becoming hyung and dongsaeng
Let's just have a hug.
A hug?
You know that... 'Hyung!'
Hyung!
It's kind of worrisome...
Oppa, break the wall!
Oh, okay.
Hyung!
Soo Ro!
-Why don't we go?
-Should we go?
You've been successful now!
Soo Ro-ssi!
-Okay...
-Hyung!
Soo Ro!
'Uh Soo Ro!'  Oppa, what is that!?
Ah, that's nice.  Congratulations!
We've become hyung and dongsaeng.  Please look at us kindly and have a happy new year!
So, in celebration...!
In celebration, dongsaeng should... the squid...
Okay, I'll completely slice up the squid.
Since you're now like this...
And that dish, and take out another one of those...
Wow, you slice it really well.
Hyung, I can do some slicing~
I should have spoken casually earlier.
Oppa, cut the radish.
The radish?
I'll do it, I'll do it.
How could you make hyung do it?
The kids don't understand things like that
[Pleased]
Take this stuff in the middle out.
Soo Ro knows all about that, too!
Why are you interfering in a male's work?
-Hyung!
Hyung!  We need a dish to put the squid in.
-Oh, dish?
-Yes, dish.
A big one?
[Something strange is going on]
That's right, if we want to slice all of these
[For now, the big brother will go find a plate]
I looked really hard
I said to get a big one, not these
Are you raising your voice at me?
No, I'm just saying
That's right
My voice is usually loud to begin with
Of course not. Can you please go look again?
I should?
You should. I'm asking you because you're my big brother. You have that kind of integrity
You're not bossing me around, right?
Don't say such things
[The big brother goes back to the kitchen...]
It's like in the movies. The manly and smart little brother and his weak older brother
Ok I found a big one
[Serving tray?]
[Awkward]
Oppa, this is a serving tray
Big.. I asked you to bring.. a big plate..
Are you clenching your teeth?
I'm not!
It's because I'm cold. Plate... a big one...
I'm not saying this because I'm mad, but you have a short temper
No, no, I'm not angry
Big plate
Oh.
Okay, okay
[Will he be able to bring the right one?]
[After a while...]
Something like this?
[The plate he brings after careful consideration]
That'll do..
You don't like it?
[Forced to accept]
It's fine.  You may bring a cauldron out next..
I'm not sure if it was a good idea to be more comfortable with each other
[Lady Yejin is preparing the skewers]
I just seasoned it with salt. Since we don't have time to make marinade
Like this?
Yeah, to the side
Where do I sit in your oppa ranking?
I think maybe 50th place?
No, I only have (Kim) Jaedong oppa
Oh Jaedong
Ok, then Jaedong is #1.  Who's #2?
Second? Jaesuk oppa
It's Jaesuk?
How about third?
(Shin) Dongyup oppa
Fourth?
Fourth.. This oppa I used to date
Hey!
So you're saying Jaedong tops the guy you used to date?!
Make me fifth
Are you upset?
Oppa, you're fifth
Are you serious?
I beat Jongshin hyung
It's because I got friendlier with her before you
[At this moment]
Chunhee, what do you think you're doing?
Do you guys see this?
Hyori, are you watching?
Wow, you're not using your hands
He does this really well
[A lot of useless talents...]
It's like it's stuck to my head
So you really did split the work between you guys?
We did, we just each did our own thing
Oppa, those two improved on their conversations
Who did?
Those two
Oh, with Jongshin hyung?
Yup, it's a lot better with this kid now
Ahh hyung, really..
[Secretly punishing him]
I like him so much I want to kill him!
[Jongshin hyung can't move]
You said you guys got closer, so why.. why are you doing that?
Because I like him
I can't look at him longer than 3 seconds
Oh you guys are already here!
We picked so many vegetables
You guys did a good job
We're back, hyung
Jaesuk: Welcome back
[The cooking starts after assigning roles]
Daniel oppa will...
Daniel: Oh oppa.. I like it I like it
[The people making the skewers]
Daniel oppa will...
Daniel: Oh oppa.. I like it I like it
[The people making the skewers]
Huh? Oh "oppa"
Daniel: Oh oppa.. I like it I like it
[The people making the skewers]
Huh? Oh "oppa"
Dip it in the batter and hand it to me please
Oppa, you're going to put it in the flour
And then I'll fry it
[Chunhee's messy flour]
[It won't fry if there's too much on it...]
[However it's an organized system]
[Will the food for the town's elders be delicious?]
Mmm, this is good
Wow, that's really good.
Really?! You should eat that in a cool way. Like a commercial
[Even the way he eats...]
How can I when you give me one that's not cooked all the way?!
There's flour all over me
[Daniel tries frying them now...]
Henney's doing a good job
[And so they prepare the food to be given to the town's elders]
[Hyori is preparing the fried squid for the Family]
[How does Hyori's fried squid taste?]
Taste this to see if it's salty or not
Spicy?
[He still can't handle spicy food...]
[The Small Eyed Brothers are preparing the vegetables]
[The Elderly inspecting the taste]
It's good
[Today's main course: Squid Stew]
Are you sure you're supposed to put in soybean paste?
Isn't this too much water?
Yeah, I put in a lot of water
Why?
So we can eat a lot
We have to redeem this soup somehow
Seriously, since squid stew is really yummy
We have a shortcut to rescue the soup
Oh we do, don't we?
But we shouldn't do it for the first week of the new year, huh?
Of course
To tell you the truth, I can't figure out what kind of stew this is
There's no taste of squid
Yeah, it's not there
It doesn't even smell like squid
All I smell are mushrooms
Just put all the fried squid in here
Why?
I think once we put that in the flavor will come out
But I worked so hard on it
Just put it in.  If we can't have the stew, we'll die
Besides we can just make fried squid again
Who will again?
You will
Just enough to bring out the flavor
Ah! No!
You're putting it all in?! No, you can't!
No, we have to save the stew
I think the color is about right now
[Hyori making the fried squid again]
[It's still not right...]
I think we have to use the soup
Yeah, we do
Oppa, how is it?
It doesn't taste good huh?
We just have to cook it a little bit more
[In the end]
[The secret formula]
My eyes are watering
[Throwing in ramen soup before the first week of the new year has passed!]
[Secretly putting it in...]
[Did it save the flavor?]
It didn't work...
[How can it be!]
[Even the ramen soup didn't work!]
[What did they use that made the stew like this...]
Jaesuk hyung!
Does it taste good?
N... No...
Henney.. we're.. we're having a big dilemma right now
Hyori, honestly.. it's not working today
We added everything
What is this? Why is it like this?
We put in onions, and red pepper paste,
and a little bit of soybean paste
Who puts soybean paste in squid stew?!
I told you!
Jongshin: No, it's okay to put soybean paste in
Daniel: Can I try some?
Ah! of course
Henney, seriously usually our cooking...
besides the first episode..
it's usually really good.. but today...
I don't think we've ever had it this bad
Is it making you cry?
Bad?!
Ah, joke joke!
He said 'bed'
Oh to sleep on?
He's just saying he's tired
It doesn't taste good?
This tastes so much better
[The grandmothers on vacation]
[Where they went sightseeing and relaxed at a hot springs resort]
[Creating a new years they cannot forget]
Hey Sooro!
Get the table ready!
[Why is Sooro all of a sudden..?]
That smoke is seriously strong
This wood is...
Hyung! Can you just do it since I can't see?
There's no one else?
Everyone's busy?
Hey, someone give him a hand
The table is as tall as me!
Why did you come out with a wall?
Jongshin hyung gets a Daesang award in the first week of the new year!
It's fortunate that the food came out so well, not ours
But the ones for the town's elders at least came out good
That's right. As long as the food for the elders are good, it's fine, let's just eat the stew
Alright
It's not that we messed up, our standards are just too high
The squid is really good though
[Always the gentleman, Daniel...]
Really?
It's good
Yummy
I think since we let it cook longer it became good
Daniel, you're enjoying the stew
Yeah, I like it
Food tastes so much better when you eat it with friends
[It's coming]
[The passionate model]
[Special runway show]
[The Family put on hanboks]
[The Family's hanbok fashion show]
[Is starting right now]
[Ch. 3: Family Hanbok Fashion Show]
So since it's the Lunar New Year
We went and put on our hanboks
It's been awhile since we've gathered like this
The reason we've gathered in our hanboks is because
Tomorrow morning, we're meeting the town's elders
And greet them and give them the food we made
We'll also accept their well-wishes
So we are wearing hanboks
Hyori: We're doing the New Year's bow, too?
Jaesuk: Ah right!
For now we have to prepare the rice cakes. I went with Daniel and Chunhee to
Hyori: We're doing the New Year's bow, too?
Jongshin: To make the dough
Jaesuk: Yes, so they gave us the dough
And now we just have to prepare it
The hanboks are magnificent
Over there is the Police Captain
Angel of Death
He looks handsome in a hanbok
No it doesn't suit me
The Handsome Angel of Death
If the angel of death looks like this then I should die soon
Jang Yeong-sil, Jang Yeong-sil
[Jang Yeong-sil]
I'm the Alien and he's the Elder
Oh Kim Sooro..
He's looks like a military officer
[Military officer?]
[More like a Fortune Teller]
Excuse me, how will my year be?
You'll get a Daesang again this year
Fortune Teller Sooro
How come Sooroo looks like a fortune teller whenever he wears hanbok
Oh you're wearing a multi colored jacket
[The elegant Lady Yejin]
When we were putting on the hanboks she said to wear one that reflects who we are
So this one is like the manager of a big traditional Korean restaurant
[Traditional Korean restaurant manager?]
You're the restaurant manager then
Let's do a fashion show
Shall we?
Let's do a new year's greeting to our viewers
Hyori: Oh a new year's bow?
Jaesuk: That's right
How do I do it?
Oh yea, Henney doesn't know how
Jaesuk: Really?
I don't really know it well
So we should show him
How about Daesung goes first
Do a walk and then a bow
Daesung!
[The door opens...]
Where's our little Daesung?
[The child groom?]
[Daesung's not here]
[Child groom acting cute explosion]
Hurry up and come out
Now bow to the viewers
Happy New Year
That suited him so well
Did you see?
I saw it, but.. do you go down on your knees first?
- Yea, knees first
- Yea, you have to be on your knees first
What about my hands?
That comes later
[Daniel learning how to do a New Years bow from the Family]
After your knees
Shall we see the Police Captain next?
Cue!
[Family Hanbok Fashion Show, Police Captain's turn]
[The Police Captain taking control before his appearance]
[Threatening]
Why is he looking at me?
[Is he going to a fight...]
Did you think about this before coming out?
It's too scary!
I was trying to look like I was checking out a scene
Oppa, you should have a soft face for the new year
Ok, one more time.
Police Captain, cue!
[Tender expression...]
[Happy]
It's different, it's different
[Taking what they said and changing his expression]
[The benevolent Police Captain runway walk]
[Even throwing in a shy hand gesture]
[But]
[He goes right into boxing]
[A police captain in shape...]
[Formal when bowing]
How about Henney tries now
[Unexpected]
You try now.
Are you ready?
[At last.. the door.. opens]
[Looking at any angle]
[His standing body fits into any photo shoot]
[Admiration]
[Cheering]
[Wild enthusiasm]
[His charisma overwhelms the onlookers]
[His intense stare]
[What about the runway walk?]
[Wherever he walks,]
[it becomes a catwalk!]
[It really feels like a fashion show runway]
[Flawless walk]
This is it, this is it!
This was what I wanted!
[Happy New Years]
[What about the bow Daniel learned?]
[His butt...]
[However, for his first new years bow, he passes]
It still looked cool
Oppa do it fast while the feeling is still alive!
Do you think I can?
Oppa, you remember this part?
[The door opens!]
[Curious]
[Huh??]
[The pose is the same...]
[But he can't capture the feel in his expression...]
[Oh no]
[Sorry to have to compare...]
[Polar opposites]
I really hate looking at his face!
Who said that?!
[They all felt the same way]
Oppa try again, but do it better
[For now the atmosphere feels right]
[But...]
[The moment he grabs the beam]
What is that?
[Lewd Confucianist]
Hyori ah~ What was lewd about that?
Daesung, was I being lewd?
Right when you got here you were like...
I didn't even open my mouth though
[Third try!]
[Serious]
[Even trying to hold back his laughs...]
Oppa, take a deep breath!
You have to walk, too
[Will he be able to pass this time?]
Okay
[The lewd Confucianist]
Just come back now
[Last bow...]
Sooro: Even that's funny
I really wasn't trying to be funny about that!
I learned a funny one from (Shim) Hyung-rae hyung
Where you do something like this
Or this
Hey! That's the one I wanted to do!
That's how (Kim) Jung-ryul bows
I wanted to do this
The PD wants us to back up a little
I guess he hates looking at my face, too
Next up, Sooro hyung, cue!
[A grand entrance!]
[This walk...]
[That person is here!]
[Fortune teller Sooro]
Everyone, have a happy new years!
[The Family excited at Fortune teller Sooro's arrival]
It's a happy event, something to celebrate!
Happy new years!
This time, let's have Yejin
It seems like a historical drama will match Lady Yejin
So can you do it like a historical drama when you do your bow?
Why isn't there anyone here?
Yes, my lady
[The graceful lady from a respected family]
[Lady Yejin...]
[Taking light, careful steps as if walking on flowers]
She doesn't want to get married but has to go
[Immediately starts sniffling~]
Young master~
She's in love with the husband's brother!
But she's in an arranged marriage
[I'll keep my beloved in my heart...]
[Lady Yejin... spins...]
You have to bow to your in-laws
Her mood is sad now
Happy new years
She's got a grace to her
Happy new years!
She's lost her mind a little!
It's Hyori's turn right now
She's the madam of the house, but a lonely one.
[Can't believe it...]
She's really pretty, but very lonely
[She all of a sudden became alone]
[The madam of a rich house...]
Ok, lonely madam!
[Unrivaled beauty... lonely madam...]
[The deepening winter night]
[The piercing lonlieness...]
Why do you keep rubbing your belly?
Because she's full
She just came out after finishing eating...
[Taking off her clothes like no one's there...]
[But it's too cold...]
[Came out to take her jacket for her...]
All of a sudden, one man comes to her house
There is just one man who only loves you~
What brings you here at this time?
My role seems to be getting bigger...
[The Lonely Madam and the Police Captain?]
At this time of night...
[Confused]
Oh, it's hot
Will these two marry?
Mother, Father...
Happy New Years
[The Awkward Couple have gotten close enough to bow together]
Hyori is greeting the parents of the household
And I'm holding the jacket
I can play it cool
This is expensive...
I'm the King's undercover agent!
[Last up, Jongshin!]
Now, Yoon Jongshin.  Please step inside
I'm going to do it like a play
- Okay, do you need anything?
- I'm going to do it with Park Yejin
PD: Tape change
[Why is it whenever the Elder has to do something]
At this time, the tape has run out
and Yoon Jongshin is left confused
The PD says 'let's stop filming!'
[After editing... the sad story continues...]
Lately there's been that thing where Yejin and Chunhee sing together
Yea, the Jingle Bells
Can you do the Jingle Bells?
- We'll do a new years version
- That sounds good
[They spin around like a child...]
[Forever couple]
How about the madam?
Child groom!
How about with Daniel?
Straighten out your legs
Like this?
- No, straighten out
- Oh, like this
When do I cry?
We first look at each other
1, 2, 3, 4
And then you cry
Like this
[Bashful]
You're getting too close...
(What'd I do?)
I'm just trying to do it real
Try it again, and start
[The tender child groom, Daniel]
[Is he really crying...]
[The highlight of child groom, face to face]
[Everyone watching is embarrassed...]
Get up, get up
Oppa, I felt good...
I know, I know
I felt good after seeing his face so close
I know.
Now we have FO's 40 brothers
The 40 brothers will now do the same thing
Sooro's the child?
I'm younger than you!
[The 40 year old child groom]
[The 41 year old, old bride]
[The strong child groom]
[The 40 brothers are playing well...]
[The child groom highlight!]
[Crawling?]
What are you doing?!
You're 40 years old!
This is fun, this is fun!
[The winter night deepens...]
[Starting to prepare the rice cakes!]
We're making this for all the elders
So do it well
Since forming Family Outing, we've spent Thanksgiving and New Years together
[Thinking of the elders who will be eating their rice cake soup]
[Working with a sincere deep heart]
[The youngest, Daesung]
[Daniel doing it for the first time...]
I forgot about getting new years money from Jongshin oppa
We should all do the new years bow to Jongshin hyung tomorrow
I don't even have a penny!
[Talking merrily while cutting the rice cakes]
[The mountain of rice cakes]
Korean citizens, have a happy new year!
[We wish you all a happy new year from Family Outing]