-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-   Proudly Presents
-=http://ytet.org=- Sync:有志青年
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Uh, can-Can we squeeze in here?
- Oh, perfect.
- Thanks.
Do you realize this is the
first time all three of us
have been in a relationship
at the same time?
Yeah, they're gonna need to
get a bigger couch in here.
Or maybe you can just
get a smaller ex-husband.
Hey, who's that girl mark's
talking to at the bar?
Her name's katie.They've been together
non-stop for the past couple days.
- He's really into her.
- Aww. Mark thinks he's people.
- The last two days have been fun.
- I know. So fun.
- I really like you.
- Me too.
I wish I liked you just a little more.
- Excuse me?
- I know.I'm so bummed.
Well, maybe I should go.
You should definitely go.
Well, at least we can always
count on mark to be single.
- Dude, what happened?
- You know what they say.
If you're not sure in 48
hours,you gotta pull the rip cord.
Is "they" you, pauly d,and
the situation,by any chance?
No.
- You ever heard of mastersofpsychology.net?
- Nope.
Because a guy who's written for them
coined the term "48 hour rule" on his vlog.
He says you know in 48 hours
if someone is right for you,
and if you don't,you're just talking
yourself into it for the hot monkey sex.
And those are his words,not mine.
The 48 hour rule was
true with me and whitney.
No.It took me way longer.
- No way. It was, like,exactly 48 hours.
- You're remembering it wrong.
How do you know? You were bombed.
I was not bombed, okay? She was bombed.
Oh, no, I was more high than bombed.
- I was sober.
- I was drunk.
I hadn't met you guys yet,but I
know what night you're talking about.
- wake up!All right.
Okay. Oh, I'm plowed.
You know, this may be
the beer goggles talking,
but I think we are the
cutest chicks in here.
- I mean, we are the only chicks in here.
- Yeah.
This makes me feel like
we're missing a sale.
Hey. There is nothing to worry about.
We are single ladies in 2008,
and we don't need a thing.
I need some tequila. I'm shaking.
Oh, roxanne's coming over here.Be nice.
What? I like roxanne.We just
don't have that much in common.
It's like,she doesn't really
drink.She's always all over lance.
I just don't know how to deal with girls who
are defined by their relationship, you know?
Shoot me if I'm ever like that, okay?
- Hey, you guys.
- Hi.
Thank you so much for coming.
Hi, roxanne. Happy birthday, lance.
Oh, thanks, but isn't every day
we don't die a happy new birth day?
Man, it's been forever
since I've seen you guys.
But I'll have more free time now,
since hillary lost the nomination
and our phone bank closed.
I can't believe our next president
could be the only black guy
in chicago lily hasn't slept with.
Still got five months.
Oh, no.
Well, we found where
chicago keeps all its dudes.
Yeah, really.The prettiest
girl in here is that asian guy.
All right, well,let's go get a
drink,and then we'll head out.
Just text that girl karen.She
has some cute friends.
No, I don't want to text
karen.She's so boring.
She doesn't have any opinions,and
she never has anything to say.
Yeah, definitely don't
text the perfect woman.
- Seriously?You're not gonna let me in?
- Not without i.d.
Uh, I left it at my office,where I work,
'cause I'm 30 years old.
But why do you still
dress like a nine-year-old?
- Wake up!Okay
- Okay.All right.
- I'm up.
- Think I'll have that cigarette.
- Okay.
Be so much easier if you
could just snort cigarettes.
Hey, check it out. There's a girl.
I think we've struck bronze.
Yeah, well,there's one of her,and there's
two of us,so how should we play this?
I don't know.She should
probably be in the middle.
Okay, well, first of all,
"probably"?
Hi. Guess I'm gonna go find that asian guy. i'm talking
about we should rock, paper, scissors for her. Second of all,
Okay, here we go.
- Listen, I never do this,but-
- oh, god, please stop.
Every time a guy says, "i never
do this,"he always does this.
- Really?
- Yes.
Because what I was gonna
say is,I never do this,
but I could tell all the way from the other
end of the bar that your personality sucks.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Oh, okay.
- Someone read the game.
- oh, yeah, no,I read the game,
but you're only supposed
to use those moves
for girls that you're
actually attracted to.
Yeah.
No, you're supposed to
have a comeback for that.
Okay, why don't you come back
as someone I'd be interested in?
That answers my question on what you're
doing alone in a bar full of guys.
You know what? I'm just gonna-
Hey, are you bipolar?
Are you bisexual?
Well, I am attracted to you.
Okay, I'm leaving.
Are you coming?
Ooh, she's playing hard to get.
You know, we're not even choosing
to talk to each other right now.
Our bodies chose for us.
It's millions of years of evolution.Are
you familiar with pheromones?
White guys, man.
'scuse me.
Sorry.
Weirdo.
Okay, uh...
This is a copy of my birth certificate.
Can I please go in now?
No.Now you just want it too much.
That guy.
Morning, whitney.
Morning...
you.
You know what? I really
have to get to work.
The boss is kind of a stickler, so-
you're a freelance
photographer, whitney.
You showed me a billboard
you did last night.
It was right after you got into
an argument with a parking meter.
Look, um, I never do this, so-
First of all, when a girl says she
never does this,she always does this.
Second of all,I actually don't
have many one-night stands either.
Oh, no, no, no, one-night
stands are, like, my jam.
I normally, um,never sleep
over.So I'm just gonna-
Oh, well, great.go.
Okay.
What, now you have dignity?
Look, dude.Here's the thing.
- I just,
um- - Dude?
You don't even know my name,do you?
Okay, I'm sorry. I forgot.
I'm sure you said it, like,
ten times last night, but-
Yeah, you know, you
said it a few times, too.
Your name is slow down?
Okay, look, I'm sorry.It's just that,
I just got out of something,and I
really need to workn on myself right now.
Okay.
I'm serious.I just,
- I could really see
myself- - Falling for me?
And you don't want to
take things too seriously?
You know what? It's okay.
You don't have to do this.
You don't ever have to
justify casual sex to a dude.
Great! Okay.
Okay, great. Perfect.
We don't have to pretend
this is more than it is.
- sometimes sex is just sex.
- Totally.
So what do I owe you?
I'm so glad we're hanging out.
We never get to have one-on-one
girl time.I mean, without whitney.
I usually only see you
when you're out... Partying.
So...what else do you like to do?
Uh, mushrooms.
Yeah, I love to do mushrooms and...
Oh. Oh, oh. Okay.
See, I was, um, I was thinking more
along the lines of rock climbing.
Oh, no, rock climbing on
mushrooms would be super-dangerous.
What do you like to do?
She likes making jewelry,meditating,and
dancing in my dreams.
Hey!
Didn't know lance was coming.
- For a girls' night.
- Just pretend I'm not here.
Yeah, you know what?Lance is
basically one of the girls anyway.
So tell me about this idea
you had for a food blog.
Oh, well, I have a very
sophisticated palate,
and I failed out of college, so...
Uh, can I get a shot?
And a shotgun.
Alex, do you remember
when you were like,
"i'll have a small
strawberry banana smoothie,"
and I was like,"do you want
a free boost with that...
Like my phone number?"
you remember that?
yeah.Well, it was two
days ago at jamba juice.
Are you mad at me?
No. Why would I be mad at you?
I'm just-I'm just being weird because
you didn't notice my new haircut.
Well, that's because we only met
once,and you were wearing a visor.
Excuse me.These drinks are
compliments of the lady over there.
Okay.
A beer for you.
And a shirley temple for the lady.
She wasn't sure that your
friend was of legal drinking age.
Unbelievable.
Who is he?Is he in a band?
Are they better than my band?
Does he have any weed?
Honestly, I don't even know his name.
This basket of bread is compliments
of the gentleman over there.
He said he was worried you may have
traded all your food for heroine.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Hey, hey, hey.
that was really cute what you
did back there with the drinks.
Thanks for the fight.
I'm sorry.I didn't mean to cause a
rift between you and your daughter.
Do you have her for the whole weekend?
- I met her two days
ago. - At build-a-bear?
- Come on, she's 26.
- Okay, I'm 26.
She looks ten years younger than me.
You know, I'm not quite
sure who you're insulting.
So I'm more clear:you need to
get some product for that hair,
because you look like courtney cox.
No, no, no.Clean hair, fresh
shave.That's like my thing.
Well, you should probably
get back to your date.
She probably needs you
to cut up her hot dog.
Well, you should probably get
back to your date.He's dead.
- Your date is terrible.
- Your date is the worst.
Hey, what the hell?
Oh, you know what?I
- I can't.
- Hey, my name is alex.
- Okay, great.
- hello?
- Hey.
I just got your message.You
had sex in the bathroom?
Yeah.
- When are you gonna see her again?
- I don't know.I haven't called her.
You don't call her, i'm gonna call her.
No-no, I don't have her number.
Oh, well, did you get a last name?
No.
I mean,she said it was cummings,but
that's obviously a joke.
You had sex in the men's bathroom?
Thank god your feet
never touched the ground.
Oh, my gosh.This is so exciting.
You know what?I'm gonna
have a second drink.
Oh, my god. He texted me.
How did he even get my number?
What's it say?
"I miss you."
This guy does not get me.
"my penis wrote that."
He totally gets you.
- Text him back.
- No, no.
Come-Admit it.You like this guy.
Okay, fine.I like him, okay?
He's really funny and super smart
and totally calls me out on my crap.
But I am not dumb enough to think that I
could have something real with him,okay?
I mean, what kind of person
leaves their date in a restaurant
to go have sex with
someone in a bathroom?
- You.
- Okay.
Yeah,and I'm a terrible person.Okay?
I mean,he's a random hookup,and
he's obviously a player.
But he tracked you down.
I mean, this guy could
be your soul mate.
Come on.Don't you believe
in fate?Or destiny?
Hey, I do not believe
in fate or destiny, okay?
Fate and destiny are names of strippers
who wind up being identified
by their dental records.
Okay, our waitress clearly
quit.I'm gonna go get us drinks.
Classic whitney.
Every time she likes a
guy,she pushes him away.
- I knew she wouldn't text him back.
- Oh, she's texting him back.
Okay, but if you want to sound like
her,it has to be something sexual.
Okay, uh...
I feel like I'm cheating on lance.
For god's sakes, give it to me.
"da da da-da da, from behind." send.
Okay, you guys, seriously,
let's go.This place is dead.
No! Dead? Are-are you kidding?
I mean, did you even notice?
Look, there's word
jumbles on the napkins.
Yeah, plus,i'm so
drunk I can't even move.
I just need to sit-
Okay, we can go.
- Hey.
- Hi.
What are you doing here?
Well, I-I got your text.
- My text?
- Yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna kill them.
I did not text you.They texted you.
So,
Well, uh...
I'm here now. Do you wanna go hang out?
Okay, you think you can just say the
word,and I'm gonna have sex with you again?
Well, no.
I mean, yeah, that
would probably work, but-
And your friends made some
pretty big promises on that text,
but-I- I'm saying that we could go
somewhere else and-and just hang out.
Okay, alex.You seem like
a very nice guy, alex.
Alex. I
- Look, I know you know my name.
But you-You're being an idiot.There's
obviously something here.
- Like what?
- Most girls I date are boring.
And, you know, you surprise me.
Mostly it's the bad kind of
surprise, yeah, sure.Of course.
But it's still a surprise.
And you know what?I
don't know how this ends.
I'm sorry, but I just don't
want a relationship.Okay?
I am on my own.And I
like it that way.So,
All right, tough guy.
You think you're tough
'cause you got sneakers.
What are you doing?
Are you-are you choking?
Everybody give us some room.Give
us some room. Here, here we go.
- Okay, I'm okay.
- One, two, three.
- I'm fine.
- Come on, shut up.Breathe!
It's-i'm fine!
It was an ice cube.It melted.
- I'm fine.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Yeah, you're welcome.
You just tried to save me. That's...
No guy I've ever dated
would've done that.
What kind of guys have you been dating?
I told lance he was not allowed to come.
Just us girls.
Am I drunk? 'cause if I am, I like it.
You've had two drinks.It
gets way better.
Oh, we should order jaeger bombs.
You know, 'cause we still
haven't seen each other naked.
Wha-oh, okay.
hang on. That's lance.
You know what?I'll just
let it go to voicemail.
Hey, I'm sorry,
you know, that I get annoyed
you're always with lance.
I
- I think maybe i'm just jealous.
You guys seem like the perfect couple,
and sometimes I just wish
I could meet the right guy.
OPEN
lance and I are not the
perfect couple.We fight a lot.
I know it seems like
we don't, but... We do.
Yeah, but that
- That's okay.
I mean, everyone fights.
Just makes you normal.
Yeah, no, yeah. You're right.
we're probably just going
through a tough time.
You see, this is good.
This is why we have girl
time.So we can open up.
Yeah, we thought that
having a baby might solve it,
but we just have not been
able to get pregnant, you know.
The doctor thinks I might
have a tipped uterus, so.
Wow, okay. Throwing it wide open.
You know, I'm kind of
disappointed in you.
It's predictable and not surprising at all
to sleep with a guy that saved your life.
Okay, you did not save my
life,and I'm not gonna sleep.
- hold on.You're not gonna spend the night?
- No. That's not my thing.
It's not your thing.Got it.
Look, uh, hey.
I think you should go.
Excuse me?
Yeah, if you're not gonna spend the
night,then I think you should go.
Okay.You're not gonna sleep with me?
Nuh-uh.Bye-bye.
Okay, what game is this? 'cause
I will play,and I will win.
I just need to know the rules.
Look, it's not a game.I don't
want to play a game with you.
I like you, okay?
The whole thing where we hook up
and then you leave,I do that too.
But I don't want to do
that with you, all right?
Trust me, I can get a much less exhausting
version of that with other girls.
Okay, well, so I'm
just gonna sleep here?
No, you're gonna sleep here, all right?
'cause I sleep here.
And if you're still here in the
morning, then this is happening,okay?
So good night.
And hopefully, you're
here in the morning.
Okay, I know what this game is.
It's not a game. Shut up. Go to sleep.
Ha, ha. You're my girlfriend.
Three years later, and we're still here.
I guess you have to admit
mark's 48 hour rule is true.
Okay, I liked you,but it wasn't
until 3:00 in the morning,
so technically, that's 53 hours.
Oh, I guess we should just call
it, then.it's probably for the best.
It's been a long time
since you surprised me.
That was a surprise.
You know what would surprise me
would be if you cleaned it up.
Okay, fine. I'll give you a real one.
Something I've never told you before
is the morning after I saw you
at the restaurant,I looked you up.
I knew it.You were into me from day two.
You insulted me,you had sex with me
in a bathroom,and you told me to leave.
I mean, i'm only human.
Whitney
S1 Ep16