For most of human history, the only light we knew came from the sky
By day, the Sun
By night, an uncountable number of stars
From the beginning, our ancestors believe that Sun and stars were heavenly out of this world
And there were right
We have been watching the sky for thousands of years
But until recently, we couldn
t see well enough to understand our connection to the cosmos
But now, our astronomical vision has sharpened
We can see farther and clearer
We can observe object that are invisible to human eyes
Our increasingly improving vision has allowed us to make great discoveries
revealing an astonishing and wonderful universe
What follows are 13 of the greatest discoveries in astronomy
:
CHD
The Planets Move
Our first great discovery happened over centuries
As the first human looked carefully into sky in places like this
The empty cloudless deserts of the American southwest, the Middle East, Africa, and South America
Of these ancient astronomers, the most important were the Mesopotamians
They consider the objects in the sky gods
And build giant tower so they can record the rising and setting of the Sun, the moon, and the stars
For more than a thousand years, they use clay tablet to record what they saw
To find out more, I paid a visit to  professor of astronomy Owen Gingerich
Here for example, is one of these clay tablets
And have a read
,
Oh
Yes
These guys, there people wrote small
-
,
Yes
Yes, I was perfectly amazed if somebody came into my office and picked it up and actually started reading it
-So what language is this
En
I think this is in Babylonian
Hundreds of these tablets were unburied
Among these hundreds of tablets is a tablet called the Venus tablet of Ammisaduqa
And this tablet contains the motion of the planet Venus
That
s the earliest record we have of a planet moving
After the Mesopotamians made the fist records, it was the Greeks who took the next step
Some of the Greek astronomers made a field trip out to Mesopotamia to find out what had been going on there
And they seemed to brought
bring
back some systematical records
So, it ultimately gave the basis for making a mathematical theory of the motion of the planets
--
From their observations, the Greeks developed the vision of the solar system that would stand for some 2000 years
that the planets move revolving around the earth
It will take our next great discovery to set the record straight
The Earth Moves
The year is 1543
A seventy-year-old man is dying
-
His name
Nicolaus Copernicus
A doctor and a lawyer by trade,
but nearly for nearly 40 years he was also an amateur astronomer
A pursue that had let him to challenge one of the most fundamental and sacred believes of his time
As a young man, Copernicus had studied the heavens
and found that the Greek
s earth center system failed when it came to predicting planetary motion
He began to wonder if the earth itself moved,but
Here is Copernicus
s idea
-
With the Sun at the center
And now suddenly, all the planet are going always the same way around
they are not stop
Copernicus realized that the movements of the planet were better explained if the Sun were the center of the solar system
And the earth circled it like an ordinary planet
It was a revolutionary insight
Despite any evidence that the earth was moving,
,
he came up with this book, which gives his new theory
This idea, this, this book changed the world
,
Yes, because it made the earth a planet and it fixed the Sun in the center
If you don
t have that blueprint you don
t march ahead to the physics, the physics of the cosmos
As it happened, the final pages,
which were just these here in the front of the book came to him on the very day he died
,
I suspect, I mean, he was lying there partially paralyzed from a stroke
he was probably just hanging in there until he could make it sure that it was done
Planetary Orbits are Elliptical
Everyone from the Greeks to Copernicus assumed the orbits of the planet had to be circular
But in 1571, German mathematician Johannes Kepler
shattered that assumption with our next great discovery
,
Lacking calculus, Kepler improvised ways to compute circular orbit of mars
The work was tedious
,
Kepler wrote that he was almost driven to madness considering in calculating the matter
His calculations began to reveal that the accepted notion of planet moving in circles simply did not work
Then a new idea came to him
Kepler realized somehow the Sun had to be driving the planet in some way he didn
t fully understand
And to get a self-consistent picture, he found that an ellipse was the path rather than a circle
With this breakthrough, Kepler devised the first method
for accurately predicting the movement of the planet and  stars across the sky
When his tables predicted the planet Mercury to pass across the front of the Sun
And nobody else
s tables were close
That was dramatical proof of the accuracy of his astronomy
They linked the motions of the planets solidly to the Sun
This was a very important point to helps stress the idea that the Copernicus
s Sun-centered system really had physical significance
Despite the success of Kepler
s theory, many remain skeptical that the Sun could be the center of the Solar System
But the final nail in that coffin was about to be driven home by a man who like Kepler
prefer to use observational evidences to form his theories
-
And that man was Galileo Galilei
Jupiter has Moons
,
Meet Galileo Galilei, a man determined to pursue truth no matter where it led
In the case of our next great discovery,
his determination led him to revolutionize our knowledge of the solar system
,
The year is 1609 and Galileo was fascinated with the new invention called a telescope
Essentially, that was a toy out of a carnival
When Galileo heard about it, he went to work, making one
He ferfected it and essentially converted the toy into a scientific instrument
Galileo turned his telescope skyward
and was the first to see the mountains on the moon
And the star clusters of the Milky Way
Then an extraordinary sight
A group of 4 small bright stars arranged around the planet Jupiter
We have the manuscript of his first week of observations
And it was wonderful
because you see him gradually coming to the conclusion
That these little stars are carried along with Jupiter
This was the moment of discovery
Galileo realized that the stars were actually four moons orbiting Jupiter
He had the insight that these moving dots were orbiting a planet
And I sometime say he invented the satellite
,
And you say, wait a minute, they were there, how could he even invent them
He invented the idea that they were going around the planet
Here was proof that Copernicus was right about the structure of solar system
If moons could orbit Jupiter, and the earth could orbit the Sun
And Galileo
s discovery demonstrated that
knowledge in astronomy can only be advanced by actual observation
A theory can only be viable when it supported by the facts
Just like our next great discovery
Halley
s Comet
For centuries, comets had been considered harbingers of evil
By the end of the middle ages, comet
s appearance invoked fear and terror
,
But the renaissance scientist Edmond Halley, like Galileo was interested in facts, not superstition
In 1695, he began searching for records of ancient and recent comet sightings
He found 24 comets whose passages across the sky have been recorded with enough detail to allow him to roughly plot their orbits
,
To his surprise, he found that three of the comets seem to follow the same approximate orbit
Circling the Sun every 76 years
On that basis, he figured, ok, this is a comet that is going to be back in another 76 years
-
He figured out the three comets were actually the same comet
The same comet
Halley was so certain of the comet orbit that he made a bold prediction
He said the comet would return in year 1758
-
And guess what
It was
The comet came back
Unfortunately, Halley was no longer live to see his discovery
Since then, Halley
s Comet, as is known, has been greeted 3 more times by excited sky watchers across the globe
,
No longer a harbinger of evil, Halley
s Comet became a milestone discovery in history of astronomy
,
replacing a superstition belief with the rational scientific understanding of the physical universe
Milky Way a Disk of Stars
In the eighteenth century, William Herschel was a classically trained musician
whose love of astronomy let him to give up music and turn his attention to the heavens
This is setting stage for our next great discovery
When he discovered the price of refracting telescope,which was beyond his meet
He decided to make his own
And he became the most fabulous and successful telescope builder of that period
He used his telescope to methodically  survey the sky, cataloging what he saw
As he was searching the sky, he came across an object that looked a little bit different,
turned out to be a new planet
--
Oh, wow, and what planet was that
,
That was the next planet beyond Saturn
The planet Uranus
,
Uranus was the first new planet to be identified in more than 3500 years
But finding a new planet was nothing compared to Herschel
s larger goal
,
And then divided the sky into equal sections, and began to systematically count the stars in each field
It was a painstaking, monumental task
Slowly, Herschel
s star count began to reveal something extraordinary
The Milky Way was much larger than anyone knew
It was a gigantic disk of stars
Some of its field were jam-packed
One showed more than a quarter of a million stars alone
Other fields, farther away, were practically empty
Herschel
s discovery was a revelation
This is a reasonable model of the Milky Way as we know it now
--
But Herschel was only work at an area about this big, is that right
What Herschel was seeing, was a small range like this, maybe that big
So was really a small part of the entire milky way
But even that small part significantly changed the study of astronomy
Herschel
s discovery revealed that our solar system was just an island in a deep and expansive universe
General Relativity
Thanks to the musing of an obscure clerk worked in the Swiss patent office
Our next great discovery revealed that the universe is a strange, mysterious place
-
That clerk was Albert Einstein
In the early 19 hundreds, he was puzzled, along with the rest scientific community
by the orbit of the planet Mercury
Despite the ability of Newton
s laws of gravity to precisely predict the motion of the planets
The laws failed when it came to correctly predicting Mercury
s orbit
The puzzle had to do with Mercury
s perihelion
that point of its orbit which is closest to the Sun
Every century Mercury
s perihelion advance slightly
A change that Newton
s equations could not account for
In the bold and startling move, young Einstein proposed his own theory to explain
the puzzle of Mercury
s orbit
and in the process developed a theory that refined the Newton
s law of gravity
Michio Kaku is the theoretical physicist at the City University of New York
And Newton says that gravity travels instantaneously through around space
And that
s what Einstein thought there was a weakness in Newton
s theory
He wanted the theory that could explain gravity
he wanted the theory that could explain acceleration, zigzag and circular motion
There has to be waves, gravity waves
It takes time for gravity to work its magic
--
To propagate
So if the Sun disappears, it will take 8 minutes for us to know about that fact
even gravity travels at this speed of light
Einstein needed a new picture to explain that and that picture was curved space
that space itself has curved
And that
s why objects move
Einstein believed that his concept of curved space was responsible for shifting mercury
s orbit
Einstein called his idea the theory of general relativity
Imagine a trampling net and place a bowling ball in the middle of the trampling net
The bowling sinks into the trampling net
And now shoot a marble, a marble around the trampling net
The marble will orbit, orbit around the bowling ball
Now, from a distance looking down, Newton would say that there is a force and instantaneous invisible force puling,
pulling the marble down to the bowling ball
But Einstein would say that
s no force, there
s no pull
It
s just a trampling net
And why is the marble orbiting the around the bowling ball
Because the trampling net is pushing the marble
,
Therefore why I am sitting on this chair
Not because gravity pulls you to the ground
It
s because space pushes me down toward the planet Earth
The idea that space itself is worked by mass was too strange for many to accept
An approaching solar eclipse gave scientists the perfect opportunity to put Einstein
s new theory to the test
Photographs were taken of the background stars before the eclipse and then afterward
These pictures were then compared with the photos taken during the eclipse
The photo show that the positions of the stars in the eclipse photo shifted slightly inward
,
bending is the lights from the stars passed the Sun
s gravitational field
Einstein
s theory of general relativity was right
His great discovery rocked the world
General relativity strikes deep emotional core and anyone who
s ever looked these equations
These equations are one inch long
and they answer these eternal question that dogged us
:
ever since we first look into the sky and ask ourselves the question what it all means
The Universe is expanding
General relativity had showed that the space was weirder than anyone could imagine
,
anyone but Einstein that is
To gain a clearer understanding of the strange universe, astronomers needed more observational data
And that required larger more powerful telescopes
Like the one that led to our next great discovery
When the Herschels had finished his survey of heavens in the 1830s
They cataloged thousands of these beautiful but hazy objects then called white nebulae
At the time, no one knew whether they were part of our galaxy
or distant island universe like the Milky Way
In 1924, astronomer Edwin Hubble was studying the stars in several white nebulae
using 100-inch reflected telescope at the Mount Wilson Observatory in California
The telescope enabled Hubble to estimate that the galaxy were routinely many hundreds of thousands, even millions of light years away
Here were objects as huge and populated with stars as our very own Milky Way galaxy, which is why we today call white nebulae galaxies
The more Hubble studied these galaxies, the more he became intrigued
At the time, scientists knew that the beam of light from the star appears as different color on a spectrum
The color changed according to the motion of the star
A shift toward blue on the spectrum meant the star was moving closer to the earth
A red shift meant it was moving away
The amount of the color shift also revealed the speed of that movement
Hubble found when he measured the distance of the galaxy, its spectrum almost always was shifting to the red
And something else, the farther the distance, the greater the red shift
In other words, the universe was expanding
It was an astonishing discovery with profound implications
Measuring backwards from the expansion, scientists found that the universe appeared to have a cataclysmic beginning
where one of the astronomers labeled the big bang
Milky Way Emits Radio Waves
Just three years after Hubble discovered the expanding universe,
our next great discovery revealed a mysterious object hidden behind the dust at the center of the Milky Way
And gave birth to a whole new branch of astronomy, using wave length invisible to the human eye
-
In 1930, Karl Jansky was a 25-year-old physicist
working for the bell laboratories in Holmdel, New Jersey
Jansky
s job was to identify the kinds of interference occurring at the 15 meter wave length
then used for ship-to-shore and transatlantic communication
After spending more than a year recording data, Jansky decided there were three forms of static at this frequency
The first was clearly produced in the earth
s ionosphere
The second was caused by local thunderstorms
And the third signal was mysterious, continuous
It was coming from what appeared first to be, the Sun
Each morning, this signal slowly rose with the Sun
During the day, it rotated across the sky
And then it set when the Sun did
But as time passed, Jansky found that the mysterious radio signals slowly drifted away from the Sun
as if it were coming from a point outside the solar system
Eventually, Jansky pinpointed this location somewhere in the region of the constellation Sagittarius
He believed he had discovered unknown interstellar object at the center of the galaxy
And he was right
Later astronomers confirmed that Jansky had discovered a super massive black hole
Equal a mass to three million Suns
Perhaps even more significant, he was the first human to look at the universe using radio astronomy
A whole new way to study the sky
It was a landmark discovery
Jansky has proved that the sky does not merely sparkle with the gentle glow of the star light
Hidden out there are many strange objects, many light years away
that actually radiate more energy than whole galaxies
Like quasars and pulsars, dead stars spinning madly with masses
that are so dense that single teaspoon would weigh millions of tons
Before astronomers could even begin understand the life and death of stars
New telescope would have to be built that we can look at the sky in many different wave lenghs
Before that could happened though, radio astronomy produced another great discovery,
that, although predicted, was as unexpected by discoverer as Jansky
s has been
And once again, it happened in bell lab that Holmdel in new jersey
Cosmic Microwave Background Radiation
In 1964, bell labs had the spare 200-foot-microwave antenna sitting dormant
Rather than destroyed it, the lab decided to let the astronomers use it for research
Two physicists, 31-year-old Arno Penzias and 28-year-old Robert Wilson
decided to use the antenna for measuring the temperature of the gas halo surrounding the Milky Way galaxy
What happened next is one of the most exciting discoveries in modern astronomy
-
Hello bill
Doc
Wilson
And I came to bell labs to get the story first-hand from Robber Wilson himself
Two of us, Arno Penzias and I, had just come to bell lab from graduate school
And we were going to measure radiation from the Milky Way
And that
s was this antenna really fit in because we could reject the radiation from the earth
And what was left is what
s coming from the sky
There are only getting about two degrees from the earth
s atmosphere
Maybe picked up one degree from the walls of this thing
But , when we first turned it on, it was about twice
that about seven degrees
And this wasn
t right
Something from the earth must be on our instrumentation
We have crossed around a hill here and overlooked New York City
We had the ideal instrument for checking on that though
We merely turned down horizon, scanned the horizon and, but pore nothing particular extra
There was a pair of pigeon that lived here, and of course it was covered with like pigeon droppings
So, we thought well, maybe the pigeon droppings are doing more than we think
Arno and I got up in here and we cleaned all the pigeon droppings out
-
You got to get rid of pigeons
What had you do with pigeons
Fist, we put them in the company mail and sent them as far as we could which was Whippany, New Jersey, to a pigeon fans there
who said these are junk pigeons and let them go
-
A couple of days they were back
-40
40 miles away and they came back
So then our technician brought out a shot gun
And how did that work
I wasn
t here and I didn
t see
But basically it didn
t solve our problem
We still have an extra three or four degrees
We were really being into perplexed
Because we believed in physics,
it
s coming from somewhere
We can calculate what the horn was doing except for this ex-noise
At the time that Penzias and Wilson detected the radio static
there are two competing theories about the origin of the universe
There was the big bang theory which Hubble
s expanding universe supported
And there was the steady state theory, which propose that universe is timeless with no beginning or end,
expanding forever
When a friend heard what Penzias and Wilson had found
he suggested they get in touch with some cosmologists at Princeton University who advocates the big bang theory
They believed that the big bang would have left a faint thermal afterglow explode in the universe,
traces of heat from the roaring of the bang itself, detectable across the entire sky
And they were about to conduct research in hopes of measuring that afterglow
We invited them over
They came over and looked what we had done
and immediately agreed that we had measured what they were setting out to do
So what is your discovery mean
It means that we live in a big bang universe
And we are seeing the radiation from three hundred thousand years after the big bang
Many cases when there is a paradigm shift of science, it takes a generation before people really accept it
But in this case, I think the world is ready for it
Human societies have always worried about where they came from
There are religious stories in every civilization that has ever been found
And I think we have the definitive answer
that we came out of big bang
Gamma Ray Bursts
The coming of the space age ushered in a golden age of astronomy that is still going on today
That golden age began strangely enough, not in space,
but was the turning point in cold war relations
That also contributed to our next great discovery
,
In the nineteen sixties, despite a nuclear-test-ban-treaty
The Soviet Union refused to allowed onside inspectors enter his nuclear facilities
As a result, the US opted to monitor the soviets by developing an orbital satellite system
capable of detecting gamma rays burst produced by nuclear explosions
Because the satellites detector looked up as well as down
Scientists decided to use them to see
if supernovae produced gamma rays when they exploded
1969-1972
Between 1969 and 1972, they detected evidence of 16 short gamma ray bursts, scattering across the sky
There was just one problem
None of the burst correlated with any of the known supernova events
And the mystery deepened
,
Over the next two decades, astronomers detected an average of one gamma ray burst a day
But each burst happened so quickly that was over before astronomers could get a telescope aimed at it
BeoopSAX
Finally, astronomers began to solve the puzzle with the help of the BEOOP SAX space telescope, which was designed specifically
X
to detect the short burst of gamma and x-rays and precisely pinpoint their locations
On December fourteenth 1997, BEOOP SAS located a gamma ray burst,
leading to the first photographs ever taken a burst and wave lengths other than gamma
To their astonishment, astronomers discovered that burst took place in a galaxy twelve billion light years away
Making one of the universe most powerful explosions
Since then, dozens of other gamma rays bursts have been similarly documented
All just as powerful and far away
As for what it all means
the discovery of gamma rays burst have once again show us that hidden now there behind the veil of the earth
s atmosphere are objects
that are not only strange and hard-defined, black holes, pulsars, quasars
But there are lethal too
Gamma ray bursts are now considered the possible cause of past distinction events on earth
The scientist sir Arthur Eddington once noted that
Not only is the universe stranger than we imagine
It is stranger than we can
t imagine
He could be talking about the gamma ray burst, the expanding universe or the theory of general relativity
And it also happened to be a perfect description of our next discovery
Planets Orbiting Other Stars
Once it would been been impossible for astronomers to imagine discovering other solar systems with planets like our own
But today, astronomers can imagine
thanks to powerful space and ground-based telescopes like the one here in the Lick Observatory in the Mount Hamilton California
where Geoff Marcy is hunting for new planets
How do you go out finding a planet around a star
Wow, it
s very easy
We watch the star to see if it wobbles in response to the planet, yanking around gravitationally
-
Very easy
you just need one of these
-
that
s right
This is the 3-meter lick observatory telescope
By definition, planets don
t produce their own energy, they shine of course by the reflected light
But planet are about a billionth as bright as their host star
So you can
t really see them even with the Hubble
you need a trick and that is what we use with this telescope
-
A trick
The Doppler
s effect are trick
We measure the wobble of the star by the changing light waves that come from the star as the star wobbles
The search for extra-solar planetary system gain momentary in the early nineteen nineties
When a polish astronomer made a surprising discovery
There was a wonderful discovery by Alexander Wolszczan of a system of three planets orbiting a pulsar
and the way he found them was quiet exciting
He watched the pulses coming from the pulsar
And their arriveal of those pulses changes as the pulsars approaches and recedes us
X
These are hideous stars
Pulsars have ultraviolet x-rays gamma rays coming often
They are the bizarre end products of a supernova explosion
And despite that bizarre environment, here we have earth-size planets going around it
If there are earth-size planet go around pulsars
you can bet there are earth-size planets that around other stars
There are earth-size planets around pulsars
Earth-size and even moon-sized among the three
-
He detected them
Detected them by this wobble of the pulsars
--
That
s just the coolest thing in the world
--
It
s unbelievable
Since wolszczan
s discovery
Marcy and other astronomers have found more than one hundred thirty extra-solar planets
We thought we would have never found even one planet
and we found the world
s only triple planet system and the quadruple planet system with this telescope
-
,
So, these are big planets though
-
These are planets the size of out Jupiter, Saturn and smallest Neptune sized
--
Oh, little Neptune
---
So it
s quite exciting that they are finding planets of Jupiter sized
But even those a few times bigger than the earth
Well, no Earth-like planets have yet been found
The search continues
How do you pick a star as a candidate
,
We indeed try to choose stars that are more or less like our Sun
some more massive some less massive, or sort of middle age or older so they
ve settled down
What you want for an earth like planet to make it habitable is that temperature has to be just right
Not so cold, the water
s locked up in the ice
Not so hot, that the water if that evaporated into steam
But the planet just the right distance from its star
so that the temperature is just right for liquid water over billions of years to let Darwinian evolution do its things
-
Sound like the Goldilocks and her porridge
,
That
s right
You don
t want it to be too hot or too cold
Suppose you have a telescope, a cosmos, a device, sensitive enough to find an earth-like planet
Would you point at some of stars that you are already identified as having planetx
Absolutely, the Jupiterx and Saturnx we are finding are the signpost
the benchmarks of system that might harobr earth
and dspecially if those Jupiterx far enough from the host star
That leaves room for an earth in the habitable zone to be orbiting that star
What made you go looking for planets on other stars
,
Oh, I remember when I was a young kid, I thought to myself, I wonder if there are other earth out there
and if so of any are habitable
and then is there life on those planets, and particular intelligent life
,
We humans I think in general would love to know are we alone in the universe
Are there other creature out there that think and dream and indeed are searching for us
,
In the end, I think we humans are trying to find out our roots out there chemically and biologically among the stars
The Universe is Accelerating
As the universe expanded following the big gang
,
logic indicted that the gravitational attraction of all matter should pull at that expanding material and cause the expansion to slow
But how much was the universe slowing down
,
In the nineteen nineties, the Hubble
s space telescope made it possible for teams of scientists to answer the question
1A
by studying the brightness of light from a special type of the exploding star called a type 1A supernova
I paid a visit to the Lawrence Berkeley National Laboratory in San Francisco
and met with astrophysicist Saul Perlmutter who has a supernova cosmology project
So, what did you find out
So, we started to make measurement to try to find how much the universe in its sustention is slowing down
:
,
When we first saw the data,You say well, that
s kind of funny, looks the universe isn
t slowing down
But you think, well we are already in the mid of doing all these checks, and collaborations and confirmations
I am sure once we get over the numbers, you
ll check out and figure out
--
that the effect will go away and change the signs somewhere that will fix
,
There are minus signs
Sgns are
like that
,
You check each step and of the process
Little by little
you  get the point we start you know this effect isn
t going way
This is the right answer
It really looks like the universe is actually speeding up
So, why is this so important
This acceleration of universe doesn
t fit at all
We understand,
pretty well the all forces of our universe and all the objects of our universe and this is the first time we come cross something that we wouldn
t have predicted
Now, we are having the fun to try to  figure out what does this all mean
,
And if you come with me, I will show you what we are doing about
>
-
Why is it accelerating
,
Oh, that
s the question, we are all dying to know the answer,
,
and when we think about this if you have a energy of this odd sort that would pervade all space
It can actually speed up the universe when gravity is trying to slow it down
And we are calling it dark energy, just reflecting the fact we don
t know what it is
-
It
s a mystery
-
,
it
s completely mysterious, bizarre
We
ve no idea what it is
We wanted studies to figure out what could dark energy be like
We want to do now is get data that could help pull apart the different answers
So, where are you going to have data
The big pictures of goal that were after is a project that you see you around you here which is a satellite project
SNAP
The design here we called SNAP which is short for supernova acceleration probe
This would be a new space telescope with a very very big field of view
So instead of looking througha little key hole of the universe, you
ll be looking through a big picture of window of universe
So let me show you what we are working on
that we think might help us get out why the universe is accelerating, what this dark energy really is
SNAP
Here we have SNAP that we are hoping to be launched just in the future
This one goes out to a location out past the moon
From that point, you can measure expansion history with such detail
that we could actually see the little changes when it goes to deceleration to acceleration
Backwards universe was really dense and close together
Gravity is more important, it slows the expansion down
As it is kept expanding though even it went slower and slower and loss out
and gravity became less important than the dark energy which took over and started to accelerate expansion,
And we are after exactly how that change over occur
that would tell us about what different possible theories could be right to explain dark energy
-
,
Always expanding
Exactly always speeding up
-
exactly
,
It is an issue of it got slow down and come to a wobble and then take off
What was that transition like
Just like the ancient astronomers
modern scientists have discovered something about the cosmos that we cannot yet explain
It will up to observers and theorists to figure out what
s going on in our expanding universe
For this, only new ideas and better instruments
No matter this mystery will solve soon or far in the future
It could be certain of one thing
We will keep watching the skies, to understand our place in the cosmos
We will continue to explore, understand and discover
CHD