When they write the book of my life,
what section will I be in?
Mystery? Horror? Romance?
Or just misfiled and jammed  in the back under "military history"?
No,I can't--I can't do it like this. I can't.
Sure you can.
Just hold onto the civil war
and put your feet on the korean conflict.
What? No,no.
You have to break up with chloe.
All right?
You said you were going to and now here we are.
We're sneaking around again--
and thank you for helping me
find this book on tanks,sir.
No,"tank" you.
I'm serious,all right?
No more fooling around until you tell her.
I will. I'll do it today.
I promise.
Okay.
Look,I wanna be with you on your birthday.
I wanna start clean with you.
I wanna be part of your life again.
It's my birthday?
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
第二人生 第1季第15集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：个人ID
校对：个人ID
时间轴：Costa
So anyway,my mom is going to throw me a birthday party,
and I'm gonna have cake and ice cream
and hats and no kazoos.
I don't like kazoos.
They sound like bees.
And I want you to be
in charge of the guest list,okay?
Me?
Yay!
Okay,I'm gonna invite your mom and your dad
and andrea and me
and,uh... um...
okay,that's it!
Oh,wow.
What do you want for a gift?
I don't know.
I feel like I have everything I want,
you know?
I have this new chance at my life.
I've got great friends and family,
and when todd breaks up with chloe a new boyfriend.
Really? Is he gonna break up with her
to be with you?
Uh-huh. Yeah,that
and because she's a total loon and emotional
and a little unstable.
You know what?
Just switch with me.
I don't want my back to the door.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
move.
I want the sun behind me today.
it'll look good in my hair.
what are you doing?
My mom's throwing me a birthday party,
so we're just figuring out who's coming.
No one's coming.
We don't do birthdays.
We go to the spa,
we fast all day,
and we wrap ourselves in seaweed
and we sweat out our toxins.
I want a piata!
Oh! ooh! Yeah.
Oh,my god. It's chloe and todd.
Duck,duck! Duck! Duck! Duck!
-get down! Get down! Andrea!
-Get down. Shh!
-What are you doing?
-Get down! Get down!
todd is breaking up with chloe today.
And I'd say she's taking it very well.
hey.
What are you doing here?
Nothing. Just came by  to see how the breakup went.
How'd chloe take it?
Pretty well.
Good,because I was afraid
she had trouble understanding you
with your tongue in her mouth.
You--you were at the aquarium?
What?! Todd!
You know,I would not have been
fooling around with you
if you weren't gonna be
breaking up with her already.
This was supposed to be just a little overlap,
but now the longer that you keep your girlfriend,
the longer I am just a boyfriend-stealing whore.
You're making me into a whore,todd.
I was gonna tell her,but her aunt is sick.
Her aunt is sick?
Yeah,she just found out her aunt wendy,
who practically raised her,
was admitted to st. Sofia's hospital.
But you know what?
If you break up with her now,
she could just meet somebody there.
I mean,a hospital's kind of like a nightclub.
You know,they got cute people and skimpy outfits
and--and drugs.
That's not really what she's thinking about.
Yeah,well,maybe it's because she doesn't know
that you promised to spend my birthdawith me.
Now you're putting chloe's feelings before mine
because she is feeling vulnerable but you know what?
You don't think that I'm feeling vulnerable?
I am turning 1!
oh,andrea.
Honey,do we need any drinking done?!
Sorry,dear. Check back next week.
Always funny. Yeah!
okay,I'm gonna make this quick,
then you can get back to your nap.
Samantha is not having her birthday party here.
No one is driving a half an hour
to the sticks to play twister
and watch a slide show of your trip to akron.
That was a gre party.
Samantha's birthday party
will be at my place on saturday.
You can come or not.
I'd love to,
but I'm having samantha's
birthday party that night.
It's too bad that you cat make it.
Okay,okay,that's enough.
Regina,I hate taking sides against you,
and I know I'll pay for this for years to come,
but,you know,maybe sam
would prefer a party in the city
you know,something hip,
you know,for the kids.
Are you telling me
that you didn't like your last birthday party?
People loved making their own place mats.
It was great.
But I'm talking about a real city party,
you know,like you see in the magazines
where--where celebrities show up,
like espn sideline reporter suzy kolber.
come on.
We'll make a night of it.
Well,okay. But i do the food.
That part's always a hit.
I mean,who doesn't love ambrosia salad?
So no todd on my birthday
because of some sick aunt.
We should get a todd piata.
A todd-yata.
So I've called 21 people,
and they all have jury duty.
On a saturday night?
There must be some really big trial or something.
No,there's no trial.
These people are just making up
lies to get out of something
that they don't wanna do.
oh,my god.
I do not want to go over to his place.
He's gonna break up with me.
I could tell it.
-I could tell it in his voice.
-Then don't--don't let him.
He has no right to break up with you,
not when your favorite cousin is
in the hospital on his deathbed.
I don't have a cousin in the hospital.
You bet your ass you do.
Oh!
Yes. Cousin what's-his-name.
Yeah.
So you go to the hospital,
you find the name of someone
who's actually there,
just in case he sends flowers or something.
Then if he gets suspicious and he goes there,
just put a picture of yourself next to
the sick guy's bed.
It's airtight. Bam.
You just bought yourself a boyfriend
through valentine's day.
Oh! Can I train with you,master?
The way of the samurai is a lonely path,darling.
Here you go,ladies. Oh!
From these gentlemen right over there.
But maybe not so lonely tonight.
sick aunt.
Chloe is lying.
once I prove that,
todd will have no problem breaking up with her,
and he will be mine...
and in time for my birthday.
So todd is coming?
Yeah.
Okay,'cause this thing is really
starting to fill up.
Oh.
Mm. Hey.
Gotta stretch it out,you know?
-help you?
-Oh! Hey there. Um... nurse.
Hi. Yeah,
I'm just looking for my,um,aunt wendy.
Last name?
It's just wendy.
Always been wendy to me.
aunt wendy. She's sick.
Don't have a wendy here.
Thank you very much.
She's lying.
Ha! I win.
I got a gwendolyn.
dr. Forrest,
dial 1-1-2,please.
Dr. Forrest,
please dial 1-1-2.
you are a worthy adversary indeed.
Sorry.
Did you need more time?
No. No.
oh,god!
yes. Okay.
Sam?
please take this woman safely into the...
bosom and grace of your all-knowing arms. Amen.
hi,chloe.
I was just...
helping this poor woman off to her reward.
What are you doing here?
Oh,chloe. Look,I-I know that
we've had our differences,
but,you know,when i found out about your aunt,
I just--
I just wanted to put all those things aside
and just--
and just be with you.
Hi,auntie wendy.
And there she is--
your aunt. Ha!
Well.... congratulations.
No,um,not congratulations.
I'm sorry.
Uh,condolences.
No,that's--no,
'cause that's not right,'cause she's not...
she's not dead.
Congratulations!
Well,I'm off.
Hey,frank.
I was thinking how it must be gratifying,
doing your job,
being such an important part of  all these people's lives,
you know,
comin' and goin' here.
there's talk of replacing me  with a motion-sensing mat.
You like birthday cake?
Hey,todd,listen
um,I've done a 180 on this whole you breaking up
with chloe dealio.
I-I don't think you should break up with her yet.
I-I--
you know,I was thinking about her aunt,
and you're right.
You know,she's really,really sick,
so why don't you just call me back
after you do not break up with her?
Do not. Okay.
Uh,bye. Hi.
So... I go to get my suit out of the cleaners
for your birthday party,
and the guys there can't stop laughing.
They say they're waiting to see
who picks up this suit so they can see
what his time machine looks like.
Well,I'm sorry I don't dress like the internet.
I know. It's strange that I just showed up here,
but...
I found yourress
when I was going through  todd's computer last week,
and I need to talk to you.
Yeah.
Todd...
-broke up with me.
-Oh?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-I really...
-what?
Need a friend right now.
All right. There,there.
There. You know what?
your hands are a little close to my neck.
just don'T...
yeah,all right.
Okay,that's better.
There,there. There,here.
dad?
so you really think That I'm the one
that you wanna talk to?
Well,yeah.
Why not?
I know you were with todd.
You do? No,I wasn'T.
When?
For three... years.
Oh,this amnesia thing is
really tiring. I'm sorry.
Oh,yeah. No. I know.
When you showed up to the hpital to support me,
that was the nicest thing  anyone's ever done for me.
I think maybe I misjudged you.
Yeah,well,it happens.
But you know what?
You seem okay.
I-I mean,it's probably good
to just get all this
just bad news out of the way.
In fact,I'm sure that you're probably
more upset about your aunt
than you are about todd,huh?
No,I'm more upset about todd.
Are you sure?
'Cause you know what? I saw your aunt,
she wasn't looking so great.
Sammy?
Hi. I can't go to this thing
tonight looking like a hayseed,
so... I'm off to the suit barn. Bye.
Okay. Yeah. He could come back at any second,
so just so you know.
oh,my god! Look at this.
Oh,don't ha a fit.
I'll clean it up.
No,it's not that.
I just have never been in here.
I wasn't even sure if
the appliances were real. Hmm.
Oh,come on.
You must have cooked breakfast
for hundreds of young men.
I can cook,you know.
I just usually go out.
That must be nice--
clubs,restaurants.
Yeah.
Sometimes it's nice to stay in.
I bet yotravel a lot,too,don't you?
Yeah,on business.
Where's the--
where's the farthest you've ever been?
I don't know. Marrakech?
Marrakech.
Oh,my god. How exotic.
Howard and I haven't been anywhere
but pensacola for years.
He won't fly.
He hates to take his shoes off in front of people.
But I'm hopeful.
I keep bing travel magazines.
Okay,do not tell anyone this,
but once a year I buy "good housekeeping"--
the issue with...
100 holiday ideas.
Me,too!
you know,andrea,
you could make this kitchen fun to use.
You could have everything out in the open.
You could hang a pot rack here over the stove.
Oh,like I can hang a pot rack.
Well,yeah,
my husband does those things for me.
See,I need that.
A man with tools--
it's very hot.
I can use a man like that.
Howard has shingles.
So anyway,todd and i were just about to record
a new outgoing message--"hi.
It's the home of todd and chloe.
Leave a message,
whether friend or foe-Y."
Anyway,so he was supposed to do
"friend or foe-y,"
and all of a sudden,e said,
"this isn't working out."
And I knew he meant us,
because I've had that message for years.
People love it.
Mm. And... ahem.
He gave no reason at all?
Nope. But I know he's seeing someone.
You do? How can you?
No,you can'T.
Because he's todd.
That's what he does.
What's what he does?
Not leave someone until he has someone else.
You know,ke how he was with you before he left
his previous girlfriend,
and he and I were making out
for a full two weeks
before he finally
broke it off with you.
Hmm.
So,howard,you enjoyingyour city party?
Even samantha didn't bother to come.
Oh,the place will fill up.
They're just fashionably late.
You know,some of these people,
these glitterati--
they don't roll in
until at least 8:30.
look at you. Very nice.
Yes,yes,he knows.
Moving along.
Ugh. Oh! Look at me.
My shoes are all wrong.
Thankfully,no one will see me
since you didn't get anyone here!
I did so!
This is not everyone.
Other people are coming!
see?
Ah!
Hello.
I wasn't going to come,
but my wife doesn't want me around
during our daughter's homework time.
She says I get impatient.
It's just decimals, for god sake.
You move it one place for every tenth.
How hard is that?
I'm going to want some wine.
Okay. Now...
everyone is here
why didn't you tell me?
I know 15 eurotrash partiers
who can be here in 5 minutes.
It's samantha's birthday party.
You can't fill it with strangers.
She has amnesia.
Start dialing.
-Hey. Happy birthday.
-Hi
Thank you. Um...
before we go to the party,
I-I need to ask,uh,
something... quick.
Were you--
were you fooling around with chloe
before you broke up with me?
You look really pretty.
Were you ever gonna tell me about it?
I did...
before the accident.
Oh,god,don'T.
You can't pull it off.
Well,I'm sorry I'm not as good a liar as you.
I mean,you were able to sleep
with the french guy without me knowing.
Oh,I can't believe that
you're gonna bring up rene right now.
Really? You know,because I think
it's a perfect time to bring him up.
Yeah,but you didn't know about
that until after we broke up.
Well,you didn't know about chloe
until after we broke up.
That is very different.
how?
Because I am not like that anymore.
That was bad sam,
and you're just,you know,
same todd.
I don't wanna live like that.
I have nothing to hide.
hide!
you know, to an outside observer,
this might not seem like
a very healthy relationship.
you sure? Okay. Anybody?
oh! Oh,frank,
my hands are kinda full.
Could you get that,please?
Nope. I'm off the clock.
I don't open doors.
I won't call you a cab,
and I won't find you an escort service.
Good ambrosia,though.
Oh,thank you.
Would you have broken up
with chloe if I hadn't pushed you?
what?
You wanna talk about this now?
You got somewhere to be?
Okay. Yes.
No,you would not.
Shh! How do you know
about chloe and me?
Because she told me.
Oh.
Because this is what you do,right?
Because you can't be alone.
You just--
you just swing from girl to girl like monkey bars.
Why is chloe talking to you, anyway?
Because that... you know...
it's not important.
Well,while you two were sharing,
did you tell her you and i have been making out?
No,todd.
I-I think that the girl has been through enough.
Don't you?
-Bad sam!
-Stop that!
-she's coming!
-What?
She's coming.
Move,move out of my way!
Get down!
Ohh!
Oh,god!
Oh,god,you scared me.
Oh,yeah,yeah, you scared me,too.
I thought you were--
I thought you were todd.
What are you doin'?
Oh,I was just gettiso me...
shoes to wear
for my birthday party.
You didn't say you were having a party.
Oh,yeah. Well,it was a--
it's a surprise.
But... you already know.
Oh,shoot.
I ruined the surprise.
What?
I don't know. I can'T...
I can't do this. I can't do this.
I'm sorry,chloe.
Todd and I are together.
Oh,my god.
You're so pathetic.
I know you have amnesia and everything,
but you tried this already,remember?
Where's todd supposed to be this time?
Huh? Where is he?
Oh,in the bathroom?
No,you did that one.
oh, maybe he's in the closet,huh?
Maybe he's in here.
That would be devastating.
I thought you were my friend.
You came to the hospital and everything.
Oh,my god.
Uh,you two deserve each other.
Good luck.
the hospital?
It doesn't matter,okay?
She's right.
I mean,look at us.
Yeah,chloe's gone,
and I am sitting here,
but maybe I'm sitting here because I'm not her.
Or maybe I'm sitting here
because you just can't be alone.
You know,w with you,
I don't know if I'm me or I'm just not her.
Well,are you saying
you don't want us to be together?
No,I'm just saying that
I am so tired of being not someone.
It's time for me to be someone.
Maybe if we were different people or...
and we had never met,
then we could have a fresh start,
but we're not.
You still have stuff here, you know.
I'll always have stuff here,todd.
happy birthday...
so "the book of sam"
is ready for volume two--
a stack of blank pages and no better way
to begin than celebrating my 1st birthday
with my parents,my friends
and my remarkably attractive
and diverse seventh grade clas
make a wish and blow.
A good one,make a good one.
that was great.
I want that candle when you're done.
hey.
Hey.
What's going on?
Oh,I'm sorry. U.. hi.
My name's todd.
Um... samantha.
Yeah. I think I've seen you at the coffee place.
Yeah,I usually don't do this,
but,um,here's my number.
Call me... sometime if you wanna get together.
-Thanks.
-Balloons.
yeah.
You--you got 21 people,
so you make 20 cuts.
It's not rocket science.
-You just--
-okay,just give me the knife.
-Give me the knife. Give me--
-I can do--
give it. Give it.
Thank you. Hold this.
-I get to cut the first piece,right?
-Get cuttin'.
Square plates for a round cake.
-who wants cake?
-This is amazing,mom.
-Thank you so much.
-You're welcome, sweetheart.
Cheers.
破烂熊字幕组谨以本片
向中国震灾的幸存者们致以最真挚的慰问
并向受难者们敬上沉痛的悼念