Mother
don't want
Don't go
Don't leave me alone
Mother
do not leave Me
don't want
elder sister
Why does the rain never stop falling?
Yes, you just got caught in so much rain
Don't catch a cold
Just blow dry it in a while
What happened to Shensu?
How many times have I told you not to make trouble on the bus?
Lao Jin, don't be so harsh on the child.
Don't mess with your sister, Tangdou'er
Whose child is so obedient?
Yes or no
Be good
Mother
I dreamed of you again
How are you
I don't know which city you live in now.
Dad said
I'm very different now than when I was a kid.
If you meet on the road
You will still recognize me
Is it right
Passengers of the Ocean Sirius, follow me.
Come on, follow me.
Hurry up, Betelgeux
I'm coming
Today is a very special day
Dad took us on a cruise
Finally I'm going to see the sea
I am really happy
This boat is nice and fancy.
Mom, look, there are seagulls.
Do not miss passing through
Portrait photography: 10 yuan per piece
Mother
I still remember when I was little
You often tell me stories about sea elves
you say
On birthday
Make a wish to the sea
It will appear
Take you to realize your wish
Come and take a photo together
Does Sugar Bean look like a little sea otter?
Come over and take some photos with us.
come on
Come come come
Take this
Sister, take this.
Dad, hold your daughter tighter
okay
Come and see how it goes
dad
Dad, I
Okay, let's go have fun.
Remember to come back before dinner.
This little sea otter is so cute
It really looks like
This is a six-day, seven-night luxury tour.
That's worth the price.
baby
Mother
Let's go find dad.
clown
It's too late. We need to go eat.
Just one minute
It's dark now
Just one second
kid
Buy a copy
The Legend of Deep Sea Hotel
168 Not expensive
Sorry uncle, I'm just taking a look
If you don't buy it, you'll break it.
Go Go
It's really unlucky
Sugar Bean, don't run around
Sugar Bean, come here
Look what this is
Lollipop
I want
Drink less old gin.
The purpose of going out to play is to have fun.
Orion
Come come come
Let's celebrate Tangdouer's kindergarten
Sugar Bean goes to kindergarten
cheers
Cheers Cup
Sea elf with little girl
Swim to a big castle
It turned out that her mother was calling her with singing.
Cake is coming
The cake is here, make a wish
I want to be with my mother forever
Okay, we'll be together forever.
Never leave each other
Mother
Wake up!
You will sing my mother's songs
Who are you
Sea elves
Mother
Where are you going
You have to take me to my mother.
You know where my mom is, right?
Mother
Hello
anyone there
Take a look
This restaurant's food is not delicious.
Still doing these fancy tricks
What's the use of this?
This is only the first day
I haven't had a full meal.
I signed up for a six-day, seven-night luxury tour.
A weight loss class
I said I wouldn't stay any longer.
Today I have to swim back even if I have to.
Everyone, please stop smoking.
I'll ask you
This scrambled eggs with tomatoes
Have you ever fried whole tomatoes?
I've never heard of oyster ice cream.
Isn't chocolate stuffed sausage disgusting?
I want to drink a bowl of millet porridge now
Look, my cheeks have shrunk due to hunger these days.
fish
Our boss likes to innovate.
This is his creative dish.
walrus
I beg you to stop innovating.
If that doesn't work, you can just give me a bowl of dumpling soup.
pimple
Coincidentally, our best
It's pimple soup
I've been talking for a long time, are you kidding me?
This is pimple soup.
Isn't this a cuttlefish?
Isn't this a squid?
Oh my God
Isn't this seafood?
How did this get here?
unlucky
You are unlucky
You let me go down
Go down
Go down quickly
Bad luck, leave now
Cuttlefish gets bigger
I'm going to change back to my original form.
The review dropped to one star again
These guys are too picky.
Is there wealth?
Isn't this dish a bit avant-garde?
No cutting corners
No big deal
Give yourself a good vacation
Dare to destroy my place
uncle
Don't hurt it
Where did you come from?
It brought me to my mother.
Don't hurt it
You stole my things
you give me
Letting go
Don't squeeze my waist.
Dare to steal things from me
Whose cell phone is this?
It's mine
South River
Did you see the bad luck that just came in?
Expelled
You got wet.
After a while of drying, it will return to human form.
What time does the work start?
I'm talking about Lao Jin
Is there anyone eating at work?
That's right. No.
I don't even exclude my parents who provide me with food and clothing.
Here, here
Just get it out.
I've never seen such difficult parents.
What about our hotel loan?
Sooner or later I can pay it back
I also promised to make dumpling soup for the guests.
etc.
Dumpling Soup
Look, Mr. Jin
I caught the sea elf
It is said that just a small bite
It can make people laugh
This thing looks weird.
Don't use it to make creative dishes
It's not that complicated
Fresh ingredients are often
Only the simplest cooking is needed
Hurry and bring our parents back
I made them dumpling soup.
You really have to eat it
Aren't you afraid of getting sick from eating this?
Eat it
October
Harvest season
Monsoons in the Northern Hemisphere
Nourishes lush crops
Golden wheat fields
Bright red peppers
Green rapeseed
Fat duck
Fresh live shrimp
Tight ham
Fresh deep sea fish
A gift from nature
The top ingredients that made our Deep Sea Hotel
High-end ingredients
The chef's professional cooking is indispensable
After stir-frying
Oil splash
Pan-Fried
Deep fried
Carefully prepared seasoning
The overflowing fragrance gently blows
Stirring the deep desire in your heart
Among the many delicious
The best
This is the secret of our store that has never been revealed for a century
Smiling pimple soup
Be careful
This is made by the boss himself, so don't spill it.
Has the boss invented a new dish?
Know and ask
This soup tastes weird.
Can I give it to the guests?
I said to make a normal dumpling soup
He is not creative
If the customer complains again, I won't clean up his mess
From now on
Gourmet food is no longer gourmet food
It's a journey that cleanses the soul
Give way
Excuse me
sorry
The big monster in the sea just now
It seems that it is not swimming fast
Maybe he's hungry like us.
Did you notice the look in his eyes?
There is a faint sadness
There are so many eyes, which one are you talking about?
Sir, Madam, please come in.
I heard there's something to eat today.
You're not dead yet, let's wait and see
waiter
gentlemen
Which table was I sitting at?
Sir, you are number 10
My memory is not very good.
You are a goldfish, is that normal?
We are at No. 9
This is not sour
Maybe the chef kneaded the dough with his feet.
Then I have to give a bad review
Can you please stop turning? I'm dizzy.
I just want to find something to eat.
Also taking photos
Look at this dish.
What is it called "Never Fish Until Death"?
I think he died with his eyes open.
Look at this again
Still asking for forgiveness
You don't have to apologize.
elder brother
do not
Why don't you try the Laughing Dumpling Soup?
what is this
I get goosebumps listening to this
I'll tell you
This soup is very nourishing
Last time, a customer took a sip.
Swimmed 1500 meters without taking a breath
I just want to drink something light
This is light
It doesn't look dangerous.
Why don't you try it?
Come on, look
Come on, here we come
Isn't this the bad luck just now?
Why are you here again?
We'll be in trouble if she's here.
Why don't you kick her out right away?
The boss is the boss.
Where is the boss?
Everyone, don't move.
Hold your breath
If you don't breathe, you won't breathe in the bad luck.
My little bear
Argonauts
Come to mom
Mother
Orion
Come here soon
What to do
Come and try it
Still eating
boss
What's this
this
I'll say it for you
Shoe sole hotpot, right?
I understand your innovation.
You can't put everything in there.
Tofu
What
Gluten
That's right
tasty
You are slow to use
Are you deliberately making things difficult for me?
You still chew
You vomited on me.
I let you give me
Sorry uncle, I didn't mean it.
Get out of here
But my mother seems to be here
I told you
This isn't your mom.
We
Playing
We will show you a wonderful show later
clown
Take care
Walk slowly, walk slowly, walk slowly
Walk slowly. Walk slowly.
How many times have I told you
You found the wrong place
look
Which of these fish heads and fish brains looks like your mother?
Am I
Is it
enough
Look elsewhere
Don't affect my business.
Then don't eat it, okay?
what
That's the sea elf you caught.
That sea elf is mine.
But it seems that my mother asked it to come to me.
It knows me
It knows you
Give me a break
Call it and see if it responds.
It's true. She can sing my mother's songs.
are you crazy
Isn't it just humming? How can it be a song?
My mother must have sent it here.
Uncle, I beg you.
Who is your uncle?
As long as you put it
You can let me do anything.
do not move
If you say don't move, then don't move.
Go, go, go, ignore him
Today, I have to swim back even if it's across the Pacific Ocean.
At most, I can travel for six days and seven nights.
Guests, please don't leave.
Let them play by themselves.
you get what you pay for
I told you to choose a more expensive group
Did you listen to me?
The purpose of going out to play is to have fun.
good
Come come come
Come here quickly
boss
Serve the soup quickly
ladies and gentlemen
Pay attention, pay attention
Next Steps
What you are about to see is
you
this
Look at this in my hand.
Magical magic
Don't miss your eyes
under
Deep Sea Hotel
Top creative dishes
Smiling pimple soup
It is not produced in our kitchen.
If it's not made in the kitchen, it's probably takeout.
Boss, that's right.
How good it would be earlier
South River
Come to the kitchen
Come to the kitchen quickly
clown
What if Lao Jin didn't see that I was busy?
Have you thrown away that bad luck?
There are so many depressed ghosts outside the window
Throw it out
Not far enough
How can you be so careless?
Is it so unlucky?
This time it's over
Being haunted by a depressed ghost can suffocate you to death.
I'll go to the lobby.
Getting ready to weigh anchor
Amitabha God bless you
What's wrong with these two today?
Don't sleep anymore
Don't sleep
Set sail! Set sail!
Faster and faster
strawberry
Uncle and aunt, that's a depressed ghost
If you get entangled, you will suffocate to death.
I'm suffocating.
Pedal hard!
Sugar Beans
The ship is about to sink, so stop making trouble.
Go play
Please clean up this red mud quickly.
Don't let the depressed ghost come back to life
You two are brave enough to use this as a facial mask
Skin Care
Sugar Melon
I'm not full after dawdling for so long.
I didn't have enough to eat.
You didn't eat
Everyone
I'm just a jack of all trades.
Can you go find the boss?
Who knows where he is hiding?
Find him for me quickly. I've been hungry for days.
This bad luck
It really attracted the depressed ghost.
Fortunately, the size is not big
uncle
Please, uncle.
How did you come back?
Just let the sea elf go.
It's the only thing that can help me find my mother.
Just let it go.
Let it go
Please, uncle.
You know this sea elf
How much is it worth?
Also put it
You make money for me
I can
As long as you put it
I can stay
What's the point of you staying?
You invite the depressed ghost again
We all have to die here.
You mean
I invited the red one.
What else?
It likes to pester sad kids like you.
Don't be afraid, I'm just trying to scare you.
The depressed ghost comes to make trouble for no reason
We are happy
Happy and depressed ghosts will naturally run away
Happy
How did this happen?
Where is the boss?
Don't let him get away
Stay happy
Just stay happy and you'll be fine
Ladies and gentlemen
Just be patient
I promise this will never happen again.
I promise
Don't say those useless things
We want to drink pimple soup
right
Dumpling Soup
Why didn't you bring out such a good thing earlier?
This soup
It's not cheap
You should have said it earlier.
I want five bowls
I want ten bowls
I've got it all
Soup
uncle
Can you release the sea elf?
Could you please stop mentioning this?
Don't worry, let me think about it.
This kid is very cute. Look at his little appearance.
Do you think this will work?
This sea elf?
Lend it to me for two days.
You just help out in the kitchen.
Look, there's nothing on it.
Wait until our rating reaches five stars
I put it away immediately
what do you think
Really
That's not good.
Our business is most concerned about reputation
Then you won't eat it?
Eat it
This is a mascot.
I couldn't wait to serve it and I ate it
Let's work hard together and it will be yours soon.
good
make a deal
Do your best.
Thank you uncle
Okay, okay, don't call me uncle all the time.
Nanhe
Thanks
Uncle Nanhe
Count it down.
excuse me
You really want to keep her here.
She wants to invite the depressed ghost again
So I have to coax her.
As long as she is happy, the depressed ghost will not appear
After five days, the ship will dock.
Throw it as far as you can for her.
Orion
What a nice name.
My name is Ahua and I am the best at making dolls.
I'm Lao Li. Do you like eating blue bean buns?
Oyster Ice Cream
I did it
What's going on with you guys?
Stop chatting. Hurry up.
I understand. Lao Jin, don't be so harsh on the child.
Let's go, let's go to work
Thank you for your hard work here.
It's better to save money
It's okay. It's safe.
sorry
No problem, smiling service
Perfect
not angry
Go
Finally two stars
it is true
For me
Three stars
Water fight
Stop playing
Get rich
Orion
Hurry up, please.
So stupid
I will be able to get rid of this unlucky burden of yours soon.
Perfect
Nanhe has made a new animation, go watch it now
On the vast ocean
The handsome captain of the Nanhe and his brave crew
Looking for the treasure left by Captain Nemo
Mysterious stars
come on
I'm really handsome
A depressed ghost
The brave crew heads towards the stars
go ahead
Defeat the Desperate Ghost
It hurts so much
Mother
I want my mother
The depressed ghost painted on the star looks like you
What are you doing here?
There are a lot of dishes to be washed. Go back and wash them.
We'll dock tomorrow.
Don't cause trouble at this time
Today, no one is working.
Open a party
What's the meaning
Everyone, listen carefully.
This is unlucky.
This can
Orion
Although she has caused us a lot of trouble
But you still try hard.
from now on
Everyone treats her as a family member
We are a family
cheers
Cheers Cup
We've all left, but we still have to go to work tomorrow.
Are you happy that Cangsu will soon be a five-star star?
Well done, Shensu.
You kid
Pretty sensible
Sometimes
You're not really laughing
Look at our service industry.
Your smile is so insincere
The guests can feel it.
you see me
Yes or no
Do you have anything happy? Think about it.
So let me tell you a joke
I see if you are happy
There used to be a little white seal on our boat.
It loves to laugh.
Not as introverted as you.
Then I asked it
Little seal!
You are so happy every day
Any secrets?
it says
It says boss
I
I'm a Samoyed
I look like this
Tongue cramp
That's right.
The weather is fine
go home
What’s wrong with you
What's the smell?
Soup
Dumpling Soup
The sea elf escaped
Go call Nanhe
baby
I called out
Do you dare to promise?
Nanhe, have you drunk the soup?
baby
Nanhe, wake up.
my God
Don't chase me
I didn't make soup with you.
Don't leave.
You thief
You promised me you wouldn't hurt it.
you shut up
I just use it to make soup, what's wrong?
I get up early and stay up late every day just to pay off the loan
You let me go before I could save enough money.
But that's the only way to find my mom
Stop dreaming, it's a sea elf
Everything you see is an illusion. It's fake.
If your mother really wanted to find you, she would have come here by herself a long time ago
No
Mom made it happen.
Even then it ran away
I ran away, do you understand?
If you run away, it means your mother doesn't want you anymore.
Will not
My mother won't give up on me.
I don't trust you anymore
You only have money in your eyes
What did you say
I only have money in my eyes
I lied to you from the beginning.
Pull her down to the shore. We don't need you.
Uncle and aunt, please take care.
Come back next time and take your time
baby
Mother
We're going home
Play for a while longer?
It's too late. We need to go eat.
Just one minute
It's dark now.
Just one second
The boss's business is good. It's four stars.
You guys move faster
You're not thinking of catching another sea elf, are you?
Be content. This money is enough to sustain us for a while.
I will do business honestly in the future.
Caution is the boat
look
Thanks for listening to you.
I coaxed her along the way so nothing happened.
Going away
hurry up
quick
Nanhe, why are you still standing there? Come up quickly.
Come on
South River
I said, who is this person who is so unhappy?
As for that?
She poked the hornet's nest of the depressed ghost
Lao Jin
Old Jin, how do you drive this boat?
money
I'm so unlucky.
South River
I'm also free
persist in
South River
Aunt Huahua
Did you see the South River?
No, no.
Wealthy
careful
Slower
South River
You are here
sorry
You've lost all your money saving me.
Are you OK
Is it okay?
Look at my injury. Look at my injury.
Really sorry
sorry
Is it any use if you keep saying sorry?
Look, you destroyed my boat.
Take a look
Look at this
I tell you
I didn't save you for nothing
You have to compensate me for my losses, you hear me?
You have to find me a place.
Doesn't the sea elf sing your mother's song?
Anyway, you can hear it, right?
Help us find the Eye of the Deep
We're even.
Eye of the Deep
That is in the deepest part of the ocean
All sea elves go there in the end
If you find it, will you still worry about not being able to see your mother?
Really
Yes
Wait till then.
I'll make my fortune, you go find your mother
Win-win
South River
What
Go to Eye of the Deep
You're crazy about money.
Isn't it just going to the fishery to catch some seafood?
We can't always be without signature dishes on the Deep Sea.
If you want to go, go by yourself. I won't take the risk with you.
no
Besides, who can find it?
She
I Nanhe
Can I really help you?
Our future good days
But we're counting on you
etc.
You take her to catch sea elves
What if I encounter a depressed ghost again?
Without her, we can't find the sea elves.
I think you are crazy
High risk, high reward?
Our broken ship
It will be crushed into an urn in the deep sea.
I'm going to repair the boat
I'll come back to reward you
How can I hear it, right?
The brave crew
Do you hear the call of wealth?
Let us look to the Eye of the Deep
Let’s go
Congratulations on your fortune
Congratulations on making a fortune
But the peaceful days
Daydreaming
What a fool.
What the hell is Eye of the Deep Sea?
Isn't it enough to suffer a loss?
I also know that sometimes
This road is not easy to walk
Full of
Thorn
But isn't life an adventure?
There are countless surprises waiting for you
I don't want to miss them
Take a rest, Shensu
What happened? Did you hear it?
Eat it while it's hot
It's already late, and we still have time to eat
Are you done yet?
Lao Jin has a sharp tongue but a soft heart
Did she say left or right?
Did you remember it correctly?
Lao Jin, how do you drive your boat?
Amitabha God bless you
You're done!
Mother
South River
Don't go
Don't leave me alone
do not leave Me
persist in
arrive
Are you hungry?
It's really cold here.
fine
Put on
You must be hungry.
I'll give you a full banquet
Snowing
South River
Where is this that you drew?
my home
your home
What's wrong
it's beautiful
Okay
It's just a small place on the third, fourth, fifth, sixth, seventh and eighth lines.
What a pity, I can't go back anymore
Why
You're looking for your mother so hard.
Then when you see your mother
What do you want to say to her?
I don't know either
that is
sometimes
I feel like I'm doing nothing right
It seems like it's my fault that my mother left
I wanted to find her
tell her
I'm all grown up
Sensible
So that she can go home
Eat noodle
Nanhe I know this is useless
Mom doesn't want me anymore
Who said that to you?
you said
me
I'm kidding you.
I promise I can help you find your mother, don't worry.
But the South River Sea Elves don't seem to have anything to do with my mother.
Otherwise, we'd better not go.
You can't back down at this time.
How can we know if there is any relationship if we don't find out?
If you can't solve this problem, it will haunt you like a nightmare.
You'll never be truly happy.
But what if I encounter a depressed ghost again?
We can't run away, we have to fight it off
Besides, you forgot that I have magic.
Will split the sea
I'm so powerful, no one can stop me from getting rich
I tell you, wait until I really make money
I will renovate our Deep Sea
Look at that
I built a 360-degree panoramic restaurant
The kind that can see the stars
A group of five-star chefs are waiting for you all day long
You can eat whatever you want.
I built a children's playground there
I built a 100-meter-long water slide
I won't charge you a ticket if you come.
If there are no guests by then,
Let's travel around the world
I don't need to be humble.
You don't have to be so sensible.
If you don't want to laugh, don't laugh.
If you want to cry, just cry out loud
By then, you won't have to please others anymore.
No need for others
Alive
Go and have a look
It seems we have arrived
You are really good.
I think this place is not that simple.
Nanhe, you have to think about it
What kind of storms and waves have we not seen?
When the enemy comes, we will stop him; when the water comes, we will cover it with earth.
brave
Brave crew members, please take your positions.
I am Captain Nanhe
Our destination is ahead
Eye of the Deep
The last stretch of road may not be easy to walk
But in order for our Deep Sea to pay off the loan as soon as possible
Also to help the little Cangsu find his mother
I ask everyone to be extremely courageous.
Deck staff, please hold the rudder tightly.
Grandpa Jin, it's time to drink less fake wine.
Come back, we have plenty of good wine.
Do you care?
Brothers in the engine room
The power of the Deep Sea is in your hands.
Tangdouer, take this candy first, you hear me?
Come back and eat
Ah Hua leads the catering department well
Bring out your usual energy in stirring the noodles and cheer for everyone
Don't worry, Nanhe, come on!
For a good day tomorrow
go ahead
come on
Watch out for bumps
seven
six
five
Four
three
two
Don't panic, our boat is very strong.
A depressed ghost
Nanhe is a depressed ghost
It's not too late to regret now
persist in
do not stop
We won't be able to hold on any longer.
It's okay. Hold on.
It will definitely pass
Nanhe, find a solution quickly
U-turn quickly
But what if I encounter a depressed ghost again?
We can't run away, we have to fight it off
Besides, I'm so awesome.
I promise I can help you find your mother, don't worry.
South River
Can't escape
We can't escape
persist in
Persist
I haven't figured out how to live my life yet, and I'm still thinking about being a hero.
bring it on
South River
If you bring the depressed ghost again, we will all die here.
You mean I brought the red one?
What else?
It likes to pester sad kids like you.
Don't be afraid, I'm just trying to scare you.
The depressed ghost painted on the star looks like you
Happy and depressed ghosts will naturally run away
Happy
I said, who is this person who is so unhappy?
She poked the hornet's nest of the depressed ghost
So that's how it is
Nanhe, come back soon
I invited the depressed ghost
The depressed ghost is me
I have magic
Grandpa Jin, turn around quickly
We can't go
Can't go
it's all my fault
I'm not afraid of you
Not afraid of you
Persistence is coming
persist in
South River
look
Here we are
South River
Look, we're here.
Who are you?
Where are you taking me?
Mother
Orion
Come to my mother's place to stay
Mother
Cake is coming
The cake is here, make a wish
I want to be with my mother forever
Okay, we will be together forever and never separate
What else can I do?
Can't you help me share some of the burden?
Do you think it's easy to take care of children at home?
If it weren't for this family, I would have left long ago
Mom, don't go.
Dad, can you please let mom come back?
I won't make you angry anymore.
Orion
This is your new mom.
Hello, Shensu, what a nice name.
Are you happy to be a big sister?
Dynamic Superman
give me back
This is my mother's red sweater
Sisters in Shensu must be sensible
Can't you give in to your brother?
show me
Daddy
You should take your child to see a doctor.
Wrapping myself in that red dress all day
So lonely
It's not good for her growth.
The teacher is causing you trouble.
What the hell depression?
I'm telling you, you're fine.
Just smile more and you'll get better.
Why are we wasting that money?
Dad, I know.
goodbye
Let my mother take you there.
Yes, let's go together.
No thanks, Auntie. My dad will pick me up.
Do you like it?
like
Sugar Bean, look what this is
Mom is so nice
There is still one
Today is a very special day
Finally I'm going to see the sea
I am really happy
Dad, Dad, Hug Your Daughter Tighter
okay
Mother
clown
Let me play for a while
Buy one, kids.
The Legend of Deep Sea Hotel
168 Not expensive
Sorry uncle, I'm just taking a look
If you don't buy it, you'll break it no matter what you look for.
Go, go, go, it's really unlucky
Orion
Come come come travel for sugar beans before entering the park
cheers
Cheers Cup
don't want
Whose cell phone is this?
It's mine
Someone, help!
Come and rescue! Come and rescue!
South River
Orion
Mother
Mom is back
Wake up!
Orion
Mom, I miss you so much
Mother
Mom, I
What's wrong with you, Shensu?
Wake up, Shensu
sorry
Cangsu, wake up!
Orion
You little brat
I
sorry
I'm so unlucky
I am free, too.
Don't sleep.
If you die, who can I ask for compensation for lost wages?
I didn't save you for nothing
Don't sleep
I'll show you a magic trick
Wake up!
quick
Are you hungry?
You must be hungry.
waiter
Let's have a full banquet
Why is it still leaking?
Don't look at him. This environment is not good.
This hot pot is ok
Gluten
Soft and elastic
What else do you want to eat? How about a roast duck?
No no
No
not real
This is not true
Let me go back
It's a nice day.
Like my home
This season in my house
Nagusa
Just like the waves
The wind is blowing and my eyes are blinded
Snow again!
Just like in the painting.
If only I had magic
Split the sea
go home
You have magic.
You kid
Looks OK
That's the smile.
A bit fake
You have to be like me
I'll give you
Tell a joke
I see you happy
Boat
here
persist in
It's coming
leave me alone
hold onto
Once upon a time
There is a little seal
Love to laugh
I asked it
So happy
Any secrets?
it says
I am only
Samoyed
look
The star on the sky
looks great
Don't leave.
Don't leave me here alone.
I don't want to be alone
Don't go.
Don't go, I'm scared.
I don't want to be here alone
South River
Wake up!
That's it for Shensu
I gotta go
Where are you going
go home
You don't want the Deep Sea anymore?
I
I want to go with you
I can't take you
That
I'll see you again
Is it right
Sorry, Nanhe
sorry
Silly boy
It's really not your fault.
Orion
look
It's almost dawn
South River I
I know
Sometimes the world looks grey
Not as colorful as in the dream
But even so
There must be some light waiting for you.
Even if it's just a small moment
It's worth your effort to live
You must never again
Nanhe, I know.
Go ahead
I hope every time you laugh in the future
It's all sincere
like me
South River
Thank you
Thanks
This season in my house
The grass is like the waves
The wind blows
All blinding
Just like
Like in the painting
*** by richardsxie ***