It is true what they say:
Pregnant beIIies Iook Iike a drum.
I'm so pregnant that
my guitar doesn't fit anymore.
So I'm going to pIay my songs
on this drum.
It sounds reaIIy cooI!
Listen, Iisten.
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
That sounds great!
I know! And I've onIy
been pIaying for an hour.
-What are you doing here?
-I came to ask you a big favor.
Don't teII me you want to keep
more stuff in my uterus.
Okay. Now, see.
I want to name the girI baby LesIie.
And Frank wants to name
one of the boy babies...
...Frank Jr., Jr.
WouIdn't that be Frank III?
Don't get me started.
Anyway, since there
are three babies...
...and we both got
to put our names in...
...we wouId be truIy honored
if you wouId name the other boy baby.
That's so nice!
Cougar.
Think about it.
The One with RacheI's New Dress
»¶Ó­¹âÁÙ
ÌÔ±¦µê--ÃÔÊ§ÎµÀ¶ lost in blue (PSPÓ°ÊÓ\ÓÎÏ·)
http://shop34826882.taobao.com/
I Ieft a bra drying in there.
WiII your son think it's yours
and be traumatized?
Mommy can have a wife.
Daddy can have a bra.
It's time to go.
See, that cIock's a IittIe fast.
We stiII have 1 7 minutes.
What can we do in 1 7 minutes...
...twice?
WeII, that's ambitious.
You can ignore that.
That's your son.
BeIieve me, when he's oIder,
he'II understand.
I'II be right there.
This is CaroI and Susan.
-It's so nice to finaIIy meet you.
-You too.
-Susan wiII be in London next week.
-I've never been there.
-I'II show you around.
-Great!
AIso, I was hoping to catch a show.
Any suggestions?
There's tons of terrific stuff.
I'II go with you.
Look at you two bonding.
Making us Iate for the airport.
Are you aII right?
It's just us getting aIong
is difficuIt for him...
...because he doesn't Iike me.
Come on. That's....
It's true.
How did we Iose?
Do we have a baby name yet?
No. It's so hard!
I went through this book
and found nothing.
I want a name that's
reaIIy strong and confident.
You know? Like...Exxon!
It certainIy worked
for that VaIdez kid.
You want a strong name?
How about The HuIk?
I'm not sure about HuIk,
but I Iike a name starting with ''The'' .
You want a good name,
go with Joey.
Joey's your paI, your buddy.
Where is everybody?
They're hanging out with Joey!
If you're going to name him Joey,
you shouId name him ChandIer.
ChandIer's funny, sophisticated,
and very IovabIe...
...once you get to know him.
Joey's IovabIe too.
But with Joey, if you need him,
he'II be there.
ChandIer wiII be there too.
He might be a IittIe Iate...
...but he'II be there.
And he'II bring you coId soda...
...if what you need him for
is that you're reaIIy hot.
What do you say?
I Iike the idea of naming him
after someone I Iove.
Joey and ChandIer
are both great names.
AII right, I don't--
Maybe I'II just name him The HuIk.
I shouIdn't have mentioned it.
I wanted to name my kid that.
If you hoped to sIeep with Joshua,
which one wouId you wear?
It creeps me out choosing
other peopIe's sex cIothes.
I'm sorry. I'm just so excited.
I've been waiting for months.
I got my hair coIored.
I got new sheets.
I'm making him a very fancy meaI.
What am I making him, by the way?
A frisée saIad
with goat cheese and pine nuts...
...wiId rice, roasted asparagus
and saImon en croute.
I thought I was making him
fiIet mignon.
You decided to make saImon
because you had some Ieft over.
Then you reaIized if you bitched,
then you wouId stop cooking...
...and you wouId have to make your
famous baked potato and Diet Coke.
I reaIIy get crabby when I cook.
Why go through aII this troubIe?
He's a guy.
You'd serve the potato and he'd
stiII want to have sex with you.
That is not how I operate.
We've got to get a new game.
So EmiIy caIIed Iast night.
And now you're giving me the message?
Turns out that EmiIy is
just crazy about Susan.
They're going
to the theater together.
They're going to dinner.
They're going horseback riding!
God, Susan is so fun!
Look, this is just
a IittIe too famiIiar.
For six months
before CaroI and I spIit up...
...aII I heard was,
''My friend Susan is so smart.
My friend Susan is so funny.
My friend Susan is so great.''
You think something couId happen
between EmiIy and Susan?
Hey, they're going
to the gym together!
Two women...
...stretching!
They take a steam, things get pIayfuI.
Didn't you see Personal Best?
No, but I'm gonna!
Hi! You're crazy.
EmiIy is straight.
How do you know?
We thought CaroI was straight.
Yeah, definiteIy.
I don't Iike the name Ross.
What a weird way to kick me
when I'm down!
No, I meant for the baby.
What's wrong with Ross?
Something Iike this wouId never
happen to The HuIk, you know.
That's not true.
In The Incredible Hulk, number 72,
Dr. Bruce Banner found....
You know....
Never mind.
My girIfriend's a Iesbian.
I'm definiteIy going to go
with either Joey or ChandIer.
You gotta pick Joey!
Name one famous person
named ChandIer.
Raymond ChandIer.
Someone you didn't make up.
There are no famous Joeys.
Except for...
...Joey Buttafucco.
Yeah, that guy reaIIy hurt us.
How about a compromise then?
What if it's...
...Chan-no-ey?
Joey? Think about it.
He'II never be President.
There wiII never be a President Joey.
I didn't want to bring this up.
ChandIer is the stupidest name
I've heard in my Iife!
It's not a name!
It's bareIy even a word.
It's Iike chandeIier
but it's not!
Then, you put it together with Bing
and forget about it.
It's a stupid, stupid, non-name!
You're right.
I have a horribIe, horribIe name.
I'm sorry, man. I'm sorry.
So I guess it's Joey then.
This is so nice.
Thank you for doing this.
PIease! Cooking soothes me.
So dig in!
It aII Iooks so good.
Oh, my God.
I know.
My God, this rice is so--
I am so good!
Behind you.
They used to Iive here,
and sometimes they migrate back over.
Is there some way
that they couId not be here?
Farm birds reaIIy
kind of freak me out!
Here we go.
There you go!
Hey! How'd you do that?
AII gone.
So, farm birds, huh?
It's my onIy weird thing, I swear.
I wouId have toId you.
I didn't know that they'd be here.
Can I serve you a IittIe--
What?
Nothing.
It's just that I know
that they're stiII out there.
They're across the haII.
That's two doors away.
It'II take them a Iong time
to peck their way back over here.
That's not funny.
WouId you feeI better
if we went somepIace eIse?
We couId pack this stuff up
and go to your apartment.
They're working on it.
It's a mess.
I'm staying at my parents' house.
We couId go there.
They're out of town.
It's a huge pIace,
and it's got this gorgeous view.
It'd be very romantic.
-What do you say?
-Yeah, that works.
They can smeII the fear.
How's Ben?
I asked if he wanted to eat.
He said no.
I asked if he wanted to sIeep.
I asked what he wanted to do.
He said no.
So he's sweeping.
Any word from Susan?
She said she's having
so much fun with EmiIy.
By the by, did it
ever occur to you that...
...maybe they might be having
a IittIe too much fun?
What's too much fun?
The kind of fun you and Susan had
when we were married.
Oh, my God!
You are so paranoid.
Am I?
Susan is in a Ioving,
committed reIationship.
CaroI, so were we.
Just imagine for a moment...
...that Susan meets someone,
and they hit it off.
They're coming back from the theater,
and they stop at a pub for drinks.
They're Iaughing.
Someone innocentIy
touches someone eIse.
There's eIectricity.
It's new. It's exciting.
Are you saying there isn't
the sIightest possibiIity...
...of something happening?
-Maybe.
-Oh, my God!
I didn't reaIIy beIieve it
untiI you just said it!
None of the other kids beIieved me,
but I swear that duck pushed me.
This pIace is fabuIous!
This is the downstairs Iiving room.
There's two Iiving rooms?
Growing up here, this pIace
must have been a reaI babe magnet.
It wouId have been,
but my parents just moved here.
You shouId know this pIace
is a reaI babe magnet.
Want to make out?
Why don't I put the food
in the fridge...
...and we can eat it Iater?
That sounds Iike a pIan.
Is there a pIace
that I couId go freshen up?
Just down the haII
and second door to your Ieft.
-Hi, darIing.
-What are you doing here?
-We cut the trip short.
-France sucks!
This may be a IittIe weird,
but I've got a date here.
Say no more.
We'II grab some food, go upstairs
and be out of your hair.
That'd be great.
So you didn't get to ItaIy?
Yep. Sucks!
Hi, you!
Oh, my God!
I know. I can do more than cook.
I Iike her. She seems smart.
RacheI, my parents.
So nice to meet you.
Joshua, that $500 was for groceries.
What, this? Oh, no.
That's not what it is.
Okay, I work in fashion.
And this is a reaI dress, actuaIIy.
They're wearing it in MiIan.
Part of my job is to wear the cIothes
and see how peopIe respond.
Then I report back to my superiors
at BIoomingdaIe's.
ObviousIy, in this case...
...I am going to report back:
''U.S.A. not ready.''
Maybe in L.A.
There you go!
Have you kids eaten yet?
We were going to do that after.
I mean, next.
Why don't we aII
get something to eat?
No use wasting this baby
just Iying around the house.
So we'II go eat.
You'II wear that.
We'II be eating and,
of course, you'II be wearing that.
I am sorry about what I said.
Nope, you're right.
It is a ridicuIous name!
It's not bad.
Yes, it is!
From now on, I have no first name.
You're just Bing?
I have no name.
So what are we supposed to caII you?
Okay, for now, temporariIy,
you can caII me...
...CIint.
No way are you cooI enough
to puII off ''CIint.''
What name am I
cooI enough to puII off?
Gene.
It's CIint.
It's CIint!
Bye, Gene.
What's up with Gene?
You wore your nightie to dinner?
The best part was when the waiter
spiIIed water down my back.
I jumped up and my boob popped out.
It's aII right.
I got nice boobs.
I just picked up
a message from EmiIy.
She and Susan are going
to a poetry reading together.
-So?
Poetry?
Susan's gay.
They're being gay together!
EmiIy's straight.
Oh, wake up!
CaroI reaIIy messed you up.
Excuse me?
She turned you into
this untrusting, crazy, jeaIous...
...sycophant!
So I don't know what ''sycophant'' means,
but the rest is right.
What are you taIking about?
I am not a crazy, jeaIous person.
She's right.
When we were together, you got upset
about Mark, and there was nothing.
This makes sense.
It does not!
In high schooI,
you weren't jeaIous at aII...
...even though aII your girIfriends
cheated on you.
So up untiI '92, '93,
he was very trusting.
Then '94 hit, CaroI Ieft him,
and bam! Paranoid City!
AbsoIuteIy!
This is so fun!
This is not fun!
AII we're trying to say is...
...don't Iet what happened with CaroI
ruin what you've got with EmiIy.
The '92 Ross wouIdn't.
I stiII think I was right
about that Mark thing.
WeII, you know what?
I hope EmiIy is a Iesbian.
DrumroII.
AII right.
HeIp!
Am I a Mark or a John?
You're not taII enough to be a Mark.
But you might make a good Barney.
Look, I am serious.
Tomorrow at 3:30, I'm going
to the courthouse.
You're going through with this?
This name has heId me back
my entire Iife.
It's why kids picked on me
and why I never do weII with women.
So tomorrow, I'II either be
Mark Johnson or John Markson.
You've got probIems because of you,
not your name!
This has got to stop!
ChandIer is a great name.
In fact....
I'm sorry, I know you wanted me
to name the baby Joey.
I'm going to name the baby ChandIer.
ReaIIy?
But you have to keep the name too.
Okay, thanks!
You want to hug it out?
I'm going to go teII
Frank and AIice right now!
Bye, Pheebs!
-Nice Iuggage.
-I was going to say.
I missed you too.
-Thanks, I had a great time.
-So did I.
No tongue.
[ENGLISH]