Hey!
Sweet sixteen!
That’s right!
Is my birthday!
Arms are better,
got my cast off too...
And it’s snowing...!
Cool!
This is gonna be a good day.
Happy Birthday, Wally.
Oh, my favorite breakfast!
Heaping piles of everything!
Thanks, Mom.
You know,
if you ever come up for air,
I can take you to the DMV to get
your driver’s license after school.
This weather would be
a good proving ground.
Not really in a big rush
to drive, Dad.
‘Cause... you know.
I’m me.
You certainly are.
Plus, the team’s throwing me
a big surprise-party
this afternoon, at the Cave.
In school today, ask your teacher
the definition of “surprise”.
You want “surprise”,
just watch Miss Martian’s expression
when I collect my birthday kiss.
Well, I have a surprise for you.
Or, at least, your aunt Iris does.
And a special shout out
to my nephew Wally,
wishing him a very happy
sixteenth birthday.
So cool!
Now, for school closures.
The following schools
have declared today a snow day:
Dubuc Elementary, Spisak Junior High,
Central City High, Keystone High...
Oh, yes!
Could life get any sweeter?
Subs by mko_ro
www.addic7ed.com
Season 1, episode 20
“Coldhearted”
Recognized: Kid Flash
B-0-3
Zeta tube network
now offline,
due to extreme
atmospheric conditions.
Wow, I just made it.
It’d be a tragedy
if I miss my own...
Surprise!
What...?
Oh, you guys, you shouldn’t have...
Right, not like you’ve been hinting
for days, or anything.
- I made two cakes.
- Awesome! What will you, guys, eat?
We’ll split the cupcake.
- Make a wish!
- Way ahead of you...
You know... If I tell you my wish,
it won’t come true.
But, if you guess...
Nope!
Guess again!
Happy Birthday!
You settling in Ok?
Oh, yeah.
Just “like home”.
I know this is all very new
and intimidating,
But I promise you...
Some day...
You’ll get used
to watching Wally eat.
Think we should tell him?
You’re getting warmer, babe!
But...
I can make you warmer still.
He is the only one
who doesn’t know!
Then, please...
Allow me.
Oh, man...
Attention, Team!
Suit up. Polar stealth.
Mission briefing in five.
Where is Flash?
Flash and Red Tornado
already have their assignments.
A massive ice storm
has paralyzed North America
from coast to coast.
Satellite imagery has detected
five flying Ice Fortresses,
source unknown,
which seem to be responsible
and must be stopped.
Well, can’t the Watchtower blow them
out of the sky, or something?
What’s a “Watchtower”?
The League’s orbiting Headquarters
is not weaponized.
And with both Green Lanterns off-world,
I need all hands on deck.
Does that mean
what I think it means?
The League and the Team,
fighting side by side?
Wow, really?!?
Now that’s a birthday wish
come true!
Superboy, use the Super-Cycle
to rendezvous with the Batplane
at Ice Fortress 1.
You’ll drop off Robin and Aqualad,
then continue on with Wolf
to meet up with Black Canary and
Red Tornado at Ice Fortress 2.
Miss Martian, Artemis and Zatanna,
take the Bio-Ship and rendezvous
with Green Arrow and Martian Manhunter
at Ice Fortress 3.
Other Leaguers will deal
with Fortresses 4 and 5.
Sending all coordinates now.
Uh... Batman?
I think you skipped...
Kid Flash.
A young girl in Seattle is in desperate need
of a heart transplant.
With all conventional air traffic
grounded by the storm,
you’ll need to pick up
the donor heart in Boston
and run the 3,000 miles
across country.
No! No, no, no, no, no!
He can’t seriously expect me to skip
the first ever League-Team team-up!
Who is this girl?!?
Does it matter?
No... of course not...
But... can’t we zeta...
Zeta-Tubes  are offline.
Sorry…
Right. Then...
How could I say “no”?
Seriously, HOW?
Guess I won’t be needing the stealth...
Speedy delivery boy...
At your service.
Law enforcement
across the country
has been alerted to your mission
and is clearing your route.
Lucky stiffs!
Put your backs to work,
we have to clear this road!
Too late, too late!
Someone ordered a pizza?
What you’re delivering
is considerably more precious
to a girl who’s life depends on it.
Duh! I meant if anyone
ordered a pizza for ME!
The guy burns a lot of calories
running a few mph higher
than the speed of sound.
Sorry, no.
Now listen:
This pack is heavily insulated
for shock absorption.
But that doesn’t mean the organ within
needs any extraneous jostling.
So no crumpling.
Got it.
Your PDA…?
You have four hours to deliver the heart
before it’s no longer viable.
- Is that clear?
- As crystal, babe...
Then, go...
Guess asking for her number
is pointless...
- Do you see him?
- Nope.
- Did you see him?
Making decent time, at least.
I’m at max speed now,
but if I push it,
maybe I can dump this load, save the girl
and still join the real action!
Aw, come on! Robin and Aqualad,
with Batman, Aquaman and Flash?
Who’s missing from this picture?
Gotta find me a little detour...
Aw, man!
I’d give this arm
for a double chili cheese burger,
or a “Tacostada”,
or a “Chicken Whizee”!
He’s due to pass here any minute.
Lovely...
Now all I have to do
is get his attention.
Any ideas?
Who is THAT?
WHO is that?
It’s him!
Go! Get outta here!
I’ll handle Vandal.
“You’ll handle” me?
Little hero...
Do you really think you have
what it takes to survive...
...Vandal Savage?
This guy is so going down...
When I heard authorities were cordoning off
this highway for a speeds trap,
I assumed I’d be confronting
Flash himself.
He and I are due for a reckoning.
But I suppose I must settle
for making him miserable,
by killing his brat sidekick,
instead.
Troopers are safely out of range...
Good.
Frees me up to show Savage
just what a “brat sidekick” can do.
Kinda bashing my head
into a brick wall here.
Need a new approach.
Well, you’re truly running circles
around me.
How will I cope?
Not “coping” so great now,
is he?
What am I doing?
Sure, I’d love to finish trashing this
big jerk, but that won’t save the girl.
It should suffice.
Wasted about 15 minutes on Savage,
but I can still reach Seattle on time.
Great,
out of snacks.
Dude, you’re so
running on fuel right now!
But that wouldn’t help the girl either.
But forget the hunger, forget
the freezing temp, forget the windchill…
Just go!
Go!
Kid Flash!
I made it!
I’m here!
I’m… I’m sorry.
You’re too late.
No! No, look, I’ve got
almost twenty minutes to spare!
I know...
But she passed away 12 minutes ago.
Twelve...?
12 minutes?
Please...
Don’t blame yourself.
I’m sure you got here
as fast as you could.
12 minutes...
The fight took 15...
Maybe another recipient
can be found...
Superman, Captain Marvel and Doctor Fate
brought down the fourth Ice Fortress.
Kid Flash! We’ve been waiting for you!
Where is the Queen’s heart?
Wait, the girl’s dead, so now
the heart’s going to a queen?
The girl IS the Queen!
Queen Perdita of Vlatava,
age ten.
And she’s not dead,
but she IS running out of time.
I’ve been conned!
No!
I’d love to take these creeps out,
but can’t put the heart at risk.
Again.
They’re blocking the stairs,
so...
We’ll take the highroad!
That was nauseatingly familiar...
Count Vertigo...
Now it all makes sense.
Queen Perdita stands between
her uncle Vertigo and the Vlatavan Crown!
Crawling away…
Is the young hero reduced to that?
- Hey, I’m not proud.
- Apparently.
But not defeated either!
Not while I still have
one weapon left!
My big mouth!
I don’t get it, Vertigo!
You were defeated,
with the rest of the Injustice League.
How come you’re not in Belle Reve prison,
with your putrid pals?
As a member of the Vlatavan Royal Family,
I have “immunité diplomatique”.
As long as no crimes against Vlatava
can be proven against me.
But when the Queen needed a heart,
Count Heartless heard opportunity knock!
The Ice Fortresses were all part
of the plan to murder your niece!
And Savage, he intentionally stole me,
as a favor to you!
It is nice to have friends...
Now, shall we see if I can kill
two hearts with one blow...?
Take your best shot...
Yes!
Enough!
‘D love to continue
this love fest, Count...
But you’re not my priority.
Tell me there’s still time...
Take it! Go!
Right, right...
Send word to all our team staff!
Wally’s birthday dinner
will be completely dried out.
Shh! Mary!
Hawkman, Hawkwoman, Captain Atom
and Wonder Woman have defeated
a fifth flying Ice Fortress.
But this just in...
Despite the best efforts of  Kid Flash
and the team of transplant surgeons,
young Queen Perdita of Vlatava
died.
On the operating table,
at Seattle Medical Center.
Count Vertigo...
That’s “King Vertigo” to you,
peasant...
- King?
- Perdita is dead.
And the beauty of it is…
I never laid a hand on her.
And now no one
can lay a hand on you...
As King of Vlatava,
I’m untouchable.
Let’s test that theory!
Now, now, little hero,
you’ll pull your stitches.
Besides,
who exactly are you mad at?
She died on the table.
All that planning,
all that effort...
Neither of us needed bothered.
Right... And now, it must kill you
to know that you owe favors
to Vandal Savage and...
I’m guessing five ice villains,
for nothing!
Not at all!
They played their roles in my attempt
to rid Vlatava of Perdita.
We couldn’t know
it was unnecessary.
So you all still deserve credit
for attempted murder!
It’s called...
“Regicide”...
“You’re busted”, jerkface!
I believe you know
Queen Perdita...
No...
It’s called...
“Regicide”....
Count Werner Vertigo...
As Queen of Vlatava, I hereby accuse you
of high treason against the Crown
and revoke your diplomatic immunity.
No!
Send this clown to Belle Reve.
Well-played, children.
Admittedly, well-played.
This round goes to you.
And, please, by all means,
allow the victory to go to your heads.
Thank you...
Your plan worked perfectly.
Well, when I woke up and found out
you were in Recovery,
I knew Vertigo would make
another attempt on your life.
Unless, A, he thought you were dead,
and, 2, he lost that darned immunity.
And was sent away for good.
That sword is belonging to my country,
not to the Count.
I would be pleased for you to have it.
As a reward?
Or as a souvenir?
It is the King’s royal lunch!
The League destroyed
the five Ice Fortresses,
but failed to capture
whomever was behind them.
But Icicle Sr., Icicle Jr., Killer Frost,
Captain Cold and Mr. Freeze are,
by far,
the most-likely suspects.
That’s impossible.
All five were in their cells
for the duration of the crisis.
The sword was cool,
but this just seemed like
the right souvenir for the right mission.
Dude, I’ve just heard.
You saved an entire country!
Major kudos!
What can I say?
I’m the man...
The man who finally figured out
that the sweetest birthday present
a lucky stiff like me could ever get...
was seeing that little girl smile.
Subs by mko_ro
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net