In one of the most remote and
unspoiled wildernesses on the planet,
a bizarre array of creatures
struggle to survive.
The place is the ever-changing Eden
called Tasmania¡­
an island sanctuary for an assortment of
creatures found nowhere else in the world,
located about 240 kilometres south
of mainland Australia.
Standing alone in what many
call the Southern Ocean,
Tasmania endures the most
relentless winds and seas on Earth.
This area, known as the roaring forties,
collects moisture from both the Atlantic
and the Indian Oceans,
and parts of the sparsely populated island
see more than 250cm of rain each year.
As the air rises,
the rain turns to sleet,
and the sleet to snow,
signalling the arrival of winter.
Seeking refuge deep inside a hollow tree
is an eastern quoll.
The quoll is a marsupial,
and her 4 babies have been out of the pouch
for just one week.
They depend completely on their mother
for warmth and food.
In order to produce enough milk
to suckle her young through winter,
the quoll must leave them to find food.
At 1,500 metres up,
few animals can survive,
and the cat-sized eastern quoll
is the largest carnivorous marsupial
to be found at this altitude.
The quoll keeps an eye out
for small birds and mammals
that could make a meal.
But instead,
she spots a struggling wombat.
At one metre long,
the wombat is the world's largest burrowing mammal,
and far too big for the quoll to eat.
But she's curious ¨C
the wombat seems to be treading on thin ice.
Cries from the nest
signal that the quoll babies
want their mother to return.
She'll have to hunt later
when they're asleep.
Introduced predators such as dingoes and foxes
have rendered eastern quolls
all but extinct on the Australian mainland.
Tasmania is believed to be their last refuge.
After its narrow escape on the ice,
the wombat moves more cautiously.
It survives on a diet of grass and roots,
and must drink regularly.
Wombats sometimes travel many kilometres
in order to find fresh water.
A white-breasted sea eagle
follows the path of Tasmania's
highest mountain chain,
the Du Cane Range.
The eagle bears witness
to a rare Australian sight.
The peaks may only be 1,500m high,
but for a few weeks each winter
they are shrouded in snow.
Tasmania was once connected
to the Australian mainland by a land bridge.
About 11 or 12,000 years ago,
rising sea levels cut it away,
creating this unique habitat.
Tasmania is home to one of the world's
largest expanses of temperate rainforest.
It is one of the only places on Earth
where you can see jungle covered in snow.
Even in the valleys,
animals must endure freezing cold winters.
The echidna manages to survive here
because it has thicker fur than
its relatives on the mainland.
It seeks out patches of soil between the snow,
then uses its long snout
to detect its staple foods
ants, termites and worms.
The snout is so sensitive to vibration,
it can locate the tiny animals
even when they are deep underground.
Unfortunately, all the echidna finds today
is a shivering potoroo
a rat-size marsupial
and relative of the kangaroo.
For the Tasmanian blue-tongue lizard,
the cold is too severe.
He spends the winter asleep
under a blanket of leaf litter.
In the lowland rainforest,
even a few days of winter sunlight
can completely melt the snow.
A female Tasmanian devil
takes advantage of the sunshine
and moves her family to a new den.
Her babies are just a few months old,
so they still rely on her
for food and transportation.
These scavengers were named "devils"
by early European settlers
because of their bad 'tempers'
and spine-chilling screeches.
Suddenly, the mother hears a cry from the old den.
She has left one of her daughters behind.
The mother scuttles back to rescue it.
Tasmanian devils give birth to 20 or more young,
but the mother can only nurse four.
So only the strongest will survive
and eventually emerge from the pouch.
When these 3 young males compete for milk,
their smaller sister is often squeezed out.
Today is just not her day.
She's been left behind,
missed her meal,
and now it seems
she's been forgotten again.
But this time,
the mother remembers to call her.
This pademelon wallaby
has just one joey to take care of,
so he's not nearly as likely to be misplaced.
He will abandon the sanctuary
of the pouch in the spring.
But right now,
the pouch provides both food and shelter
so there's very little incentive to leave.
As spring arrives,
the alpine ice begins to melt
and the water feeds the streams.
This is when Tasmania's many rivers and waterfalls
reach their highest levels.
And at this time of year,
the rivers and estuaries
are also brimming with fish.
It's the perfect time for the sea eagle to feast
The sea eagle is the ultimate aerial predator.
Its two-metre wingspan
gives it aerodynamic versatility,
but it's also cunning.
When stalking,
a sea eagle flies towards the sun
to prevent its shadow falling ahead
and warning prey of its approach.
It then swoops in low
and takes the fish by surprise.
Sea eagles rarely miss,
and the technique is so effective
that they only need to
spend 10 minutes a day hunting.
As spring warms the coast,
millions of seabirds flock to Tasmania to feed.
Migratory stints and shearwaters
join permanent residents
like the cormorants and swans.
And Tasmania's offshore islands
are colonized by gannets and shy albatrosses,
who gorge themselves in preparation for breeding
Due to a collision of ocean currents,
the seas surrounding Tasmania
form some of the most biologically unique
cold water habitats in the world.
Giant kelp-forests,
up to 65 metres tall,
dance in the swell
and provide a home for a host
of bizarre sea creatures.
Some display bold patterns or colours.
Others, like the weedy sea dragon
and the leafy sea dragon,
have had millions of years to
evolve almost perfect camouflage.
In the weeks following the long winter,
the sea remains cold,
and this triggers Tasmania's
marine creatures to breed.
This male giant cuttlefish snatches a female
right under the watchful eye of a rival.
During the act of mating,
the nearly one metre long male
places a sperm sac inside the smaller female.
The female stores the sperm in 2 special organs
until she is ready to fertilize her eggs.
With big-bellied seahorses,
it is the male rather than
the female, who gives birth.
But first he has to persuade
her to hand over her eggs.
The male displays his swollen
pouch to attract a mate
and deter any rivals.
The pair then performs a courtship dance
that can last for several days.
Once the female is suitably seduced,
she transfers her eggs into his pouch.
The male is then responsible
for fertilizing and incubating the eggs,
and eventually giving birth to the babies.
The courtship rituals employed
by Australian carpet sharks
are anything but tender.
The male tries to seduce his intended
by biting her violently,
and females must often contend
with several suitors at once.
Once the male has secured a mate,
he will hold her in a pre-mating grasp for hours
until eventually she allows him to mate with her.
Then immediately afterwards,
the relationship is over
and the male leaves in search of another mate.
During spring,
Tasmania's highlands are bathed in sunshine.
The warmth awakens the frost-covered vegetation
and turns the winter ice to water.
Alpine flowers now flaunt their colours.
At four months old,
the young eastern quolls are
nearly as big as their mother.
They emerge from their den
to explore their surroundings.
A venomous tiger snake
is on the lookout for a meal,
and an inexperienced marsupial like this
makes an easy target.
The quoll retreats to the safety of the den
but the snake won't give up that easily.
It hasn't eaten since autumn.
Following her instincts,
the mother stands between
the snake and her young,
even though she is putting
her own life on the line.
Her show of aggression succeeds,
and the snake slithers away.
For now at least,
her family is safe.
As temperatures rise,
the last remnants of fog
disappear from the rainforest.
Sunlight begins to penetrate
deep into isolated valleys
that contain some of the oldest
and tallest trees in the world.
There are trees here 90 metres high,
and some are over 2,000 years old.
The blue-tongue lizard emerges from hibernation.
He is hungry,
and on the lookout for a meal.
The potoroo rarely ventures
far from dense cover.
It uses its long nose to forage for fungi.
But today it finds some fruit.
Soon, the lizard joins in the feast.
Nearby, a carnivorous tiger quoll
is also looking for food.
It follows the scent trail of a potential victim
but then spots an easier target.
The Tasmanian devil is Australia's
largest carnivorous marsupial,
and it possesses an excellent sense of smell.
She moves in for the kill.
The tiger quoll quickly retreats.
He is not prepared to risk his life,
and he knows he is no match for the devil.
Tasmanian devils have jaws as
strong as a dog 4 times their size,
and the hungrier they are
the more aggressive they are.
The mother devil often leaves
her 6 month old offspring
while she searches for food.
For the youngsters, it's a chance to play
and explore the lush world around them.
The little female is content
to bask in the sun.
But with three boisterous brothers around,
it's difficult to get any peace.
The males still like to ride
on their mothers back,
even though they are far too big to do so.
It won't be long
before the mother will leave them
all to fend for themselves.
Her patience is already wearing thin.
Once again, there's no room for the little female.
She is fast becoming the outcast of the family.
By summer,
the sun-baked mountains are
completely free of snow.
Many of the alpine plants found here
do not occur anywhere else in the world.
Massive cushion plants dominate the landscape.
The giant pandani is the world's
largest heath plant,
standing up to 12 metres tall.
The buttongrass plains are home to many animals.
A mountain dragon basks in the summer sun,
but keeps one eye on the wombat
as it bulldozes through the scrub.
It's on the lookout for water again¡­
and so is the tiger snake.
In mid summer,
even temperatures in the highlands
can soar to more than 30 degrees Celsius,
so freshwater streams are popular destinations.
The ungainly wombat disturbs the tiger snake.
It is one of the most venomous
snakes in the world,
and not to be toyed with.
The wombat wisely decides to give way.
Nearby, a male eastern quoll
is looking for some shade from the scorching sun,
but he's being attacked by mosquitoes.
A skink turns the quoll's attention to food.
The stunned reptile
releases its tail as a defence mechanism.
The quoll devours it as a starter,
then consumes the main course.
No reptile, bird or small mammal
is safe from jaws of this carnivore.
Tasmania's kangaroos are out in force,
enjoying the summer sun.
Now that some of the joeys
have left the pouch,
the females are ready to mate again¡­
and there's always a willing male to be found.
Meanwhile, the youngsters start
learning how to be independent.
The odd one takes the easy option
and goes back to the pouch to drink,
but most are now eating grass.
Offshore, thousands of gannets have
taken up residence on Pedra Branca Island
off Tasmania's south coast.
The males and females greet each other
with a ritualized display.
Each couple raises just one chick.
This one is 7 weeks old,
and still covered in down feathers.
As summer progresses,
these soft feathers will be shed
first from the wings,
then the body,
and finally from the head.
Older chicks often pester
and bully the younger ones.
Off the northwest coast of Tasmania,
shy albatrosses gather to breed
on the aptly named Albatross Island.
The fluffy 8-week-old chicks
depend on their parents for food.
Even in mid-summer,
the birds need thick down feathers
to protect them against any weather
the roaring forties may bring.
It's difficult to survive here,
and up to half of the island's 5,000 chicks
will be lost to either starvation
or the elements.
Exposed to 16 hours of light
every day during summer,
the rainforest soon becomes parched.
The echidna might not have to
overcome icy obstacles any more,
but he must now contend with bone dry soil.
If he detects something edible,
his short limbs and powerful claws
can dig through even the hardest terrain.
He is now permanently out of the pouch,
but the pademelon joey still
stays close to his mother.
For youngsters,
the rainforest can be a frightening place.
A young cockatoo begs to be fed,
and its mother obliges.
The commotion attracts the
attention of the tiger quoll.
Although it's adapted for life in the trees,
the quoll more often finds
its meals on the ground.
A young pademelon,
away from its mother,
makes a perfect target.
The predator uses the tree canopy as cover
to sneak up behind its quarry.
It takes just one lethal bite
to the joey's neck.
The tiger quoll can kill animals
over 3 times its own size.
The noise and the scent have
alerted the mother devil,
who is hot on the quoll's trail again.
Once more, the quoll must relinquish
its prize to its rival.
Tasmanian devils will hunt mammals and birds,
but they mostly scavenge and are equipped
with some of the strongest jaws
in the animal kingdom.
One of her 10 month old sons
tries to claim the meal for himself.
The quarrel draws one of his brothers.
Realizing she is out-numbered,
the mother devil takes a last look
at her children,
then leaves the area for good.
The brothers must now compete for the spoils.
The third son takes his place
at the carcass unopposed.
But once again,
the young female is left out.
Her brothers refuse to let her share in the feast.
The male devils will continue to squabble,
until they head off to live on their own.
The land has been sun-baked throughout the summer,
but the seas surrounding Tasmanian
are only just reaching their peak temperature.
This is when many marine creatures give birth.
But for others,
the warm water triggers aggression.
The carpet shark has found an octopus.
But the scent of blood in the water
attracts rivals to the scene
and starts a feeding frenzy.
Scavengers grab whatever they can
before the victor claims the prize.
A blue devil fish waits for his meal to hatch
in the form of baby cuttlefish.
Just 2.5cm long and defenceless,
many will not survive for more than a few minutes.
The mother tasselled anglerfish
reduces the risk of losing her young
by guarding her eggs until they hatch.
She has laid about 5,000 eggs
which are bound together in a gelatinous mass.
The young are only 1cm long,
yet already they resemble their mother.
At just 15mm long,
newborn seahorses are also perfect miniatures
of their father.
There's safety in numbers,
so their first instinct is to congregate.
They will grasp onto anything,
even each other.
During autumn the sea remains warm,
but temperatures above the water
are starting to cool.
The gannet chicks are preparing
to become independent.
By 3 months old,
their cries for food are already ignored.
The chicks have lost most
of their down feathers,
but are still prone to squabble.
Soon they will all leave the island,
only to return when they themselves
are ready to breed.
Now 4 months old,
the albatross chicks have doubled
in size since the summer.
Only the youngest chicks
still have down feathers,
and most have developed adult features.
The albatross has the longest
fledgling period of any bird.
And after several months of dependency,
it seems hard for the chick
to understand why its mother
now refuses to feed it.
The fledglings regularly flap their wings
in preparation for their first flight.
Even with a 2-metre wingspan,
each must wait for exactly the right wind
to help it lift off.
Finally, the moment arrives.
The young chicks watch the older ones leave.
Most of these birds will return
to breed after a few years,
but the albatross is unique
in that some remain at sea
for up to 9 years.
Autumn is when the animals
of the button-grass breed.
At 10 months old,
a newly-independent female quoll
looks for her first partner.
Female quolls woo males,
but because the males
are bigger and stronger,
they risk serious injury in doing so.
Luckily, this female will be accepted.
Soon the couple will mate,
and she will raise a family of her own.
With tiger snakes,
it's the male that courts the female,
and this male has mating in mind.
The snakes are immune to their own venom,
but rejection could still
result in a vicious fight.
The male carefully aligns
his lower body with hers.
If mating is successful,
the female will store his sperm over winter
to delay fertilization.
This means her young will be born in spring
when food is more plentiful.
As autumn progresses,
mountain clouds thicken
and head down towards the forest.
Temperatures in the valleys drop
and the fog returns.
The animals in the rainforest
begin to prepare for the
cold winter months ahead.
A platypus searches for a meal.
This mammal forages 12 hours day,
diving underwater
with its eyes, ears, and nostrils closed.
Closely related to the echidna,
the platypus has a highly
sensitive duck-like bill
that it uses to seek out prey.
But the platypus is not the only unusual animal
to lurk in Tasmania's streams.
Autumn is mating time for giant crayfish,
and the male must emerge from the water
to defend its territory against rival males.
At one metre long,
the giant crayfish is the world's
largest freshwater invertebrate.
The stand-off is mainly bluff,
and fights to the death are rare.
Most will live to be 60 years old.
The giant crayfish is only found
in the freshwater streams of northern Tasmania.
For this primeval animal,
Tasmania is definitely an Eden.
Nearby, the young female devil
attempts to cross a river.
Now a year old,
she and her three brothers have parted ways
and must fend for themselves.
This young pademelon
is also now independent,
but it is still vulnerable.
Fortunately, the Tasmanian devil
is looking for a mate,
not a meal.
She follows the scent trail of a nearby male.
He is wary of her approach,
and with good reason
courtship between devils
takes the form of ritualized combat.
The intense courtship lasts several days,
then she will fight him off.
The female devil has proved
she is a survivor.
Soon, she'll be the mother
of a family of her own.
As winter sets in once more,
the cold, roaring winds return.
But the creatures that live here
remain protected by the isolation
of this island paradise
- Tasmania.
www.mvgroup.org