Please buy a present for your wife.
They may not look good but they smell wonderful. Buy my flowers.
Lovely day
One should have flowers on a day like this. Buy some flowers
lt's a bargain. Please
- A present for your girlfriend!  - l don't have one.
Well
Maybe later
l'm here if you change your mind!
- Kaluga
Another one's coming. Looks like our man.
Herman
Let's go. Kley
Hey
l haven't got a girl. Give 'em to Mihailich. He's in a bad mood today.
Never mind Mihailich. You'll have a girlfriend soon.
- Did you forget?  - What?
You need to train your memory instead of chasing crooks.
Tomorrow
lmagine that Mihailich
Andrey
Be ready. Tomorrow you...
Sod off!
What a madhouse!
My stomach still hurts.
- Kaluga
They are bringing up the car.
Need some flowers? Fresh! From the countryside!
Stand by
Look at these flowers! So white!
What's happening there?
Where the devil did they come from?
What's the traffic police doing here?
Lots of people drive the wrong way down one-way streets to dodge the jams.
Don't worry
Unlike us
They'll just grab their money and leave.
Senior lieutenant Zhelyaznikov. Central district traffic police.
Hi.
Why have you parked here? Not enough space?
Sorry officer. Just stopped for a moment.
We needed to load something. We've got a heavy bag.
l'm already on my way.
What's the bag got to do with anything? This is a one-way street.
That sign doesn't apply to you? You reversed halfway down the lane.
So
Kaluga
We have a problem. A couple of plods are holding up our guys.
Get rid of them! Odessa
Listen
Did you hear that? Didn't see it... So what are we going to do now?
l don't like them.
- Maybe we can sort this out here and now?  - l don't like them.
You don't have to like us. But check my driver's permit.
Perhaps you'll like that.
A verbal warning
All OK
Well
What's in your bag?
Get out and open the bag for inspection.
Come in
Send backup and paramedics. Urgently! Can't you hear me? Now!
Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Cover me!
lnto the car! Quickly!
Kon! Do it!
Grenade! Down!
They're leaving!
Don't scream!
Watch your driving
- Guys
- Aksinya
- Whose fault is this accident?  - Please
She's probably bought her driving licence.
Daddy
Nice car. Could be an automatic.
But what guy? lt's that lady's car.
Get out!
Herman
lnto the ambulance!
Orda
Let's go!
Where did the medics get to?
God...
He could have killed me.
He aimed right at my face.
l want to live!
l have a family.
Don't
This morning
"Breaking News" reporters filming a traffic accident
involving the popular singer Aksinya witnessed a gunfight...
General Boldyrev speaking.
Call all department heads and Special Services commanders.
Meeting in my office. Right away.
This shootout put innocent citizens at risk
and the gangsters managed to escape
Now to an eyewitness report on these incredible events from pop singer Aksinya.
ln this street crowded with cars and people
The shooting that followed put people's lives at risk
including famous pop star Aksinya.
Please tell us
Honestly
They were running all over the place
And then the grenades! Just like in a real war.
And now some unique footage from our cameramen at the scene.
Both innocent bystanders and police died as a result of this firefight.
According to police
Not to compromise the investigation
Simply unbelievable! A cop crying on TV. That's a first.
You know
My key objective is to soften the image of the police.
No one will believe that they are heroes anyway.
So why not show them as
And a scandal is always good for any media campaign.
OK
l wish they'd give me a flashing light so l could sail through the traffic jams.
Miss! Check
- l didn't get it!  - Don't worry. lt'll be OK.
l'm at work
...this means that nobody is in control of the situation in our city.
lf even policemen fear to walk the streets
what about ordinary people like you and me?
We are forced to face an unpleasant fact.
The Moscow police is unable to remedy the current situation.
The forces of law and order are thoroughly corrupt
lf this corrupt
cannot protect our citizens
then let it not stop us from protecting ourselves.
l have always pushed for the free sale of small arms
and now the time has come.
Enough? Or need we see more?
What can we say to that?
We launched plan 'lnterception' while the trail was still warm.
Unfortunately it didn't bring swift results
so plan 'Hurricane' has been initiated.
The entire force has been put on full alert.
We've just received the first reports.
Eleven cars reported stolen have been recovered.
Nine wanted persons were apprehended.
Seven firearms and twelve knives have been seized
as well as two kilograms of narcotic substances...
What?
What are you saying?
Two kilograms of narcotic substances...
Don't you understand what's going on?
Grenades exploding in the streets!
And not just anywhere
All day the TV news has been showing a Moscow police sergeant crying at gunpoint.
The President's office has already called me twice.
And what do we have to show them? Seven knives?
Twelve.
Twelve knives and seven firearms.
Don't you see that these bastards declared war on us?
And we've got to respond not someday
Sergei Petrovitch
We have to wait until they give results.
Are we living in Japan?
Their clear-up rate for armed robberies is 76%.
And what is it here? Should l remind you?
Your standard measures usually have little effect.
ln a war they're useless.
No need to be dramatic. What war?
They're not terrorists. They're common criminals.
Really? Anything else of interest you can tell us about them
Sadly
We have reason to believe this gang
is responsible for a number of armed robberies of bank security cars
in different regions of the country.
They appear infrequently
All their raids are planned in great detail and executed impeccably.
So far they have made no mistakes.
Smirnov has been after them for two years
but so far has been unable to run them to ground.
Yesterday we received information about a possible hideout used by this gang.
The rest you are all aware of it by now.
Sooner or later they'll screw up and we'll get them.
And all this media hue and cry will gradually run its course.
lt's happened so many times before.
OK. l see. Any other suggestions?
Let's listen to our PR Director. Media witch-hunts are right up her street.
Captain Verbitskaya
l agree with Sergei Petrovitch. They've declared war on us.
So
won't be enough to lessen the impact of this PR disaster.
We must beat them on the same battlefield
within the virtual hyperspace of mass communications.
What space?
We need to turn the capture of this dangerous gang into a reality show.
A reality show!
One that demonstrates the courage and professional skills of the Moscow police
as well as the openness and humanity of the law enforcement authorities.
This show will be a world first.
lmagine
and the internet
Our defeat today must be turned into a triumph!
This is an interesting idea.
But to make it work we have to find them first.
Exactly.
You find them for me
and l'll take care of everything else.
- Sergei Petrovitch
ls the press release ready?
Just finishing it. l'll bring it for approval in half an hour.
Sergei Petrovitch
thank you for your support.
Katya.
You do understand what's happening?
All these TV reports
Some silly sergeant raised his hands.
My God
That's just an excuse.
You think l don't have enemies up there?
lt's all just politics!
lf you knew how much l miss your father now.
What a clever guy he was!
l hope you take after him.
Sir
Fine
What you're suggesting has never been done before.
But in the current situation it might be the only right solution.
lt's all or nothing.
l've already made all the necessary arrangements.
You'll have wide powers and resources
But you mustn't let me down.
You understand what the consequences would be?
Sir
l won't let you down.
Hamlet
Hot dogs again! Sanya
Thanks.
Actually
What are you looking at? Enjoying the view?
What's here to admire?
lt's not a city
Oleg
Otherwise
Why get married?
l've read that Moscow is 14th on the list of the world's most polluted cities.
Baku is top of the list
Oleg
Vovchik has turned up.
Let's go.
Well
A worthy death
lf he'd been a Viking
What shall we do?
- Hole up for a couple of days
Why did we get together
Why should we give up our business?
There's one less of us
What do you think
We should get out of here.
Someone must have tipped the cops off. This place may no longer be safe.
Yeah
There always is.
Well
Once
He'd hooked up with a chick and they wanted to smoke some weed
so they ordered a home delivery. Like a pizza
What's the address?
What address? l've only been there once in my life!
- Let's go
- To Chertanovo.  - l'm at work here.
What bloody work? Some worker...
What floor?
lt's on either the fourth or fifth floor. With a crappy door.
- Come on
What's up?
That's not part of the deal
And then they gave you the slip. This time
Of course they will. That's your fate.
No
Won't you
l'll rub you out myself!
What a madhouse.
Fine.
Calm down. Calm down.
We were joking
- That's the door.  - You sure?
Dead certain.
Ladies and gentlemen
We're having a party here.
Too late.
What now? Home to bed?
No. Let's drive around the district a bit more.
They've hardly gone far
They're somewhere here.
My inner voice tells me.
That's not your inner voice
That's how mine started.
So
Do you understand who the client is? What connections l'm offering?
All right
Look
You're a genius!
They went that way. Over there.
Your documents
Our cops are working hard
Bit insolent though.
Attention!
- At ease!  - At ease!
Special forces troopers!
Our mission is to neutralise a dangerous criminal gang.
We are also duty bound to avenge our comrades who fell yesterday.
Let us be worthy of their cherished memory!
Lieutenant-General Boldyrev will personally take command.
This means that those distinguishing themselves will be rewarded
and those screwing up will get the opposite treatment.
Now deputy operational commander Captain Verbitskaya
will explain some technical details.
Men!
Today you are not just special forces troops
but participants in a unique media project!
You will all be issued with miniature video cameras
that will be attached to your helmets using special fasteners.
Millions of TV viewers will be able to follow your every move virtually live.
What are you worried about
That's easy for you to say. This stuff costs fifty grand!
So what? You're letting the cops
Nobody will steal your precious cameras.
Are you sure?
Just consider the product placement value in such a top-rated show.
At today's prices that's worth far more than fifty thousand.
lnformation received suggests the suspects were spotted in Chertanovo.
An old lady recognised the photo.
Two patrols are on duty there. We're in contact and awaiting confirmation.
No need to wait. Action is always better than inaction.
lf they're there
And if not
Following up leads and suchlike.
What are we supposed to do with it? How's it switched on?
Just make sure you don't touch anything.
They're all switched on from central command.
- To your places!  - At the double! Come on now!
An incredible block.
Well
That old woman is hardly reliable.
Why not? lf l was a criminal
- Do you read me? You understand?  - Yes
- So
We're off the case. Special forces.
Until they get here we keep the building under surveillance.
Then we'll go home to bed.
Herman
Four in plain clothes are already in the block. We need to split.
Gotcha. See you on the eighth floor.
We're leaving.
Where are we going? All the entrances here connect up.
- He could be anywhere
Crazy architecture! Never seen anything like this.
Doesn't matter. We've got them cornered. Now
Dear
All these hunky guys in flak jackets
And the great thing was nobody's interfered with my work yet. Just the opposite.
OK
Verbitskaya
Firefight in Chertanovo. Smirnov's team reports they are in pursuit.
Call them off immediately! Everyone must stick to the plan!
Nobody does anything until we get there.
Have them block the entrances and wait for us.
Fall out!
To your positions!
Quickly!
How did they find us? Some bastard has ratted on us.
Valera
Look
l understand you're in a traffic jam but you'll be in time
What's this?
Valhalla. The official mineral water of our operation.
What water?
Pure and ecological.
Don't worry
Our troops need to drink. And the reporters won't say no to a freebie.
Free
They should pay us for the honour.
We can talk about that later.
We'll hold the first press conference in about 40 minutes when everyone is here.
Who's that biker?
ls he also with you?
He's not a biker. He is a well-known director.
Perhaps the best. At least in advertising.
ls he cleared for security?
- Yes
Sanya! Grenades!
My God! What was that? A gas explosion?
Have they all gone raving mad up there?
Why? They're catching criminals!
Get me a walkie-talkie! l'll talk to this Smirnov myself right now.
Smirnov?
Major Smirnov?
Call him Tambov. lt's his call sign.
Tambov! Do you read me?
ls he deaf? Tambov!
Smirnov!
Major Smirnov!
Tambov! Do you read me?
Tambov's here.
This is Captain Verbitskaya. What are you up to?
Grenades. Anti-personnel.
Almost cut us to ribbons. This floor is clear
Major
You were stood down long ago. l order you to leave the building immediately.
Do you understand me?
She's giving me orders?
Who am l speaking to?
Deputy chief of the operational HQ.
Captain
There are no special forces troops on our floor.
You can block the stairways and start combing the lower floors.
Listen
This is a special operation.
l've no time or desire to explain all its details.
Just follow orders and don't get in the way of professionals.
Understood?
l repeat
Understood.
So
lmmediately! Get all the inhabitants out of there.
Stop smiling. You're not on the dance floor.
So what do we do now?
Bitch!
Verbitskaya. Where the hell did they get hold of her?
You remember there was a General Verbitskiy
Died a couple of years ago. l heard about him getting his daughter a very cushy job.
- lt's probably her
l have to kiss her arse now?
Verbitskaya
What are you sitting here for?
Rise and shine! Let's go and check out the seventh floor.
Today you have a unique opportunity to watch
the capture of a dangerous gang live on TV.
Criminals hiding out in this block were involved
in yesterday's shootout in central Moscow.
Every half-hour there'll be a live update on the progress of this operation.
Helping us is deputy head of PR at Moscow police headquarters
Ekaterina Verbitskaya.
Good afternoon
Residents of block twenty-eight
Well
Get your documents and wait in your apartments.
Law enforcement officers will take you to safety.
Dad
Son
You should listen to them and do the opposite.
When you grow up
Besides
Hello.
You should have listened to the cops
We've got to go to Grandma's
Here's your granny!
You're policemen
Policemen don't point their guns at regular people. They're gangsters!
The son is smarter than his dad.
You're gangsters?
But we've got nothing. We're ordinary people! l'm just a taxi driver.
Smile
Don't be shy!
Please
Stop clucking
Smile
Kley!
You're always like this! lt's all your fault
We won't harm you. Just stay with you a while.
My God
Draw the blinds
Stop fidgeting.
Evacuate the building! Collect your documents and go to the exit.
Leave now! Evacuate the building!
Take your documents.
There's an evacuation. l'll call you back.
Please remain calm. You are being evacuated.
Get your documents and wait in your apartments.
Law enforcement officers will take you to safety.
Orda
We're on the 1 1 th floor
Keep your cell phone on.
Got you
lt's so noisy! Everybody's running! Shouting!
How would you assess the police evacuation operation?
Well
- Were they polite to you?  - Yes
They rang the doorbell and said:
"Come on
Listen
Do you understand yourself what you want to shoot here?
Roman
lt's all about to start and we'll handle whatever comes along.
About to start? lt's already begun! Or do grenades explode all the time here?
And you don't even know yourself what'll happen next.
Are you scared?
No
By the way
lt's common knowledge how all your special operations finish.
Walk down the corridor! Don't stop.
Go on. Have your documents ready.
Stop!
You there in the leather jacket! Stop!
Are you deaf?
Hurry!
After them
Grandpa!
- Grandpa!  - Looks like he's deaf.
Grandpa
- Orda.  - Herman
- How many?  - Five
Try to get to us. We'll meet you.
Herman
- Don't shoot! lt's Orda!  - Where is he?
Upper floor?
Are you wounded?
lf you feel like shooting
l noticed.
Who are you?
Us? We're doctors. And you?
We're doctors without borders.
And l'm Yuri.
But you can call me just Yura.
- Daddy!  - What?
We're all in the same boat here!
A submarine.
The first battle has definitely been lost.
What about the wounded?
Being evacuated via entrance No. 8. We cleared the place of journalists.
There are from five to seven gangsters. They're holed up in apartment 1 28
home to taxi driver Yury Shirokov and his two children.
l spoke to the Kremlin half an hour ago.
lf innocent people die during the operation
and it's shown live on TV
they will not forgive us our mistakes.
For now
l would prefer to conclude the operation in the evening
which is peak prime time.
Stop talking to me about the evening!
What should we do now?
What are you going to show the press? Not this
Prime time!
Katya
- Yes.  - So it's already digitised?
We can extract everything we need from it.
- What do you think?  - Sure
Roma
l still don't quite get what we are going to do.
Get ready for the press conference!
Two explosions over the last hour
Hey
A Moscow police spokesman claimed officers exchanged fire with the gang.
Look!
A Beretta 92. 9mm calibre.
A 1 6-round semi-automatic pistol.
Made completely out of stainless steel. Very rare
- Hold it. So
When you grow up
Listen
He may yet grow up to be a normal person.
What was it l said? You'd think normal people don't carry guns.
Kley
OK
At 1 6:35
There were more gangsters than we anticipated. Our troops returned fire.
And the criminals cowardly retreated into an apartment
where they probably have taken hostages.
Now we know where they are.
The first stage of this operation has been completed successfully.
Our top priority is to avoid civilian casualties.
Successfully completed? Bullshit!
So? lf you want to hear the truth on TV
The rest is just all lies.
They're not lying. lt's a reality show.
They might have a show
Look!
Do something useful instead. Bloody Spielberg wannabe.
- Hey
- Listen
You can't play Entropia without the internet working!
Can you connect a phone to your computer?
Yes
My son is a computer genius.
See the computer l bought him? Had to take a loan for it.
He'll do anything you ask him to.
l'm not helping criminals!
What do you mean you're not helping? Do what the man says right now!
You're a coward.
We're not suggesting you do anything bad. We're just telling people the truth.
Listen
And don't disrespect your father
OK
Of course. Here you are.
My daughter is also good at computers.
She hangs out online all day long.
So
Once again we look like complete idiots!
The criminals are always one step ahead of us.
What does it have to do with me? lt's your material.
What else is there for me to work with?
All l can do is to propose an editing solution.
Hold on. They've declared an information war on us. But they don't stand a chance.
- We hold all the aces.  - l hear this all day.
What exactly are you proposing?
Of course
Can't you hack into this damned "mail.ru"?
l'm afraid not. Most likely they've sent it elsewhere too.
lf they're smart enough they might have sent their footage to all the news agencies
and TV channels... Already.
Are you aware of what you're saying?
Do you realise what it means for us?
l am.
And l'm preparing countermeasures.
l'll write a new press release.
lt'll show these gangsters as terrorists who took two small children hostage.
Terrorists?
That's good.
That's right. Get on with it!
l need high-quality photographs of these kids.
Get in touch with the school they go to or find their relatives.
By any means necessary get me
heart-warming photos of these kids within an hour.
So that all female viewers' hearts will just melt.
And cut all telephone and cable lines in this block that allow internet access.
Great job! And the picture quality is good.
Your little video clip doesn't make any sense.
You uploaded it to the internet but they've got all the TV channels.
At least
- Maybe we should eat something?  - l don't want to eat.
- Did you do your homework?  - l'm not doing my homework!
We're hostages
And what if they don't kill us? Then we have to go to school tomorrow.
l'm not doing any homework anyway!
You are! Do what you're told.
Completely out of hand. Doesn't want to study.
Playing on his computer is all he cares about.
Every week the school calls me in for a talking-to.
You want me to try to have some positive influence on him?
Son
Cops always on your tail. Do you really need that?
- Yura
Then make something for us all.
Take a photo of me in this outfit with my bike. Then l'll take yours.
So what was the press conference like?
How were the reporters?
Buzzing like a swarm of bees but swallowed everything l told them.
Now everyone feels for the poor children.
Look over there. They're already on air. Good work.
Because of you the internet is down.
- How can l do my homework now?  - How is that my fault?
Hand me your Skylink
lnteresting
Look at your daddy
Need any help?
Want some coke? Come on.
Can your father really cook?
No. He can only use the microwave. Granny comes over to do the cooking.
Hey
- Shoot him
- Great stuff! Come on. Let's go again.  - Don't stop
What are you doing? Don't daydream! Can't you see he's attacking?
Drive him into the corner! Fire!
1 Kostikova Street. 6pm
Yura
Keep an eye on the potatoes.
Pass me the knife.
Did you leave your jacket there to test my curiosity?
Maybe l did.
l had a different image of your line of work.
But you've got a partner and a photo in your pocket. Against all the rules
TV has ruined you youngsters.
Rules...
You know
ls there any basil here?
- Only dill.  - That'll do.
Are you familiar with this apartment block?
What's your plan?
What an optimist you are.
l'm just starting to fall behind.
The best plan is not to have a plan.
- You like your food spicy?  - Yes.
Well
- lt'll be ready soon.  - Get a move on!
And young four-eyes?
Valera?
Well
lt's a tough business.
Police HQ is now trying to establish contact with the gang holding the hostages
in order to conduct negotiations. Here's our special correspondent Olga Stolyarova.
You're watching PBK and a special edition of the Market Report.
lnvestors reacted negatively to the events in central Moscow.
Blue-chip stocks were down by around 5%...
Once again l urge you to contact us.
Your only way out of the current situation
is to release the hostages and surrender.
Please don't make an already difficult situation...
Come on! Come on
Vadik
- Got any vodka?  - No
What with the kids
But l've got a bottle of Ararat
Here we go. Come on now!
lt's 20 years old. l thought you were hard up.
A present from a regular customer. l've had it for ages.
Never opened. No time
Dude
lsn't that true
Well
l'd never make anything this delicious even with the same stuff.
Kids
Listen
Maybe he can't stand eating at the same table as us.
Or are you afraid the cops will grab your dessert?
Kley!
Guys
Let's drink to us getting acquainted.
Come on
Vadik! Sit down.
Don't be mad at him. That's just the way he is.
You understand
and nothing but shootouts and car chases!
Not like in our day
Not like kids nowadays? Well
lt was so much better when we grew up. Let's drink.
Vadik
When you grow up you'll become a cop and catch guys like us.
l also wanted to be a cop once.
Let's drink.
They don't look like ruthless terrorists.
Look.
Why don't we take a lunch break too?
We never take lunch breaks during operations.
We always manage without food.
Don't forget this is an unusual operation
l want to show that cops are normal human beings and they also need food.
This is a clever move.
We'll feed the reporters too. That lot love their freebies.
Yan
Watching TV now?
Good boy.
Your restaurant does home delivery
l've got a fantastic offer for you.
Where are we going
- Are you OK?  - Yes. Fine
Maybe we should contact HQ.
No need to contact anyone.
They're here somewhere.
- l feel it.  - Feel it? l feel it too!
Been on the force so many years.
ln the movies people like me are always killed first.
And look at me now
And why? Experience! Experience and premonitions too!
Look
Tearing his nuts off would be too good for him!
What's your name?
Crackpot.
Everyone calls me that.
Why did you get into the closet
Demons are after me. They come after sunset.
What a great country! No one with brains
Why did you shoot?
- Are you deaf? Why did you shoot?  - l don't know.
l'm conking out
Well
Can't waste my time on scum like you.
But if l ever see you again
Get it? Or shall l elaborate?
Sod off! Get him out of here.
They're eating sushi.
- Did you ever try sushi?  - No.
Oleg
This sushi's not bad. For Moscow
Especially with tuna. What do you say
- Why aren't you eating
We've hacked into their computer.
Excellent. Can you connect me?
Hey
l am deputy chief of the operational HQ
Who can l talk to?
A TV star calling!
Talk to me
- Can l call you Katya?  - Call me what you like.
l suggest that you immediately release the hostages and surrender.
We can come to an agreement.
Katya
Actually
Thank you.
Pity l don't know what you look like.
Pretty ugly. But l do have one advantage over you.
l don't lie to people.
Don't they say
You just don't understand what l do.
And you're no model citizen either.
You rob banks
This means we're two of a kind. We both know what's good and what's bad
- but this doesn't bother us.  - lt's interesting to talk to you.
To you too. Perhaps we could get together in more pleasant surroundings.
Major Smirnov is on the air.
Give me the walkie-talkie.
Wait a minute. We haven't finished our conversation.
Major
lt's you again
Put me through to Colonel Petrushin.
Obey orders
l have no time to explain anything or put you through.
l am in important negotiations with the criminals.
Negotiations? What can you talk to them about?
They took out three of our guys yesterday.
One of them was my best friend.
- Major
l don't want to pry
Yes. He wants your blood.
l understand him. We'd like to get together with him too.
Verbitskaya
Just tell your negotiating partner that it's all very simple.
He's a criminal and l'll catch him.
And eat him.
- And eat him.  - What did he say?
What does it matter?
What's important is something else.
Your impossible situation.
You must surrender. You're a reasonable person
Surrender
But we have different plans.
What's happened?
Where's he gone?
We haven't finished. He didn't make any demands.
They turned off the computer. Nothing we can do here.
That was cool.
A stylish guy
Great move. Audiences would like him. He'd look great on TV!
What are you saying? What move?
What TV star? He is a criminal
lt is the police who must look great on TV.
- This is what we agreed.  - Sergei Petrovtich
We'll edit this footage exactly how we want.
l beg you. Please find Smirnov's team and remove them from the building.
Use force if you have to. This major is ruining everything for me.
Sir
- What foreigner?  - l'm not sure.
- Either Danish or Swedish. From TV.  - Let them in.
Are you mad? This is operational headquarters.
We cannot let any foreigners in here.
Sergei Petrovitch
Foreigners? l've had enough of this.
OK
Didn't you hear me? What are you doing?
Lie down! Down! Get down!
Major Smirnov?
The infamous Smirnov?
- Yes
ls it true they gave you Japanese food?
Yup. Raw fish. Like the penguins at the zoo.
lt's like this
We all have orders to escort your team out of the building.
l think it'd be better if you left of your own accord.
Do you follow me?
l get it.
l understand.
Thanks.
OK. The show's over.
- Everyone go home.  - Finally!
What else do you think l could do?
Do you know how many there were of them and how many of us?
Can l say something? My husband did nothing wrong.
He can't be blamed for anything. We have two children! They almost killed him!
He should be promoted. Our children are small
she'll be starting her first year at school.
Well
Just eating
We like it here. We're doing fine.
We've got hostages
at the entrance or a helicopter on the roof.
Get real.
When was the last time you ever saw them accept such demands?
They'll just waste us and the hostages too.
And on TV they'll say:
"The final stage of the operation was successfully concluded."
Stay cool
We're going to break out. Where there's life
And if they get us
Destiny decides. ln any case
Break out and go where? What's this about life?
Who's going to get wasted? l've got nothing to do with this!
Why don't you say anything?
l'm listening to you.
Shit your pants
Herman
We need a diversion. Create chaos. And then we'll sort things out.
Hey
- Have you got any blankets?  - Yes
Blankets
Bring them here.
Oleg
Quiet. Everything's OK.
Well
Oh
Oleg
The special forces will get them
We'd all stay
We've chased them into a blind alley. Let the warriors get them.
Why do you have to stay?
Don't know. Watch them being caught. Might be helpful
- You know...  - What?
lt's an order.
This time it's mine. So follow it
Thanks.
Go now
What did he say?
He says that our show is very good.
He wants to buy the worldwide rights to produce it.
His opening offer is 50
Plus a percentage from international licensing.
We need to think about it. We're likely to receive more offers like this.
Especially when the evening ratings come in.
Translate: "This isn't a market."
The situation hasn't changed in the last hour.
As a police representative said: "lt's the waiting stage of the operation."
They are trying to make contact and get them to release the hostages.
- Turn off your camera!  - Put your hands up!
They've probably used the grenade launcher again! This is a live broadcast.
ls this your show?
ls this what you wanted to show the entire country?
You have disgraced me!
Wait
- The new footage is nearly finished.  - Show? What bloody show?
Don't you understand anything? People are dying here!
You're relieved of command. Colonel!
What are these civilians doing here?
Disperse them to a safe distance. Clear?
Begin the assault on the apartment. At the double! Carry on!
- Yes
Stop! They've got grenades.
Five and Seven
A second group is coming out. Withdraw! Withdraw!
Calmly
This might be the hostages. Withdraw! Withdraw!
Don't let them go. Come on! Come on!
They're entering the lift.
Careful
We'll take them down the stairs.
Check the left-hand lift! There's somebody inside it!
Grenade!
Anyone down?
l'm a hostage!
Take him away!
ln a hurry?
l'm used to finishing what l set out to do.
Admirable.
My reputation has no price.
Everyone withdraw! Withdraw!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot! We're hostages!
l'm a hostage!
You're listening to Radio Mayak. Life goes on!
Life goes on and so does our report from North Chertanovo.
The rescue of the hostages is under way and is being videotaped
so you can follow it on TV.
You have all this technology
Katya
All the criminals were caught or killed. All the hostages survived.
- Stand back! Stand back!  - Please
Two bodies at the top. One in the basement!
Two captured. One missing.
ls it you
Tired of running away from my boys? Come out for a breather?
There'll be plenty of time for that at the inquiry!
That's it
The findings of the official review will be passed to the prosecutor.
Your fate is now in his hands!
Don't even contact me!
l've had enough of you now!
You know what l think of you. l'm talking to you! Always playing the hero.
- Drive!  - Where to?
Straight ahead!
Stop! Stop!
- Help!  - Sorry
You bastard! Arsehole!
You're even more beautiful in real life than on TV.
Your boyfriend's one lucky guy.
l haven't got a boyfriend.
And your girlfriend is really out of luck.
Today will end very badly for you.
l'm single too.
Oh
He's a really brave cop.
He's an idiot!
l value courage in people.
You should value brains instead.
Are you still hoping to escape after all?
Don't get your hopes up
ls that how you drive?
Didn't you see the sign there? l should call the traffic police.
Sit down.
That's better!
Where are we going?
Why don't you give yourself up?
lt'd be better for both of us.
The show's been over a long time. They'll just shoot you now.
Show
So
Does the bad guy get killed in the end?
- And who did you play?  - The director.
So why didn't anyone let me read the script?
A show?
A show dedicated to those who finish their work.
Before you start asking questions
and we try to answer them as frankly as we can
l would like to make the following statement:
The success of this operation was
well-prepared and highly professional actions.
First of all
Major Smirnov and Captain Verbitskaya.
The success of the operation was also thanks to thorough planning
and competent coordination on the part of all units
practised to perfection many times during training exercises.
That was all l had to say. And now
As a result of the operation four criminals were killed
two were arrested. Police found their arsenal:
four automatic guns
a grenade launcher and seven grenades.
The victims are receiving help from psychologists.
Captain Verbitskaya
-       -
...
.
-
-   -
.
-
-   -
-         - 5
.
-
92  9
16:3510
Entropia
-    -
Skylink
-      -
-  -
-           -
.
PBK
5...
...
-   -
!
- .  -
-   -
-   - .
.
-   -
-  -
45 1