Central Partnership
Central Partnership presents
Halt!
A Kolibri Studio production
Sergei KOLTAKOV
Get them out!
Sergei GOROBCHENKO
One, two, three, one, two, three!
Yelena LYADOVA
Anatoliy BELIY
Viktoria ISAKOVA
Alexander GOLUBEV
Pavel DEREVYANKO
In a Yury Moroz film
THE BROTHERS KARAMAZOV
Based on the novel
by F.M. Dostoyevsky
Screenplay:
Alexander CHERVINSKY
Director of photography:
Nikolai IVASIV R.G.C.
Artistic directors:
Yekaterina KOZHEVNIKOVA, Marat KIM
Halt!
Composer:
Henri LOLASHVILI
New Russia State Symphonic Orchestra
Conductor: Yury BASHMET
Sound director:
Marina NIGMATULINA
Make-up:
Marina FIRSOVA, Olga UIKOLAEVA
Forward march!
Move!
Costume design:
Dmitri ANDREEV, Alexandra ANDREEVA
Editing:
Alla URAZBAEVA
Part Five
Just imagine a square
in front of a cathedral.
Flame and smoke.
The cardinal, the Grand Inquisitor
looks at the fire,
where heretics must be burnt
by his order.
Fifteen centuries have passed
since He promised to come.
Fifteen centuries the humanity prayed :
'God, come to us! '
And here He decided to come down
to the people.
In His infinite mercy
He came once more among men
in that human shape in which He walked
among men fifteen centuries ago.
The air is 'fragrant
with laurel and lemon.'
And here He comes.
Take him!
I don't quite understand.
They recognized Him
and put Him in a prison?
What does it mean?
An inquisitor's mistake?
You are so corrupted by modern realism
and can't stand anything fantastic.
Just listen.
Is that you?
I see it is you.
Why did you come?
Christ doesn't say a word.
That is what supposed to be.
You do not deign me worthy
of even a word of reproach.
I want to make you free.
You have been saying that
for fifteen hundred years.
They have brought their freedom to us
and laid it humbly at our feet.
Now they are sure
they are completely free.
We are completely free?
Is it freedom?
The old man is ironical.
Not a bit of it!
He claims it as a merit for himself that
at last they have vanquished freedom
and have done so to make men happy.
Because people need
bread, not freedom.
But in Gospel devil says those words.
Fifteen centuries ago
the spirit of desert showed you
how to make people happy.
And you denied it.
You didn't deprive man of freedom
And didn't turn stones into bread.
And with words
'Feed men, and then ask of them virtue! '
they raised against you,
and with which they destroyed your temple.
Trying to make them free
you did something like you didn't love them.
And having tired of that freedom
they came to us.
And they said 'Enslave us, but feed us.'
And they bowed down before us.
You didn't expect that.
You were expecting free love.
And those creatures
just want to bow down before anyone.
They are weak and mean.
And sometimes they remember their freedom
and they can revolt against the power
and to flood earth with blood.
But when all rebellious destroy each others,
the rest will crawl up to us.
And they would ask
'Save us from ourselves! '
For only there are three forces
which can make one happy.
This is miracle, mystery and authority.
That's absurd!
There could not be such
a fantastic creature as your Inquisitor.
To lead people by the Christ’s name,
but by the Devil’s way.
And what are these sins of mankind
they take on themselves?
They don't even believe in God.
That's Rome,
and not even the whole of Rome,
it's false-those are the worst
of the Catholics the Inquisitors!
How does your poem end?
Or was it the end?
I meant to end it like this.
When the Inquisitor ceased speaking
he waited some time
for his Prisoner to answer him.
But he is silent.
Say just a word.
Even the worse one.
Go.
And never come back.
Never come back.
Never.
Your Grand Inquisitor
doesn't have any secrets.
He just doesn't believe in God.
That's his secret!
Enough of it.
I might be an
author impatient of your criticism.
But still you are right.
My Grand Inquisitor doesn't believe in God.
You don't believe in God.
Why do you take it so serious?
Why, it's all nonsense.
It's only a senseless poem
of a senseless student,
who could never write
two lines of verse.
Let us go. I have to go.
Leaves, blue sky, your woman. How can you
love them with that hell in your head?
There is a strength to endure everything.
What strength?
The strength of the Karamazovs.
To sink into debauchery?
Possibly even that.
Only perhaps till I am thirty
I shall escape it, and then...
Everything is lawful,' you mean?
Ah, you've caught up yesterday's phrase,
which so offended Miusov -
and which Dmitri pounced upon.
Yes, if you like.
Everything is lawful.
I thought that going away
from here I have you at least.
But now I see that there is no place
for me even in your heart.
The formula, 'all is lawful,'
I won't renounce.
Will you renounce me for that, yes?
That's plagiarism.
You stole that from my poem.
If I am really able
to care for the sticky little leaves
I shall only love
them, remembering you.
Take it as
a declaration of love if you like.
Don't say a word more on these subjects.
And about Dmitri too,
never speak to me again.
It has all been said.
Good-bye.
I am going downstairs to my room.
Send someone for the horses
in the morning.
I'm leaving for Moscow for good.
What a fellow you are!
Never mind.
Listen, Ivan.
Do me a great service.
Go to Tchermashnya on the way.
It's only to turn to the left from the station,
only another twelve versts
and you come to Tchermashnya.
It's eighty versts to the railway and the
train starts at seven o'clock tonight.
I can only just catch it.
You'll catch it tomorrow.
It won't put you out much
to humour your father!
You see,
I've two pieces of copse land there.
The priest at Ilyinskoe wrote to me.
A merchant called Gorstkin, had turned up.
He wants to buy it.
He will give me
eleven thousand for the cops.
I just want to know
whether he is lying or speaking the truth.
I shall be no use in such a business.
I have no eye either.
I will tell you the signs
by which you can judge about him.
Sit down.
Listen.
You see, you must watch his beard.
If his beard shakes
when he talks and he gets cross,
it's all right, he is saying
what he means, he wants to do business.
But if he strokes his
beard with his left hand and grins -
he is trying to cheat you.
Only let me know it's serious,
and I'll run over and fix it up.
I can't spare the time.
You must excuse me.
You've no heart, any of you!
You force me to go to that damned
Tchermashnya yourself, then?
Welcome, my dear.
Have you seen your brother?
To whom I bowed down.
I could not find him today.
Make haste to find him.
Leave everything and make haste.
Perhaps you may still have time
to prevent something terrible.
I bowed down yesterday to the great
suffering in store for him.
Your words are too obscure.
What is this suffering in store for him?
A look came into his eyes -
so that I was instantly horror-stricken
at what that man
is preparing for himself.
Once or twice in my life
I've seen such a look in a man's face,
reflecting as it were his future fate,
and that fate, alas, came to pass.
Maybe your
brotherly face would help him.
Everything is from the Lord.
All our fates.
I will get up.
Everyone hides what he has, from the rest.
And instead of fullness of life
he gets only solitude.
And that will be till
everyone understands
that besides his own sin
he is guilty for any other sin.
But throwing your impotence on others
you will end by murmuring against God.
I now thirst to love,
but my earthly life is over.
And there will be nothing great.
You are waiting for a miracle?
It stinks.
God forgive me.
We should open the window.
There was no smell of corruption from the
late elder Varsonofy, but a sweet fragrance.
So here's the miracle.
He was not strict in fasting,
allowed himself sweet things,
ate cherry jam with his tea,
ladies used to send it to him.
Not miracles made him great,
but his great love.
It shows God's judgment is not as man's.
Where are you hastening?
The bell calls to service.
Can you be with those of little faith?
Alexey!
What's the matter?
Are you angry?
Let me alone.
So that's how we are feeling!
Can you be so upset because
your old man has begun to stink?
You seriously believed that he
was going to work miracles?
No schoolboy
of thirteen believes in that now.
I believe,
I want to believe, and I will believe.
What more do you want?
The holiest of holy men should have
been exposed to the jeering?
What for? Who had judged him?
And this is 'the higher justice'?
It's not miracles I need, but justice.
So now you are
in a temper with your God?
I am not rebelling against my God.
I simply 'don't accept His world.
How do you mean,
you don't accept the world
What idiocy is this?
Have you had anything to eat to-day?
You need keeping up.
I've got some sausage in my pocket.
Only you won't eat sausage.
Give me some.
You are going it! Why, it's a regular
mutiny, with barricades!
Well, my boy, we must make the most of it.
Come to my place.
Shouldn't mind a drop of vodka myself.
Vodka is going too far for you, I suppose.
Give me some vodka too.
You surprise me, brother!
Alyosha, do you know where
we had better go?
I don't care... where you like.
Let's go to Grushenka, eh?
Will you come?
Let's go to Grushenka.
Let's go.
Four years had passed since the merchant
Samsonov had brought the shy girl of eighteen.
She was dreamy and sad.
There were rumours that she had
been betrayed by someone,
some sort of officer,
and immediately afterwards
abandoned by him in poverty and disgrace.
Her name is Agrafena
Alexandrovna Svetlova.
Though Grushenka's hold upon him was
so strong that he could not live without her,
he did not settle
any considerable fortune on her.
But he had presented her with a small sum,
he helped her with his advice
to increase her capital.
Needless to say, Grushenka had shown
marked abilities in that direction.
For instance, that she had for some time
past, in partnership with old Karamazov,
actually invested in the purchase
of bad debts for a trifle dirt cheap,
and afterwards had made out
of them ten times their value.
So that many people began to say
that she was no better than a Jew.
If you have to choose between the two, father
or son, you'd better choose the old man,
if only you make sure the
old scoundrel will marry you
and settle some fortune
on you beforehand.
But don't keep on with Mitya,
you'll get no good out of that.
Who's there?
It's not he, it's nothing,
only other visitors.
It's you, Rakitin?
You quite frightened me.
Whom have you brought?
Haven't I managed to please you?
Do send for candles!
Fenya, fetch him a candle.
Well, you have chosen
a moment to bring him!
I thought it was Mitya again.
I am afraid
of your brother Mitya today, Alyosha.
Why are you so afraid of Mitya today?
I should have thought
you were not timid with him.
I am expecting news, priceless news,
so I don't want Mitya at all.
Fenya, did you look everywhere?
Perhaps he is hiding and spying.
Are the shutters fastened?
Everything's shut.
I am dreadfully frightened myself.
And why are you so dressed up?
I tell you, I am expecting a message.
Why do I have to talk to you
while such a visitor is standing here?
Alyosha, my dear boy,
I gaze at you and can't believe my eyes.
Though this is not the moment now,
I am awfully glad to see you.
How everything comes together today!
And why I am so glad to see you,
Alyosha, I couldn't say myself!
Come, don't you know why you're glad?
You used to be always
pestering me to bring him.
You'd some object, I suppose.
I had a different object once,
but now that's over,
this is not the moment.
Why are you so depressed, Alyosha?
Are you afraid of me?
Let me sit on your knee.
I'll cheer you up, my pious boy.
You won't be angry?
You've talked nonsense enough.
You'd much better give us some champagne.
You owe it me, you know you do!
Yes, I really do, I promised him
champagne, if he'd bring you?
Fenya, Fenya,
bring us the bottle Mitya left!
So be it, I'll drink with you.
I long for some dissipation.
And what is this message,
may I ask, or is it a secret?
It's not a secret, and you know it, too.
My officer is coming, my officer is coming.
He is at Mokroe now.
He'll send a messenger from there.
Mitya'll be up to something now - I say!
Does he know?
He know!
If he knew, there would be murder.
Be quiet, Rakitin,
don't remind me of him.
He has bruised my heart.
I can think of Alyosha here.
Alyosha, smile at me.
Smile at my foolishness, at my pleasure.
How kindly he looks at me!
I've been thinking all this time
you were angry with me.
Because of that young lady.
Katerina Ivanovna.
I was a cur, that's the truth.
But it's a good thing it happened so.
It was a horrid thing,
but a good thing too.
She screamed out
that I 'ought to be flogged.
To win me over with her chocolate.
No, it's a good thing
it did end like that.
But I am still afraid of your being angry.
She is really afraid
of a chicken like you.
Because I love him.
Do you believe I love you?
Ah, you shameless woman!
She is making you a declaration.
Well, what of it, I love him!
And what about your officer?
And the priceless message from Mokroe?
That is quite different.
That's a woman's way of looking at it!
Don't you make me angry, Rakitin.
I love Alyosha in a different way.
Here's the champagne!
I had sly designs on you before.
For I am a horrid, violent creature.
You're excited,
Agrafena Alexandrovna, and not yourself.
When you've had a glass of champagne,
you'll be ready to dance.
Alyosha, take a glass.
What shall we drink to?
The gates of paradise?
What gates of paradise?
No, I'd better not.
And you bragged!
Well, if so, I won't either.
He is rebelling
against his God and ready to eat sausage.
How so?
His elder died today,
Father Zossima, the saint.
So Father Zossima is dead?
Good God, I did not know!
Goodness, what have I been doing,
sitting on his knee like this?
Rakitin, don't taunt me
with having rebelled against God.
I don't want to feel angry with you,
so you must be kinder, too.
I've lost a treasure such as you have
never had, and you cannot judge me now.
You had much better look at her.
Do you see how she has pity on me?
I came here to find a wicked
soul - I felt drawn to evil.
And I've found a loving heart.
She had pity on me just now.
Agrafena Alexandrovna,
I am speaking of you.
You've raised my soul
from the depths.
She has saved you, it seems.
And she meant to get you in her
clutches, do your realize that?
Stay, Rakitin.
Hush, both of you.
I'll tell you all about it.
Alyosha, your words make me ashamed.
For I am bad and not good.
That's what I am.
And you hush, Rakitin,
because you are telling lies.
I had the low idea of trying
to get him in my clutches,
but now you are lying,
now it's all different.
And don't let me
hear anything more from you.
They are both crazy.
I feel as though I were in a madhouse.
They'll begin crying.
Only let me tell you, Rakitin, though
I am bad, I did give away an onion.
An onion?
You see, Alyosha, I was boasting when
I told Rakitin I had given away an onion,
but it's not to boast I tell you about it.
Sit in that corner and be quiet,
as though you were my footman!
And now, Alyosha,
I'll tell you the whole truth.
I used to hear from Matryona, my cook.
Once upon a time
there was a peasant woman
and a very wicked woman she was.
And she died and did not
leave a single good deed behind.
The devils caught her
and plunged her into the lake of fire.
Sit!
So her guardian angel
stood and wondered
what good deed of hers he could
remember to tell to God.
And she said,
She once pulled up an onion in her
garden, and gave it to a beggar woman.
And God answered :
'You take that onion then,
hold it out to her in the lake,
and let her take hold and be pulled out.
And if you can pull her out of the lake,
let her come to Paradise,
but if the onion breaks,
then the woman must stay where she is.'
The angel ran to the woman
and held out the onion to her.
When the other sinners in the lake,
began catching hold of her.
And she began kicking them.
'I'm to be pulled out, not you.
It's my onion, not yours.'
As soon as she said that,
the woman fell into the lake.
So the angel wept and went away.
The onion broke.
So that's the story,
Alyosha ; I know it by heart.
For I am that wicked woman myself.
I boasted to Rakitin
that I had given away an onion,
but to you I'll say:
'I've done nothing but give away
one onion all my life,
that's the only good deed I've done.
Don't praise me.
I promised Rakitin twenty-five
roubles if he would bring you to me.
I wanted to get you in my clutches.
Take it, Rakitin.
I owe it you,
there's no fear of your refusing it.
Likely I should refuse it.
Fools are made for wise men's profit.
And now hold your tongue.
You don't like us, so hold your tongue.
One loves people for some reason,
but what have either of you done for me?
You cannot understand that. He can.
Alyosha, tell me what to do.
Am I to forgive the officer or not?
But you have forgiven him already.
Yes, I really have forgiven him.
What an abject heart!
To my abject heart!
Why are you dressed up like that?
Perhaps I didn't forget him.
You don't know all that is in my heart!
I'll sit by him, fascinate him.
'Do you see what I am like now?'
I'll say to him.
'Well, and that's enough
for you, my dear sir.'
Or I'll take a knife with me.
I haven't decided it yet.
Oh, you started crying!
Misha, be merciful.
She's found someone to plead her cause!
Why, are you in love with her?
Agrafena Alexandrovna, he's really
in love with you, you've made a conquest!
Hush, evil tongue!
Mistress darling,
a carriage from Mokroe for you.
And a letter, here's the letter.
He has sent for me.
He whistles!
Crawl back, little dog!
I will go.
Good-bye!
Good-bye, Alyosha, my fate is sealed.
Grushenka is flying to a new life.
I feel as though I were drunk!
Mistress darling!
Go!
Alyosha, give my greetings
to your brother Mitya,
And tell him that Grushenka
loved him only one hour,
only one short hour she loved him.
So let him remember
that hour all his life.
Go!
She murders your brother Mitya.
And then tells him
to remember it all his life!
What ferocity!
Well?
So you've saved the sinner?
Driven out the seven devils?
Hush!
So you despise me now
for those twenty-five roubles?
I've sold my friend, you think.
But you are not Christ,
you know, and I am not Judas.
I'd forgotten about it,
you remind me of it yourself.
Damnation take you all and each of you.
Why the devil did I take you up?
I don't want to know you.
Go alone, there's your road!
THE BROTHERS KARAMAZOV
End of Part Five