Who the winny-binny boy?
You the winny-winny-binny-binny boy!
Yes.
Now, don't cry.
Don't cry.
Why is he still crying?
Don't worry. It's nothing that can't
be solved by ''happy keys.''
I feel better when someone
shakes jagged metal in my face.
All right, here.
Let me hold him for a sec.
Here we go.
There we are.
Maybe it's me.
Don't be silly. Ben loves you.
He's being Mr. Cranky Pants.
You know, I once dated
a Miss Cranky Pants.
Lovely girl. Kind of moody.
There we go. All better.
There's my little boy.
Can I see something?
-Cool!
-He hates me. My nephew hates me!
-I知 unemployed and he hates me.
-Don't do this.
You're just unemployed.
What if my own baby hates me?
What do I do?
Monica, this is nuts!
You know how long it'll be
before you have to deal with this?
You don't even have a boyfriend yet.
Joey, she does not look fat.
The One With the Baby on the Bus
-Here you go.
-Hey, Mon.
Goo, goo, goo!
That is so funny!
Let me see that a sec.
-You okay, Ross?
-I don't know.
What's in this pie?
I don't know. Butter and eggs,
flour and lime and kiwi--
Kiwi? Kiwi?!
You said it was key lime.
No, I said kiwi lime.
That's what makes it special.
That's what's gonna kill me.
I知 allergic to kiwi.
No, you're not. You're allergic
to lobster, peanuts and--
Oh, my God!
-It's definitely getting worse.
-Is your tongue swelling up?
Either that or my mouth
is getting smaller!
We're going to the hospital.
-Is he okay?
-He's gotta get a shot.
You know, actually
it's getting better. It is.
Let's not go.
Anyone for Scrabble?
Jacket, now!
What about Ben? We can't
bring a baby to the hospital.
We'll watch him.
I don't think so.
I have seven Catholic sisters.
I take care of hundreds of kids.
-We wanna do it. Don't we?
-I was gonna play basketball but...
...I guess that's out the window.
If you take him for a walk,
remember his hat.
There's milk in the fridge
and extra diapers.
Hat, milk....
-Got it!
-Let's go.
Consider it done!
-You understood that?
-My uncle Sal has a really big tongue.
Is he the one
with the beautiful wife?
Want to hear the song
I知 singing this afternoon?
-I wrote it this morning in the shower.
-Okay.
I'm in the shower
And I'm writing a song
Stop me if you've heard it
My skin is soapy and my hair is wet
And Tegrin spelled backward is Nirget
Rachel, sweetheart,
could I see you for a minute?
What's up?
FYI:
I致e decided to pay a professional
musician to play on Sundays.
Her name's Stephanie something.
She's supposed to be very good.
-But what about Phoebe?
-Rachel...
...it's not that your friend is bad.
It's that she's so bad...
...she makes me want to put my finger
through my eye into my brain...
...and swirl it around.
Okay, so you're not a fan.
But, I mean, come on.
You cannot do this to her.
Oh, no.
I have to do this?
Lather, rinse, repeat
And lather, rinse, repeat
As needed
We didn't bring enough.
Did you forget to pack
the baby's anvil?
It'll be worth it.
It's a fact that women love babies.
Women love guys who love babies.
It's the sensitive thing.
Aim him at that pack of babes.
Maybe one will break away.
Wait, forget them.
We got one. Hard left.
-Give me the baby.
-I got him.
-Come on, seriously.
-Oh, seriously you want him?
Hello.
Who is this cutie-pie?
Well, don't think me immodest, but...
...me.
-Want to smell him?
-We're talking about the baby?
He's got that great baby smell.
Get a whiff of his head.
My uterus just skipped a beat.
What'd I tell you?
-It's great you're doing this.
-Well, we are great guys.
My brother and his boyfriend
are trying to adopt.
What agency did you two go through?
But this is my gig.
This is where I play.
My name is written out there in chalk.
You know, you can't just erase chalk.
Honey, I知 sorry.
And he's going to
be pay this woman?
Why doesn't he give her a throne
and a crown?
And, like, a gold stick
with a ball on top?
Terry is a jerk! That's why we say,
''Terry's a jerk!''
That's where that came from.
Yeah, okay. You probably did
everything you could.
Okay, you know what? Let me just see
what else I can do.
All right. Let her go on after
Stephanie whatever-her-name-is.
You won't be here. Don't pay her.
-I don't know.
-I値l clean the cappuccino machine!
You don't clean
the cappuccino machine?
Of course I clean it.
I mean, I will clean it.
-I mean, I will clean it.
-All right, fine!
-Done.
-Really?
Who's working for you, babe?
Oh, my God! This is so exciting!
How much am I gonna get?
What?
You said he's paying
the people who play.
I meant, he's paying that other woman
because she's a professional.
I知 not gonna be the only one
not getting paid.
-But Pheebs--
-No, I知 sorry, no!
No, I知 not some sloppy second,
you know, charity band.
There are thousands of places...
...where people would pay
to hear me play.
When I play, I play for me
I don't need your charity
Thank you!
I知 not getting a shot.
They can take the needle...
...and squirt it in my mouth.
Like a squirt gun.
See what the doctor says.
They've got to do something.
These are the '90s.
Hello, there. I知 Dr. Carlin.
I see someone's having
a little allergic reaction.
Doctor, can I see you
for just a moment?
My brother has a slight phobia
about needles.
Did you tell him
about my squirt gun idea?
My brother would like to know...
...if there's a way
to treat this orally?
Under these circumstances, it has to
be an injection and it has to be now.
So?
Have a seat. The doctor says
it's gotta be a needle.
You're just gonna have to be brave.
Can you do that for me?
-Okay.
-Okay. Oh, boy!
You are doing so good.
You want to squeeze my hand?
Ross, don't squeeze it so hard.
Honey, really.
Don't squeeze it so hard!
Ross, let go of my hand!
Good. Next time we pick up women...
...we should go to the park
and make out.
Taxi! Taxi!
Hey, look at that talent.
Just practicing. You're good.
Carry on.
Wait, wait, wait!
Hey, you. He is just adorable.
Can you tell him that?
Because he thinks he looks too pink.
-What are you guys out doing today?
-We're not out.
We're two hetero guys
hanging with the son...
...of our other heterosexual friend,
doing the usual straight-guy stuff.
-You done?
-Yeah.
There's our stop.
Get out of here! This is our stop.
You guys live here too?
We live in the building
by the sidewalk.
Do you know it?
Since we're neighbors, what do you say
we get together for a drink?
So you wanna go to Marquel's?
Sure, they love us.
Where's your baby?
Ben! Ben!
That's good. Maybe he'll
hear you and pull the cord!
-Stop the bus! Hey!
-No!
-We need the baby!
-Wait!
You sure it didn't break?
It hurts.
No, it's just a good bone bruise.
And right here is the puncture wound
from your ring.
-I知 really sorry.
-It's okay.
Sorry.
Sorry! Hey! I got my ''S''s back!
Which we can celebrate later.
Celebrate. Celebrate....
He was a double, double
Double-jointed boy
Hey, so are you the professional
guitar player?
Yeah, I知 Stephanie.
Right. My name was on there.
Now it just says carrot cake.
-Okay.
-So how many chords do you know?
-All of them.
-So you know D?
-Yeah.
-Okay. Do you know A-minor?
Okay, do you know
how to go from D to A-minor?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
So does your guitar have a strap?
-No.
-Mine does.
Stephanie knows all the chords
Come on! Pick up, pick up! Hello.
Transit Authority? Yes. Hello.
I知 doing research for a book.
I was wondering what somebody might do
if they left a baby on a city bus.
Yes, I realize that would be stupid.
We lost a car seat on a bus today.
It's white plastic
and it fits onto a stroller.
And there was a baby in it.
He wants to talk to you again.
Everybody, let's give a warm
Central Perk welcome to--
Terry's a jerk
And he won't let me work
And I hate Central Perk
To Stephanie Schiffer!
I壇 like to start with a song I wrote
for the first man I ever loved.
Zachary--
Are all invited to bite me
We're the guys that called
about the baby! Is he here?
He's here.
Is one of you the father?
-That's me.
-I知 him.
Actually, we're both the father.
-Oh, Ben!
-Hey, buddy.
Tell me you know
which one is our baby.
One has ducks on his shirt
and one has clowns.
And Ben was definitely wearing ducks.
Or clowns.
That one's Ben! Remember, he had
that little mole by his mouth!
Hey, Ben! Remember us?
Okay, the mole came off.
What are we gonna do?
Flip for it.
Ducks or clowns.
We're gonna flip for the baby?
All right, call it in the air.
-Heads.
-Heads, it is.
We have to assign heads to something!
Right! Okay.
Ducks is heads
because ducks have heads.
What kind of scary-ass clowns
came to your birthday?
-Hey.
-Oh, hi.
Here. I thought you might be cold.
Thank you.
Look at you!
You did well.
8 dollars and 27 cents.
But not really
because I put in the first two.
Just to get the ball rolling
and to make myself feel better.
-Do you?
-No.
This whole playing for money thing
is so not good for me.
I don't know, when I sang
''Su-Su-Suicide''...
...I got, like, $1 .75.
But then ''Smelly Cat''?
I got 25 cents and a condom.
So, you know, now I just feel
really bad for ''Smelly Cat.''
Honey, I don't think
everybody gets ''Smelly Cat.''
I mean, if all you've ever actually
had are healthy pets, then whoosh!
But it's not even that, you know?
I played my songs
because it made me happy.
Now it's just all
about the money, you know?
People missed you in there.
In fact, there was a request
for ''Smelly Cat.''
Really? From who?
Well, me.
I know it's not your big money song,
but it's my favorite.
Hi. Did I accidentally drop a condom
in your case?
-It's kind of an emergency.
-Yeah.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
Hey, Christine! I got it!
I want to thank you
for being there for me.
Sorry I almost broke your hand.
That's okay.
I知 sorry I poisoned you.
Remember when I jammed
a pencil into your hand?
Remember it? What do you
think this is, a freckle?
What about the time I hit you
in the face with a pumpkin?
Remember, I stuck a broom
in your spokes...
-...and you hit your head on a curb?
-No.
But I remember
people telling me about it.
-I hope Ben has a little sister.
-Yeah.
And I hope she can kick his ass.
I知 gonna get a new Band-Aid.
How about when I cut the legs
off your Malibu Ken?
That was you?
They were infected.
He wouldn't have made it.
My little nephew.
Come here, little one!
There's my little baby Ben!
Hey, my little boy.
Hey, he's not crying!
Yes!
There's still pie!
I知 here. I知 here.
How's my little boy?
You want Daddy to change
your diaper? I know, I know.
Did you have fun with Uncle Joey
and Uncle Chandler today?
Yeah. He rode the bus today.
Big boy riding the bus--
Hey, I have a question.
How come it says ''Property
of Human Services'' on his butt?
You....
You are gonna love this.
Can you hold Ben for a sec?
Come here.
Stay back! I致e got kiwi!
Run, Joey, run!
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
No, no. I知 sorry, it's:
Smelly cat, smelly cat
-Better!
-Yeah?
Much better. Good.
Don't feel bad
because it's a hard song.
-You want to try it again?
-From the top?
There is no ''top,'' all right?
That's the beauty of ''Smelly Cat.''
-Why don't you just follow me?
-Okay.
Smelly cat, smelly cat
What are they feeding you?
It's not your fault
That's too much. Sorry.
denanet for torrents.ru