Chandler, Mon, there's only
one muffin left.
- I ordered mine first.
- Yeah, but I'm so much faster.
- Give it to me.
- No.
Give it to me!
Okay, you can have it.
There you go. Enjoy your coffee.
That was there when I got here.
Hey, you'll never guess
who's coming to New York.
Tell us before he can swallow.
Ryan, that guy I dated
who's in the Navy.
You dated a guy in the Navy?
I met him while playing guitar.
Ryan threw in saltwater taffy.
He had no change.
Is that when you wrote
"Saltwater Taffy Man"?
He's my submarine guy.
He resurfaces every couple years...
...and we have an amazing
three days together.
Only, he's coming for two weeks.
Two whole weeks, which means yea!
So, wait, this guy goes down
for, like, two years at a time?
That'll teach you to lick my muffin.
Hi.
- Oh, no. What happened?
- Ben's got the chickenpox.
So if you haven't had it,
chances are you will.
- I've had it.
Had it.
I've never had it. I feel so left out.
Oh, look!
The One With the Chicken Pox
Honey, you made the bed again.
You don't have to do that.
This isn't camp.
I guess the panty raid last night
was totally uncalled for.
Okay, I'm taking a shower. Today
I'll sing Jim Croce's "Leroy Brown."
Hey, Mon, I have a question.
Is Leroy the baddest man
in the whole damn town...
...or the fattest man?
The baddest. Or the song
would be "Fat, Fat Leroy Brown."
What are you doing?
I'm just waiting for you, sweetie.
Are you remaking the bed?
I'm sorry. The way you did it,
it was just fine.
Then you're redoing it because?
You'll think I'm crazy.
You're pretty much
running that risk either way.
Okay. You see...
...the duvet tag shouldn't be
at the top left corner...
...it should be
at the bottom right corner.
- It's not crazy.
- I'm easing you in.
All right.
You see these flower blossoms?
They should be facing up, not down...
...because the head of the bed
is where the sun would be.
You don't love me anymore, do you?
Actually, if it's possible,
I love you more.
Really?
Wow. Well, then, come on!
I wanna show you how to fold
the toilet paper into a point.
Look, if you need something...
...I can get you a job here
as a processor.
- Don't you need experience?
- It's not hard to learn.
As far as not knowing
what you're doing, you're an actor.
Act like a processor,
people will think you're a processor.
Here's this morning's projections.
Thanks.
Scott Alexander, Joey Tribbiani.
Joey is a fellow processor.
No kidding?
Yeah.
I process. People want the processing,
I'm the one they call.
- Where do you work?
- Well, I'm in between things.
You know, one day
you're processing, the next day...
...not so much processing anymore.
I told Joey about Fleischman's group.
Fleischman's group?
Whatever you do,
don't touch his sandwiches.
Are all you processors dorks?
This lipstick looks just great on you.
You look fabulous, really.
Yeah, are you sure? Really?
See, you look beautiful.
For God's sakes, dim the lights.
I'm hideous!
It's gonna be okay.
Ryan's been underwater.
He's just gonna be so glad
you don't have barnacles on your butt.
Come in.
Hey, baby, I'm back...
Hey, Ryan. What's up?
- What's going on?
- No, no. You have to stay back.
I have the pox!
Chicken or small?
Chicken, which is so ironic
considering I'm a vegetarian.
- Why aren't you at home?
- My grandma's never had it.
Please tell me you have, because
oh, my God, I forgot how cute you are.
I'm sorry, I never had them.
If I had one wish,
I'd go back to when I was 7...
...when Jimmy Hauser had chickenpox,
and I'd rub him all over my face.
Yeah, or you could wish
that I didn't have them now.
Can I see your face?
You don't wanna see a face
covered with pox.
It could be covered with lox,
I wouldn't care.
And you hate fish.
So sweet. All right.
Okay, all right. You can see.
This is me.
Sorry!
I am scary!
Sorry, the lightning was
an unfortunate coincidence.
- You look lovely! Lovely!
- I hate this.
I had the most amazing
two weeks planned for us.
And everything I had in mind,
we had to be closer than this.
Phoebe, I've spent the last eight
months in a steel tube with men...
...thinking about this moment.
I am not gonna let a bunch...
...of itchy spots stand between us.
Okay. This is the most
romantic disease I've ever had.
- How's the first day?
- It's like you said.
It's mostly just putting numbers
from one column into another.
Everybody's so nice. I just had
a good talk with that lady, Jeannie.
Jeannie? The head
of East Coast operations?
Turns out our kids
go to the same school.
Yeah. Small world, huh?
Weird world.
- Your kids?
- I figure my character has kids.
There isn't a part of that sentence
I don't need explained.
In acting, you need
to think about that stuff.
My character, Joseph,
the processing guy...
...has two little girls,
Ashley and Brittany.
Ashley copies everything
Brittany does.
Well, invisible kids
can be that way sometimes.
You know, Joseph and his wife, Karen,
are thinking of having a third kid.
You know what?
Just did.
Wow, that's some pretty powerful
imaginary sperm you must have there.
- Know what makes the itching worse?
- That you don't stop talking about it?
- Fine.
- Let's just play, okay?
Good, okay. Here we go, double sixes.
Here we go...
Here we go. Come to Mama. Just getting
ready to roll the dice...
- What're you doing? Are you scratching?
- No. This is what I do for luck, okay?
- You're scratching. Give me the dice.
- No.
- Give me the dice.
- No! Here. There!
Look, double sixes!
We can't scratch. We'll scar.
I can't stop thinking about it.
It's just so hard.
I wanna grab these houses
and rub them on my body.
- No!
- Give it! Yeah, come on!
You know you want it too.
Come on.
Let's just be bad.
It'll feel so good.
Come on.
Oh, God help me.
- Oh, yeah.
- Good. Now do me.
Do my back.
Oh, come on. Harder!
- There you go. Don't move.
- Why?
- Don't move.
- What are you?
Stop that! Stop that right now.
I might've expected this of Phoebe.
But, Ryan, you're a military man.
She made me do it.
That's a nice color on you.
Yeah, well, it comes in pink
and blotchy, baby.
I hope you get a weenie pock.
You and Milton have to join us
on the boat.
- We'll make a day of it.
- That sounds lovely. We'll set it up.
I better get back.
Hope the baby feels better.
- Thanks. Bye-bye, Jeannie.
- Bye-bye, Joseph.
What a phony.
You'll teach her a lesson when she
steps off the dock onto nothing.
- Hey, Mr. Douglas.
- Sir.
Bing, I got your memo. We won't
see the report till next Friday?
- My group wants the weekend for family.
- I have a family. I'm gonna be here.
Yeah, Bing. What's that about?
It's about cutting people
slack for morale.
I can get some rough numbers
by Wednesday.
Rough numbers?
This company wasn't built
on rough numbers. Right, Mr. Douglas?
Have the final numbers
on my desk by Tuesday.
If you say so, sir.
Joseph's good, isn't he?
I'm going to kill you.
Hey, I figure Joseph's the kind of guy
who likes to mix it up.
You know, get in there,
ruffle some feathers.
Why?
Look, I'm sorry,
but that's what Joseph does.
Okay? If you try to pull something,
he'll call you on it.
"What're you trying to pull?"
He'll say.
Duct tape.
Was I supposed to bring something too?
This is for the scratchy twins.
I taped oven mitts to their hands.
- You're strict.
- Well, it's for their own good.
You know, I like the way you have
efficiently folded this tab under.
See, in a tape emergency you could
shave valuable seconds off your time.
Exactly!
God, I love that I can be
totally neurotic around you now.
Don't you like it better with
everything on your desk perpendicular?
If it's not a right angle,
it is a wrong angle.
- Very good.
- Thank you.
Tomorrow I'm gonna do your clocks.
- You're gonna do what to them?
- Set them to my time.
I'm confused.
I thought we shared time.
No. See, in my bedroom, I set my clock
six minutes fast. Know why?
Because it's in a slightly different
time zone than the kitchen?
- Forget it.
- No, come on, tell me.
You don't understand. You don't
have any of these obsessions.
No, that's not true.
Oh, yeah? Tell me one of yours.
Okay.
One of my things is,
I always separate my sweat socks...
...from my dress socks.
- What if they get mixed up?
- Boy, I would just...
I would freak out.
You would not.
I can't believe this.
I hate this. You're too normal.
I can't believe you don't have a thing.
My boyfriend doesn't have a thing.
See, if anyone overheard that,
I didn't come off well there.
Hey!
- Mr. Douglas is looking for you.
- Why is Mr. Douglas looking for me?
He has a suspicion you dropped
the ball on the Lender project.
Why? Why does he suspect that?
At first, he thought it was Joseph.
But after he asked Joseph about it...
Turns out it was you.
- I thought you should know.
- All right. That's it!
Look, Joey, I realize this
is the role of a lifetime for you...
...and if I could just fire Joseph,
I would. But that's not possible.
So I'm gonna have to let
both of you go.
- What? Everybody loves Joseph.
- I don't. I hate Joseph.
I think he's a brownnosing suck-up.
Oh, yeah? Well, you can't fire Joseph.
He's not in your department.
All right, okay.
So I can't fire Joseph...
...but I can sleep with his wife.
Not Karen!
Yeah, I'm thinking about
having an affair with her.
You know what?
I just did.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Oh, it's not me.
It's my character!
Chandie.
The rogue processor who seduces
his coworkers' wives...
...and then laughs about it.
I have her panties
right there in my drawer!
- Really?
- No, freak! She's fictional!
All right. Hey, take it easy.
If it means that much to you,
I'll go find something else.
Thank you.
It's just that I'm gonna miss Joseph.
I liked him. His wife?
She was hot.
And the kids. You know he was gonna
put in a pool next summer.
Take these off.
I swear I won't scratch.
No, sorry, hon. Monica's orders.
Well, that wasn't easy.
Okay, dinner's on.
There's a peach cobbler
in the oven.
So the plate's gonna be hot, but that
shouldn't be a problem for you.
All right, you kids. Bye, now.
- Bye.
- Oh, look.
A low-budget puppet show.
It's a shame you can't see
what finger I'm holding up.
- Wine?
- Please.
- Spilled some.
- I got it.
I must say,
you look beautiful tonight.
What?
Sorry.
You look beautiful.
Okay. You know what? That's it.
Oh, yes.
Good.
You guys, did you...?
Monica, wake up.
- What's up?
- I thought of a thing.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I have to sleep, have to,
on this side of the bed.
No. You have to sleep
on this side of the bed...
...because I have to sleep
on this side of the bed.
Or so I would have you believe.
So you have a side of the bed.
Everybody has a side of the bed.
Come on. You haven't
heard my reason yet.
- All right, go on.
- Okay.
I have to sleep on the west side...
...because I grew up in California,
and otherwise...
...the ocean would be
on the wrong side.
Oh, my God.
- You're a freak!
- Yeah.
How about that?
- Where are you shipping off to?
- I can't say.
- Do you have nuclear weapons onboard?
Do you get to look
through a periscope?
I'm sorry, but I can't say.
Wow, it's neat learning
about submarines.
- I better get out of here.
- I'll walk you out.
- Bye, Ryan.
- A pleasure. Take care.
So do you think we could get you
one of those uniform things?
- You like that, do you?
- Oh, yeah.
- I'll make some calls.
- Okay.
- Can you believe how we spent our time?
- We didn't do anything I planned...
...like having a picnic in Central Park
and coffee at Central Perk.
Oh, I just got that!
Taxi!
Bye, you.
I'm sorry, we're clo...
- Hey, sailor.
- Is this what you had in mind?
I'll say.
I'm shipping out tomorrow.
Well, then...
...we better make this night count.
Wait, I forgot to turn off
the cappuccino machine.
Anchors aweigh.
Oh, wait, wait!
My purse, my purse!
Oh, I forgot to turn off the light.
Why don't I just meet you upstairs?
Honey!
denanet for torrents.ru